<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="87183a624dfd58a503d73b1b529d62b7" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Highlighter Pack Hyperdunk 2010 Vivid Pink Black On Sal<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oaWdobGlnaHRlci1wYWNrLWh5cGVyZHVuay0yMDEwLXZpdmlkLXBpbmstYmxhY2stcC0zMi8_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_268051_34763783.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oaWdobGlnaHRlci1wYWNrLWh5cGVyZHVuay0yMDEwLXZpdmlkLXBpbmstYmxhY2stcC0zMi8_" target="_blank">Highlighter Pack Hyperdunk 2010</a> can be seen at Kicks-Sale.com where there are variety kinds of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Nike Basketball Shoes</a> on hot sale in some great summer colorways. Dubbed the &quot;Highlighter&quot; Pack, this threesome of kicks makes use of super bright colors and black Zoom soles. The Nike Hyperdunk Highlighter 2010 features four radiant colorways of the newly released basketball shoe in pink, neon yellow, electric green, and blue, and will surely catch the eyes of your opponents on the court. Each feature a black midsole, bottom sole, inner lining and swoosh, etc. For this drop the performance shoe is given a vibrant make over that translates into giving a performance shoe that lifestyle feel. 
<br /><br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oaWdobGlnaHRlci1wYWNrLWh5cGVyZHVuay0yMDEwLXZpdmlkLXBpbmstYmxhY2stcC0zMi8_" target="_blank">Nike Highlighter Pack</a>, which includes this vibrant colorway in the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oeXBlcmR1bmstMjAxMC1jLTMv" target="_blank">Nike Hyperdunk 2010</a>. This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oaWdobGlnaHRlci1wYWNrLWh5cGVyZHVuay0yMDEwLXZpdmlkLXBpbmstYmxhY2stcC0zMi8_" target="_blank">Hyperdunk Highlighter Pink</a> shoe features a predominantly pink colorway, which is accented by a black hue, visible on the inner lining, Nike swoosh, and midsole. Nike incorporates their signature flywire technology, making the shoe strong and lightweight. Stay tuned in for more information as their release date approaches.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c50da1def9ed0951313669c867a87cad" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Hyperdunk Olympic White Gold Basketball Shoes Hot Sale<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oeXBlcmR1bmstb2x5bXBpYy13aGl0ZS1nb2xkLXAtMjgv" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_13193363_34763836.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oeXBlcmR1bmstMjAxMC1jLTMv" target="_blank">Nike Hyperdunk</a> has definitely been one of the most exposed shoes this year, with an infectious marketing campaign, as well as a strong on-court presence on the feet of the NBA’s best.  However, the one arena in which the Hyperdunk was truly omnipresent was that of the Olympics, where it seemed every other national basketball team had a different colorway of these kicks on their feet.  In honor of said recently completed games then, Nike has release this Olympic-themed colorway of the Hyperdunk in a white and gold design, based on the gold medals of the Olympics.  While golden themed releases aren’t exactly unheard of at this time of year, such as the Closing Ceremonies Air Force 1?s here, these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oeXBlcmR1bmstb2x5bXBpYy13aGl0ZS1nb2xkLXAtMjgv" target="_blank">Nike Hyperdunks Olympic</a> are definitely a nice clean drop from Nike, and definitely do their flagship <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Nike Basketball Shoe</a> justice.
<br /><br />During these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oeXBlcmR1bmstb2x5bXBpYy13aGl0ZS1nb2xkLXAtMjgv" target="_blank">Olympic Hyperdunks</a>, Nike has put out so many Olympic inspired colorways that we’ve lost count. Featured here is the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9oeXBlcmR1bmstb2x5bXBpYy13aGl0ZS1nb2xkLXAtMjgv" target="_blank">White Gold Hyperdunk Olympic</a>, which sport a white and gold colorway. The tongue has Hyperdunk 08 stitched into it, and the gold color scheme ties into the USA Men’s Basketball team bringing home the gold. These shoes were also inspired by the olympics, which were finished about a couple of days ago. The shoe colorway is all white with a gold back and some gold on the bottem of the shoes, along with a gold Nike swoosh.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="113ace7f8823f65cd3439ca371236fc2" url=""><![CDATA[Air Max LeBron 7 Low White Green<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9haXItbWF4LWxlYnJvbi03LWxvdy13aGl0ZS1ncmVlbi1wLTkxLw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_16055890_35106807.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Followers of the low-cut <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Nike Basketball Shoe</a> brigade warmed up to the drop-top version of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9haXItbWF4LWxlYnJvbi03LXZpaS1jLTcv" target="_blank">Nike LeBron 7</a>, and this new colorway might get some oohs and aahs likewise. The neon green addition to this pair makes for a LeBron VII Dunkman Low, although there is no logo on the bottom sole. Metallic silver trim is also used on the heel, inner lining, and the Flywire panel. 
<br /><br />While LeBron James may be wearing the new Nike Lebron VII P.S. in last year's 2010 NBA playoffs. And that is not to say we will not see LeBron James in a pair of these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9haXItbWF4LWxlYnJvbi03LWxvdy13aGl0ZS1ncmVlbi1wLTkxLw__" target="_blank">Low Lebron 7 White Green</a>, in the offseason during the time when he was busy making his decisiona boutleaving or staying in Cleveland , and trying to win his second potential title. This pair of  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9haXItbWF4LWxlYnJvbi03LWxvdy13aGl0ZS1ncmVlbi1wLTkxLw__" target="_blank">Nike White Green Low Lebron 7</a> hosts a perfect summer colorway that lie ahead, With a mostly White along with a hont of Mean Green color, this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9haXItbWF4LWxlYnJvbi03LWxvdy13aGl0ZS1ncmVlbi1wLTkxLw__" target="_blank">Low Air Max Lebron 7 White Green</a> shoes also features a white leather upper came down with various Mean green accents including in the Nike Air Max 360 bubble a white shoe in the Nike Air Max 360 shoes.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dff29e91694d08e5c1e02cea76070b0a" url=""><![CDATA[Buy Nike Zoom Kobe VI Blue Black White Shoes<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9uaWtlLXpvb20ta29iZS12aS1ibHVlLWJsYWNrLXdoaXRlLXNob2VzLXAtMTUyLw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_1970018_35155444.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS96b29tLWtvYmUtNi12aS1jLTYv" target="_blank">Nike Zoom Kobe VI</a> has introduced a new style and design.This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9uaWtlLXpvb20ta29iZS12aS1ibHVlLWJsYWNrLXdoaXRlLXNob2VzLXAtMTUyLw__" target="_blank">Kobe VI Blue White</a> belongs Nike Zoom Kobe VI. The model sports a Blue White Black colorway with blue taking on the majority of the responsibility. A major detail of the design is the blue snakeskin - like scales that cover the upper. This pair of  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Nike Basketball Shoes</a> is lower, lighter and more responsive than ever.
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9uaWtlLXpvb20ta29iZS12aS1ibHVlLWJsYWNrLXdoaXRlLXNob2VzLXAtMTUyLw__" target="_blank">Nike Blue White Kobe VI</a>  has a unique upper design bump, and FLYWIRE more streamlined structure will also be hidden in the upper Among the texture. More importantly, is the sole positive image for the first time exposure, similar to the surface of the lungs full of conceptual patterns, but this &quot;bionic&quot; design <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS9uaWtlLXpvb20ta29iZS12aS1ibHVlLWJsYWNrLXdoaXRlLXNob2VzLXAtMTUyLw__" target="_blank">Blue White Zoom Kobe VI</a> shoes, fans can finally be accepted, we can look at Kobe Bryant on the ultimate effects of the foot.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="35775eec9577f1def08064665bc399eb" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Zoom Kobe 6 VI Christmas Grinch Save:30%-60% OFF<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS96b29tLWtvYmUtdmktY2hyaXN0bWFzLWdyaW5jaC1wLTE1NC8_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_15005225_35349356.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS96b29tLWtvYmUtdmktY2hyaXN0bWFzLWdyaW5jaC1wLTE1NC8_" target="_blank">Nike Kobe 6 Grinch</a> shoe, which has been given the ‘Grinch’ as well as ‘Green Mamba’ nicknames.These new images give further detailing of the neon scaly upper and candy-apple green translucent outsole and red Kobe Shozoku logos and signature on the heel. 
<br /><br />These performance <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Nike Basketball Shoes</a> were inspired by Bryant’s on-court alter ego, the Black Mamba and draws its cues from the fearsome snake. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS96b29tLWtvYmUtNi12aS1jLTYv" target="_blank">Zoom Kobe VI</a>incorporates key performance elements in a low-profile shoe that weighs just 10.6 ounces making ithis <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS96b29tLWtvYmUtdmktY2hyaXN0bWFzLWdyaW5jaC1wLTE1NC8_" target="_blank">Grinch Kobe Shoe</a> one of Nike’s lightest basketball shoes.
<br /><br />Inspired by the Grinch, this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raWNrcy1zYWxlLmNvbS96b29tLWtvYmUtdmktY2hyaXN0bWFzLWdyaW5jaC1wLTE1NC8_" target="_blank">Zoom Kobe 6 Grinch</a> shoe feature a gradient design along the upper which starts with a yellow hue at the top, and quickly becomes a shade of green as you move down towards the bottom. Finishing off the design are black and red detailing, which were used to represent the Grinch’s &quot;Santa&quot; hat.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a7c0fb8ee1be0648f967b01e00e022b" url=""><![CDATA[Buy Beijing Triumvir X Fly Nike Dunk Mid SB Shoes<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rc25lYWtlci5jb20vYmVpamluZy10cml1bXZpci14LWZseS1uaWtlLWR1bmstbWlkLXNi" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_12506744_35530026.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1kdW5rLW1pZA__" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Mid</a>,which is one of Nike's most popular branch line, has all the high quality design features that Nike company offers.They also feature a nice, simple, and subtle coloway, a relief  for many <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Shoes</a> out there.
<br /><br />Based on a close relationship with China’s Fly,Triumvir founder Brandon Cheng was offered the role of sneaker designer.The design of this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rc25lYWtlci5jb20vYmVpamluZy10cml1bXZpci14LWZseS1uaWtlLWR1bmstbWlkLXNi" target="_blank">Dunk Mid SB Beijing Triumvir X Fly</a> was inspired by Beijing including its dust,traffic,highways,noodles,and Tiananmen Square.This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rc25lYWtlci5jb20vYmVpamluZy10cml1bXZpci14LWZseS1uaWtlLWR1bmstbWlkLXNi" target="_blank">Nike Beijing Triumvir X Fly Dunk SB</a> consists of white and grey toned uppers with black appearing on the mid-section toebox and gold stitching around the swoosh.It also come with a set of charcoal grey laces and a gold logo &quot;SB&quot; on the outside of this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rc25lYWtlci5jb20vYmVpamluZy10cml1bXZpci14LWZseS1uaWtlLWR1bmstbWlkLXNi" target="_blank">Beijing Triumvir X Fly Dunk Mid Shoes</a>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89df58b80da7d4d5550386cf70b22be8" url=""><![CDATA[Nike SB Dunk - Shop For Athletic Sneaker Online<br/><br/>In 1985 the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20v" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a> Shoes Were first introduced by Nike company.Originally crafted as a basketball sneaker in the 1980s, the Dunk became the foundation of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20v" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk</a> branch in the early 2000s. The Nike SB line rode on the back of the Nike Dunk SB.The Nike SB Dunks were the same shapes as the Original Nike Dunk but featured a few alterations. At first, the line had plain colors, like the Lodens, Gino 1, Paul Brown Highs, and wheat lows, but with a zoom air insole and stuff tongue.Second, thicker padding was added to the areas around the ankle and the tongue. Besides, there was no shortage of material used on the SB Dunks.
<br /><br />On our website Sellsneaker.com,we <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20v" target="_blank">Sell Nike Dunk</a> with variety types now!All shoes such as <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20v" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk High</a> ,Nike SB Dunk Low,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20v" target="_blank">Women Nike SB Dunk</a> and so on are sold in best discount! .Fast delivery and good service are bring to you,just feel free to get your right shoes in our website!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7854d7932de8bf9c6ea9b9a58ace78d1" url=""><![CDATA[Flamingo Women Nike Dunk High Low Price<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLWhpZ2hmbGFtaW5nbw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_13181443_35865795.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />New non-team colors were introduced including the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk</a> series.The became popular in basketball, skateboarding and streetwear fashion, and so on.Here’s a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLWhpZ2hmbGFtaW5nbw__" target="_blank">Flamingo Women Nike Dunk High</a> that female sneakerheads will greatly appreciate. First,This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLWhpZ2hmbGFtaW5nbw__" target="_blank">Women Nike Dunk High Flamingo Shoes</a> come with flamingo and another shade of pink along with a touch of zest yellow.Then,The Nike swoosh is accents with the yellow while white in the laces and midsole.Besides,two shades of pink with a hint of yellow on the curv.
<br /><br />Now this fashion <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLWhpZ2hmbGFtaW5nbw__" target="_blank">Flamingo Women Dunks For Sell</a> in best discount at Sellsneaker.com where there are variety kinds of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tZHVuay1oaWdoLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Women Dunk High Shoes</a> on sale!Wonderful design, special style. Please use less money to buy goog quality dunks shoes as soon as possible!.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d114b735d122ef6440bb3845e5e8cc28" url=""><![CDATA[Custom Plum Blossom Women Nike Dunk High In Best Discount<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXBsdW0tYmxvc3NvbQ__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_9503208_35896332.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Many people admire the Plum Blossom still stand proudly in severe winter.Nike company is no exception. They combine the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tZHVuay1oaWdoLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Women Dunk High Shoes</a> with the Plum Blossom. So this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXBsdW0tYmxvc3NvbQ__" target="_blank">Women Nike SB Dunk Plum Blossom</a> is inspired by the Plum Blossom which is a a symbol of grace and nobility. The plum blossom is the wind of the Ao-xue.And now the plum blossom can be seen in ankle strap.This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXBsdW0tYmxvc3NvbQ__" target="_blank">Women Nike Dunk Plum Blossom</a> feature a Yellow/Pink/Brown/Turquoise colorway.Yellow is used for the Nike swoosh and midsole, while the pink is comes into the place on the side of the shoes. Clean white shoes lace and outsole, brown base and heel.
<br /><br />If you are the stweet girls liking the plum blossom very much will fall in love at this pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike SB  Dunk</a> shoes.Now,this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXBsdW0tYmxvc3NvbQ__" target="_blank">Plum Blossom Women Dunks For Sel</a>l at Sellsneaker.com in best discount now!We offer you high quality shoes,good service and fast shipping with resonable price!Taking action buying them as soon as possible!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5f41818ab2013e82f7564482eb3e788a" url=""><![CDATA[Strawberry Shortcake Women Nike Dunk High In Best Discount<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1kdW5rLXN0cmF3YmVycnktc2hvcnRjYWtl" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_1119079_36003595.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk</a>, Nike's most popular skateboarding shoe, has all the high quality design features that Nike offers.As such it has zoom air insoles which the regular Nike dunks do not have.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tZHVuay1oaWdoLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Women Dunk High Shoes</a> right now attract more and more young ladies all over the world!
<br /><br />The most outstanding feature of this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1kdW5rLXN0cmF3YmVycnktc2hvcnRjYWtl" target="_blank">Strawberry Shortcake Women Nike Dunk High</a> is the similar Strawberry Shortcake pattern on area of the heel and tongue.This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1kdW5rLXN0cmF3YmVycnktc2hvcnRjYWtl" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Strawberry Shortcake</a> also owns a dominant green upper along with white and some pink as well. The toe area, lace area and ankle strap will come in green while the toe box and the midfoot will be white. The swoosh on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1kdW5rLXN0cmF3YmVycnktc2hvcnRjYWtl" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Strawberry Shortcake</a> will be pink and the laces will be yellow.The upper area of the heel will feature a similar Strawberry Shortcake pattern as the other shoe.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bc21db52512cf6cad16aa8436f1404a2" url=""><![CDATA[Custom Tsunami By Twitch Women Nike Dunk High Hot Selling<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXRzdW5hbWk_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_9807551_36076659.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />This pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tZHVuay1oaWdoLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Women Dunk High Shoes</a> was well designed customs by TWiTCH which he has called the Nike dunks high wmns Tsunami - Mermaid. TWiTCH based his idea for these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXRzdW5hbWk_" target="_blank">Custom Tsunami By Twitch Women Nike Dunk High</a> from Hokusai woodblock prints and Sam Flores.Moreover,Twitch also know as Sole Affection got the Japanese inspiration for this design from Hokusai woodblock prints and Sam Flores. Let us take a look at this fashional <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXRzdW5hbWk_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Tsunami</a>shoes.They feature an image of a Japanese girl along with the rising sun which is actually a removable velcro tongue piece. The overall design involves a lot of bright vibrant colors such as pink, yellow, blue and a comic-like tsunami image.So,I think this pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Shoes</a> isn't a pair to wear, more of a collectors item or once in a blue moon sort of thing.
<br /><br />Now this wonderful <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXRzdW5hbWk_" target="_blank">Tsunami Dunks For Sell</a> at Sellsneaker.com in best discount now!Just stop there and pick up what you want as soon as possible!High quality,good service and fast shipping are all bring to you!Enjoy your shopping time there!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="572b1feb8bcdd6cf6638fcd1ab349ffc" url=""><![CDATA[Women Nike SB Dunk High Valentines Day Amor<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLWFtb3I_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_11423236_36114022.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Over the years Nike has released their fair share of red or pink Valentine’s Day-themed sneakers. So, it’s nice so see for 2011 they took a completely fresh approach with the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a> High 'Amor'. This pair of  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tZHVuay1oaWdoLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Women Dunk High Shoes</a>  features a Sail-colored canvas upper with intricately embroidered, love-inspired illustrations. The illustrations include lovebirds, hearts, roses, Cupids, and the word 'Amor' (Latin for love). Nike completed the Nike Dunk High 'Amor' with a red tongue tag and red insoles, which showcase lovebirds on the right, and 'Amor' on the left. The attention to detail and craftsmanship will surely impress. They look so nice that I suggest skipping the flowers this year, and picking up a pair these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLWFtb3I_" target="_blank">Amor Nike Dunk</a> Shoes for the sneaker-loving sweetheart in your life.
<br /><br />The Valentine’s Day had passed,but did you remember this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLWFtb3I_" target="_blank">Women Nike Dunk Amor</a> which named by it,Maybe many more people bought the shoe as a gift on that day.Now here we take a look at this woderful and fashion shoes.First of all,this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLWFtb3I_" target="_blank">Nike Amor Dunks</a> feature an Sail upper with a Black all-over print on it. From a distance it looks like lace however upon closer inspection you will noticed that birds, roses, Cupids and “Amor” is printed all over the sneaker.Second,the leather Swoosh matches the laces, liner and outsole.Moreover,Its black-on-grey construction reflects where the kick game’s at in 2011, with the entire shoe colored in these two neutrals yet very busy thanks to all-over embroidery.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c7109c8604fb484474305be002c5917c" url=""><![CDATA[Women Nike Dunk High Jordyn Symone Winnie Big Pooh Edition<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXdpbm5pZS1iaWctcG9vaA__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_3400674_36177869.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />It seems this pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tZHVuay1oaWdoLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Women Dunk High Shoes</a> would be good and much appreciated. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Shoes</a> get to the current fashion. Popular as Winnie in the past at a time when it was a popular Disney characters. As we know, Disney is synonymous with the richness and magic of life, people always memorable endless amount of visual delights of this faithful to the characters that are alive as long as you remember. If you're a big fan of Disney,I think this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXdpbm5pZS1iaWctcG9vaA__" target="_blank">Women Nike Dunk High Winnie Big Pooh Shoes</a> will be the best choice for you.
<br /><br />Winnie is enjoyed by people all over the world,Pooh is the nickname of Winnie the Pooh which is a famous and adorable cartoon character of The Walt Disney. Now here is <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXdpbm5pZS1iaWctcG9vaA__" target="_blank">Winnie Big Pooh Women Nike Dunk High</a> over Winnie.This Nike Dunk Big Pooh with a cute Winnie in the shoe's upper in orange and red. The white leather toe box and red lace panel of these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vd29tZW4tbmlrZS1kdW5rLXdpbm5pZS1iaWctcG9vaA__" target="_blank">Women Nike Dunk Winnie Big Pooh</a> is a good combination. The Pooh image in the shoes both sides are different but they all show the lovely of Winnie.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c692d7efcde243b74a8d602ba800ab69" url=""><![CDATA[Custom Batman Nike Dunk High Hot Sale<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vY3VzdG9tLWJhdG1hbi1uaWtlLWR1bms_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_4178379_36254162.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Nike SB determined to grant them a pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1kdW5rLXNiLWhpZ2g_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk High</a> Dinosaur Jr to commemorate the group’s return and their comeback back again album. It attributes a metallic silver color-way with purple accents, which include purple stitching, outsole, and laces. It also attributes a little figure holding up a peace symbolic representation around the heel from the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Shoes</a>.
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vY3VzdG9tLWJhdG1hbi1uaWtlLWR1bms_" target="_blank">Batman Nike Dunk</a> is inspired by the Batman and also is made for paying homage to the super hero Batman. This  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vY3VzdG9tLWJhdG1hbi1uaWtlLWR1bms_" target="_blank">Nike SB Batman Dunk</a> would be satisfied by the fans of Batman and is no doubt that the one would match Batman's black cape attire. The bright yellow used in the Swoosh and other place of the Nike Dunk High Batman make the sneaker much more brilliant. The sneaker has a black/grey upper just like the Batman cape and a black sole. In addition, if you look close to this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vY3VzdG9tLWJhdG1hbi1uaWtlLWR1bms_" target="_blank">Batman Dunks</a>, you would find that there is a popular Batman logo on the sneaker.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ebf62b148c81e859dad2b67cc7d5d01f" url=""><![CDATA[Premium Id Superman Nike Dunk High For Sale<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1zYi1kdW5rLXByZW1pdW0taWQtc3VwZXJtYW4_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_13693139_36302308.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a> combine the superman with the the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1kdW5rLXNiLWhpZ2g_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk High</a> shoes.This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1zYi1kdW5rLXByZW1pdW0taWQtc3VwZXJtYW4_" target="_blank">Superman Dunks</a> inspired by the SuperMan, whose color scheme is just similar to the uniform of the SuperMan. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1zYi1kdW5rLXByZW1pdW0taWQtc3VwZXJtYW4_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Superman</a> features blue leather as base in the upper and the stylized 'S' shield on his chest has been printed in the side of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1zYi1kdW5rLXByZW1pdW0taWQtc3VwZXJtYW4_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Superman</a> shoes. It should not be missed by the superman fanatics. In addition, the shoe is customizable by customers and has excellent cushioning for the use of the full-length EVA midsole.
<br /><br />Superman is well known as a fictional character, a comic book superhero appearing in publications by DC Comics, widely is considered to be an American cultural icon. Superman was created by American writer Jerry Siegel and Canadian-born American artist Joe Shuster in 1932. Superman also helped to create the superhero genre and establish its primacy within the American comic book.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5f39ea4607d054193c0f6292f1a024fd" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk Low Pro SB Unkle Newest Sale<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXVua2xlLXNob2Vz" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_13606241_36360541.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXVua2xlLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low Pro SB Unkle</a> is one of those rare finds as they had a production run of about 5 pairs. Designed by Futura for the music group, this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXVua2xlLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Dunks SB Low Unkle Shoes</a> were made for the James Lavelle’s relatives and friends.As you can see, the “Mo Wax” records label is on the footbedding of the kicks. Mo Wax is also the record label James Lavelle started. The Nike Low Pro SB Dunk Unkle shoes of coursework come with the three original authentic pairs of laces with the Nike SB logo on the outer bag that contains the additional pair of laces.The FUTURA-designed <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1sb3ctc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Low</a> Pro ‘UNKLE’ was/woulda been basically an olive green take on the same Never, Never, Land look, but you’ve probably never seen a pair cos only something like four were ever made.
<br /><br />Now this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXVua2xlLXNob2Vz" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Unkle For Sell</a> in best discount at Sellsneaker.com where there are variety kinds of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Shoes</a> Hot Selling now!Just get your right shoes there!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e4e20a53b9e3749fc464de0d6aac0456" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk Low Astro Boy On Sale<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LWFzdHJvLWJveS1zaG9lcw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_2868783_36438330.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Here is the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LWFzdHJvLWJveS1zaG9lcw__" target="_blank">Astro Boy Nike Dunk Low</a>,which is an amazing collection of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk</a>. Original Dunk Pro SB Astro Boy Edition feature a &quot;fat tongue&quot; and a &quot;Zoom Air&quot; insole. Full leather upper breathable mesh tongue with elastic centering straps Phylon.This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LWFzdHJvLWJveS1zaG9lcw__" target="_blank">Astro Boy Dunks</a> inspired by the famous Astro Boy that the beloved'60s Japanese anime series.color red black white has its own style, it wears a very awesome layout for the ankle belt have astro boy’s mode. This pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1sb3ctc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Low</a> shoes adopted general Nike Dunk swoosh, darkness bottom and interior lining. Nike Dunk Astro Boy Shoes in colourway ribbon, whitening. These<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LWFzdHJvLWJveS1zaG9lcw__" target="_blank">Dunks SB Low Astro Boy Shoes</a> mix of very simple and inspiring shades of red, black and white. To make it stylish, it wears a very amazing design for its ankle strap with a astro boy pattern. The astro boy shoes has a red leather that covers the mostly area followed by the black nike swoosh, midsole and inner lining. The shoes lace comes in a white colourway.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dc10b4fb17c0dc6e3df72969a152c51d" url=""><![CDATA[Nike SB Dunk Mid Premium Northern Lights Shoes Buying<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1taWQtbm9ydGhlcm4tbGlnaHRz" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_6020548_36573345.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1taWQtbm9ydGhlcm4tbGlnaHRz" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Northern Lights</a> with a dark but clean colorway which features a nice mix of charcoal grey suede and pebbled black leather for the upper. Along with an iridescent check which is meant to resemble the storied Northern Lights or Aurora Borealis.
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1taWQtbm9ydGhlcm4tbGlnaHRz" target="_blank">Dunk SB Mid Northern Lights</a> isn’t a special strain of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1taWQtc2Itc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Mid</a> that’s only legal in a few states, but rather a shoutout to the southern hemisphere’s breathtaking natural laser light show.  The irridescent green Swooshes mimic the Aurora Borealis’ light emissions that eminate from rapid collisions of solar particles.  These <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1taWQtbm9ydGhlcm4tbGlnaHRz" target="_blank">Northern Lights Dunks</a> look just fantastic in a mix of brown suede and black leather, and they’re set to release at select <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20v" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk</a> retailers today.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c244da8578c72bb837f7a4f0f58535ed" url=""><![CDATA[LeBron VIII V2 Black Red On Sale<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vYmxhY2stcmVkLXYyLWxlYnJvbi12aWlp" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_10247012_36615619.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Lebron 8 V2 shoes features mesh and Flywire team up for a super-strong upper,and signature details represent <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LWxlYnJvbi1zaG9lcw__" target="_blank">Nike LeBron 8</a>'s style on and off the court.Benefits Flywire at the upper for ultra-lightweight support and lockdown control,Mesh at the upper for breathability, reducing the overall weight of the shoeMax Air 360 unit for basketball-specific cushioningLightweight outsole designed specifically for LeBron's quick cuts.StructureMaximizing support and minimizing weight is what the LeBron 8 V2 is all about.Now let us take a look at this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vYmxhY2stcmVkLXYyLWxlYnJvbi12aWlp" target="_blank">Black Red Lebron VIII V2</a> shoes.
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vYmxhY2stcmVkLXYyLWxlYnJvbi12aWlp" target="_blank">Lebron VIII V2 Black Red</a> shoes owns a full-length Max Air sole and Flywire along the side, similar to  the standard LeBron 8.And this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vYmxhY2stcmVkLXYyLWxlYnJvbi12aWlp" target="_blank">Nike Black Red Lebron VIII V2</a> shoes features simple Miami Heat style with Black being the base color. Red swoosh, outsole and the laces match perfectly with their road uniforms. The speckled air unit is just an additional pop, which really makes the shoes stand out.  Outfitted in a mostly black upper, the model takes red and white to task and incorporates the Nike swoosh and Flywire. This pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Lebron Shoes</a> is a design in the vein of the LeBron VII PS as a stripped down version of the regular season original.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1809311bc0979432842d316ae210098a" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk Low SB St Patrick Celtics On Sale<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXBhdHJpY2stY2VsdGljcw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_10292192_36650795.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXBhdHJpY2stY2VsdGljcw__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low SB St. Patrick Celtics</a> - white classic green launched the Nike SB line in March of 2002 at the start of the rise of the Skateboarding trend. For years in California, the skate culture was very popular and skateboarding shoes and clothes were worn more as casual wear than by actual skateboarders. Nike saw the potential to tapping into this market and thus launched the Nike Skateboarding line.Nike launched their skateboarding lines on the back of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk</a> .
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXBhdHJpY2stY2VsdGljcw__" target="_blank">St Patrick Celtics Nike Dunk</a> is a simple pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1sb3ctc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Dunk SB Low Shoes</a>, and features an all white leather upper with a green Nike swoosh and green laces. The nickname has to do with the colorway and the March release date (St. Partrick’s Day). It is also dubbed the Celtics Dunk SB because the color resembles those of the Boston Celtics basketball team. They were designed by Hunter Muraira, and really had no hype behind their release.Moreover,this great <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXBhdHJpY2stY2VsdGljcw__" target="_blank">St Patrick Celtics Dunks Shoes</a> are now hot selling at sellsneaker in best discount and coming in both men and women sizes.Get your right shoes there as soon as possible!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bcd0387b8a6d70f2f6f935e5e30cc165" url=""><![CDATA[Nike SB Dunk Low Premium Kuwahara Et Shoes Shopping<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LWt1d2FoYXJhLWV0" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_8106945_36740436.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Here is the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LWt1d2FoYXJhLWV0" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Low Kuwahara ET</a> shoes,which has named the Kuwahara ET. The latest pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1kdW5rLWxvdy13b21lbi1zaG9lcw__" target="_blank">Women Nike SB Dunk Low</a> Premium draws inspiration from the bicycle featured in the late 80?s movie. The bike was something special at the time as it had not been widely produced outside of Japan until director Steven Spielberg put in a order for 40 of these custom BMX bikes to be shipped out to Hollywood.This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LWt1d2FoYXJhLWV0" target="_blank">Dunk SB Low Kuwahara ET</a> feature a white to red gradient, constructed entirely from patent leather. The heel tab also features some sort of stitched illustration on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LWt1d2FoYXJhLWV0" target="_blank">Kuwahara ET Dunks</a> .
<br /><br />Now this wonderful shoes are in best discount at sellsneaker where there are variety kinds of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a> shoes for sale now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bf0e93b00f1fe3a86de8035d25d95e17" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunks Low SB Slam CITY Skates Best Sell<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXNsYW0tY2l0eS1za2F0ZXM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_11650938_36782405.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Here is the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXNsYW0tY2l0eS1za2F0ZXM_" target="_blank">Slam City Skates Dunks</a> shoe which is a collaboration between Slam City Skates and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20v" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk</a>. Slam City set out to design a truly functional skate shoe that was an improvement from the basic Nike SB model. This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXNsYW0tY2l0eS1za2F0ZXM_" target="_blank">Slam City Skates Dunk SB</a> features reinforced padding in the footbed and upper, white contrast stitching, scratch -off color on the Swoosh, rubber panels on the toe for durability, and maps on the insole to legendary London skate sports. Each pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1sb3ctc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Low</a> comes with white laces and an extra set of turquoise laces with Zoom – Air innersoles.This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3Mtc2ItbG93LXNsYW0tY2l0eS1za2F0ZXM_" target="_blank">Slam City Skates Dunk Low</a> feature mainly light taupe upper while black accents in the lace pane, overlay sidewall and midsole. The special turquoise is applied to the Nike swoosh, tongue tab and heel logo.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a835ce2179c9e6a1f149e5a6ff19bec" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk Low Pro SB Apple Green Black Low Price<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1zYi1kdW5rcy1sb3ctYXBwbGUtZ3JlZW4tYmxhY2stc2hvZXM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_9831642_36837491.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Here is the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1zYi1kdW5rcy1sb3ctYXBwbGUtZ3JlZW4tYmxhY2stc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low Apple</a> shoe that is one of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk</a> which is the Street attention degree first shoe.This pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1sb3ctc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Low</a> feature a suede and leather mixed upper accented with apple green in the swoosh, toe box, outsole and so on. The design of Chrome Brender Incident Pack form the legendary skateboarding artist Neil Brender, alluding to the late 1990s, when snowboarders to create own strong style, BanXie. This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1zYi1kdW5rcy1sb3ctYXBwbGUtZ3JlZW4tYmxhY2stc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Nike SB Apple</a> will alteration of shoes tongue Dunk SB is thick, simple sense the design of Nike is great, the SB skateboarding series little of course not the peculiar complex modulation Zoom Air insoles, the foot feels soft mattress. For comfort is greatly ascend.
<br /><br />Now this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vbmlrZS1zYi1kdW5rcy1sb3ctYXBwbGUtZ3JlZW4tYmxhY2stc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Dunk SB Low Apple Green Black For Sell</a> at sellsneaker.com in best discount now!Buy more,save more!Just stop here and get your right shoes as soon as possible!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="816eb3d8ac1a17c1edd9a99a1d573b57" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk Low Custom Kicks By Elna Shoes Online<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVua3MtbG93LWVsbmFzLWJsdWUtc2hvZXM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/158310323_7154817_36891208.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />The impressive &amp; very artistic customized designs - <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vY3VzdG9tLWR1bmstbG93LWtpY2stYnktZWxuYQ__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low Custom Kicks By Elna</a> are design by the student named ELNA. ELNA created three customized pairs of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a>as part of his final project at the Bezalel Academy of Art &amp; Design and then created a video to help market them.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vY3VzdG9tLWR1bmstbG93LWtpY2stYnktZWxuYQ__" target="_blank">Custom Kicks By Elna Dunks</a> is a graphic designer from Israel who created a broadcast design project for Bezalel Academy of Art and Design. ELNA Obviously spent a lot of time to this often Dunk custom shoes to give the most color and appearance of the imagination.Each of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vZHVuay1zYi1sb3ctc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Dunk SB Low Shoes</a> were outfitted in bold strokes, playful shapes and vibrant colors. The color choices are a bit crazy but works really well with each other and undeniably unique in some ways.
<br /><br />Moreover,this wonderful <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWxsc25lYWtlci5jb20vY3VzdG9tLWR1bmstbG93LWtpY2stYnktZWxuYQ__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Kicks By Elna For Sell</a> at sellsneaker.com in best discount!Just get your right shoes as soon as possible.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>