<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="17">
		<document id="21f66ece1c716dafd14cbf181a44dc9b" url=""><![CDATA[PAN sucks!!<br/><br/>OK, pan.netused to be a meeting places for likeminded individuals who wanted to share ideas  and make friends across the country/world who have similar outlooks on life as they do. 
<br />Now though, ntelog officially SUCKS!! The new layout is confusing, hard to make sense of and distracting. The only people chatting are those posting up 'chain' blogs or horny twats who think they can actually get a shag off here (try going out into the real world, meeting a real girl and having some real sex rather than beat urself off like a brain damaged monkey watching some filth on webcam!!). The only people who 'look' at my profile are all fucking sex site links. No-one seems to reply to any messages they get sent (other than the token &quot;im fine thanks, how r u?<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" />. To be perfectly honest, for the last few months i havent had a decent or stimulating conversation on here!! So fuck it, im off to Facebook untill 'facebox' returns!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="239bdff72287e2733852adfcdbdb9579" url=""><![CDATA[Ta Dah!!!<br/><br/>Well I've finally arrived on FaceBox! Where was the fanfare and adoring fans??? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />  Oh well, an oversight im sure. So, guess I'd better do a quick bit of interaction with anyone reading this: Hi there, how are u? Had a busy day? Much trouble finding my page?
<br /><br />Right then!that should be enough to make u feel like we have a connection and keep u interested. Dont really have much to say at the moment so that whole 'getting to know each other' was a bit of a waste of time, not so much for me cos i only have to write this once and forget about it, all u guys have to read it, and still are reading it, which says a lot about u! haha, only joking (showing my quirky side of my sense of humour, coupled with an apology to convey my more 'human side' for the ladies out there <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />  ) Actually, thinking about it, thi whole interaction bit has been pretty one sided, i feel like u know me, but i haven't a clue who u are! Not that that is a bad thing, i might not like u, so drop me a line and lets get chatting. BFN!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bbdfb56327fc6514057e5082ffc061df" url=""><![CDATA[Hmmmm<br/><br/>Just a quickie, but am i the only person disturbed by the fact that if u dont have a pic on here ur automatically designated a male little picture thing?? Or are they all secretly males?? and whats with its haircut? Its like Jimmy Carr in Face Off 2!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d8d2526e37df2ddd9e2451386829d468" url=""><![CDATA[My Clan<br/><br/>Join my clan if ur bored of having randoms try and speak to you when ur really not interested and if girls u actually wanna talk to turn out to be bots!!!! In fact, just join my clan!!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e7332e7ab6eba83c315e63b316fdc816" url=""><![CDATA[Question for the day<br/><br/>Ok, question for the day: If you went out on the pull, and pulled a Hermaphrodite, would that count as a threesome?? puzzler, aint it!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d717950b13980caa8c3e6c00c77c1c98" url=""><![CDATA[Serious question<br/><br/>Ok, serious question! Why is it that (single) guys post up blogs like 'do you think im sexy? would you date me? would you kiss me? would u let me suck your toes? would u rub hot fudge into my ass crack whilst i wear your underwear and sing the national anthem in a girly voice????? What do they think will happen? that a hot, porn starlet will see it and think &quot;you know what, this guy sounds like exactly the kinda guy i want, a guy full of self esteem and confidence! I could well fall head over in heels with this guy and spend long nights of hot sex with him when his parents arent in!&quot; Why guys, why do u reduce yourselves to this??? And more importantly, which (single) guy after reading that a girl is interested in rubbing hot fudge into ur ass crack whilst u wear the girls underwear and sing the national anthem in a girly voice would honestly think to themselves &quot;She doesnt sound like a nutter, i think i might say hi to this one!!&quot; GET HELP PEOPLE!!!!!!!!!!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b74ca749e3f2c79af4110909f65721c3" url=""><![CDATA[Muesli<br/><br/>Who invented muesli?? They have a lot to answer for!! Its shit!! Just ahd to get that off my chest!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71356dc9f33c7e210e03913230401df2" url=""><![CDATA[Random rants<br/><br/>Ok, just a few things that have annoyed me recently. 
<br />1. why do people feel the need to tell me all their probelsm when im out on a nite on the town?? Serious, i was just happily at a bar and some random comes up and starts pouring their heart out!! pissed me right off!! lol
<br />2. Why do some people go all moody and huffy, then when u ask &quot;whats wrong?&quot; they say &quot;nothing, it doesnt matter&quot; when clearly it does? Not being funny, but i was asking because ur bringing everyone else down around u, if u want to wallow in ur own self pity, do it on ur time, not mine!!
<br />3. Why is it, no matter how many times u give somone the advice they asked for, they still dont do what u said and come back and say &quot;noone likes me, they all take the piss out of me, im so depressed&quot;. &quot;I've told u repeatedly why, and how to fix the problem, ur just seeking attention now and i really cant be arsed with u!!&quot;
<br />Aaah, feel sooooooo much better now
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="73723f1bdf2ba4314935467f3d0c80bd" url=""><![CDATA[Sex Therapists<br/><br/>Ok, why is it, on any TV sex therapy program (ie, The Sex Doctors, Good Sex Guide, etc.) that as soon as the topic of conversation gets to masturbattion they cut to a 50yr old dragon/lady saying, in a gruff, 50 fags a day voice, that &quot;Oh, i love to masturbate most days, its a great experience to get to know my own body&quot; while her worringly thin old fella is sat there just nodding his head in agreement?? I thought the idea of these programs was to get us to go out (or stay in, lol) and enjoy sex more. Now, whenever im getting down and dirty, or im 'enjoying myself' im gonna have the mental image of that decrepid old witch next to me saying &quot;explore yourself honey&quot; as her gollumesque partner sits there like a freakin nodding dog!! 
<br />Aaaaaargh!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fc1dd6f7b8350fc0dbab62fdded9d4c8" url=""><![CDATA[Sci Fi movies (im a geek, get used to it!!)<br/><br/>OK, i know im gonna sound a bit geeky, but theres something about sci fi movies with androids in it that winds me up. Why is is that the character who through the whole film we are led to believe is a human who turns out to be a psyco killer robot, only starts making robot noises and talking in a robot way once they've been found out?? Did the other characters overlook the mechanical whirring noise whenever he moved or did they just think they had chronic arthiritis?? And the 'all of a sudden monotone voice'? Whats that about? did the robot character think &quot;oh well, ive been found out, no point trying to hide now?&quot; Grrrr! if ur gonna pretend to be a human, just keep it going till the end, u never know, if u kept up the act u coulda sneaked off that sapce station and been off on ur merry way by now!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f1ce16223140788f4001d067161429d9" url=""><![CDATA[Final sci fi rant<br/><br/>While im on the subject, why is it that when someone on an alien film reveals themselves as an alien imposter, is there always one person who says &quot;I knew all along they were an alien&quot;. Not being funny, but that alien/person has just eaten, maimed and killed an entire ship of people because u didnt speak up earlier!! Smarmy twat!
<br /><br />on another note, if u were injured by an alien, would the crew be able to claim under work related accidents for compensation?? these things need to be addressed!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="753f201d957bc6d6ca1e38bea76a8e7d" url=""><![CDATA[Mashed Potato<br/><br/>Mashed potato fucking rocks!! Im eating some right now, and I actually think its that good i should let u all know. I fucking love mashed potato!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2541c0333292be7505e390bff0997ed6" url=""><![CDATA[Detox is sooooo funny!!<br/><br/>Ok, forget going to comedy clubs, paying to see comedians or going to see a funny film! The cheapest way to nigh on piss yourself with laughter is to go out on a nite out/party/pub nite with your mates, and NOT get drunk while watching everyone else get battered!! I did that last nite and oh my fucking god it was hilarious!! Admittedly I was at a house party and did kinda stir things up by starting a game of truth or dare, but when your surrounded by very drunk mates who are very open to suggestion, it makes for a really funny nite!! Try it, its fucking hilarious!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f95ee4e85edb4ae146ce92c3e22b11c" url=""><![CDATA[Jack and Jill<br/><br/>Jack and Jill went up a hill,
<br />So Jack could lick Jills fanny.
<br />Jack got a shock 
<br />And a mouthfull of cock
<br />Cos Jills a pre op tranny
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1dfe74e71ce46904bddc59158b3c29b1" url=""><![CDATA[Clans shutting down<br/><br/>OK, does anyone else agree that by shutting down ALL the adult clans, those people who are members of clans that ARENT about teen sex, cam sex or other sickass stuff are being punished for THEIR perversions?? What about the clans for Tattoos, Music, Art, Films, Literature, Lifestyle, etc. who dont go into their clan to try and watch someone beating themselves off like a wind up monkey on webcam?? 
<br />Am i the only person who thinks its all a bit unfair??
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ac604019bb080e169a4401f856ae2665" url=""><![CDATA[ladies<br/><br/>Ok ladies, this one is aimed at you! i got only 2 words to say: 'Matching' and 'Underwear'!!
<br />Seriously, is it that hard to wear underwear that is at least the same colour?? i mean, if ur bra is white, then wear white panties, if ur wearing a black thong then wear a black bra!! its not hard, and make it look like u put a bit of thought into what u wear which makes u look like u give a shit about what the guy ur 'entertaining' thinks!! 
<br /><br />Im glad i got that off my chest! lol
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b6e07d4ab97d4f432f2510b07da117a0" url=""><![CDATA[Supervillains<br/><br/>Ok, Dr. Evil, Dr. Doom, Dr. Octopus, Dr. Strange, Dr. No, Dr Moriarty. All of them are super villains, all of them are doctors but what do they actually have a doctorate in?? Has anyone ever wondered that?
<br />I personally feel that i would be extremely let down if say Dr. Doom had a doctorate in say 'fine art' or was vet!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>