<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="14">
		<document id="11c10fbd56bd83e7089c8efe72936d4f" url=""><![CDATA[A Review of Recordingconnection.com<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9tZWV0LW91ci1tZW50b3Jz" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordproduction.com%2Fblossom-recording-studios-1.jpg%26quot%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.recordproduction.com/blossom-recording-studios-1.jpg&quot;</a>; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;260&quot; height=&quot;190]</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9tZWV0LW91ci1tZW50b3Jz" target="_blank">Recording Connection</a> (<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.recordingconnection.com</a>) has ignited a few conversation both in the music and academic fields due to the fact that of its unique method to relay education and learning. The gist of the program is that pupils of the Recording Connection are placed as apprentices in real recording studios, instead of in campus classrooms and studio laboratories. Offered that the price of this program is considerably less than additional audio schools charge, it fuels some dispute as to whether the program is successful, or also legitimate.<br /><br />Lots of times, worries are raised over a program merely because its method is different from the norm, and frequently those concerns can be reduced just by doing some analysis. To this end, virtually any sort of question about Recording Connection's mentor-apprentice approach can be answered by going to their web site, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.recordingconnection.com</a>. The school has actually gone to wonderful lengths to create an extensive web site filled with practical and informative material, clearly corresponding their vision and philosophy, along with sharing openly about the outcomes of their program.<br /><br />Visiting the internet site is no contrast, but to give a general idea on what you can easily discover at the website of Recording Connection, they are as follows:<br /><br />ACCREDITATIONS AND MEMBERSHIPS<br />Recording Conneciton is professional like the additional schools and it has actually even acquired certification from 2 companies. Those organizations are detailed, along with links to their particular web sites.<br /><br />EXPLANATION OF APPRENTICESHIP<br />The school offers a clear explanation of its mentor-apprentice technique: exactly how it works, how pupils are placed in studios, the benefits of one-on-one direction, and the distinction between an apprentice and an intern.<br /><br />FINANCIAL DETAILS<br />The school discloses full information about its tuition, funding possibilities, and refund policy.<br /><br />EDUCATIONAL PROGRAM SUMMARY<br />Although the school puts each pupil in a recording studio to be mentored by a working specialist, it also offers a structured curriculum to be followed. The school supplies a review of each lesson on its internet site, so prospective students can see exactly what is covered.<br /><br />STAFF/ADMINISTRATION INFORMATION<br />The internet site also features the list of administration personnels together with their contact details, including CEO and Chief Academic Officer emails.<br /><br />STUDENT TESTIMONIALS<br />Potentially the most expansive part of the site, Recordingconnection.com features hundreds of unedited reviews from students and graduates who have actually experienced the program. These speak volumes about the school's usefulness.<br /><br />PROFESSIONAL ENDORSEMENTS<br />A great several music market professionals have actually endorsed the school for its functional mentor-apprentice technique, and some have actually also come to be mentors. The advertisements are found in the different areas of the web site, particularly at the &quot;Ambassadors&quot; page.<br /><br />In short, anything you like to know about the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXBlZXEuY29tL2hvbWUvYXJ0aWNsZS8zMjI4Ny9BLVN1bW1hcnktb2YtUmVjb3JkaW5nY29ubmVjdGlvbi5jb20_" target="_blank">Recording Connection Audio Institute</a>, you can discover on their site. The program is for chosen individuals just and not all, but <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.recordingconnection.com</a> has actually made terrific efforts to help you determine whether it is right for you or not.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6564a6a688fbaf431c11c5a7ce3325b9" url=""><![CDATA[How the Recording Connection Assists Pupils Link to the Musi<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fimg.ehowcdn.com%2Farticle-new%2Fehow%2Fimages%2Fa07%2Fgq%2Fhs%2Fmusic-recording-colleges-atlanta-ga-800x800.jpg%26quot%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://img.ehowcdn.com/article-new/ehow/images/a07/gq/hs/music-recording-colleges-atlanta-ga-800x800.jpg&quot;</a>; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;260&quot; height=&quot;190]</a>Students of audio engineering encounter a barrier when it pertains to creating connections in the music business. Through its mentor-apprentice approach, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Recording Connection</a> (<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnection.com</a>) delivers its pupils a one-of-a kind possibility to make those connections while they're studying.<br /><br />Audio engineering education and learning is not a problem for standard schools and institutions. The problem is that the music sector is mostly relationship-driven, to the point that without having business contacts, it's extremely hard to land a job, no matter how extensive your education is. A lot of audio engineering education and learning confine their students in an enclosed atmosphere such as classrooms and laboratory studios which is where they fall short. Students can find out the necessary abilities in these atmospheres, however they just can't make any feeling of connection to the real music industry. As an effect, the pupils locate it challenging to land a job in the music world, forcing them to participate in works beyond their industry simply so they can make ends meet.<br /><br />The Recording Connection (<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnection.com</a>) efficiently solves this issue with a simple answer: train pupils in the places where the action in fact happens-in genuine recording studios. With the mentor-apprentice approach, each pupil is put individually as an apprentice in a real recording studio, and each student gets customized, one-on-one direction from a working audio qualified inside that studio. In addition to working through a structured curriculum, the pupil gets to find out the cordages on actual recording projects-and at the same time, he/she gets to fulfill plenty of industry professionals who're working on those projects. By learning in the &quot;genuine world,&quot; so to speak, the student has the chance to show himself/herself to the people in the studio every day-so by the time the student graduates, if he/she has done well and built a rapport, the pupil will likely be amongst the first to be considered for any sort of job openings that emerge. In short-each Recording Connection pupil has the opportunity to become a business expert throughout the course of apprenticeship.<br /><br />One concern that has actually been prevented is the total amount it will cost for the education. When a college or trade school sets up a separated learning environment, it is usually very expensive to create and preserve that environment, and those expenses get passed to the students in the sort of high tuition. (This is why so many graduate with high levels of pupil debt.) On the other hand, the training being offered by Recording Connection does not ask for a high overhead price, resulting to a friendly-priced program.<br /><br />It ought to be evident currently that education alone isn't enough to establish oneself in the music recording industry. Students are assisted by <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXBlZXEuY29tL2hvbWUvYXJ0aWNsZS8zMjg3MS9FeGFjdGx5LWhvdy10aGUtUmVjb3JkaW5nLUNvbm5lY3Rpb24tQXNzaXN0cy1QdXBpbHMtQ29ubmVjdC10by10aGUtTXVzaWMtSW5kdXN0cnk_" target="_blank">Recording Connection</a> to develop their very own network of qualified connection in the music world that not all schools can easily offer.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a8d2696e31d2014923405c75d59df9d" url=""><![CDATA[http://www.recordingconnection.com<br />The Selection<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fimg.ehowcdn.com%2Farticle-new%2Fehow%2Fimages%2Fa05%2Fsr%2Fhb%2Fmusic-recording-jobs-1.1-800x800.jpg%26quot%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://img.ehowcdn.com/article-new/ehow/images/a05/sr/hb/music-recording-jobs-1.1-800x800.jpg&quot;</a>; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;260&quot; height=&quot;190]</a>Excited in embarking on a career in audio or sound engineering? Or possibly you  would certainly like to be a music producer with the real, strong abilities it takes to accomplish that best audio? Well go the typical route and you're examining $ 25,000 to $ 50,000 and as much as Five years in school, or for $ 8,400 and merely six months of intensive training, you can get a real-world, hands-on education and learning that blows the others away. Take your pick.<br /><br />Recording Connection's fully approved, certified program is backed by the extremely exact same professionals who make records for The White Stripes, Alice in Chains, Pearl Jam, Led Zeppelin, Eminem, Black Eyed Peas, M.I. A, Mos Def, 50 Cent, Usher, Madonna, Outkast, Beyonce, U2, Michael Jackson, Alicia Keys, Paul McCartney, Bob Dylan, and Willie Nelson, to name simply several. Select them and in nearly 6 months you can easily have what it takes to work in the studio and also be at the helm of your very own projects, working with the artists of your choice.<br /><br />Rather than deliver you to some classroom or lecture hall, The Recording Connection (<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnection.com</a></a>) gets you on the inside of a genuine recording studio on day one. Instead of being one of numerous, thanks to their groundbreaking mentor-guided method, you study one-on-one under the direct tutelage of an industry pro who has actually undoubtedly worked on the very exact same tunes you know and enjoy.<br /><br />The approach is what makes Recording Connection efficient and inexpensive and additionally resulting to the system to come to be more effective. When you take audio engineering and music production from the studio and attempt to instruct it by making use of a talk-down approach, you lose the very context and framework you have to make it appropriate to the pupil. Therefore, pupils may be able to mention what &quot;analog&quot; is during a test, but might perplex it with the digital works after they get moving in an actual studio. Additionally, their understanding will certainly frequently have substantial spaces precisely since all the lots of elements that go into the craft have actually been taught at different times and by different teachers. Spending time inside the laboratory or doing studio work is simply part of their course and it is not very well included with the ideas and the equipment they deal with are not that advanced to satisfy the requirements of the sector. For this reason, finding out within the bubble that is academia just does not make them prepared for work in the genuine world.<br /><br />Since Recording Connection places their pupils in a real studio and not in standard classrooms, the expense of the program is extremely inexpensive and the students and their household can considerably benefit from the discounts. Learning hands-on, directly from a pro, makes it possible for the apprentice to obtain a genuine understanding of the practices and methods used in the production environment. Backed by the solid, extensive Recording Connection program of studies, their expertise base will certainly consist of the both the scientific and functional in a means that is incorporated, as 2 sides of the same coin, because that's precisely what they are. Because of the sturdy and extensive curriculum delivered by Recording Connection, they will obtain both the incorporated theoretical and functional understanding, hitting two  with one stone.<br /><br />The Recording Connection program of studies includes: noise, acoustics, waveforms, digital and audio basics including sampling and quantizing sound and Nyquist Theorem, quantization principles, Pro Tools, the blending board (or console), mic placement and operation, audio processing, signal flow and patch bays, USB, MIDI, Electronic Music, sync and automation, drum and guitar microphone techniques, signal processing, EQ processing, surround sound mixing, final mix-down, plus more.<br /><br />And since they will certainly be finding out in a real working atmosphere, the apprentices will certainly have the possibility to establish important contacts while discovering at the exact same time. Such an option is vital when it pertains to landing paid work and making the contacts one needs to be a genuine contender in the field. Other programs leave you on the outside at college graduation and it can easily take years for even the most blessed to locate their &quot;in,&quot; which is precisely where Recording Connection puts you right from the beginning.<br /><br />To discover more, go directly to their internet site <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXBlZXEuY29tL2hvbWUvYXJ0aWNsZS8zMzYzNy9odHRwJTNBJTI1LSUyNS13d3cucmVjb3JkaW5nY29ubmVjdGlvbi5jb20lM0Nici0lMjUtJTNFVGhlLUNob2ljZS1mb3ItYS1Qcm9mZXNzaW9uLWluLVNvdW5kLXRoYXQlMjdzLUVuZG9yc2VkLWJ5LVRoZS1Qcm9zJTNDYnItJTI1LSUzRQ__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnection.com</a></a> and fill in the web-form or offer them a call. You can even establish a meeting between you and your possible mentor in your location entirely free of cost or any sort of obligation. When it concerns a sound education that pays, select the pros at The Recording Connection.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="726f6c419b646e4d14291b070c81e872" url=""><![CDATA[Establish Your Future in Music Materialize by way of The Rec<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9zY2hvb2wtbG9jYXRpb25z" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsummerization.files.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F09%2Fwater-music.jpg%26quot%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://summerization.files.wordpress.com/2011/09/water-music.jpg&quot;</a>; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;260&quot; height=&quot;190]</a>Whether you dream to come to be a recording audio engineer, a music producer or a sound professional in a studio, Recording Connection can definitely assist you in making that dream come to reality with their extensive mentorship programs which run for six months. With additional programs you hear instructors lecture concerning the engineering and recording process to a roomful of pupils. Together with Recording Connection, you can easily experience the ins and outs due to the fact that of the one-on-one learning you get from a specialist who is greatly familiar with the chosen industry. Right from the beginning, you're in the mix, finding out the genuine ways of the business at a genuine, bona fide recording studio. No additional registered, certified program on the world delivers the exact same level of direction, real world knowhow and extensive program of studies as The Recording Connection (<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9zY2hvb2wtbG9jYXRpb25z" target="_blank">recordingconnection.com</a>).<br /><br />Simply think about it. What do you think is more successful? Being inside a classroom with all other pupils, finding out from the same teacher or working side by side a real expert, discovering everything the most practical means?<br /><br />For this very reason, The Recording Connection is advise by the extremely same pros who make records for the following musicians: Usher, Jack Johnson, Alicia Keys, The White Stripes, Prince, Paul McCartney, Pearl Jam, Lenny Kravitz, Alice in Chains, 50 Cent, Madonna, Outcast, Willie Nelson, and Bob Dylan to name merely a couple of. Getting strong chops requires being educated by somebody who actually understands their stuff. This is the only accredited, accredited program in the world that gets you in on the action finding out from a couple of the very best pros in the business.<br /><br />By all means, shop around and do your analysis. See simply what the others are actually offering you. Then, as soon as you're major about really going full throttle and getting on with your profession, get to their website. You can fill in their web form or call them straight. They'll set up a meeting between you and your potential mentor free of charge. Bear in mind, these people (and gals) are pros and they don't take simply anyone on. They need to think you're worth their time and effort prior to they choose to mentor you.<br /><br />Additional schools and programs will charge an impressive $ 25,000 to $ 50,000 for a talk-down, paper-writing education and learning with nominal studio-time that still leaves its graduates with absolutely no connections and zero expertise about the real world business of making music. The Recording Connection costs a simple portion at $ 8,400 (materials consisted of) for six months of quality, intense training backed by a strong curriculum, geared at getting you the abilities you really need to be competitive in the market.<br /><br />With even more than 100 areas all throughout the United States, possibilities are there's a facility and coach within an hour of where you live. That implies you can easily start on your future right now. No need to stop your day job, no need to let yet another thing stop you. Get going and get to their website to discover even more about their programs <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXBlZXEuY29tL2hvbWUvYXJ0aWNsZS8zNDY4Ni9NYWtlLVlvdXItRnV0dXJlLWluLU11c2ljLU1hdGVyaWFsaXplLXdpdGgtVGhlLVJlY29yZGluZy1Db25uZWN0aW9uJTIx" target="_blank">recordingconnection.com</a>. And bear in mind, when it comes to a future you want, just YOU can easily make it occur!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ad668a75322f289fda09dd9757df3978" url=""><![CDATA[The Music Production and Audio Engineering Program that Defe<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmusic-production-recording-studios.com%2Fimages%2Frecording_studio.jpg%26quot%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://music-production-recording-studios.com/images/recording_studio.jpg&quot;</a>; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;260&quot; height=&quot;190]</a>Do you feel that you can be a wonderful audio engineer or music producer? Want to start working on that future now or would certainly you rather spend a few years in school first? Well if you're exactly about fast-tracking it into the dream job of a life-time, check out The Recording Connection. Their totally approved, accredited school is recommended by the extremely exact same producers and engineers who make records for Eminem, Madonna, Black Eyed Peas, M.I. A, Mos Def, 50 Cent, Usher, The White Stripes, Alice in Chains, Pearl Jam, Outkast, Beyonce, U2, Michael Jackson, Alicia Keys, Paul McCartney, Bob Dylan, and Willie Nelson, to name merely several. In the course of just 6 months, you will certainly have the capability to land a job in a genuine studio and even get projects of your very own, working side by side different musicians of your own choosing.<br /><br />The pros understand when you truly desire to create solid recording and producing chops, the only method to do it is to find out directly from a pro. The Recording Connection is the only program on the world that does simply that, putting you inside a professional recording studio with a high-caliber audio engineer or producer on day one.<br /><br />Since their launch in 1983, The Recording Connection <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.recordingconnection.com</a></a> has actually assisted even more than 10,000 apprentices get their beginning by placing them in studios all around the globe. Their demanding mentor-apprenticeship program is supported by a strong curriculum composed of specialists who work in the real atmosphere and can help you prosper in the real world. The explanation they're much faster and more effective than the others, is due to the fact that their methods are hands-on and holistic. You have to discover about the concepts of sound waves during one semester then discover ways to apply them in a real set up the next semester. Rather, what you read about as part of your research is the really exact same stuff you get to talk to your mentor about and place into action in the studio at the next session. If you bear in mind on the stuff you have questions about, you can review it with your coach and you'll get an extensive explanation that makes sense. Just think about what it takes to get a real, comprehensive explanation in terminology you can recognize when you're in a customary school-setting and only a simple face in the crowd.<br /><br />When you take audio engineering and production out of the studio environment you lose the context and platform you need to make it significant and pertinent to the pupil. Hearing someone lecture from the podium on the more rarefied parts of sound production is basically a full waste of time. There are numerous, several aspects to music and sound production and being led by a pro in a hands-on way in an alternative means is the only means to get useful, incorporated, real-world abilities.<br /><br />In addition, while additional programs will have you up to your eyeballs in scantron tests and composing papers, The Recording Connection will certainly have you rubbing elbows with other market pros and making contacts that can easily promote your profession. A great deal of their mentored pupils ultimately get a job at the exact same studio where they had their apprenticeship. Explanation being, the pros have actually currently become accustomed to having them in on the procedure and they know their skillsets are solid. They hire them as an alternative of deciding on somebody they barely understand. Begin inside the studio, and you're most likely to stay on the inside.<br />Some other programs will cost about 25,000 to 50,000 USD and take as long as 2 to 5 years to finish. Or opt for The Recording Connection and in six months you can graduate from their fully recognized, licensed program and get on to making it in the entertaining world of audio engineering. Thanks to their on-site approach, their rate is low. For $ 8,400 you will certainly get all the reading products, software program, and also ProTools, and the expense of tuition. Now matter where you stay in the US, could it be Houston, Seattle, Miami or Honolulu, you can undoubtedly locate a coach working in a recording studio within your area. Have a look at their website for more information at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.recordingconnection.com</a> and bear in mind, fill out their web-form due to the fact that brand-new locations are popping up all the time. If you can easily not discover your location in the listing, there is still an opportunity that you can get a coach around your location. When it pertains to getting the training you need to get the career of your dreams, no one defeats The Recording Connection (<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXBlZXEuY29tL2hvbWUvYXJ0aWNsZS8zNTM3My9UaGUtTXVzaWMtUHJvZHVjdGlvbi1hbmQtQXVkaW8tRW5naW5lZXJpbmctUHJvZ3JhbS10aGF0LVRvcHMtdGhlLVBhbnRzLW9mZi1BbGwtdGhlLU90aGVycyUzQ2JyLSUyNS0lM0U_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.recordingconnection.com</a></a>).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2b13c5856afe623e08d880e89fee2d7f" url=""><![CDATA[Hands-On Training with the Recording Connection Music School<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9yZWNvcmRpbmctY2FyZWVycy9tdXNpYw__" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fphilly360.visitphilly.com%2Fuploads%2Fmedia_items%2Fphiladelphia-international-records-famous-recording-studio-1.562.325.c.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://philly360.visitphilly.com/uploads/media_items/philadelphia-international-records-famous-recording-studio-1.562.325.c.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;The Recording Connection music school&quot;; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;150]</a>Working in the music sector does not just mean that you need to discover music alone; rather it needs thorough expertise which is the explanation why <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU2OTYyNQ__" target="_blank">the Recording Connection music school</a> applies an alternative teaching method called hands-on training.<br /><br />There are many music schools nowadays that include audio production within their curriculum, and these schools typically pledge to prepare you for a music market profession. Nevertheless, getting equipped for such a profession is usually not enough. The music market is really relationship-driven, and just about no one gets employed without having prior associations, no matter where he/she went to school. If you think earning a college qualification will certainly improve your possibilities, you are sadly mistaken; the music market simply does not care whether you have a degree. In fact, not just are there many successful industry professionals who were never officially trained, but these industry professionals will almost always get chosen over a fresh college graduate!<br /><br />Why is this? Just put-the business values proven work experience and prior connections over any quantity of official training. The even more experience and contacts you have, the more most likely you are to get employed. Sadly, the majority of music schools (also the ones with a music sector emphasis) do not offer a means for children to get either associations or experience-and as an outcome, numerous of these pupils graduate with no task prospects.<br /><br />The Recording Connection music school delivers an easy solution to this complication: rather than training children in isolated classrooms, why not train them where the action is-in real recording studios? In fact, this is exactly what the Recording Connection does. Every pupil of the program, without exception, is put from day one as a working apprentice in a real recording studio, to be trained one-on-one by a seasoned audio professional. The student finds out all aspects of the recording industry by actually participating in the recording procedure, following an ordered program of studies to guarantee all the bases are covered. This hands-on strategy enables students to gain actual work experience and to form useful market connections-both of which will substantially raise their chances of locating gainful employment after graduation. In fact, with this strategy, it is not unheard of for recording apprentices to be employed by the very same studios where they were trained, simply because of the relationships that form throughout the process.<br /><br />Immersing in the genuine bargain immediately is the best means to find out the ropes of the music sector and be guided by industry professionals that can be useful to you as soon as you graduate. This is why <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9yZWNvcmRpbmctY2FyZWVycy9tdXNpYw__" target="_blank">the Recording Connection music school</a> places its students in the heart of the action.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1c217329defb91d1f3b539573b75a0cd" url=""><![CDATA[Just how Recording Connection Trains Students for Audio Care<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmedia.sae.edu%2Fmedia_thumbs%2FSydney%2FGallery%2F1027_Our_traditional_Sony_console_with_24-track_analog_recording_studio.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://media.sae.edu/media_thumbs/Sydney/Gallery/1027_Our_traditional_Sony_console_with_24-track_analog_recording_studio.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;Recording Connection&quot;; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;150]</a>For students wanting a profession in audio, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU2OTg1Nw__" target="_blank">Recording Connection</a> offers an unique training answer compared with other schools. As an alternative of putting students in classes of 10 or more and training them in on-campus studios and labs, this school utilizes the mentor-apprentice strategy to position students for one-on-one training as apprentices in real recording studios.<br /><br />What makes this technique more efficient in training up brand-new talent in the field of professional audio? Let's look at 3 key factors to a successful job: experience, connections and expense.<br /><br />THE EXPERIENCE ASPECT<br /><br />The reality of the music business is that no one really cares about that university qualification you worked so difficult to make. The main thing that studios and clients are searching for from audio engineers is shown work experience-and that can just be obtained in the studio, not in a classroom. Students just can't get the training that they receive from music studios from classroom lectures. By training students in genuine recording studios, the Recording Connection offers them the possibility to log real experience in the studio, offering them more credibility in the job market.<br /><br />THE CONNECTION ELEMENT<br /><br />&quot;It's not what you understand, but who you know.&quot; No place is this saying more real than in the music industry. No matter how substantial your education and learning, you won't land a career in the music sector without having inside networks and working relationships. You can only form those connections inside a recording studio. This is why Recording Connection positions students individually into recording studios as apprentices-learning the ropes in a genuine recording studio offers the student the opportunity to make networks in ways additional schools cannot match.<br /><br />THE COST FACTOR<br /><br />A great deal of students are restrained to their student loans by the time they graduate since of the high expense for education and learning. This can easily be devastating to brand-new audio engineers, for whom the job market is less predictable than it is with additional occupations. In numerous situations, the debt itself can require brand-new audio professionals to desert their dreams and take dead-end tasks. With Recording Connection's mentor-apprentice approach, overall education prices are a fraction of what they are with additional schools (since there is no independent campus or studio to develop, keep or pay for). Hence, their students pay far less for their education and learning, shouldering little or no student debt.<br /><br />The bottom line is that there is no substitute for real-world experience and business connections when it comes to launching an audio career-and starting that career without a hefty financial concern is also a must. For this reason, the most effective way to build a profession in music is with getting into the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Recording Connection</a>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6f02bc0244e9e36b99b8aa01163ea4eb" url=""><![CDATA[Exactly how Students Can easily Build Music Market Connectio<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9hdWRpby1wcm9ncmFt" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fs2.hubimg.com%2Fu%2F3932365_f260.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://s2.hubimg.com/u/3932365_f260.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;Recording Connection Audio School&quot;; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;150]</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU3MDE5NA__" target="_blank">Recording Connection Audio School</a> spots their students in actual recording studios so they can easily find out the ropes of music producing.<br /><br />THE RECORDING SCHOOL DILEMMA<br />When colleges and trade schools first started instructing audio engineering, it appeared like a great concept at the time. It has actually been typical belief that you require a degree to have a career in a specific industry. If it worked for other professions, it ought to work with audio engineering too.<br /><br />However, it has actually been observed that in audio, formal training has its pitfalls. While scholastic establishments (and also trade schools) focus on teaching the theoretical and technical skills, the music industry itself continues to value real-world experience over scholastic education and learning. In the music business, connections are important and you can not establish your own if you are constrained in a classroom. As a result, many students graduate from these well-intending recording schools with no work experience, and no market networks, making them virtually not able to land a job.<br /><br />THE OPTION<br />Many music market experts today still believe that the very best way to discover audio engineering and music production is by training in the recording studio-the same means everyone learned before it was taught in schools. In-studio training offers students both the work experience and the job connections they need in order to launch a profession.<br /><br />The Recording Connection audio school has taken this concept to heart, and has actually created its entire structure around in-studio apprenticeships. This innovative approach requires no separate classroom and no simulated studios; instead, every student of the Recording Connection is independently placed as an apprentice in a real film production business, where an experienced, successful audio engineer or music producer trains the student one-on-one. This idea assists students work on actual recording projects and create an expert network. Even better-because this strategy calls for no campus or independent studio, the general price is a fraction of what the majority of colleges and trade schools should charge.<br /><br />Even if you have the knowledge you still need networks in the music business. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9hdWRpby1wcm9ncmFt" target="_blank">Recording Connection audio school</a> makes this feasible where other schools can not.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e32c5b60a71a83729ca87e61923e96e" url=""><![CDATA[A Music Producing School That Trains You the Right Means<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9yZWNvcmRpbmctY2FyZWVycy9tdXNpYy1wcm9kdWNpbmc_" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.soundpunk.com%2Fuploads%2F167f99e5c7c7d9579f651ac599a5c567.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.soundpunk.com/uploads/167f99e5c7c7d9579f651ac599a5c567.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;A music producing school that trains you&quot;; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;160]</a>Numerous schools now offer audio engineering and music production courses, but you need <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU3MDE5NA__" target="_blank">a music producing school that trains you</a> the right method. Being a music producer requires more than just the skills of audio production; it needs a strong blend of work experience, connections, and a capability to bring things together. You're going to be at the losing end if all you do is to learn audio engineering. This is why you need a school that will train you the right method.<br /><br />What is the &quot;right means?&quot; you may ask. If you were to ask many music business experts, they would certainly inform you that the right method to learn music production is to get into a real recording studio and learn on-the-job from an experienced professional-NOT in a college class or simulated on-campus recording studio. Simply put, you should be in a music production school that permits you to learn on-site.<br /><br />Why is this so important? Like we stated before, you need more than just an education in the technical skills of audio if you intend to become a music producer. The majority of audio production programs can teach you the rudiments of recording and blending with their on-campus facilities, however these schools can't help you get the real-world experience and business connections you will additionally require. A great number of striving music producers have finished from those schools however end up taking non-industry jobs since they typically have no job leads and a stack of financial obligation.<br /><br />The right method to learn music production is to get into a real recording studio and learn the ropes straight from somebody who does it for a living-in other words, apprenticeship. This is how everyone learned music production before there was such a thing as a music producing school or an audio engineering school, and to this day, in-studio apprenticeship continues to be the very best way to learn.<br /><br />So how do you get into apprenticeship? In case you do not have connections to put you through an apprenticeship, enlist in a school that utilizes the mentor-apprentice approach like Recording Connection. This is a music production program that will make the plans for you, placing you in a neighborhood recording studio as an apprentice, appointing you a skilled coach, and providing a structured curriculum to manage the process. This method places you in a much better position to learn the technical skills, plus acquire the work experience and the connections you'll require for your future job as a producer.<br /><br />If you're major about being a music producer, do not lose time and money on an education that only takes you part of the method. Discover <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9yZWNvcmRpbmctY2FyZWVycy9tdXNpYy1wcm9kdWNpbmc_" target="_blank">a music producing school that trains you</a> the right means.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d492cf455719644bb857da721c440cee" url=""><![CDATA[Complete Audio Engineering School in Just Six Months and for<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9yZWNvcmRpbmctY2FyZWVycy9hdWRpby1lbmdpbmVlcmluZw__" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2F1.bp.blogspot.com%2F_yPTrCvI8wPQ%2FTDjxiF_a5tI%2FAAAAAAAAABQ%2F1Wtkac6-FSM%2Fwww.00%2Fmixingdesk__540x304.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://1.bp.blogspot.com/_yPTrCvI8wPQ/TDjxiF_a5tI/AAAAAAAAABQ/1Wtkac6-FSM/www.00/mixingdesk__540x304.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;audio engineering school&quot;; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;160]</a>Are you serious about becoming an audio engineer the most functional means without any debts and in a great <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU3MDE5NA__" target="_blank">audio engineering school</a>? Well if that sounds like you, Recording Connection has a program you ought to absolutely explore. In roughly 6 months and for less than $ 9,000 you can have the abilities and intelligent it takes to work in an expert recording environment, meaning you'll be well onto structure that profession when students in other programs are just making it through their very first semester!<br /><br />The reason Recording Connection can get you quality recording education in record time comes right down to its one of a kind technique. <br /><br />Standard schools are more concentrated with being &quot;schools&quot; than teaching you in a more practical way. Their strategy is fragmented, abstract, and just plain inefficient when it pertains to constructing the abilities are real-world knowhow it takes to be an asset to the field. Recording Connection aspires to turning novices into audio engineers using real-world experience as well as experience. Ask around and they'll tell you that you need to be instructed, hands-on by a skilled audio engineer in a genuine studio to learn audio engineering. Recording Connection is the only qualified, certified audio engineering school on the world that's made to do just that!<br /><br />The coaches with Recording Connection are far more than just individuals who know the best ways to function the console or know a thing of 2 about Pro Tools. These guys (and gals) are authentic specialists, many of whom have tackled the identical tracks you know and love and with the artists you hear. In fact, Recording Connection is recommended by the very same pros who make records for Eminem, Madonna, Black Eyed Peas, M.I. A, Mos Def, 50 Cent, Usher, The White Stripes, Alice in Chains, Pearl Jam, Outkast, Beyonc?, U2, Michael Jackson, Alicia Keys, Paul McCartney, Bob Dylan, and Willie Nelson, to name just a couple of. They know the only means to actually learn what it takes to be an audio engineer with some solid chops is by learning from a pro and THIS is the school they choose.<br /><br />Since it began in 1983, Recording Connection has actually put hundreds of individuals in expert recording studios all over the world. The school now boasts places all over the United States, Canada, and the Uk and has actually become the go-to solution for thousands, including many working adults who have located it feasible to keep their tasks while they study.<br /><br />And when it comes to building the connections that lead to work, no other program can hold a candle to Recording Connection. Just consider it, they get you in a real recording atmosphere, learning from a pro right on the first day! That indicates you'll have the possibility to connect not just with your coach but with everybody who deals with him as well. Show them just how devoted you are to the job and they will take you as far as you can possibly picture.<br /><br />Traditional schools can cost from $ 25,000 to as much as $ 70,000 and take two to six years to complete! Go with a program that makes sense and for a cost you can afford with Recording Connection, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9yZWNvcmRpbmctY2FyZWVycy9hdWRpby1lbmdpbmVlcmluZw__" target="_blank">audio engineering school</a> especially designed to obtain you the abilities it takes to make it!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ebd5a4cc83d54929e44c7428b0772db7" url=""><![CDATA[Be a Music Producer in Just Six Months with Recording Connec<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9pbmZvcm1hdGlvbi93aHktdHJhZGl0aW9uYWwtc2Nob29scy1kb250LXdvcms_" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.loudcloudsounds.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2011%2F09%2Fproducer_man.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.loudcloudsounds.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/producer_man.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;become a music producer&quot;; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;140]</a>Did you know you can <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU3MDE5NA__" target="_blank">become a music producer</a> in six months with Recording Connection's extensive, mentor-guided program? If you're aching to obtain choosing your future and do not want to squander your time (and money) with years of inefficient education, you most likely want to have a look at Recording Connection as the program that can assist you launch your future.<br /><br />The licensed, approved school is the innovator of the mentor-guided strategy in audio engineering and music production. Apprenticeship allows you to gain real-world understanding of the practices in the production environment from a knowledgeable music producer. Mind you, this is NOT an internship however a structured, educational program, backed by the exclusive, one-of-a-kind Recording Connection educational program that's made by the pros.<br /><br />Thanks to Recording Connection's special on-site method in which apprentices research in real recording studios, instead of the dumbed-down variations found at standard universities and trade schools, the institute's programs are shockingly cost-effective and budget friendly. In twenty lessons that are comprised of preparatory reading (by the apprentice by themselves time) and one-on-one meetings with the mentor, individuals will study: sound idea, acoustics, waveforms, digital and audio basics featuring sampling and quantizing sound and Nyquist Theorem, quantization principles, Pro Tools, the mixing board (or system), mic positioning and operation, audio processing, signal circulation and patch bays, USB, MIDI, Electronic Music, sync and automation, drum and guitar microphone techniques, signal processing, EQ processing, surround-sound mixing, the last mix-down, and much, much more!<br /><br />And because apprentices are training in a genuine recording atmosphere starting on the first day, they have the included perk of meeting other pros working in the business, musicians and recording experts alike, and they can actually develop those important connections while they learn. The opportunity of constructing real market contacts while you learn is definitely rare in other schools. Go with them and you're out in the cold come graduation day with usually absolutely no real-recording studio experience and absolutely no connections. You can choose Recording Connection and become a music producer in just 6 months. Others can flounder for months, even years just trying to get their &quot;in&quot; which is right where Recording Connection places you on day one.<br /><br />Traditional programs usually cost between $ 25,000 to $ 50,000 and take years to complete. For a portion the price, Recording Connection's quality mentor-guided program gets you learning one-on-one with a professional. The bachelor's program is just $ 8,400 (at the time this article was written) and yes, materials and software (ProTools) are featured. With areas all over the United States, Canada and the UK, opportunities are there's a studio and a mentor near you, so what are you awaiting? Go on and get the skills for you to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9pbmZvcm1hdGlvbi93aHktdHJhZGl0aW9uYWwtc2Nob29scy1kb250LXdvcms_" target="_blank">become a music producer</a> with Recording Connection or at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnection.com</a>, the school selected by expert.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6e615828d72257d72001da7341f6de45" url=""><![CDATA[Become an Audio Apprentice on Day One with Recording Connect<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9jb21wYXJlLXVzL2hvdy13ZS1kby1pdA__" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fimg.ehowcdn.com%2Farticle-new%2Fehow%2Fimages%2Fa05%2F03%2Fhp%2Fmusic-producer-description-800x800.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://img.ehowcdn.com/article-new/ehow/images/a05/03/hp/music-producer-description-800x800.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;become an audio apprentice&quot;; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;140]</a>Are you dead serious about to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU3MDE5NA__" target="_blank">become an audio apprentice</a>? Ask yourself this question because Recording Connection is not for every person. You need to be a self-starter to make the program work for you. If you think you are, their six month audio apprenticeship program might be the right method to fast jump start your job and jumping into the amazing world of audio engineering.<br /><br />Thanks to their innovative mentor-apprentice approach, Recording Connection's qualified, approved program can get you the strong abilities and knowhow you should be an audio engineer in just 6 months.<br /><br />Other programs are costly and impractical. This program blows the others away. Rather than send you to some school where you'll be lectured to and anticipated to write papers, they match you up with a skilled, credible expert audio engineer as your coach. Under the direct support of your coach, you work with the standard, thorough Recording Connection program of studies and become an audio apprentice starting on day one. Please not that this is not an internship, it is a strenuous life-changing program in an expert studio while creating your network of connections that is very important and is frequently overlooked.<br /><br />Standard university and trade school programs, aren't just costly, they're notoriously unsuccessful when it concerns actually enabling you to accomplish the strong, hands-on, practicable understanding you need to be competitive. Simply put, an audio engineering degree from such programs actually means very little to the pros in the field that search for hands-on technical capability, simplicity in the studio environment, and a strong foundational understanding of the underlying theories and concepts behind all of it; things like the distinction between analog and digital and Nyquist theorem, acoustic waves, etcetera. Colleges as well as universities customarily spend a considerable amount of time on learning the theory with extremely little practice, producing graduates that are not excellent on the application side of learning. Trade schools aspire at providing hands-on experience but instruct in dumbed-down versions of recording studios which aren't the exact same and they still do not provide the one-on-one instruction you manage apprenticing with a Recording Connection coach. In addition, trade schools fall sadly short when it concerns getting their students are strong foundation in the concepts behind audio engineering which is crucial if you intend on being an engineer who understands and comprehends the real particulars of the craft. Manipulating a computer system program can be learned and the format of a console can be memorized. Just a specialist can hear the finest details and they know exactly what to do to get things right instantly.<br /><br />You can invest up to 6 years and someplace between $ 25,000 and $ 50,000 and not learn as much as you can with Recording Connection. Graduate from one of these schools and you can bank on having no market experience, absolutely no connections, and little hands-on know exactly how and LOTS of student financial obligation. This suggests spending your time, effort and money for nothing. Or, you can take a more logical technique and learn in a holistic, hands-on way right from the start for, believe it or not, less than $ 9,000 featuring materials and Pro Tools. Review <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnectionl.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnectionl.com</a> to find out what professionals have to say about Recording Connection's ingenious programs. With locations all over the United States, UK and Canada, there's a huge possibility that there's a studio near you. Save the cash, your time and distress, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9jb21wYXJlLXVzL2hvdy13ZS1kby1pdA__" target="_blank">become an audio apprentice</a> with Recording Connection and be on your means to making your dreams a reality.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5942e399f07791343ff18752fc4c1904" url=""><![CDATA[Recording Connection: You're "In" on The first<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fimg.ehowcdn.com%2Farticle-new%2Fehow%2Fimages%2Fa08%2F3r%2Fmd%2Fadvantages-disadvantages-being-music-producer-800x800.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://img.ehowcdn.com/article-new/ehow/images/a08/3r/md/advantages-disadvantages-being-music-producer-800x800.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com%26quot%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnection.com&quot;</a>; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;140]</a>Ever dreamed of working in music as an audio engineer, sound tech, live sound engineer or music producer? If so, Recording Connection <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU3MDE5NA__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnection.com</a></a> could assist you to get the skills you have to organize your future and your life in just 6 months!<br /><br />Since the school was founded in Hollywood, California in 1983, numerous people have been placed in recording studios throughout the United States, Canada and the UK for quality hands-on instruction in the recording arts with a pro. Instead of sending its students to a campus, absolutely isolated from the action, this school puts its students inside bona fide recording studios on the first day. If you truly wish to get some solid studio abilities, this is the finest means to do it. Just think about it. We can't deny the fact that learning by experience is a great deal more reliable than any other approach. Hearing somebody lecture about it, being one of eight to ten or also twenty students watching an instructor show, or sitting at the mixing system right next to a pro, learning exactly how it's all done hands-on?<br /><br />Even if you ask every pro in the market, they will all tell you that hands on training in a genuine studio setting is still the best foundation. That's why Recording Connection is backed by the very same recording and production experts who make records for 50 Cent, Madonna, The White Stripes, Pearl Jam, Eminem, Madonna, Alicia Keys, Bob Dylan, Willie Nelson, Outcast, M.I. A, The Black Eyed Peas, Led Zeppelin, The Black Crowes, U2, Price, Jack Johnson, Mary J. Blige and even more!<br /><br />Go the conventional path and it'll take years and cost you a massive $ 25,000 - $ 50,000 annually! Or get in on the first day with Recording Connection and learn through their unique mentor-guided technique that's backed by their industry oriented program of studies and in 6 months you could release your job. While students in other will certainly still be slogging through papers and sitting in lecture halls, you'll be meeting experts and making connections with the very same people who can easily get you work.<br /><br />If you're determined about working in the music business and you're motivated and ready to strive finding out all the ns-and-outs of the business, this is a great means to get your start. Know what the students of the Recording Connection have to say about their coaches and the experience they had along with how the institution helped them to bw effective at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.recordingconnection.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.recordingconnection.com</a></a>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d89cced91587f03dfc482129321e1e3" url=""><![CDATA[Train in the Studio and Be an Audio Engineer<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9jb3Vyc2VzL2F1ZGlvLWVuZ2luZWVyaW5n" target="_blank">&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdreamrow.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2012%2F07%2FIVM-studio1_500x325.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dreamrow.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/IVM-studio1_500x325.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;become an audio engineer&quot;; style=&quot;margin: 0px 4px 4px 0px; float: left;&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;140]</a>Did you know you could <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hdGhpYXNmYWxrMTIzMC5kbXVzaWMubmV0L2pvdXJuYWwvMTU3MDE5NA__" target="_blank">become an audio engineer</a> by exercise straight in the recording studio, as opposed to going to a pricey college or trade school? Not only is in-studio training feasible, but it is actually how most music sector experts recommend that you learn these skills. There are an excellent lots of successful audio engineers and music producers who have never ever had formal class direction; in fact, in the very early days of the sector (when no schools existed to instruct audio engineering), in-studio training was the only means to learn it!<br /><br />WHY CLASS LEARNING IS INEFFECTIVE FOR AUDIO ENGINEERS<br /><br />The concept about producing trade schools along with university courses to formalize training for audio production appeared efficient very first. Besides, formal education works for professions like medicine and law. This could additionally add prestige and credibility to a student.<br /><br />For a number of vital explanations however, it has actually become visible that classroom learning is basically ineffective for audio engineers<br /><br />1. Classroom direction and studio simulations are controlled atmospheres that can not duplicate the dynamics of a real studio.<br />2. Isolated learning environments prevent students from making sector connections, placing them at a fantastic negative aspect at the job market.<br />3. It is really expensive to train audio engineers for simulated environments, making the price of education and learning surpass its benefits.<br /><br />In reality, a college degree doesn't truly matter in the music sector; they simply want to know you have the proven experience to do the job well. You  would certainly be more competitive if you become an audio engineer by training in the studio over someone who learned in the classroom. For what explanation? Because learning in the studio gives you the work experience plus the opportunity to construct the connections you have to be taken seriously.<br /><br />TRAINING IN THE STUDIO<br /><br />One straightforward means is to find an engineer or producer and get him or her to train you. This could help you however not everybody has that kind of connection. Besides you  would certainly like to be certain that your mentor is in fact efficient his or her craft. So an excellent alternative path is to register in a school that utilizes the mentor-apprentice technique, like the Recording Connection. Recording Connection has the connections to be able to put you in a high-quality studio where an expert can be your mentor or instructor at up to 75 % less than typical schools.<br /><br />Why invest 10s of hundreds of bucks on a qualification or diploma that many sector professionals regard as meaningless? <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWNvcmRpbmdjb25uZWN0aW9uLmNvbS9jb3Vyc2VzL2F1ZGlvLWVuZ2luZWVyaW5n" target="_blank">Become an audio engineer</a> by training in the studio, and you can be on your method to a gratifying career.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>