<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="23">
		<document id="2cc18428465629879fa772c256304a35" url=""><![CDATA[flyin solo<br/><br/>well im finally singel Travis is history i coundent take it anymore! so im foot lose and fancy free! always on the lok out fr a sweetheart tho! o if u noe any..jks
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="622823c6f0f017b33f7a6fa31ad92f08" url=""><![CDATA[Movin on<br/><br/>Well, its been a day it was starting to loko like everyother day but i turned out good! i strated talking to some reall cool guys PURPOSE and SITH_CRACKERS and they either made me laugh or just helped witht eh pain so thanks guys i really nedded it!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angel.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />Robyn
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f827c45291c84a4b562df341215af640" url=""><![CDATA[Unpredicatlbe<br/><br/>Omg! seriously best day ever! today Tom,Conner and Jon all went to see Employee of the month and i noe it is proably to early for me to like someone eles! since be and travis just ended things but i do kinda like him he so nice! jon i mean hes just so nice and so good lokking not pretty lol jon very hansom! he so much taller then me anyways! my friend connor dosent like him its stupid! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" />  it was really anoying! well anyways g2g <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a19b154c9cc07ba19bf8dcff71e5dc1e" url=""><![CDATA[untiteled<br/><br/>hey all:
<br />i met this great guy named Jon remeber him? well we went to the movies Sunday night life was good! but now i seem to wonder if he'll contuie to talk to me and want to speend more time together ! i shouldent deubt it is what i keep hearing because of the way we act together, i hope my friends are right... i dunno im starting to fall for hime i think my Counciller Emily says im smittin what ever that means but that i really like him! i dunno about that we just met but i do noe that i do have feelings for him! but like i said i dunno how he feels about me maybe i should talk to him about this before i start to panic! it would make sense right?? but what would i say?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="78a1501447aaee99d44900d9d05a805f" url=""><![CDATA[Stuipity<br/><br/>Arg this isent kool i got a call home cause apperently i skipped but the teacher marked me avbsent cause i was late! stupid teacher!
<br />why would i skip a class i would have the same teacher with right after lunch!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f8386274671f706b457450cb7b6592d1" url=""><![CDATA[Almost Amzing<br/><br/>omg today being hallowen so much fun me and my friend conner went trick or treatin and he walked into a grage door that was part was open for the haunted house, it was so comical! and i talked to travis he is bitchen bout gettin me back! not happeneing but anyways! and thanks purpose for making me feel better latly! love talking to you!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="156c9c68fcb203bf87dd4c2764f5977a" url=""><![CDATA[Fucked up<br/><br/>This will be one of 2 blogs one is happy then there is this one!, a girl at y school Elisha over dosed on drugs today she was doing crack/cocaine weed herion and E.... she was carried away on a strecher during forth period! shes a really goodf riend of mine and im so worrie i mean not that good of a friend but still! pretty good! she was high everyday! her parents didnt know yet... they do now! they found a needle in the girls upper washrrom second floor of my highschool! police and ambulance came! it was a horrible sight this girl was a year and half younger than me! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1b67f0d0531354de0ec8c93e8fe837c" url=""><![CDATA[Thomas Mckenzie<br/><br/>well this is named Thomas after my boyfried, hes been my friend since last year and i love him! he goes to SJAM (sir john A macdonald!) hes a really sweet guy... and has liked me for the longest time so i thought hell why not id give him a chance!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6f4387ef7508490c6322847b5cda6cd0" url=""><![CDATA[Improable or impossible...<br/><br/>Rememeber that great guy i was talking about...Thmoas, well turns out not so wonderful he got high and drunk got another chick pregent then he got kicked outta school and both his parents homes, grrr this is so AHH! i dont even know!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a93c5d852e355185a1f7825e92a6145e" url=""><![CDATA[Travling Soldier (written by the dixie chicks)<br/><br/>&quot;Travelin' Soldier&quot;
<br /><br />Two days past eighteen
<br />He was waiting for the bus in his army green
<br />Sat down in a booth in a cafe there
<br />Gave his order to a girl with a bow in her hair
<br />He's a little shy so she gives him a smile
<br />And he said would you mind sittin' down for a while
<br />And talking to me,
<br />I'm feeling a little low
<br />She said I'm off in an hour and I know where we can go
<br /><br />So they went down and they sat on the pier
<br />He said I bet you got a boyfriend but I don't care
<br />I got no one to send a letter to
<br />Would you mind if I sent one back here to you
<br /><br />Chorus: I cried
<br />Never gonna hold the hand of another guy
<br />Too young for him they told her
<br />Waitin' for the love of a travelin' soldier
<br />Our love will never end
<br />Waitin' for the soldier to come back again
<br />Never more to be alone when the letter said
<br />A soldier's coming home
<br /><br />So the letters came from an army camp
<br />In California then Vietnam
<br />And he told her of his heart
<br />It might be love and all of the things he was so scared of
<br />He said when it's getting kinda rough over here
<br />I think of that day sittin' down at the pier
<br />And I close my eyes and see your pretty smile
<br />Don't worry but I won't be able to write for awhile
<br /><br />[Chorus]
<br /><br />One Friday night at a football game
<br />The Lord's Prayer said and the Anthem sang
<br />A man said folks would you bow your heads
<br />For a list of local Vietnam dead
<br />Crying all alone under the stands
<br />Was a piccolo player in the marching band
<br />And one name read and nobody really cared
<br />But a pretty little girl with a bow in her hair
<br /><br />[Chorus]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a1647e5ace229368cebe2792afe4249" url=""><![CDATA[long time<br/><br/>srry its been so long, i went to my teachers dughter visitantion it was so so sad! anways i have a councelle meeting on tuesday with mf bffl cassi then a conscert (panic at the disoco0 on thurs shall be a good week
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f9f12d50399e33035767188fa63513cc" url=""><![CDATA[Blondie<br/><br/>hey all, srry i havent written in a while... but iu have greatish news im a blnde i went from brunette to blonde i love it so much a pic will be up as soon as i can get it from the camera!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aa6af0ebb5f7573d54e5dee7f6ba930c" url=""><![CDATA[where i last left you<br/><br/>well where i last left you i dyed my hair blonde! in which it is still... my boyfriend dakota broke up with me so again singleness! umm thats all! we went through a hugly mess break up cause he wanted to be back with his ex! who &quot;cheated&quot; on him! agggh i quite!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="838cdc2ad17d77380a25f90952024a08" url=""><![CDATA[My day<br/><br/>Well its Sunday October 1st
<br />i had rep tryouts today! total bust, grr other than that... um i might try out for the under 17 team as a goalie! also i got to spend my night with the most amazing guy ever! his nmaes Tom! as you could proably guess my boyfriend, we watched coach carter! its a good movie basketball related! well anyways thats it! oh yeah by the way!
<br /><br />this guy Josh.T hes my ex is a total loner! im serious he called my boyfriends house twice when he heard i was over he hates me! lol dont care! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d6ae72da3077379e29d65d582b1dea33" url=""><![CDATA[What a day!<br/><br/>Well let's  my old school got put under code red lock down because of inrudders! today there was a huge storm so i didnt end up going to school which is kinda good because yesteday tom and i broke up because im still inlove with my ex Steven! we dated for almost 8 monthes on and off and i havent forgot about it! were thinkin of maybe getting back together which i would love because i miss him alot! but still i could be out of field hockey for the rest of the season! and i have rep soccer tryouts as a goalie! next weekend! under 17 girls i cant wait! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />  there was a half day today at school! i didnt end up going at all! my dads a bit irritated!
<br />anyways gotta go!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fad870a4a2ff66718f4417d2a0fe7c02" url=""><![CDATA[This boy<br/><br/>Omg this so sucks im startin to fall for my friend  hes sooo hot and arh the only problem is that hes a year younger than me! stupid people! grr but my ex Josh keeps tellin me this guy i like is like scared that i like him! hmm josh is a bit of an ass somedays, so idunno what yto belive plus my bestdriend likes me! this is so wierd! anyways thats m,y story!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="da74486d42210046c9e57bf70fbc0436" url=""><![CDATA[trashed<br/><br/>this is somehting i need to vent about... how the stuipd skanky people always get the really nice//hot guys! why all they do is treat them like shit! or even how guys treat girls like there nothing at least in my school! its really bothering me! so the &quot;okay&quot; people all seem to date in the same catogloy why??
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb88416e36264e18279543cc848e62ad" url=""><![CDATA[ouch!<br/><br/>hey all well i figure i can get this done at school and one later! im so sore i had a triple soccer shift yesterday then work i skined my noes! and me an my step mom were fighting today all in all! ouch! g2g bells gunna ring more later
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e8ba0b8e0af7ae68fd4f0cd010631eea" url=""><![CDATA[cherry for a perfect day<br/><br/>Grrr, why is it that everytime somehting good happenes it crushed with 50 million bad things? me and my boyfriend Travis have been together for i dont wanna say how long but still and this chick his ex from the summer say she three monthes pregnet and it might be his kid! this was alil while ago! than she told me earlier today it wasent no she is positive it is! like im seriouse she has her own man why is she commin after mine? this si annoyin! she does a sever amount of drugs and im so stressed! shes tellin me all these things about Travis that i new were from his past like a year or 2 ago and I dont think its true  she clamis me to be one of her friends but if i was why would she be doing this to me right? im finally happy! and to top it off some stupid bitch from my school is tellin everyone im talking trash about her which im not toehr than shes a bitch but we new that already! she is mad because my bestfriend broke up with her! but fuck her! what should i do i trust my b.f i love him and i noe he loves me but i keep havin his ex tell me hes liein to me and cheatin on me! its gettin to me!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d98976487f5ad82bdc1667061cf2a161" url=""><![CDATA[8 a.m.<br/><br/>Okay so i pretty much live on this blog right? well its 5 am on a Thrsday im waiting for this 8 year od kid to get oto my huseother thna being so tired my mouth really hurts i cut on of my lower gums open! ouch!!grr! i have this english essay do Novemeber 3ed and i dunno what to write about i mena i have to do it on Anne frank its a comperitive essay stupid essay  I think i street sweeper just drove by...hmmmm? its to early for htis (prince mosers sweeping!) well i dunno what im gunna do today other than possably sleep during Msip! its a study period!
<br />the kid is here gotta go. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="27b54f73cbb227db91942ddec9b8e600" url=""><![CDATA[Sweeps<br/><br/>this is interesting its how i got my nick name SWEEPS! it started at the beginning of the eyar second or thirded day i was trying out for my schools field hockey team i really wanted to be a forward i love to score get the gloary you no? but my coach always put me in defence, it wasn't too bad pretty fun so i started playing in the last defence postion
<br />   Called Sweeper, there fore Sweeps it also tise into my other sports nick nmae Spic-n-Span from a couple eyars ago in soccer when i played sweeper and never et the ball my me! or played striker and scored 6 goals either way, as you can tell i love sports! im trying out for the curing and badminton teams for the winter! and either Soccer or Softball in the summer!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f7e31a4fc8182870c743f38de8a822d5" url=""><![CDATA[a good day wasted<br/><br/>well to day was an amazing day i got to see my boyfriend, but when i getin msn and check me emails i find out he could be datin 2 other chicks and i have a thret put  on me great huh! now when i called him his brother or his brothers sluty g.f hung up on me! this is bullshit! im so upset! :'(
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aa1302ac8ca5b18e0fec8a7b38f0172b" url=""><![CDATA[school<br/><br/>To any one who has been reading this, i'm having a bad day once again... traivs is still being questioned bou cheatin i cant get a hold of him now this stupid bitch at my school nmaed Rachel was thinkin of gettin me suspened for &quot;saying&quot; shit about her! like what the hell eh just cause my friend broke up with her! wtf! so other than that! i guess everything is okay im in communication Technology... teacher is behind  me so i gotta go...
<br />Robyn
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>