<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="15">
		<document id="6aa8817447672199aa15a43bdd16f692" url=""><![CDATA[Bangladesh Politics<br/><br/>Dont u think the politicians or politics of Bangladesh are the major issue, what stopped and killed all the positive aspect to development...!!!!  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/dry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a61dad57abe0b25103ed8e775980956" url=""><![CDATA[A-Haa<br/><br/>Would u pls check whats going on here in Bangladesh...
<br /><br />Jalil ,Babor two Top leader are arested !!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6ce3ccc39134edf9fddef516f09cb311" url=""><![CDATA[Outsource Job-Web design<br/><br/>New site - check it out .
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newtop.fi"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.newtop.fi</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.beautyconcept.fi"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.beautyconcept.fi</a>
<br /><br />Just done the Job,as Bangladeshiiiiii
<br /><br />want more nock me iiii
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2ab8190a731f82ed7155eb9a0a5e3b19" url=""><![CDATA[New Era -Unicorn Trade International<br/><br/>Hey check it out - 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Funicorntrade-international.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://unicorntrade-international.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9ecdc95d23241d2f0fdf9c826595340d" url=""><![CDATA[Bored<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/afro.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />Vogus Day ..
<br />No Work at office ..no net ..no books,papers and even i cant go out caz of heavy rainfall here in Dhaka...
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angel.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b6bbbf0d534f4596e4555c7ce69a6be1" url=""><![CDATA[Cool<br/><br/>Find out of my resources---
<br /><br />Click the link -  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ailbd.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.ailbd.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5d4221f5f63a7510881f41d45582ec67" url=""><![CDATA[No one has the right to choose to do what is wrong.<br/><br/>No one has the right to choose to do what is wrong. - Abraham Lincoln 
<br /><br />Bangladesh is fortunate that there are good thinking people like those who can talk well, write admirably and distinguish between right and wrong, but it is the endless greed, reckless use of power and perverted arrogance of politicians brought enormous miseries to millions in this impoverished nation. 
<br /><br />Most unfortunate is that the leaders at the highest level of political parties those who ruled the country for past fifteen years, namely former Prime Ministers Begum Zia of BNP and Sheikh Hasina of Awami League do not even want recognize the fact that they were responsible for the shameless acts of corruptions during their rules as they allowed corruption to thrive. 
<br /><br />From what these two leaders are talking as being reported by the news media, it appears that they do not have any repentance and continue to believe that those who are now running the country are wrong and they should get back the power. Facts are clear that they were not only directly responsible for the corruptions but beneficiaries too. 
<br /><br />And the beneficiaries of corruption are gradually emerging in the various forms of lobbying and protest strategy including Black Badges in the Dhaka University for the arrests of corrupt leaders. 
<br />To make democracy work in Bangladesh all those leaders who are responsible for the current predicament and their beneficiaries without any exception or immunity must be punished.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="65a0d490c565fdbb948ee9465a8fdabc" url=""><![CDATA[Technology<br/><br/>A good binocular can enhance your view. Now you can easily get the Digital Binoculars will do the same for your memories. We've combined the high magnification and powerful performance of a binocular with the advanced technical wizardry of a compact digital camera, giving you the option to capture and save any sight you experience. Compact enough to carry in a pocket, Our Digital Binoculars are ideal for private investigators, sports fans, outdoor enthusiasts, adventure travelers, anyone with a desire to view and record whatever experiences come their way. Why settle for magnifying life when you can preserve it for all time?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6f03cc303670129a911617cb4998686" url=""><![CDATA[" This Policy aims at building an ICT Policy<br/><br/>&quot; This Policy aims at building an ICT-
<br />driven nation comprising of knowledge-based society by the year 
<br />2006. In view of this, a country-wide ICT-infrastructure will be 
<br />developed to ensure access to information by every citizen to 
<br />facilitate empowerment of people and enhance democratic values and 
<br />norms for sustainable economic development by using the 
<br />infrastructure for human resources development, governance, e-
<br />commerce, banking, public utility services and all sorts of on-line 
<br />ICT-enabled services.&quot;
<br /><br />You may get the detail policy from the link below:
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.btrc.gov.bd%2Fict_policy.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.btrc.gov.bd/ict_policy.htm</a>
<br /><br />I would like to start this topic to get some engagement and generate 
<br />response to get a feel for the status of the project. I am doing 
<br />this because I did not found a status report on the success or 
<br />failure over the net. Please let me know if there is any 
<br />comprehensive report or any status update.
<br /><br />Once we know that I will be useful for US (the ICT Enthusiasts) to 
<br />learn what went wrong and do a &quot;post mortem&quot; and learn what went 
<br />wrong, how to make forward progress.
<br /><br />Each of us from our respective field and business area may share the 
<br />bottom up data. This way we may get a feel for the achivemets and 
<br />missed opportunities. You may want to refresh your policy goals 
<br />looking at the policy link above to keep the focus of the discussion.
<br /><br />I appreciate your time and attention in this regards
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f6514597da369b482ca0a7b49a0c15d" url=""><![CDATA[browsing Bangladesh Governments’ web pages<br/><br/>I have been browsing Bangladesh Governments’ web pages. Trying to find information and also trying to understand the dynamics of those web sites. If I had to summarize about these web pages, I would say “pathetic”. Sorry for the word, but could not resist myself. There are some good web pages as well, but most of them need huge upgrade. Whoever designed these web pages haven’t done proper homework before building the content or not knowing the fact about good web design. 
<br /><br />Please review good web pages and there are plenty of examples which can be considered good web design. Please follow those and build a good template and show others that “you can do it”. Without proper web representation, you can not claim that “we are ready” for the prime time. 
<br /><br />Compare:
<br /><br />[Bangladesh] Chief Adviser’s office: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cao.gov.bd%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cao.gov.bd/</a> 
<br /><br />[India] Prime Minister’s Office: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fpmindia.nic.in%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://pmindia.nic.in/</a>
<br /><br />[Vietnam] Government Web Page: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vietnam.gov.vn%2Fportal%2Fpage%3F_pageid%3D33%2C1%26amp%3B_dad%3Dportal%26amp%3B_schema%3DPORTAL"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.vietnam.gov.vn/portal/page?_pageid=33,1&amp;_dad=portal&amp;_schema=PORTAL</a> 
<br /><br />[Bangladesh] Ministry of Science and Information &amp; Communication Technology: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mosict.gov.bd%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mosict.gov.bd/</a>  (????<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />[India] Department of Information Technology: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mit.gov.in%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mit.gov.in/</a>
<br /><br />Why our web pages are so “pitiable”? Are we seeing the “World” from “Bangladesh” through web pages or we are giving others the opportunity to see “Bangladesh” through “Web Pages”. Why the quality of these web pages are so poor by any standard. Why?
<br /><br />PLEASE, whoever is responsible for these pages please update them effectively where you can claim “we all can do it”. Please do these update “Immediately
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3002b9b7544384f61eeb49131fd14cf2" url=""><![CDATA[Think about Bangladesh<br/><br/>To me both mothers son are not suitable for Bangladesh if we do want to have changes in our political environment and do want to have true democracy, we all know how our politicains (might not be all of them) used democracy as for the sake of their own, anyway see what happen but if we do love Bangladesh we should support any step in order to stop those corrupted peoples and their successors, otherwise after 2008 same thing will happen as previous.
<br /><br />Lastly I woundered when see some peoples are actively working and spending a lot of US$ to free our top level corrupt leaders and their sons, pls use those money for the poor peoples in Bangladesh and let's do something good before time goes away and leave the earth.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8438fce5a6895e78ced5795e0229b63a" url=""><![CDATA[CEGIS<br/><br/>I would like to share with you an activity that CEGIS (Center for Environmental and Geographic Information Services) carried out to support  flood disaster management. I have noticed some similar maps being circulated in the ict yahoogroups, and thought you might find this interesting.  
<br /><br />Iffat Huque
<br />CEGIS
<br /><br />Please Visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cegisbd.com%2Fflood2007%2Findex.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cegisbd.com/flood2007/index.htm</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2b0c4c91b3c1fb00dd9592743b418a69" url=""><![CDATA[Check it Out<br/><br/>Friends,
<br /><br />You will be glad to know that, Ankur is going to organize a day-long exciting Hacking Festival / Contest with the support of JUOSN in the dept. of CSE, Jahangirnagar University, on Friday January 18, 2008. It is, in fact, a *Hacker Hunt* for Ankur. 
<br /><br />Ankur HackFest '08 is the first of it's kind in Bangladesh, upon getting optimistic response and the feedback the participants, Ankur will organize more HackFest within this year in other universities as well.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4b349bed7fe53ff5bd3d52c45c7ab721" url=""><![CDATA[becomeexpert.com<br/><br/>&lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbecomeexpert.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://becomeexpert.com</a>'&gt;&lt;img src='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbecomeexpert.com%2Fup_img%2Fthumb_m_120045998512004599858224.jpg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://becomeexpert.com/up_img/thumb_m_120045998512004599858224.jpg</a>' border='0' width='110' height='100' alt='Anupam Infotek Limited'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a0474fb64c8a526a60ddc71298077aa5" url=""><![CDATA[AEx IT Limited<br/><br/>AEx IT Limited established in 2008 is specialized in researching and developing the Applications Platform of Integrated Systems. The integrated system includes a comprehensive range of products - hardware and software modules with unique features, as well as a full range of peripherals like readers, cards, tags, locking devices, barriers, turnstiles, detectors, etc.
<br /><br />AEx IT Limited offers The system fully supports the integration of Access control, Time and Attendance, Hotel, Remote CCTV Surveillance, Complete POS (Point of Sales) Solutions with related Hardware peripherals, EAS(Electronic Anti-Shoplifting) Parking and Intrusion systems and GSM/GPS Car and Motor cycle Alarm for prevent the Anti-Hijack etc creating a Total Security Solutions.
<br /><br />The Purpose of Establishment
<br /><br />* The Integration, Transfer, Localization of Technology and Experiences.
<br />    * Vertical Technology Advise, Consult
<br />    * Large-Scale Project Planning and Management
<br />    * System Planning, Integration, and Management
<br />    * Research, Develop and Customize Advanced Science and Technology
<br /><br />To Know More- <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.aexit-bd.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.aexit-bd.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>