<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="21">
		<document id="b51865d64765c94e8c0bba9f70dc11b5" url=""><![CDATA[check out this video<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmyspacetv.com%2Findex.cfm%3Ffuseaction%3Dvids.individual%26amp%3Bvideoid%3D11065839"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://myspacetv.com/index.cfm?fuseaction=vids.individual&amp;videoid=11065839</a>
<br /><br />OK not sure how ot upload videos from myspace.. but this one is someone I went to HS with .. 
<br /><br />Rock On John
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="539edb61b58fdd270903f0c5cee99425" url=""><![CDATA[last time with Lizzaard Runn<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmyspacetv.com%2Findex.cfm%3Ffuseaction%3Dvids.individual%26amp%3Bvideoid%3D11127964"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://myspacetv.com/index.cfm?fuseaction=vids.individual&amp;videoid=11127964</a>
<br /><br />John formed Lizzaard Runn and played as its lead singer for yrs.
<br /><br />then he went to big cat band and now think he is solo
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1cc253f545a8346f5db166dcfba644e7" url=""><![CDATA[another one<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmyspacetv.com%2Findex.cfm%3Ffuseaction%3Dvids.individual%26amp%3Bvideoid%3D11137694"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://myspacetv.com/index.cfm?fuseaction=vids.individual&amp;videoid=11137694</a>
<br /><br />John trying to be a big hair rock band?  OMG
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c57a24d9bd0cedf3d80129f8140d4e5e" url=""><![CDATA[looking for record<br/><br/>Hey everyone Im in the hunt for a record most likely a 45 rpm..  &quot;Framed&quot; by Richie Valens.
<br /><br />Ok this is like imposible to fine.. but if you come across it im in the market ...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4e96894945850d8799f2a567196176ec" url=""><![CDATA[to far to hold<br/><br/>Here we are clear across the country from each other.   I cant turn back the clock to not go without you
<br />I cant hug you in my arms like I use to .     I cant hear your laughter.   See your smiling face.
<br />My only comfort is we see the same moon stars and sun.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4454878776977ff7dc7ab9aa3b108452" url=""><![CDATA[korny jokes<br/><br/>1:  what do you call a unicorns dad?
<br /><br />2: why did the cookie go to the dr?
<br /><br />3: why can't a dalmatian play hide and seek?
<br /><br />1: Pop corn 
<br /><br />2: cause he was feeling crumbie
<br /><br />3: cause they are already spotted
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a3ea4097995dda099d4d2d678aac77bc" url=""><![CDATA[great vampire flick<br/><br/>Ok I will admite it I have a thing for great vampire flicks and enjoy anne rice's books ( ps I hate to read)
<br /><br />but just saw 30 days of night  I have to say I got a new favorite vampire flick
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71ee835c879842c6c97155ffdb600583" url=""><![CDATA[pain so deep<br/><br/>with pain so deep 
<br />he was only 15 
<br />I remember the day he talked to me 
<br />I remember his voice loud and clear 
<br />everyone thought he was happy and dear 
<br />but no one knew deep inside 
<br />he had sumthing he'd always hide 
<br />deep at night 
<br />he would think 
<br />&quot;no one cares about me&quot; 
<br />no one knew the pain and sorrow 
<br />no one knew he wouldn't be there tomarrow 
<br />the next day he got the rope 
<br />he thought there was hope or use 
<br />so he tied the rope into a noose 
<br />up and up the tree he went 
<br />and put the noose around his neck 
<br />with just one leap with his eyes closed 
<br />now he just hung there dead and cold 
<br />people stood and cried 
<br />now he's constantly on the family's minds 
<br />and they keep wondering why 
<br />I wish I was there to say goodbye 
<br />I wish he didn't have to die 
<br />now his mother falls on her knees 
<br />by her bed and weeps 
<br />all because her beloved son 
<br />had pain so deep 
<br />(in memory of my beloved cousin Kenny Madride 1987-2004) R.I.P I luv ya and miss ya 
<br /><br />Written by XxgoldwanterxX
<br /><br />Miss you my dear nephew ...your loving aunty Lostapache
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a34f91500885ae3ed26312a3e6e0f518" url=""><![CDATA[Looking for old friends and ppl I knew<br/><br/>I was born in Kermit Tx in 1961  left there in 1970.    Im looking for pple who went to school with me.
<br />Or where my friends.
<br /><br />Teresa Sanchez ( Ur Dad owned Vicks Cafe we danced with someone famous on your brothers wedding day)   KAthy and Donna Compton ( taught me cheerleading), Holly Dodd, Cole Mitchel,  Gerald and Carol MOrgan, Teresa Jones ( had a handicapped brother and your bday is June 14 flag day),  Mrs Williamson ( think you where my 3rd or 4th grade teacher), Lane Nutt, Marvin Smith ( your father George and my dad Nolan where at one time best friends), 
<br /><br />If anyone I missed grew up in Kermit Tx during these dates let me know PLZ  Im going on 47 ..   
<br /><br />I was Lisa LaVella Tison..
<br /><br />I think we lived on Bryant Street across from High school I remember that the high school front door was right across the street,  and next to our house was a 4 car garage my dad owned N L motor Sales and Service.     My mom worked in hopsital  ( with a nice lady named Dovie)    and some where I think in the country where she made donuts and I played with a Rebecca across the street from there.
<br /><br />ANy way that is my trip down memory lane.     The getting in touch with old buddies is sort of ( not that there is a rush) bucket list thing.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="22112a54f87b77d5253133c8223084c1" url=""><![CDATA[yelling again<br/><br/><strong></strong> Your are yelling at me again.    It is so hard for me to understand the whys.
<br /><br />I only try to help you and I get yelled at.   You remind me of my mother who I could never
<br /><br />do anything right no matter how hard I tried.
<br /><br />You scare me when you slam your fist into the trashcan or throw a chair across the floor
<br /><br />breaking it into pieces.   Yelling at me to get out.       I cant live like this.  Your anger hurts your words 
<br /><br />hurt.   Im tired of feeling bullied by you to how I spend my little bit of money.  
<br /><br />I wish I had a place to go to.  I dont.. The one I want to talk to is dead.   And here you are yelling at me 
<br /><br />again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f243778235759558e4d743c1fcf727d3" url=""><![CDATA[His Voice<br/><br/>When I wake up with him beside me and a gentle &quot;good morning&quot;. 
<br />His Voice moves me.
<br />No matter how he seaks to me.
<br />His voice sooths me.
<br />In my darkest moment of my life.
<br />His voice lights my way.
<br />His touch brings me sunshine on the most cloudest of days.
<br />With him, there's no fear, the gentle touch of his hand calms them away.
<br />His words of advice always sinks deep within my heart.
<br />I long for his caress to be held in his arms as if he could not ever let me go.
<br />To feel his heartbeat in rhythm with mine.  
<br />When I look at him deep into his eyes, his eyes speak to me, without him uttering a single word.
<br />His kiss warms me on the coldest nights.
<br /><br />His 
<br />Voice
<br />Moves
<br />Me
<br /><br />By Lisa LaVella Tison-Wilson
<br />dedicated to ( YOU KNOW WHO YOU ARE!)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="db94d9ee42bcf9c685040ec5df1482d3" url=""><![CDATA[native american<br/><br/><object width="336" height="295"><param name="movie" value="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-911394"></param><param name="wmode" value="window"></param><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"></param><embed src="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-911394" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowFullScreen="true" wmode="window" width="336" height="295"></embed></object>   Native American and proud!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6af5885d9a2e2b845cad6ef6fb948fcd" url=""><![CDATA[House burning down<br/><br/>Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey
<br /><br />Look at the sky turn a hell fire red
<br />Somebody's house is burnin' down down, down down
<br />Down, down, down.
<br /><br />Well I asked my friend where is that black smoke comin' from ?
<br />He just coughed and changed the subject and 
<br />said oh wa I think it might snow some
<br />So I left him sippin' his tea an' I jumped in my chariot
<br />And rode off to see just why and who could it be this time.
<br /><br />Sisters and brothers daddys mothers standin' 'round cryin'
<br />When I reached the scene the flames were makin' a ghostly whine
<br />So I stood on my horse's back an' I screamed without a crack
<br />I say oh baby why'd you burn your brother's house down ?
<br /><br />Hey ! Hey ! Hey ! Hey !
<br /><br />Look out the sky turn a hell fire red Lord
<br />Somebody's house is burnin' down down, down down
<br />Look out the sky turn a hell fire red Lord
<br />Somebody's house is burnin' down down, down down down.
<br /><br />Well someone stepped from the crowd he was nineteen miles high
<br />He shouts retired and disgusted so we paint red through the sky
<br />I said the truth is straight ahead so don't burn yourself instead
<br />Try to learn instead of burn, hear what I say, yeah, yeah.
<br /><br />So I fin'ly rode away but I'll never forget that day
<br />'Cause when I reached the valley I looked way down cross the way
<br />A giant boat from space landed with eerie grace
<br />And came and taken all the dead away.
<br /><br />Hey ! Hey ! Hey ! Hey !
<br /><br />What'd I say.
<br />Look at the sky turn a hell fire red Lord
<br />Somebody's house is burning down down, down down
<br />Look at the sky turn a hell fire red Lord
<br />Somebody's house is burning down down, down down
<br />Look at the sky, look at the sky.
<br /><br />Ooh, ooh, ooh
<br />Ooh, ooh, ooh
<br />Oh baby
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="234c7715444a3b05867edb3517cf77f8" url=""><![CDATA[a mothers love<br/><br/>A mother's love is there from the start.   From the diaper changes, splinters in your fingers to the very first heart break.     A mother's love is without end she becomes your closest friend.    Through gray clouds or sun shinny days.  Through love and laughter there are there for ever and after
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cffbee0ae08af2241fef13047c10e179" url=""><![CDATA[Missing mom<br/><br/><strong></strong> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />    
<br /><br />10-27-08 you would of been 89.  There is so much I wish I had of said.   I wish you where here to impart words of wisdom on relationships, mothering among some of the things I wish I could talk to you about.
<br /><br />I remember the day you past away how I was by your side.  At long last things between us where working out to where we got along.    Slowly dying in pain from liver cancer which had spread all out your internal organs.    I signed the papers to use enough morphine to make it not painful.  As you slowly left this world my heart broke.    I have been so depressed lately wishing I could turn back hands of time to talk to you again.  Some of the paths I took I would love to undo and have a second chance at once again to know what I know today.      Such is life I guess we are allowed to make stupid mistakes.   I so wish you where here to let me know if this path is one I should of taken.  I believe you watch me, I just wish I could hear you to talk to you.
<br /><br />My dearest mom even though you did not give birth to me, I have always thought of you and only you as my mother.
<br /><br />Love forever in loving memory of you
<br /><br />Lisa
<br /><br />Dedicated to Erma Ninette Clinton-Tison  10-27-1919  to 04-16-87
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e86f9b7b724af0ab55bbf6a060c17a70" url=""><![CDATA[searching for<br/><br/>Hello again!
<br /><br />I was thinking aobut you once more wondering where you where.    I often do when things go wrong in my life wondering what you are doing and where you are.     Wishing I could turn back time to when we where.
<br /><br />My life is full of heartbreak and wish we could be together.  I still remember seeing you in NC at that race track wishing I would of got the nerve to talk to you.  I was scared of being beat i had a bruise on my arm from sholder to my elbow.   My heart jumped when I saw you.     Here I am living so close to your last know address and I cant find you still.   Has time been cruel to me once more.   
<br /><br />I am not sure I can love again Im tired im mentally gone.  I drive the ones I love away from me.  It hurts to see them slowly slip away.   No one gets the bipolar issues then mix ptsd on that and I'm a basket case.
<br /><br />It was odd today my daughter asked if I thought of you.  I am always honest with her and I do from time to time.     
<br /><br />I wish I could just get through the doughts I get when I am with someone.  The convinced they are with another seeing someone else but alas I can not.   That breaks up the relationship, once again I am see a releationship go away.    I am tired of my heart breaking.      How can I tell if someone is messing around on me?    I thought maybe this time but again I am sad all the time.   I can only remember a few times being happy no matter what.   
<br /><br />I guess that is it for now.   Just sad right now.  Tired of feeling all I will be is someones bed toy.  
<br /><br />So my dearest friend Steve Lambuth.  I hope this finds you only in the best of life.
<br /><br />Lisa
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c207d208716749117e1c9c685d3df481" url=""><![CDATA[Cursed in Love<br/><br/>Today as I was wondering why I am so stupid when it comes to love.  Why I have the hardest time finding the true soul mate.   When I think I have found him.  Either I mess it up ( as with Steve)  Or he is so self centered jerk that the only thing that seems to matter to him is the bedroom.    I want more in a relationship than that.    I want the sholders in the bad time,  hand to hold in the good times.  Someone to walk beside me, not infront or  behind.    I want someone that will just listen to me as I vent or cry.    I want true love.  Does it really excist?    If I could turn back time and take some things with me where would I start.   I would want to keep my daughter.   I would love to try to really have that special feeling with Steve I had.      I know he is out there.  So much has happened.      Why did I ever leave?  Why am I so jelous over the most stupidest stuff.   When in this relationship part of me getting to be a huge part of me really wishes he had or has someone else.   The other what is left is hoping things work out.  I am so tired of relationships turning out to be crap.     I know somewhere out there is that special one.  Are we allowed more than one in a life time?   Why do the fate hate me so?  Why am I cursed in love?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ef3bf00035e2f3c603bce81d3840527f" url=""><![CDATA[my birthday present<br/><br/>I am gonna be gone may 16th to 17th  to Depoe Bay Oregon.   Gone Fishing
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yaquinabaycharters.com%2Findex.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.yaquinabaycharters.com/index.html</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3b22c807fb3b658e7f780fbace855b4c" url=""><![CDATA[saying goodbye<br/><br/><strong></strong>  This week I will have to put down my daughters dalmatain who was almost 14.. 
<br /><br />He was a certified seizure alert assist animal, companion dog.     
<br /><br />Chocolate chip would alert to an on coming seizure of my daughters 2 hrs before hand.   
<br /><br />He will be loved and missed.     
<br /><br />Chocolate Chip  july 7th 1995 - may 2009
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7ce8d8d7279182c94bada28ffe8d5dd8" url=""><![CDATA[I WANT A PIRATES 4!!!<br/><br/>Lyrics:
<br /><br />Yo, ho, haul together,
<br />hoist the colors high.
<br />Heave ho,
<br />thieves and beggars,
<br />never shall we die.
<br /><br />The king and his men
<br />stole the queen from her bed
<br />and bound her in her Bones.
<br />The seas be ours
<br />and by the powers
<br />where we will we'll roam.
<br /><br />Yo, ho, haul together,
<br />hoist the colors high.
<br />Heave ho, thieves and beggars,
<br />never shall we die.
<br /><br />Some men have died
<br />and some are alive
<br />and others sail on the sea
<br />– with the keys to the cage...
<br />and the Devil to pay
<br />we lay to Fiddler's Green!
<br /><br />The bell has been raised
<br />from it's watery grave...
<br />Do you hear it's sepulchral tone?
<br />We are a call to all,
<br />pay head the squall
<br />and turn your sail toward home!
<br /><br />Yo, ho, haul together,
<br />hoist the colors high.
<br />Heave ho, thieves and beggars,
<br />never shall we die.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7716054d82b0ac735a4cef511b745adf" url=""><![CDATA[AMBER ALERT!!!<br/><br/>MY 17 YR OLD DAUGHTER IS MISSING AN ENDANGERED RUNAWAY.  LAST SEEN 2-23-10 IN EUGENE OREGON.    PLEAASE HELP ME FIND HER!  HER NAME IS SHUSHANNA NINETTE WILSON ( GOES BY SHANNA)  5'8&quot; 140-150 LBS  DRK BROWN HAIR WITH BLONDE HIGHLIGHTS SHE MIGHT OF DYED IT BLACK.   THERE IS A MISSING PERSONS CASE ON HER... JUNCTION CITY OREGON PD CASE #10-162   PLZ HELP ME FIND HER.   IF ANY WUESTIONS EMAIL ME AT  
<br /><a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=lostapachellt@yahoo.com">lostapachellt@yahoo.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>