<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="1a1a6bac0b3faca5809971d734dc8bf" url=""><![CDATA[Volunteer Experience: Help in a Library<br/><br/>I helped in a library with Carol and Alice in Nanjing Gulou Region Culture and Art Centre form the November 22nd, 2009 to the February 6th, 2010. In this library, we usually arrange the books and reception readers. I learned many things after doing those work.
<br /><br />Most of the time, we arranged the books here. We needed to put all the books that people returned to the bookshelves. At the same time, we should use the numbers beside each book to make sure the book’ Sequence. It seemed that the work is easy, but too much numbers made me Upset. So I realized that the thing which seems easy to do, but in fact, it might be very difficult. I also learned the importance of working as a group. When we did the work together, we were like a team and we often did group work. One person arranged the book in the small cart, and then two people put them into the bookshelves. That made us work very quickly and effectively, so I felt happy about it. 
<br /><br />During the work, I also needed to converse with the curator and different administrators. I think it needed many community skills during this process. At very beginning, we even did not know what things we will do because we did not do any volunteer work before. I asked the administrator, and she taught us. We also faced some problems during our work. For example, some readers asked me some questions, but I do not know how to answer them. At this time, I usually asked the administrator and she will tell me. So I realized that we have some community skills for our work in the future so that we can converse with others in a better way and the results will be more Satisfactory. 
<br /><br />In the past, I thought I am good at conversing with others, but the truth is that it is not enough. I am lucky to have the chance to work with others now. I will have the volunteer experience to improve it, and I will keep on doing this volunteer work. I think I will have good community skills and will do some community work easily in the future.  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f35663c2b6c3f8d297e0302a5823902" url=""><![CDATA[Ate at a Japanese Restaurant<br/><br/>On Friday, March 5th, 2010, my classmate Alice, Miles and I went to a Japanese restaurant named Tairyo Japanese Restaurant to learn another culture by eating Japanese food. The restaurant is on the Taiping North Road, and in 1912. One of my friends recommends this restaurant to me, and she said the food is very traditional and delicious, so I chose this restaurant. It was my first time to eat Japanese food. We reached there at about 6 P. M. after school.
<br /><br />In the restaurant, we all chose the buffet, and we can eat anything we want. Because each food is very little, we ordered many kinds of food like salad, roll, beefsteaks, eel, scallop, oyster, chicken wings, shrimp and ice-cream. After tasting the food, I like the eel best. The ell which fried by the cook was very fresh and tender. I also had some special feelings that I can not describe. It was a little salted, but that made it more delicious. I also like the California Roll, Tairyo’s Grilled Scallop and Mushroom Beef Roll. They are all very traditional. In many ways, Japanese food is quiet different from the food we usually eat. Compared with Chinese food, Japanese people like to eat food that in small plate, and they also eat some fresh food like Sashimi. I do not like it. 
<br /><br />The environment and atmosphere was very clean and tidy. It gave me a good feeling to eat food there. The waitresses were very active to us, and they gave us the food very quickly. I saw some white people there, and they said the food was good. I will recommend this restaurant to others because the food is quite delicious. The environment and service is also very good. It is a good choice to eat Japanese food in Tairyo Japanese Restaurant
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9385078e6822228c73f2b35ad8fb9bed" url=""><![CDATA[Interview an Art Professional<br/><br/>On March 24th, Alice and I had an interview with our Art teacher—Ms. Hadley about her art career during our lunch time. We had a great time talking to each other. We learned a lot art and knew a lot about Ms. Hadley. 
<br /><br />As our art teacher, Ms. Hadley has much work to do every day. For her, she has more than 150 students in Grade.10. She needs to prepare the lessons that follow the BC curriculum, and then teach students how to draw a great painting. In Art class, she also shows us some videos about art history and visual culture. She also needs to prepare the quiz and exams, and mark the students. People always think that art teachers only need to teach students how to draw a picture, and their work is so easy and relaxed. The truth is that they also have a lot of work to do, and it is not easy work. 
<br /><br />Ms. Hadley was not very interested in art when she was very young. She used to study education in Canada. Once she went to India, an idea suddenly went into her mind on the bus—she wanted to be an art teacher. So she went to many universities to learn art. She got a bachelor degree in the University of Toronto. After that, she stayed in Ontario for further study, and then went into Emily Carrl and studied at the University of British Colombia. Now she is an art teacher, and she likes to talk with her students not only about art, but also about life. That will make her keep young. She also has many good friends here, such as Ms.Bartell and Mr.Gallinelli. They have a good time working together. 
<br /><br />To be a good teacher, there are also many challenges. The most important thing that she should care is her students’ safety and to make them have a good mind. When she was a teacher in Canada, one of her students made her worried. He is a quite thin boy, and his legs are just half of Ms. Hadley’s legs. He liked art very much. Every time he talked with Ms. Hadley, they are all about art. Also, the boy’s actions are not normal. Ms. Hadley realized there is something wrong with his thoughts, and that may harm other students. So she tried her best to enlighten him. It was difficult for her because she knew nothing psychology. In China, she also has some problems, and the most difficult thing is organization. It’s really hard to make different kinds of people work together, and make them have the team spirit. 
<br /><br />Ms. Hadley really likes printmaking, and her favorite artist is R.B.Kitaj who is American and lives in Britain. He is a painter, and his artwork is a little abstract. He likes to draw food and people, and his lithographs are the most famous part.
<br /><br />She often organizes some activities, such as Free Hugs in March 2010. Although she faced some problems in the activity, it was a big success. Before Ms. Hadley became an art teacher, she tried many jobs, and she thinks this one is the best. She wants to try more new things in the future. 
<br /><br />After we interviewed Ms. Hadley, I knew more experiences that she had before, and some of them are surprised for me. I will never forget her in my lifetime. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="94ae0d1db17d9cde8132ae5c682de17f" url=""><![CDATA[Volunteer Experience? Do Volunteer Work for Ms. Bartell<br/><br/>In the last 2 term, my friends and I did volunteer work in Gulou Region Culture and Art Centre for 24 hours, and we had a good time here. In this term, we did volunteer work for our Planning teacher—Ms. Bartell with Alice and Carol in her office from March 12th 2010 to March 19th 2010. Until March 19th 2010, I have done 6 hours’ volunteer work. Every Friday, our class had no class in the third period and last period, so they became a good time to do the volunteer work for our teachers. Ms. Bartell usually let us sorts out the Degrassi Junior High quiz, make some envelopes, do some computer work and other work. 
<br /><br />We often sorted out the Degrassi Junior High quiz in the third period because most of the quiz was in the morning. All of the sheets were not in a correct order, so we needed to put them in a correct order, and then wrote 10 on each because it was the total mark. We also needed to find out the questions that the students did not write anything and put a“×” on the serial number. At the very beginning, when we used the name paper that Ms. Bartell gave us to help us sort out the quiz, we did this work very slowing because we did not know anything about the serial number of other class. But after we did many times, the situation is better. Now, I can do it within a very time. It is known to all that Practice makes perfect. It is not only suitable for our study, but also for our work. 
<br /><br />We also made some envelopes for Ms. Bartell. We used the calendar paper that Ms. Bartell gave us to make the cover. First, I used the sample to draw on the paper and then Carol cut the shape down by the scissors, Alice was responsible to fold the paper carefully. We work together very quickly and effectively, and we finished many envelops within a short time. Ms.Bartell said: “Your guys are my super volunteers!” She also told us that we can choose one envelope which is our favorite. I choose an envelope with the beautiful view of New Zealand, and she told us those envelops will be sent to all the teachers. 
<br /><br />Not everything that we did is full of happiness, some of them are crazy. Once Mr.Gallinelli asked Ms. Bartell to help him find 600 just one-side-used papers that is used for English Only Project. So we three super volunteers helped her find the papers in a box that is full of papers. I was responsible to sort and count the papers. Alice and Carol were responsible to find the papers, and they are crazy. Suddenly, I could just see Carol’s body. Where was her head? Oh, her head and two arms were in the box. I first found that Alice was a “violent” girl. She tried her best to find the papers, just liked fight with an enemy. That was so amazing. Finally, we finished the task, and we all felt interesting. At the same time, I realized that we should save papers all the time! 
<br /><br />Compared with the volunteer work in the library, the volunteer work for Ms. Bartell was full of amazing, surprising and interesting. Although sometimes the volunteer work made me tired, I enjoyed my volunteer work. I will also do volunteer work for Ms. Bartell when I am in Grade. 11. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1112a8c01f11f257437b9030791d8c6e" url=""><![CDATA[School Club and Organization<br/><br/>I joined in Badminton Club, Table Tennis Club and Volunteer Club in GCA. The Volunteer Club did not have many club activities in these 3 terms, so I took part in many activities in Badminton Club and Table Tennis Club. Until February 28th, I have done 7 hours for badminton activities in Badminton Club, and 3 hours for Table Tennis Club activities.
<br /><br />The Table Tennis activities are usually in the school on Wednesdays during lunchtime. Alice, Carol and I often played together. Most of the time, I taught them how to play table tennis because they could not play table tennis very well or even could not know how to play table tennis, I could teach them some basic action although I could not play it very, very well. The reason why we joined in Table Tennis Club is that we wanted to try something new even Alice and Carol could not play table tennis at all. I think if we don’t try anything new, we will never know whether we can do it well. So we went there for 3 hours under my suggestions.
<br /><br />Until February 28th, Alice, Carol and I have done 7 hours for Badminton Club activities. I first played badminton with my father when I was about 5 years old. So I like to play badminton very much. Carol and Alice were also interested in badminton. So we joined this club together. The place was in Nanjing Normal University every Saturday afternoon from 2 p.m. to 4 p.m. Once when Alice and I went to the badminton courts, we found that there were no empty courts, so we could just play badminton with two men and played mixed doubles badminton. I tried my best to play it, and I still remember my two arms, two legs and waist could not move the following day. On October 31th, I took part in the Badminton Team Member Screening Test, and I came second in the junior part. I was very happy about that. 
<br /><br />Until May 4th, I finished the other 5 hours for Badminton Club activities. The place was not in Nanjing Normal University and moved to the school stadium every Wednesday night from 7pm to 8pm. There were only four courts there, so not many people went there. Because we only have two rockets, only two people could play badminton, and another people waited her turn to play it. Sometimes I played badminton with other students from other class. So the Badminton Club activities also made me have more friends from other class. 
<br /><br />It thinks it is necessary for us to do some sports every week, even on Wednesdays nights. In GCA, the students do not need to do morning exercises every day, and there are only two P.E. classes every week. So we need to do some extra exercise to keep healthy. Although it will take my study time, I think it is worth. I will join the Badminton Club next year, and I hope my badminton skills will be improved next year. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c98c88cc145b9b833727ae5f7c2facb6" url=""><![CDATA[Public Events<br/><br/>On March 12th 2010, Alice and I went to Xuan Wu Lake to see the Italian International Light and Sculpture Show after school. Because we entered the park by the side door, it took us half an hour to go to the exhibition area.
<br /><br />Sky was black at that time, but the Xuan Wu Lake Park was full of light. The first object we saw was many colorful lights that made them look like many doors, and the doors disappeared in a very far place. The doors were shining one by one. When they turned blue, it looked like a fairyland. We kept walking, and we saw many big structures that made by many colorful bulbs. Some bulbs could change the color, but some were not.
<br /><br />Then we saw a big structure named the Rome Colosseum. It was blue, and the color was not changed. It was a huge three-dimensional circle. We walked in it, and the feelings were special. Because it was black outside, when we saw the light inside the circle, it looked like a number of crystal, and the lights were very dazzling. I stander in it, and it was dreamful. I could not even believe mu eyes. It was quite beautiful.
<br /><br />Although the Rome Colosseum was amazing, I think some other structures were not successful. Many of them were full of red, yellow, green and orange. I think they were very Chinese, and I did not like them very much.
<br /><br />Although I did not like all of the sculptures, it still widens my eyes. I enjoyed them a lot, and I like them.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="77a7b4a981ec069afee81080afb16902" url=""><![CDATA[Act in a performance<br/><br/>In December 2009, our school had an Art Festival in the big hall. Our class sang a song called “Yesterday Once More” during the celebration. There were eight people that took part in the song—Rita, Alice, Carol, Miriam, Rowena, Lucy, Miles and me. 
<br /><br />Before the Art Festival, we practice a lot after school. Rita, Alice, Carol and me are the main singers, and the other people will sing it behind us and do some action the suit the song. So we should create some action for them and that took us some time. 
<br /><br />Then the big day came finally. Because our song was a little behind on the performance menu, we all sat in the audience seat at first. When two programs before our song, we were all asked to go to the backstage. At this time, I suddenly felt nervous because it is my first time to sing a song in front of all the teachers and students. And it seemed that Carol has the same feeling, so we encouraged with each other, and it made me feel better. 
<br /><br />Later we were on the stage, and the sick feelings cane again. I felt my heart shake a lot, and then I felt that my face is becoming hotter and hotter. I believed that my face must turn red at that time. The music was open, and I can heard Rita’s voice—“when I was young I listen to the video waiting for my favorite songs. When......” Oh, it was my turn next, and I was still nervous. I did not know how I opened my mouth. I did not know whether my classmates clapped the hands for us. I could not even hear my voice. I just remembered it was black in the audience seats. I just remembered that I was singing.
<br /><br />After we finished singing the song, I did not know what to do. When I told carol my feelings, she said she had the same feelings. 
<br /><br />Maybe it was not a successful performance, but it gave me much confidence, and I believe I will not be too nervous when I stand on the stage next time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3db60592bb505a4a888913333d5bc3f9" url=""><![CDATA[Participate in a service Activity organized by a GCA teacher<br/><br/>On March 13th, three GCA teachers—Ms. Bartell, Ms. Hadley and Mr. Burt organized an activity called “Free Hugs” in Gulou Square. The activity means we can give a hug to anyone who wants it for free. The goal was to encourage and give warm hags others 
<br /><br />At about one o’clock in the afternoon. Alice and I took a bus there. Ms. Hadley and Ms. Bartell have already reached there. Ms. Hadley said the she was a little nervous because she never did this before. So did I. Ten minutes later, Mr. Burt and other students from other classes reached the Gulou Square, too. Ms. Bartell gave us some papers that explain what free hugs are, and then we began our activity.
<br /><br />Alice and I went to the edge of the square that beside the street. We hand out the papers and told the people about the free hugs. Many people gave there hugs to us, even a young child. But the things are not full of happiness. A man who rode a bicycle perplexed me a lot. At first, it seemed that he was interested in the activity and asked me about it, and I told him about the activity. Then he took a photo of Alice and me, and he said he will send it to the Newspaper Office. At the same time, he also took several photos of us. I realized that maybe he was not a good person, and I nearly shouted to him and asked him to stop. Finally, he went away, but he had our photos. That really perplexed me.
<br /><br />Although there were some bad things happened, I still think this activity is a good in China. It was a good chance for people to Interflow to each other.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dff282ccb6185adc8f45aad425ad0af4" url=""><![CDATA[Go to a Performance<br/><br/>On the November 21st, Alice, Carol and I went to the Great Hall of the People to see the play called “Sorry, Baby”. The main character is named Zhou XiaoTan. He was the member of F4—a music composition that was very hot in Asia during 2001 to 2009. We met at the gate at about 19:15, and then we went into the hall. 
<br /><br />The play told us a story of a man with his two wives. A man named Zhang LiGuo is a taxi diver. He has two wives, and they do not know each other, and this man go to his wives in different time, so he keep this secret well for a long time. One day, he got a car accident, and he goes the wrong house. Because of this, the two wives start to doubt the man. 
<br /><br />After the police also go to one of his wives house, and go to another wives house, the truth appears slowly. Finally, two wives meet together and know the truth, and the man gets the punishment. 
<br /><br />The play is vey interesting, and the characters have good acting skills. Maybe because Zhou XiaoTan is the main character in this play, and he was quite hot many years age, the audiences clap their hands for many times. But it seemed that this play is not suitable for teenagers. Although Zhou XiaoTan was a singer, I think his acting skills are quite good. 
<br /><br />I was very happy that I could see Zhou XiaoTan’ acting skills and the other characters also did very well. So I like this play very much.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8be8ada842a563ca0338ee6fcc395c53" url=""><![CDATA[Go to an Exhibition<br/><br/>On the April 5th, I went to Jiangsu Provincial Art Museum to see the exhibition by myself. The title of the exhibition was Children’s Collected Paintings. The exhibition was free, but there were only few people there. The artists there were all children, and their paintings all use papers. The artworks there are all contemporary, and from 2008 to 2010. 
<br /><br />My favorite painting is drawn by a child called Li Chen. The title of the painting is “After I lost my mother”, and it made in 2009. 
<br /><br />Because this artwork is drawn by a child who is only nice years old, there are not too many lines and shapes in his artwork, and he just uses one color which is black. In his artwork, there are three bottles, and the last two bottles are bigger than the first one. In the first two bottles, each bottle has a boy in it. The boy in the first bottle is happy, and the boy in the second one is lonely and sad. I do not know what things that in the third bottle. It just looks like some floating leaves. In the first bottle, there is not a lid, but in the last two bottles, the lids make the bottles closed.
<br /><br />When I first saw this artwork, I was sure the theme of this artwork is not happy. The artist just used black in the picture. Then I saw the title is “After I lost my Mother”, and I know his mother died when he was very young. The first bottle refers to the boy that before his mother died, and he was happy. After his mother died, he always does anything by himself, and he did not want to talk with others, and he closed his heart. But I can not understand the meaning of the third bottle. Maybe he wants to tell us after he lost his mother, his heart broken and hopeless just like the floating leaves, but I am not sure. This artwork reminds me of my grandfather’s death. He died when I am only four years old or even younger. I was so young that I even did not know what happened. I just know after that, I did not see my grandfather any more. Maybe I was so young that me heart was not broken, but this boy is different from me. So I show sympathy for him. I think the reason why he shows these terrible things to us is that he wants to tell us we should treasure the thing that we have at present.
<br /><br />For some parts, I think this artwork is successful, but for some other parts, I don’t think it is successful. This artwork reminds me of my grandfather. It makes me have the same response. Maybe because of the same experience, I can even feel his sadness, and do not forget that he is just a child. So I think it is a successful artwork. But I can not understand what he wants to tell us about for the third bottle. So I think it is a little unsuccessful. But I will not buy this artwork if I could, because my grandfather has been dead for a long time, will be full of sad all the time. So I will not buy it.
<br /><br />Most of the artworks there were about childhood. Although these children do not have good drawing skills, these artworks made me have a happy feeling. I like them very much.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eef6c0fe875fb0f776c8d15e0e47aea7" url=""><![CDATA[Physical Activity<br/><br/>I rode a bicycle to school and went back home every sunny day during October 26th 2009 to March 4th 2010. It took me half an hour to go to school or to back home, so if I use a bicycle, it will take me one hour to go to school and go back home every day. If it was a rainy day, I will take a bus to school instead of riding a bicycle. For the physical activity hours, I have done 72 hours until March 4th 2010.
<br /><br />I think it is necessary for me to do some sports every day to keep fit, but I don’t have much time to do some sports because I should study every day, and sometimes I have a lot of work to do. I think ride a bicycle to school is a good way to help us to do some sports, it will not take us too much time. Another important reason I like to ride a bicycle to school is that there is always too much traffic on Beijing East Road every morning. It will help me to save time if I ride a bicycle. For me, there are many benefits to ride a bicycle.
<br /><br />At very beginning, it was not an easy thing for me to ride to school within a short tine in the morning, and I often felt tired ay that time. Sometimes, I got up late, so I must rode my bicycle by using a higher speed, and that made me quite tired. But later I did not felt tired any more because I ride a bicycle every day, and that equals I practiced it every day. Now, I don’t feel tired at all even I ride it a little quickly, so I believe a good body need a lot of exercise.
<br /><br />In fact, riding a bicycle in the street is not an easy thing to do. When I went back home, there were many other bicycles on the street every day. Sometimes, although I have a good riding skill, maybe other people will crash me when I am riding. So if I ride a bicycle to school and go home, I should have a good riding skill and I must be very careful, or I will be very dangerous. So I learnt to be careful after I rode the bicycle.
<br /><br />In winter, riding a bicycle can make my body warm although the wind is strong and cold, but in summer, riding a bicycle may be too hot. So I probably will not ride a bicycle to school and go back home.
<br /><br />Sometimes, I also played badminton with my father at the weekend. So I spend at least 5 hours doing sports every week. Now, my body is healthier than before. I think it is very necessary for me to do some sports every day, and I will keep on doing those sports to keep fit, and I will also encourage my parents to do some sports.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bffe93d58bd718a6bfb145478abd5e8b" url=""><![CDATA[Physical Activity--Gr. 10 30 hours for Personal Health<br/><br/>When I was in Grade 10, I rode a bicycle to school and back to home every day except rainy days and I did this for my physical activity in that portfolio for 72 hours before May 4th . During this summer holiday, I played badminton with my friend Carol at Nanjing Olympic Centre every week, and after playing badminton, we usually rode our bicycles to relax ourselves. So I did the physical activity for 32 hours total during the summer holiday. 
<br /><br />After I first played badminton this summer and back to home, I was too tired to do any other things. My two legs, two arms and belly were quite painful the following day, and I could only stand up or sit down very slowly maybe because I have not do any sports for a long time.
<br /><br />Carol had a great badminton skill although she used her left hand. When I played badminton with Carol, in my mind, I knew I tried my best and I wanted to win although Carol is my best friend. Maybe this is the meaning of a competitor – just focus on the competition, not think too much about the other things such as friendship. Nevertheless, I knew we are still the best friends after the competition. Equally, to be an athlete, I should just think about the match and tried to get the first place in the real competition. 
<br /><br />Played badminton not only made me learn the meaning of the real competition, but also helped me to keep fit during the hot summer holiday. I was quite happy that I did not get fat during the holiday, and I think doing some sports every week is necessary for everybody. I will keep on doing sports in my spare time when I am in Grade 11.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="94f8a69b70ab725c2c8b650bc3e2da9f" url=""><![CDATA[Gr.11 Go to a performance<br/><br/>On August 18th, 2010, Carol and I went to Nanjing Cultural and Art Centre to see the Puppet Show of the Grimm’s Fairy Tales. We met at the gate of the centre at about 7:20 P.M. and I found that all the audience is children who are around five old and their parents. I even regret about my choice, but in another way, I was a little bit excited to see the play that children like to see and remember my child memories. So I still kept seeing the play. 
<br /><br />Because this is a play for children, the story has simply substance. Hunter and Gretel’ mother order them to pick some mushroom in the forest for they ate all the cheese in the jar when she is not at home. However, they lost their way in the forest, and they fall asleep. When Hunter and Gretel wake up, they meet the old witch who wants to eat them. After they defeat the old witch by using their wisdom, they meet their parents and then go back home. 
<br /><br />Although the play seems a little bit babyish for me, in some ways, I still found it quite interesting. It made me think of my childhood. I still remember that I was quite interested in the stories and plays like this and although there was an old witch in the stories, the endings were always full of happiness. After I grow up, I never read those kinds of books, and I am not as happy as before any more. 
<br /><br />In some ways, I think it is still meaningful for our teenagers to watch some kinds of Puppet Shows to think of our happy childhoods and have an optimistic attitude to face all kinds of challenges and difficulties.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e2da925a98268734d0054eef83adc047" url=""><![CDATA[Gr. 11 Public Events<br/><br/>On June 12th 2010, our school organized a big trip to Shanghai to visit the Shanghai EXPO, and most of my classmates and some of the teachers went there at that day. I was so excited about this trip because this was the first time that the trip which organized by school had a destination that was out of Nanjing, and I could go there with my good friends and lovely classmates and teachers. 
<br /><br />We met at the school gate at about 5:10 A.M. and everyone got on the special yellow T-shirts which provided by school and had the special GCA logo on them. The three coaches took us from Nanjing to Shanghai for about 4 hours, and when we entered in the park, we were all astonished about the big space, too much pavilions and the beautiful environment. Nevertheless, after we found big pavilions such as the USA, Canada, Australia, the UK, Japan, Arab and China had a number of people waiting in front of the pavilions. My two friends—Carol and Alice, who visited with me, decided to visit some of the small pavilions like Cuba, Chile and Columbia, which had fewer people waiting. 
<br /><br />Then we joined the waiting line in front of Switzerland pavilion because we three were all attracted by the beautiful cable car on the top of the pavilion. After waiting for more than two hours, we entered that pavilion and enjoyed the grand views of the EXPO Park on the cable car. In the afternoon, we felt a little bit tired, so we sat on the bench and chatted for some time. At about 7 o’clock at night, we met at the park gate and took the coach to Nanjing. 
<br /><br />I love this trip so much, and I think it was quite interesting, excited and meaningful. Going on a trip with my friends, classmates and teachers gave me a free feeling that I have not felt it before, and I became more independent during this trip. I spent a happy time with my classmates and teachers and I hope I can have more experience like this.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c2cd196a285310135ca52584c210cb24" url=""><![CDATA[Gr. 11 Religious Service<br/><br/>On July 14th, 2010, Carol and I went to the Christianity Chapel on Mochou Road. In China, many people believe in the Buddhism, and not too many people know well about Christianity. So I chose a Christianity Chapel to know more about the Christianity. 
<br /><br />Before, I just saw the Christianity Chapel on the TV, so it was my first time to see the real Christianity Chapel, and I felt a little bit excited. We met at the gate at about 7:30a.m. When I came into this chapel, I saw many benches were in a good order. The roof, with the beautiful patterns, was quite tall and grand. There was a small cross in the front of the chapel. 
<br /><br />At that time, there were about ten old people knelt on the ground and prayed in front of the cross. One of the old women said some words and other people repeated that. They were praying for a four-year-old boy who was ill for some months and nearly to die. Those old people looked quite sad, and one of women even cried. Carol and I sat on the bench, and showed sympathy for them. 
<br /><br />For us, this was a different experience because we knew a sad story about a little boy. But I still like this experience. Before, I thought most of the old people in China should believe in the Buddhism because Buddhism has a longer history in China but I was wrong. The people who believe in the Buddhism are also many old people. I saw the real Christianity Chapel, and I also know more about the Christianity, so I like this experience.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="17a0c6139399e7595bc06a84ebd16ec9" url=""><![CDATA[Gr. 11 Act in a performance<br/><br/>On December 23rd, my classmates and I acted in a play in the school Christmas Show. This experience still gave me lots of new feelings although it was not my first time on the stage and in front of all the whole school. 
<br /><br />The play was written by Gina, and almost everyone in my class joined the show. It showed several small stories of love when Christmas coming, including in the flower shop, restaurant and the train station. I sang a Christmas song with other eight classmates at the end of the play, and showed love by free hugs. Although each story was really simple, I can still feel the warmness among people at Christmas. 
<br /><br />Throughout this acting, I could easily felt a big change to me --- I was not nervous at all during the show. I will never forget the Christmas Show last year. Last year, I sang Yesterday Once More with my classmates. I remember my face got really, really hot during the song, and I found there was no emotion on my face at all on the video. I even made a mistake on the song. This time, however, I just felt like sing a song in front of my good friends, and I even slimed on the stage. Even I cannot believe this is the truth. 
<br /><br />The biggest thing I learned during the show was confidence. Before, I did not think it is an easy thing to learn because I think my heart control my whole body, feelings and action, but I got it from the show. I really need more practice like this to make me more confident.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c9ecca34c175d21b1de62b2d0b3159c1" url=""><![CDATA[Gr. 11 Go to an Exhibition (1)<br/><br/>On October 6, 2010, I went to the old Jiangsu Provincial Art Museum which is on Changjiang Road with my parents to see an exhibition named Liuhe Artworks of Farmers. All the artworks in this exhibition are drawn by the farmers in Liuhe, a small town seat near Nanjing, and the theme of the exhibition is about the Youth Olympics and the Shanghai EXPO. The “artists” usually do not have good drawing skills, and some of the art work even seemed silly to us. However, I still went to this exhibition for the common “artists”. 
<br /><br />Lots of artwork gave me the impressive feeling. One of the artworks, with a name of Olympics in China, let me think of something. On the Olympic Logo artwork, there is a big heart with Tiananmen Square and Beijing National Stadium in the middle and on the top. Around the middle heart, there are some farmers, scientific instruments, new buildings and some dancing people. 
<br /><br />The drawing so very simple that even a little child can know the meaning of this artwork maybe because the artist is a farmer. In my opinion, however, I think it is unusual, and we can learn lots of thing from it. The meaning of this artwork is very easy to understand --- the Tiananmen Square and Beijing National Stadium represent the capital city Beijing which is the heart of China, and the other stuffs represent the countryside. The Olympics will be held in China, and that make farmers or the people in the countryside very happy and excited, and I am sure they are also pound of China. Because of the Olympics, the crops have a great growth rate. Also in their eyes, our country is developing so fast, including the scientific technologies and the living conditions of the people both live in city and countryside. They use the crops to represent their happiness. I can really felt their native mind. 
<br /><br />Another artwork I love has a name of Happiness. On the artwork, there is a smiling old woman with lots of chicken or darks around her. I really love the smile on the old woman’s face, with no stress and complain. I always think of our lives. The people who live in the city have different kinds of scientific technologies making us out of stress and have fun. Also that makes our lives easier in some ways. Lots of people think the environment in the countryside makes then crazy, and they think countryside is a place showing their low class levels. In my opinion, however, countryside is the native land must have a happier live rather than city. 
<br /><br />I really like this exhibition although the artwork is a kind of “silly” in our mind, and the environment in the old museum was not very good. It remains me of the real live. Lots of people think live is always terrible, but if our mind become simple without too much vanity, I am sure the live in our minds will become better.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bcfaf1cfea1a4327d8807591896efff2" url=""><![CDATA[Gr. 11 Go to an Exhibition (2)<br/><br/>On October 7, 2010, I went to the new Jiangsu Provincial Art Museum which is on DongJiandao Road with my parents to see an exhibition named Two “Shi” in North and South. The name is hard for the people who are not Chinese to understand. This exhibition showed the artworks which was drawn by Fu Baoshi and Qi Baishi. This two artists was very famous in China even now although they passed away long time ago. Their artworks were all Chinese traditional artwork drawn by Chinese brush. The exhibition named “Two ‘Shi’ in North and South “for they both has “Shi” in their Chinese names and one of them is from northern China and other is from southern China. I chose this exhibition, for those two artists are so famous in China and their drawing styles are different and special. 
<br /><br />Fu BaoShi was born in 1904 in Qing Dynasty, and he was good at drawing landscape paintings, especially in mountains and water. One of my favorite artworks drawn by him was named “A! Changbai Mountain”. If I watched it several meters away, I could feel the luxuriant leaves of the forest. However, if I watched it closely, I had another feeling, which was that the trunk of the trees was all very strong. 
<br /><br />Although, Fu BaoShi was so popular at that time, I do not really like his artwork. I think his artworks are all landscape paintings, and they are so boring. Now, we can take a photo if we want the view instead of draw by hand, and the photo will have a much higher clarity. I know he was a big artist at that time, but I just do not like his “boring” artworks. 
<br /><br />Unlike Fu BaoShi, the drawing by another artist Qi BaiShi was much more interesting. Qi BaiShi was born in 1864, and he was good at drawing small insects, plants, etc. Anyways, his drawings are super simple of the common thing we see in our lives. One of my favorite artworks was named Dragonfly. That artwork was just like the name, and there was only a dragonfly on the sheet. There was really nothing else on it. It may seem strange, but it is the style of Qi BaiShi’s artworks. Once his drawing has a theme, the “theme” will be on the sheet, and there is just the “theme” on it. This is Qi BaiShi. 
<br /><br />Maybe some people will think Qi BaiShi’s drawings cannot show his talent, but I do not think so. Although his drawings are really simple, I still think that simpler the drawings are the more interests I will find. Some other themes like plantain and loquat even made me laugh at that time, just because they were so simple.
<br /><br />I really like this experience to see this exhibition. Well, although the drawings by Fu Baoshi made me a little bit boring, I still found interests about Qi BaiShi’s drawings. Also, it is really important to know those two artists as I am a Chinese because they were so popular at their time. Knowing their drawings is a good way for me to know more about Chinese culture. I really enjoyed it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7aed55cbbdd77bfe8539f114f60bb1d9" url=""><![CDATA[Gr.11 Volunteer experience (1)<br/><br/>This year, I did several types of volunteer work. During the summer holiday, I helped in the Phoenix International Book Mall, which is located in Hunan Road, with Carol and my junior high schoolmate for 9 hours. Fortunately, the air-conditioning in the book mall worked very well so that we had a quite comfortable working environment although it was hot outside in August. 
<br /><br />I did several works in the book mall during my volunteer experience. Firstly, there was a recitation competition in the book mall, and I was respond to be the reception personnel to the parents and children who wanted to sign up their names to join the competition. I wore the trademark in front of my crest, and sat near the elevator waiting the parents and children come to me. My responsibility was to answer the questions they had and gave them the number card with the date, which the children will perform, on it. After, the manager let me give some phone calls to the children’s parents to make sure the date. 
<br /><br />When I did those work, I found both interesting and nervous, although the work was very easy to do. When my friends and I sat beside the desk, a little boy came to us and said he wants to enroll. I said we need some of his information, maybe he did not know some of the information, so he stood in front me with no word, and he just looked at me. The boy was so lovely, and I did not know what I should say. Then his mother came to us and tells the information to us. After I gave the number card to him, he was so excited. However, I face some problems when I gave the phone call. Some parents had the good attitude when I ask the date, but some parents answer me irritably, and that really made me nervous. 
<br /><br />After helping to organize the recitation competition, the manger gave me a new work --- checked whether the solicit articles were effective or not in a solicit articles competition. The solicit articles, written by the students from primary and secondary school with different levels, whether had the name, school and contact information on it so that the articles can be effective. 
<br /><br />When I check the articles, I have a look of some articles, and I could find the certainly difference between the students from different levels. Some words used by primary students seemed silly to me, but I could feel their native mind as the people like me just let the paragraphs to be a hard task to finish. Maybe because of the exams, they will become rigid. At least at this time, they can write their true mind even I lots of silly words. 
<br /><br />I felt something different during this volunteer experience. During this volunteer experience, I always worked “with” children or their parents. I felt the importance of communication. To be good reception personnel, I should answer the question in an appropriate tone, and sometime, I need to be patient to the parents. The same thing when I gave the phone call to parents. For me, this experience was interesting which I never tried before, and I really enjoy it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="841e3bd19f47377d00ccabf4fee8e7cc" url=""><![CDATA[Gr.11 Volunteer experience (2)<br/><br/>This year, I did several types of volunteer work. After the summer holiday, I did the volunteer work for GCA teachers, including 4 extra hours from last year (7.5 hours) and helped in a Magazine Department in a company (15 hours). For me, it was a unforgettable experience, and I saw lots of thing which I never seen before. 
<br /><br />I did 4 extra hours volunteer work last year with Carol and Alice for Ms. Bartell making envelopes, coloring the certificate for the people who got first place in the film contest and marking the Digrassi Junior High quiz on Fridays. We are not in the same class any more in Grade. 11, so for me, it was a meaningful memory. We had a great time with Ms. Bartell --- my Planning teacher at that time. I learnt the skill to make envelopes by using the old calendars. 
<br /><br />This year, I did 2.5-hour-volunteer work for Mr. Davis before the school started, and 1-hour- volunteer work for Ms. Bartell after class. I helped Mr. Davis tear the answer keys of the vocabulary book for Grade. 10s, and then carried them to Mr. Fyfe’s office in Building E. I remembered that it was so hot that day, and after carrying the book, we were so tired. Even Carol helped us to carry the book. After, Mr. Davis gave us some candies. I also helped Ms. Bartell --- the previous Planning teacher --- clean her new office in Building E. We worked together finishing cleaning the horrible big table there. 
<br /><br />Also, I did the volunteer work in Guodian Nanjing Company Magazine Department for 15 hours. This Magazine Department is responded to collect the news of the company, organize the news into the company newspapers and of course, print the newspaper to let clerks know the news. Because I did not get the practice or work experience for this kind of job, the manger just let me check the newspaper on computer, print the newspaper and do the helper of other clerks. Although it sounded easy, I still needed to be patient; otherwise, I will get board very soon. I needed to check the dates, names, titles and the type of the magazine. The first I printed the newspapers, I let it a wrong order, so that newspaper was not effective, and of course, I need to redo the work. 
<br /><br />I found that during the work, especially the work I do not familiar with, I need the communication with the manger or the people who are familiar with this work. I also need to be patient listening the advice other people give us. Only if we do so, the result can have the possibility to be perfect or almost perfect. 
<br /><br />Unlike last year, this year, I tried more kinds of volunteer work, and I think that let me see more, and know more about a job. Those are all importance experience to me, and next year, I want to try more different kinds of volunteer work.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2d24511c7381e168bc01c732743eb15" url=""><![CDATA[Gr.11 School Club / Organization<br/><br/>This year, I organized my own club with other two friends --- Hiking Club (15 hours), and at the same time, a joined DIY Club as well (2.5 hours). Organizing my own club let me have another feeling about the club activity, and by joining DIY Club, I found that I am really interested in doing some little stuffs by my hands. 
<br /><br />Our Hiking Club organized four activities on four Saturdays in total to Purple Mountain and Mr. Harris also joined us for several times. I still remember the first time we climb the mountain with a little danger. At that time, we went by the small “roads” among lots of trees instead of the large road people usually walk by. Those “roads” were actually solid which walked by people for thousands of times, and created the “roads”. They were a little bit dangerous; once we kept climbing, there were really hard to come back because it had a big slope. However, it was excited for climbers, and it was the shortcut to the top of the mountain. During the trip, we were too tired to keep walking by the small road, but we even could not recognize the location of the large road. We took a rest together, and then figure out the direction together. That really took a really long time. When we face some “hard” road, we helped together, and finally we reached the top of the mountain. The trip was more like a venture. 
<br /><br />Sometimes, we felt climbing made people too tired, so we walk slowly to a lake, and walked around the big lake. At that time, the weather was just suitable, and we did not feel cold or hot. During the walk, we saw about five couples taking their wedding photos around the lake or under the trees. They all wore pretty white wedding veil, and they made the view of the lake more beautiful. 
<br /><br />Joining the activity in Hiking Club made me have a special feeling because I am the leader for every activity. First of all, I must make sure the safety of each member during the way to Purple Mountain and the way back home and during the trip because hiking may become dangerous in some ways. Also, I need to come up lots of new ideas to make each activity interesting; otherwise, they will not be a member of Hiking Club any more. I felt there were more responsibilities for me, and some mistakes must not happen during the activity, like the safety problems. After these activities, I realize the responsibilities for a leader, and it also helped me to improve the ability of organization. At the same time, I did lots of exercises during the hiking, and it was really good for my body as there are not many chances for me to do exercises at the usual time. 
<br /><br />I am also a member of DIY Club, and I took part in the painting-mask-activity. Gina and I responded for each half of the mask. Finally, we painted in totally two different styles for one mask, and the mask looked like a mixture of two cultures. DIY Club helped me find the ability for Art, and I really enjoyed myself during painting the mask. 
<br /><br />I really had fun in lots of clubs this year, and I was quite pound of that to be a leader, I organized the successful activities. I am looking forward the clubs next year.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7fec22b09bdda36f32cfd959b9abc27d" url=""><![CDATA[Gr.11 Cultural Awareness-Turkish<br/><br/>On October 30th, 2010, I went to a Turkish restaurant called Istanbul on Shanghai Road with Ann, Carol and Gina. I chose this restaurant, for I have never eaten Turkish food before and this restaurant is the only Turkish restaurant in Nanjing which owned by Turkish people. 
<br /><br />The restaurant is on the first floor of a residential flat. Actually, the owner changed the house into a restaurant. I ordered the entrée called Adana Kebap with some rice, salad and bread. It is actually a kind of roast meat. There are also some cakes to allow putting the meat into it and eating together. I want to say my entrée in this restaurant was too salty, and my friends also had the same feeling. So when the cakes were not enough, we drank a lot of water. In some ways, however, the food in this restaurant is different from the food we eat. For example, the rice in this restaurant is green. It is just like to eat vegetables, and it has lots of nutrient in it I think. 
<br /><br />The environment and the atmosphere there is just OK. The space is not very large, and there are not too much tables. When I first went into the restaurant, I saw several black people sitting in the back side of the restaurant talking in a kind of langrage I did not hear before. Maybe they are the owner or the owner’s friends, but they made us a little bit afraid. Other customers were all Chinese. The waiters were friendly, and the service was good with the unfamiliar Chinese. 
<br /><br />In my opinion, the food in this restaurant is not very tasty, and they are so salty. I think the food is just OK. So I may not recommend it to my friends.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9a6f02c5e6d51341d15b33fa90c6e062" url=""><![CDATA[Gr.11 Cultural Awareness-Henry's House<br/><br/>On May 2nd, 2010, I went to an American restaurant called Henry’s House in Hexi with my mother. Before I went there, one of my friends recommended this restaurant to me, and I heard it many times before, so I chose Henry’s House. 
<br /><br />My mother and I both ordered the set meal with bread, soup, salad, dinner and cake. Within every food, there were several choices, and I chose the creamy corn soup, chicken salad, beef and Tiramisu. Well, many people went this restaurant for more than one time, and maybe they think the food in Henry’s House is good. In my opinion, however, I do not think it is as tasty as other restaurant. The bread was so hard with lots of bread scrap. The soup was just OK. The beef should be good, but it tastes a little bit bitter and too hardened. The beef which near the bone had the smell of seafood and finally the Tiramisu was not very sweet, which was my favorite. Anyways, there were not special of the food in this restaurant. Also, this American restaurant even has the pizza and Spaghetti. So I do not very like this restaurant. 
<br /><br />The façade of the restaurant is not very big, and the word Henry’s House is much smaller and others. After entering the door and walking further, I found this restaurant is much bigger than I think. The atmosphere of the restaurant is really good. There were many small exquisite lanterns with dark yellow light. The people in the restaurant were all Chinese. But the service was not very good, and the waiter ever did the wrong math. 
<br /><br />I do not think I will recommend Henry’s House to others, for the no-special-food and the overall feeling of this restaurant.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ce75fdc76278e98105d035d7648dddf4" url=""><![CDATA[Gr.11 Physical Activity<br/><br/>Last year, I rode a bike to school and back to home every day for 50 hours, and then played badminton in Nanjing Olympic Centre during the summer holiday for 30 hours. This year, I still rode a bike to school and back home every day (52 hours) until the winter because it was so cold in winter. Also, I did exercise by using the physical instrument in front of my house every weekend started from February 26th, 2011 (30 hours). 
<br /><br />Actually, doing exercise by riding a bike to school is a really good way for us, especially for the people who do not have the habit that do some exercise regally , just like me. Also, I don’t have much time to do some sports because I should study every day, and sometimes I have a lot of work to do. I think ride a bicycle to school is a good way to help us to do some sports, it will not take us too much time. Another important reason I like to ride a bicycle to school is that there is always too much traffic on Beijing East Road every morning. It will help me to save time if I ride a bicycle. For me, there are many benefits to ride a bicycle. 
<br /><br />In the winter, because of the cold weather, I no longer ride a bike to school. Instead, I kept on doing exercise by using the physical instrument in front of my house every weekend. I found that is also a good way to exercise myself. There are some physical instruments in front of my house, and those physical instruments are so common in Nanjing since some time ago. Every Saturday and Sunday, I will spend about 3 hours total doing exercise by using those physical instruments. Different kinds of instruments that exercise different parts of our body give me some choices of doing the exercise. 
<br /><br />Sometimes, when I do the exercise in the morning, I can see some old men or old women using those physical instruments as well. They usually did it slowly, but the goal was reached. Sometimes, I even talked to them. One of the old women said she do exercise every day in the early morning. She does not have work, so doing some exercise can make their healthier. Her daughter was also very happy to see her mother doing exercise every day. 
<br /><br />What I was thinking was that, more and more old people like to do exercise in the early morning. Even the elderly can kept exercising themselves, why our students cannot do this. Yes, we have lots of tasks to finish. But, I think we should learn their spirits, and one we have the time, or we are too stressful, we can do the exercise. 
<br /><br />Those exercise really helped me a lot, and they really make my body become healthier. Now, my body is healthier than before. I think it is very necessary for me to do some sports every day, and I will keep on doing those sports to keep fit, and I will also encourage my parents to do some sports.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>