<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="21">
		<document id="e679aed81c1a2111052ea68d7456f658" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital eco management /CCEM<br/><br/>http://www.zimbio.com/Business+News/articles/YPrSyUpazjO/crown+capital+eco+management+CCEMCrown Capital Eco Management works with government bodies, international entities, private sectors and other non-governmental organizations in providing extensive information to the public, media and policymakers that are involved in addressing environmental issues and sustainable initiatives in a worldwide scaleCrown Capital Eco Management works with government bodies, international entities, private sectors and other non-governmental organizations in providing extensive information to the public, media and policymakers that are involved in addressing environmental issues and sustainable initiatives in a worldwide scale.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="739cbdd0843121ffdba9414328a02c22" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital eco management, CCEM - About US<br/><br/>http://www.slideboom.com/presentations/624540/crown-capital-eco-managementFeaturing an authoritative source of legislation across the world that deals with environment preservation through promulgating policies on sanctions, regulations, authorizations and restrictions on natural resources.Crown Capital Eco Management works with government bodies, international entities, private sectors and other non-governmental organizations in providing extensive information to the public, media and policymakers that are involved in addressing environmental issues and sustainable initiatives in a worldwide scale.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9665579ae77304088e2a9b39d54738b1" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital eco management, CCEM: About Us<br/><br/>http://www.wellsphere.com/stress-management-article/crown-capital-eco-management-ccem-about-us/1757938Although Crown Capital Management cooperates with various organizations, we maintain our being an independent body, free from control of any particular government, state or institution and unimpaired by their own respective interests.With emerging renewable energy alternatives today, it is highly important that they be given enough attention even early on their developmental stages.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2673e55a81648ab340f44b166f22c4e" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital eco management, CCEM - About US<br/><br/>http://groups.drupal.org/node/260608With emerging renewable energy alternatives today, it is highly important that they be given enough attention even early on their developmental stages. Such technologies might not be ready for commercial uses yet but their potential should be amply tested and funded. Society's modern lifestyle is in serious need of energy that can be generated and consumed and yet, not compromise the future state for generations to come; to have no anxiety that it would cause damage to the environment.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="36c1679b03b8c01d92392610bb5c0827" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital eco management /CCEM<br/><br/>http://www.wellsphere.com/happiness-article/crown-capital-eco-management-ccem/1757955Environmental monitoring details the activities and procedures involved in ascertaining the condition of a particular environment. This, in turn, will be used in preparing or supporting environmental impact evaluations, where potential detrimental effects of human activities on nature will be calculated. The conclusions drawn from the monitoring programs are reviewed and analyzed before publishing.Public AwarenessEducating and enlisting the public to secure and maintain the quality of our natural resources is one of our priorities. We believe that by having well-informed and knowledgeable people, especially in the government sector will make it possible to maximize the benefit of existing legislation, and creating more, in order to preserve our environment.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5aeb69095882e0053936f2628fcd8e10" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management: CCM<br/><br/>http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xu6goe_crown-capital-management_newsEnvironmental monitoring details the activities and procedures involved in ascertaining the condition of a particular environment. This, in turn, will be used in preparing or supporting environmental impact evaluations, where potential detrimental effects of human activities on nature will be calculated. The conclusions drawn from the monitoring programs are reviewed and analyzed before publishing.Public AwarenessEducating and enlisting the public to secure and maintain the quality of our natural resources is one of our priorities. We believe that by having well-informed and knowledgeable people, especially in the government sector will make it possible to maximize the benefit of existing legislation, and creating more
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="83037f94095bbaa04032fbbd70251ecf" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management - The just haj<br/><br/>https://www.quora.com/Diana-Gibbs/crown-capital-management/crown-capital-management-The-just-hajThe 2008 law on haj management gives the government the task and responsibility for sending Indonesian Muslims on the annual pilgrimage to Mecca on the principles of “justice, professionalism, accountability and nonprofit operations”. It may be worth asking how the government fares as this year’s haj operation — a major undertaking of sending some 211,000 Indonesians over to Saudi Arabia — gets under way this week.Going on haj is the fifth pillar of Islam and is mandatory for all physically and financially able Muslims at least once in their lifetime. Now that the waiting list to go on the haj has grown longer — in some provinces it means a wait of 10 years or more — it is time that the government clean up its act once and for all.The rise in the nation’s general prosperity means that more Muslims in Indonesia can now afford the official fee, which has been set at Rp 34 million (US$3,500). Banks, in the meantime, have become creative in making it possible for people to register for the pilgrimage, by taking out a loan to pay for the Rp 25 million down payment, and making payments while waiting for their turn. In the meantime, Indonesia can only send so many people each year, limited by the quota set by the Saudi government in proportion to the number of Muslims. As the country with the largest Muslim population, Indonesia sends the largest delegation of any country every year. Logistics, particularly the availability of flights and accommodation on the ground, further limits how many pilgrims Indonesia can send.Since this is a religious undertaking, all would-be pilgrims will likely be content to wait 10 years or even longer for their turn. If they have to make a huge down payment now — whether out of their savings or from a loan — that too would not matter. Nobody quibbles about the haj fee, although surely there are ways to achieve greater efficiency and savings.However, the government fails the justice tests on two counts:First, it earns an enormous sum from the interest (dare we say usury of the deposits that would-be pilgrims have paid. The pilgrims earn nothing for their money, even if it sits with the government for the next 10 years or so. As is practiced today, they have to pay up the remaining fee, adjusted each year taking into account changes in airfares, exchange rates and other factors, at least six months before departure. This year, this comes to an additional Rp 9 million for each pilgrim.Second, the government every year “sells” a part of the haj quota to private operators to organize haj trips on a commercial basis.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="75c8eff123d7d986545d768c8fcebad8" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management Headlines: The just haj<br/><br/>http://crowncapitalmanagement.bravesites.com/entries/business/crown-capital-management-news-the-just-hajThe 2008 law on haj management gives the government the task and responsibility for sending Indonesian Muslims on the annual pilgrimage to Mecca on the principles of “justice, professionalism, accountability and nonprofit operations”. It may be worth asking how the government fares as this year’s haj operation — a major undertaking of sending some 211,000 Indonesians over to Saudi Arabia — gets under way this week.Going on haj is the fifth pillar of Islam and is mandatory for all physically and financially able Muslims at least once in their lifetime. Now that the waiting list to go on the haj has grown longer — in some provinces it means a wait of 10 years or more — it is time that the government clean up its act once and for all.The rise in the nation’s general prosperity means that more Muslims in Indonesia can now afford the official fee, which has been set at Rp 34 million (US$3,500). Banks, in the meantime, have become creative in making it possible for people to register for the pilgrimage, by taking out a loan to pay for the Rp 25 million down payment, and making payments while waiting for their turn. In the meantime, Indonesia can only send so many people each year, limited by the quota set by the Saudi government in proportion to the number of Muslims. As the country with the largest Muslim population, Indonesia sends the largest delegation of any country every year. Logistics, particularly the availability of flights and accommodation on the ground, further limits how many pilgrims Indonesia can send.Since this is a religious undertaking, all would-be pilgrims will likely be content to wait 10 years or even longer for their turn. If they have to make a huge down payment now — whether out of their savings or from a loan — that too would not matter. Nobody quibbles about the haj fee, although surely there are ways to achieve greater efficiency and savings.However, the government fails the justice tests on two counts:First, it earns an enormous sum from the interest (dare we say usury of the deposits that would-be pilgrims have paid. The pilgrims earn nothing for their money, even if it sits with the government for the next 10 years or so. As is practiced today, they have to pay up the remaining fee, adjusted each year taking into account changes in airfares, exchange rates and other factors, at least six months before departure. This year, this comes to an additional Rp 9 million for each pilgrim.Second, the government every year “sells” a part of the haj quota to private operators to organize haj trips on a commercial basis.This year, about 17,000 Indonesian pilgrims are able to circumvent the long line by paying more than double the official price through these government-sanctioned private operators. It may not sound much, but it is still a gross violation of the principles of justice and nonprofit operations stated in the 2008 law. Besides, since when does access to the House of God depend on the color of your money? This is nothing short of a deplorable financial scam in the name of God.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6d059a27b9e6e97bb1bd33db6e35249a" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management news - The just haj<br/><br/>http://crowncapitalmanagement.bravesites.com/entries/business/crown-capital-management-headlines-the-just-hajThe 2008 law on haj management gives the government the task and responsibility for sending Indonesian Muslims on the annual pilgrimage to Mecca on the principles of “justice, professionalism, accountability and nonprofit operations”. It may be worth asking how the government fares as this year’s haj operation — a major undertaking of sending some 211,000 Indonesians over to Saudi Arabia — gets under way this week.Going on haj is the fifth pillar of Islam and is mandatory for all physically and financially able Muslims at least once in their lifetime. Now that the waiting list to go on the haj has grown longer — in some provinces it means a wait of 10 years or more — it is time that the government clean up its act once and for all.The rise in the nation’s general prosperity means that more Muslims in Indonesia can now afford the official fee, which has been set at Rp 34 million (US$3,500). Banks, in the meantime, have become creative in making it possible for people to register for the pilgrimage, by taking out a loan to pay for the Rp 25 million down payment, and making payments while waiting for their turn.In the meantime, Indonesia can only send so many people each year, limited by the quota set by the Saudi government in proportion to the number of Muslims. As the country with the largest Muslim population, Indonesia sends the largest delegation of any country every year. Logistics, particularly the availability of flights and accommodation on the ground, further limits how many pilgrims Indonesia can send.Since this is a religious undertaking, all would-be pilgrims will likely be content to wait 10 years or even longer for their turn. If they have to make a huge down payment now — whether out of their savings or from a loan — that too would not matter. Nobody quibbles about the haj fee, although surely there are ways to achieve greater efficiency and savings.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b87318e781f74654b95e62a44f5e83a2" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management news: The just haj<br/><br/>http://open.salon.com/blog/dianagibbs/2012/10/15/crown_capital_management_news_the_just_hajThe 2008 law on haj management gives the government the task and responsibility for sending Indonesian Muslims on the annual pilgrimage to Mecca on the principles of “justice, professionalism, accountability and nonprofit operations”. It may be worth asking how the government fares as this year’s haj operation — a major undertaking of sending some 211,000 Indonesians over to Saudi Arabia — gets under way this week.Going on haj is the fifth pillar of Islam and is mandatory for all physically and financially able Muslims at least once in their lifetime. Now that the waiting list to go on the haj has grown longer — in some provinces it means a wait of 10 years or more — it is time that the government clean up its act once and for all.The rise in the nation’s general prosperity means that more Muslims in Indonesia can now afford the official fee, which has been set at Rp 34 million (US$3,500). Banks, in the meantime, have become creative in making it possible for people to register for the pilgrimage, by taking out a loan to pay for the Rp 25 million down payment, and making payments while waiting for their turn.In the meantime, Indonesia can only send so many people each year, limited by the quota set by the Saudi government in proportion to the number of Muslims. As the country with the largest Muslim population, Indonesia sends the largest delegation of any country every year. Logistics, particularly the availability of flights and accommodation on the ground, further limits how many pilgrims Indonesia can send.Since this is a religious undertaking, all would-be pilgrims will likely be content to wait 10 years or even longer for their turn. If they have to make a huge down payment now — whether out of their savings or from a loan — that too would not matter. Nobody quibbles about the haj fee, although surely there are ways to achieve greater efficiency and savings.However, the government fails the justice tests on two counts:First, it earns an enormous sum from the interest (dare we say usury of the deposits that would-be pilgrims have paid. The pilgrims earn nothing for their money, even if it sits with the government for the next 10 years or so. As is practiced today, they have to pay up the remaining fee, adjusted each year taking into account changes in airfares, exchange rates and other factors, at least six months before departure. This year, this comes to an additional Rp 9 million for each pilgrim.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f5bf6159fd44a88e613aac48a327594f" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management news, The just haj<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.getjealous.com%2Fcrowncapital%2Fjournal%2F2733057%2Fcrown-capital-management-headlines-the-j.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.getjealous.com/crowncapital/journal/2733057/crown-capital-management-headlines-the-j.html</a>
<br /><br />The 2008 law on haj management gives the government the task and responsibility for sending Indonesian Muslims on the annual pilgrimage to Mecca on the principles of “justice, professionalism, accountability and nonprofit operations”.  It may be worth asking how the government fares as this year’s haj operation — a major undertaking of sending some 211,000 Indonesians over to Saudi Arabia — gets under way this week. 
<br /><br />Going on haj is the fifth pillar of Islam and is mandatory for all physically and financially able Muslims at least once in their lifetime. Now that the waiting list to go on the haj has grown longer — in some provinces it means a wait of 10 years or more — it is time that the government clean up its act once and for all.
<br /><br />The rise in the nation’s general prosperity means that more Muslims in Indonesia can now afford the official fee, which has been set at Rp 34 million (US$3,500). Banks, in the meantime, have become creative in making it possible for people to register for the pilgrimage, by taking out a loan to pay for the Rp 25 million down payment, and making payments while waiting for their turn. 
<br /><br />In the meantime, Indonesia can only send so many people each year, limited by the quota set by the Saudi government in proportion to the number of Muslims. As the country with the largest Muslim population, Indonesia sends the largest delegation of any country every year. Logistics, particularly the availability of flights and accommodation on the ground, further limits how many pilgrims Indonesia can send.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7d3d7ffa11cff4c99eb8370cc80970d8" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management _ The just haj<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailymotion.com%2Fvideo%2Fxu6goe_crown-capital-management_news"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xu6goe_crown-capital-management_news</a>
<br /><br />It may be worth asking how the government fares as this year’s haj operation — a major undertaking of sending some 211,000 Indonesians over to Saudi Arabia — gets under way this week. 
<br /><br />Going on haj is the fifth pillar of Islam and is mandatory for all physically and financially able Muslims at least once in their lifetime. Now that the waiting list to go on the haj has grown longer — in some provinces it means a wait of 10 years or more — it is time that the government clean up its act once and for all.
<br /><br />The rise in the nation’s general prosperity means that more Muslims in Indonesia can now afford the official fee, which has been set at Rp 34 million (US$3,500). Banks, in the meantime, have become creative in making it possible for people to register for the pilgrimage, by taking out a loan to pay for the Rp 25 million down payment, and making payments while waiting for their turn. 
<br /><br />In the meantime, Indonesia can only send so many people each year, limited by the quota set by the Saudi government in proportion to the number of Muslims. As the country with the largest Muslim population, Indonesia sends the largest delegation of any country every year. Logistics, particularly the availability of flights and accommodation on the ground, further limits how many pilgrims Indonesia can send. 
<br /><br />Since this is a religious undertaking, all would-be pilgrims will likely be content to wait 10 years or even longer for their turn. If they have to make a huge down payment now — whether out of their savings or from a loan — that too would not matter. Nobody quibbles about the haj fee, although surely there are ways to achieve greater efficiency and savings.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f24b49c8b51a31d11aaf8553abc3c1b5" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management Headlines_The just haj<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fopen.salon.com%2Fblog%2Fdianagibbs%2F2012%2F10%2F15%2Fcrown_capital_management_headlines_the_just_haj_1"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://open.salon.com/blog/dianagibbs/2012/10/15/crown_capital_management_headlines_the_just_haj_1</a>
<br /><br />The 2008 law on haj management gives the government the task and responsibility for sending Indonesian Muslims on the annual pilgrimage to Mecca on the principles of “justice, professionalism, accountability and nonprofit operations”.  It may be worth asking how the government fares as this year’s haj operation — a major undertaking of sending some 211,000 Indonesians over to Saudi Arabia — gets under way this week. 
<br /><br />Going on haj is the fifth pillar of Islam and is mandatory for all physically and financially able Muslims at least once in their lifetime. Now that the waiting list to go on the haj has grown longer — in some provinces it means a wait of 10 years or more — it is time that the government clean up its act once and for all.
<br /><br />The rise in the nation’s general prosperity means that more Muslims in Indonesia can now afford the official fee, which has been set at Rp 34 million (US$3,500). Banks, in the meantime, have become creative in making it possible for people to register for the pilgrimage, by taking out a loan to pay for the Rp 25 million down payment, and making payments while waiting for their turn. 
<br /><br />In the meantime, Indonesia can only send so many people each year, limited by the quota set by the Saudi government in proportion to the number of Muslims. As the country with the largest Muslim population, Indonesia sends the largest delegation of any country every year. Logistics, particularly the availability of flights and accommodation on the ground, further limits how many pilgrims Indonesia can send.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2942a96d8fd2d1054572aa992b319341" url=""><![CDATA[Crown capital, CCM news - Indonesians clash with police outs<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wellsphere.com%2Fhealthcare-industry-policy-article%2Fcrown-capital-ccem-headlines-indonesians-clash-with-police-outside-u-s-embassy%2F1760729"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.wellsphere.com/healthcare-industry-policy-article/crown-capital-ccem-headlines-indonesians-clash-with-police-outside-u-s-embassy/1760729</a>
<br /><br />JAKARTA, Indonesia — Indonesians enraged over an anti-Islam film hurled rocks and Molotov cocktails at the U.S. Embassy in Jakarta on Monday, in the first violence in the world’s most populous Muslim country since outrage exploded last week in the Middle East and beyond.
<br /><br />Eleven police officers were hospitalized after being pelted with rocks and attacked with bamboo sticks, said Jakarta police chief Maj. Gen. Untung Rajab. Four protesters were arrested and at least one hospitalized.
<br /><br />Protesters burned a picture of President Barack Obama, who spent part of his childhood living here. They also tried to torch a fire engine parked outside the embassy, ripping a hose from the vehicle and igniting it, which sent plumes of black smoke billowing skyward.
<br /><br />Molotov cocktails exploded against a fence surrounding the compound as police used a bullhorn to call for calm and deployed water cannons and tear gas to try to disperse the crowd.
<br /><br />“We will destroy America like this flag,” a protester screamed while burning a U.S. flag. “We will chase away the American ambassador from the country.”
<br /><br />The demonstration started peacefully as several hundred protesters from the Islamic People’s Forum and the Front of Islamic Defenders, many dressed in white, marched toward the diplomatic mission. The protesters paused to observe afternoon prayers about 100 meters (yards) outside the embassy, then resumed the rally. They threw rocks at riot police, who used shields to push the crowd back.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="351e70f1a4c415319c692f3619b01bed" url=""><![CDATA[Crown capital, CCEM headlines: Indonesians clash with police<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcrowncapitalmanagement.bravesites.com%2Fentries%2Fbusiness%2Fcrown-capital-ccm-news-indonesians-clash-with-police-outside-u-s-embassy"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://crowncapitalmanagement.bravesites.com/entries/business/crown-capital-ccm-news-indonesians-clash-with-police-outside-u-s-embassy</a>
<br /><br />JAKARTA, Indonesia — Indonesians enraged over an anti-Islam film hurled rocks and Molotov cocktails at the U.S. Embassy in Jakarta on Monday, in the first violence in the world’s most populous Muslim country since outrage exploded last week in the Middle East and beyond.
<br /><br />Eleven police officers were hospitalized after being pelted with rocks and attacked with bamboo sticks, said Jakarta police chief Maj. Gen. Untung Rajab. Four protesters were arrested and at least one hospitalized.
<br /><br />Protesters burned a picture of President Barack Obama, who spent part of his childhood living here. They also tried to torch a fire engine parked outside the embassy, ripping a hose from the vehicle and igniting it, which sent plumes of black smoke billowing skyward.
<br /><br />Molotov cocktails exploded against a fence surrounding the compound as police used a bullhorn to call for calm and deployed water cannons and tear gas to try to disperse the crowd.
<br /><br />“We will destroy America like this flag,” a protester screamed while burning a U.S. flag. “We will chase away the American ambassador from the country.”
<br /><br />The demonstration started peacefully as several hundred protesters from the Islamic People’s Forum and the Front of Islamic Defenders, many dressed in white, marched toward the diplomatic mission. The protesters paused to observe afternoon prayers about 100 meters (yards) outside the embassy, then resumed the rally. They threw rocks at riot police, who used shields to push the crowd back.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d8e06ef6805b0272348db05d51b69e51" url=""><![CDATA[crown capital management Jakarta news, Debate: Romney slams<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcrowncapitalmanagement.bravesites.com%2Fentries%2Fbusiness%2Fcrown-capital-eco-management-jakarta-news-debate-romney-slams-obama"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://crowncapitalmanagement.bravesites.com/entries/business/crown-capital-eco-management-jakarta-news-debate-romney-slams-obama</a>
<br /><br />During Wednesday night’s presidential debate between President Barack Obama and Republican contender Mitt Romney, Obama accused Romney and the GOP of destructive attacks on the Environmental Protection Agency rules and regulations. Obama stated that curtailing these regulations would “gut crucial public health protections.” In reply, Romney pointed out how Obama uses the EPA to bypass both houses of the U.S. Congress.
<br /><br />Obama also accused Romney of opposing EPA regulations that provide Americans with clean air and clean water. But Romney claims he opposes the Obama/EPA green agenda and its negative impact on American taxpayers and its policy of “outsourcing” U.S. funds to foreign governments’ green programs. Romney lamented the fact that the Obama agenda is implemented by fiat rather than being passed by both houses of the U.S. Congress.
<br /><br />“People in the coal industry feel like they are being crushed by your policies,” Romney said to Obama. Romney also criticized what’s become known as “crony capitalism” by which the Obama administration picks winners and losers in their pursuit of government funding and contracts.
<br /><br />There are some who believe an investigation — perhaps a criminal investigation — may be in order since much of this financial activity is done without Congressional oversight and without examination of the people involved in these transactions, said former white-collar crime investigator George Lestieri, now a corporate security consultant.
<br /><br />“This is a lot of money switching hands and no one even bothered to vet these recipients,” said Lestieri.
<br /><br />For example, Obama EPA administrator, Lisa Jackson, who launched an enormously expensive program to make America’s minority communities green, has sent millions of taxpayer dollars to environmental causes in nations overseas, including China, Russia and India.
<br /><br />These foreign nations were experiencing economic growth while millions of Americans suffered from joblessness, losing their homes due to foreclosures, and watching their health care being transformed into another government entitlement program, according to political activist Joshua Tallis.
<br /><br />“Ranking members of the U.S. Congress Energy Committee called the program “foreign handouts” amid record deficits, soaring unemployment and a looming debt ceiling in the U.S. The money — $27 million since 2009 — has been issued by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), which is headed by Ms. Jackson,” Tallis said.
<br /><br />“It’s a sad situation made sadder by the fact the news media — always looking out for Obama’s best interests — are ignoring this story. If it wasn’t for a public-interest legal group, Judicial Watch, who knows if we’d ever find out about this giveaway before the November election,” said Tallis.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b345e8e6400233742146fcc3468aeeb6" url=""><![CDATA[Crown Capital Management Legal, CCM<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcrowncapitalmangt.blog.com%2F2012%2F10%2F23%2Fcrown-capital-management-legal-ccm%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://crowncapitalmangt.blog.com/2012/10/23/crown-capital-management-legal-ccm/</a>
<br /><br />Acceptance of Terms
<br /><br />By the act of opening an account, the Client is considered to have accepted all of the terms and conditions contained in this section and/or upon the ‘Account Opening Form’.
<br /><br />Account Opening Form
<br />Crown Capital Management ‘Account Opening Form’ contains all of the terms and conditions with respect to the operation of an account in the applicants name (our Client). This account may be used for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO, restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds.
<br /><br />Cash Account
<br />Crown Capital Management will manage a cash account for our client and act as our clients broker for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO or restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds. Which purchases and sales may be based on either verbal or written instructions from our Client.
<br /><br />Currency of Trade
<br />Tardes may be executed on any of the major exchanges and the currency of trade will be that of the exchange on which the trade is executed. Conversions to our clients currency of choice will be at the best market rate available, Crown Capital Management cannot be held liable for any currency losses which our client may incur.
<br /><br />Rules of the Stock Exchange
<br />All instructions on behalf of our client shall be subject to the rules, regulations, constitution, by-laws and industry practice of the stock exchange and it’s clearing house where such instructions are executed.
<br />Written Correspondence
<br />Execution notes and/or correspondence from Crown Capital Management to our client, by email or hard copy will be considered accepted, unless contested by our client using registered mail or courier, no more than seven business days from our Clients receipt of such correspondence.
<br /><br />Liability
<br />Crown Capital Management and/or it’s directors or officers cannot be held liable for any losses and/ or any manner of damages incurred by our Client as a result of investment advice provided by Crown Capital Management. Crown Capital Management invests heavily in controls to prevent client exposure to external “scams,” — fraudulent, dishonest or unscrupulous practices. Our fraud prevention and research teams review each opportunity to identify irregularities, scams, frauds or otherwise suspect aspects of these investments. Crown Capital Management exhausts every avenue available to minimize risk, but cannot be held liable for broad market trends or shifts in the investment environment.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31a1ae775466054493155c18daca681f" url=""><![CDATA[Crown Capital Management - Legal: CCM<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.videobash.com%2Fvideo_show%2Fcrown-capital-management-legal-wmv-426257"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.videobash.com/video_show/crown-capital-management-legal-wmv-426257</a>
<br /><br />Acceptance of Terms
<br />By the act of opening an account, the Client is considered to have accepted all of the terms and conditions contained in this section and/or upon the ‘Account Opening Form’.
<br /><br />Account Opening Form
<br />Crown Capital Management ‘Account Opening Form’ contains all of the terms and conditions with respect to the operation of an account in the applicants name (our Client). This account may be used for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO, restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds.
<br /><br />Cash Account
<br />Crown Capital Management will manage a cash account for our client and act as our clients broker for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO or restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds. Which purchases and sales may be based on either verbal or written instructions from our Client.
<br /><br />Currency of Trade
<br />Tardes may be executed on any of the major exchanges and the currency of trade will be that of the exchange on which the trade is executed. Conversions to our clients currency of choice will be at the best market rate available, Crown Capital Management cannot be held liable for any currency losses which our client may incur.
<br /><br />Rules of the Stock Exchange
<br />All instructions on behalf of our client shall be subject to the rules, regulations, constitution, by-laws and industry practice of the stock exchange and it’s clearing house where such instructions are executed.
<br /><br />Written Correspondence
<br />Execution notes and/or correspondence from Crown Capital Management to our client, by email or hard copy will be considered accepted, unless contested by our client using registered mail or courier, no more than seven business days from our Clients receipt of such correspondence.
<br /><br />Liability
<br />Crown Capital Management and/or it’s directors or officers cannot be held liable for any losses and/ or any manner of damages incurred by our Client as a result of investment advice provided by Crown Capital Management. Crown Capital Management invests heavily in controls to prevent client exposure to external “scams,” — fraudulent, dishonest or unscrupulous practices. Our fraud prevention and research teams review each opportunity to identify irregularities, scams, frauds or otherwise suspect aspects of these investments. Crown Capital Management exhausts every avenue available to minimize risk, but cannot be held liable for broad market trends or shifts in the investment environment.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f76a655492e6f6a172c23f91f06b4836" url=""><![CDATA[Crown Capital Management: Legal<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wellsphere.com%2Fhealthcare-industry-policy-article%2Fcrown-capital-management-legal%2F1767215"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.wellsphere.com/healthcare-industry-policy-article/crown-capital-management-legal/1767215</a>
<br /><br />By the act of opening an account, the Client is considered to have accepted all of the terms and conditions contained in this section and/or upon the ‘Account Opening Form’.
<br /><br />Account Opening Form
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management ‘Account Opening Form’ contains all of the terms and conditions with respect to the operation of an account in the applicants name (our Client). This account may be used for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO, restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds.
<br /><br />Cash Account
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management will manage a cash account for our client and act as our clients broker for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO or restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds. Which purchases and sales may be based on either verbal or written instructions from our Client.
<br /><br />Currency of Trade
<br /><br />Tardes may be executed on any of the major exchanges and the currency of trade will be that of the exchange on which the trade is executed. Conversions to our clients currency of choice will be at the best market rate available, Crown Capital Management cannot be held liable for any currency losses which our client may incur.
<br /><br />Rules of the Stock Exchange
<br /><br />All instructions on behalf of our client shall be subject to the rules, regulations, constitution, by-laws and industry practice of the stock exchange and it’s clearing house where such instructions are executed.
<br /><br />Written Correspondence
<br />Execution notes and/or correspondence from Crown Capital Management to our client, by email or hard copy will be considered accepted, unless contested by our client using registered mail or courier, no more than seven business days from our Clients receipt of such correspondence.
<br /><br />Liability
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management and/or it’s directors or officers cannot be held liable for any losses and/ or any manner of damages incurred by our Client as a result of investment advice provided by Crown Capital Management. Crown Capital Management invests heavily in controls to prevent client exposure to external “scams,” — fraudulent, dishonest or unscrupulous practices. Our fraud prevention and research teams review each opportunity to identify irregularities, scams, frauds or otherwise suspect aspects of these investments. Crown Capital Management exhausts every avenue available to minimize risk, but cannot be held liable for broad market trends or shifts in the investment environment.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3aec25089ca721858eabf9b25ccd3891" url=""><![CDATA[Crown Capital Management - Legal: CCM<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fopen.salon.com%2Fblog%2Fenchonggo%2F2012%2F10%2F23%2Fcrown_capital_management_legal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://open.salon.com/blog/enchonggo/2012/10/23/crown_capital_management_legal</a>
<br /><br />Acceptance of Terms
<br /><br />By the act of opening an account, the Client is considered to have accepted all of the terms and conditions contained in this section and/or upon the ‘Account Opening Form’.
<br /><br />Account Opening Form
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management ‘Account Opening Form’ contains all of the terms and conditions with respect to the operation of an account in the applicants name (our Client). This account may be used for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO, restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds.
<br /><br />Cash Account
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management will manage a cash account for our client and act as our clients broker for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO or restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds. Which purchases and sales may be based on either verbal or written instructions from our Client.
<br /><br />Currency of Trade
<br /><br />Tardes may be executed on any of the major exchanges and the currency of trade will be that of the exchange on which the trade is executed. Conversions to our clients currency of choice will be at the best market rate available, Crown Capital Management cannot be held liable for any currency losses which our client may incur.
<br /><br />Rules of the Stock Exchange
<br /><br />All instructions on behalf of our client shall be subject to the rules, regulations, constitution, by-laws and industry practice of the stock exchange and it’s clearing house where such instructions are executed.
<br /><br />Written Correspondence
<br />Execution notes and/or correspondence from Crown Capital Management to our client, by email or hard copy will be considered accepted, unless contested by our client using registered mail or courier, no more than seven business days from our Clients receipt of such correspondence.
<br /><br />Liability
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management and/or it’s directors or officers cannot be held liable for any losses and/ or any manner of damages incurred by our Client as a result of investment advice provided by Crown Capital Management. Crown Capital Management invests heavily in controls to prevent client exposure to external “scams,” — fraudulent, dishonest or unscrupulous practices. Our fraud prevention and research teams review each opportunity to identify irregularities, scams, frauds or otherwise suspect aspects of these investments. Crown Capital Management exhausts every avenue available to minimize risk, but cannot be held liable for broad market trends or shifts in the investment environment.
<br /><br />Termination
<br /><br />Our Clients trading account may be terminated at any time by either Crown Capital Management or our Client. Crown Capital Management are obliged to deliver to the Client all proceeds of any sales made on a best efforts basis, or the applicable share certificates.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="47ff0676cf76e9253d2b7015943537d2" url=""><![CDATA[Crown Capital Management Legal: CCM<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.videobash.com%2Fvideo_show%2Fcrown-capital-management-legal-wmv-426257"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.videobash.com/video_show/crown-capital-management-legal-wmv-426257</a>
<br /><br />Acceptance of Terms
<br /><br />By the act of opening an account, the Client is considered to have accepted all of the terms and conditions contained in this section and/or upon the ‘Account Opening Form’.
<br /><br />Account Opening Form
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management ‘Account Opening Form’ contains all of the terms and conditions with respect to the operation of an account in the applicants name (our Client). This account may be used for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO, restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds.
<br /><br />Cash Account
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management will manage a cash account for our client and act as our clients broker for the purchase and sale of any investment instrument, on all of the major exchanges, including, but not limited to; class A stock, IPO, pre-IPO or restricted stock, other securities, alternative instruments and government bonds. Which purchases and sales may be based on either verbal or written instructions from our Client.
<br /><br />Currency of Trade
<br /><br />Tardes may be executed on any of the major exchanges and the currency of trade will be that of the exchange on which the trade is executed. Conversions to our clients currency of choice will be at the best market rate available, Crown Capital Management cannot be held liable for any currency losses which our client may incur.
<br /><br />Rules of the Stock Exchange
<br /><br />All instructions on behalf of our client shall be subject to the rules, regulations, constitution, by-laws and industry practice of the stock exchange and it’s clearing house where such instructions are executed.
<br /><br />Written Correspondence
<br />Execution notes and/or correspondence from Crown Capital Management to our client, by email or hard copy will be considered accepted, unless contested by our client using registered mail or courier, no more than seven business days from our Clients receipt of such correspondence.
<br /><br />Liability
<br /><br />Crown Capital Management and/or it’s directors or officers cannot be held liable for any losses and/ or any manner of damages incurred by our Client as a result of investment advice provided by Crown Capital Management. Crown Capital Management invests heavily in controls to prevent client exposure to external “scams,” — fraudulent, dishonest or unscrupulous practices. Our fraud prevention and research teams review each opportunity to identify irregularities, scams, frauds or otherwise suspect aspects of these investments. Crown Capital Management exhausts every avenue available to minimize risk, but cannot be held liable for broad market trends or shifts in the investment environment.
<br /><br />Termination
<br /><br />Our Clients trading account may be terminated at any time by either Crown Capital Management or our Client. Crown Capital Management are obliged to deliver to the Client all proceeds of any sales made on a best efforts basis, or the applicable share certificates.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>