<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="17">
		<document id="1a2dd8d8032059cd9ad892417be8f954" url=""><![CDATA[Total Epistane Information.....<br/><br/><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/183800073_9733901_49744426.jpg" />
<br />What is Epistane, what does it do and what products contain it? 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vZXBpc3RhbmUtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Epistane</a> or 2a,3a-epithio17a methyl-17b-hydroxy-5a-androstane or 2a,3a-epithio-17a-methyl-5a-androstan-17b-ol or Epi or Hemaguno, Havoc, IBE, Epi 2A3A. Epistane is an excellent prohormone for lean muscle gain, estrogen blocking and increasing libido. Epistane can be found in products such as (product titles link to product pages): 
<br />How does Epistane increase lean muscle mass? 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vZXBpc3RhbmUtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Epistane</a> also binds to androgen receptors in skeletal muscle cells and muscle stem cells. This leads to changes in muscle cell function and protein synthesis. In the case of muscle stem cells, which will actually change and fuse with your active adult skeletal muscles increasing the muscles potential for growth and repair. On the opposite side, the presence of androgens actually decreases the ability of stem cells to form new fat cells. So now have increased stem cell conversion to muscle cells and decrease the conversion of stem cells to fat cells, giving you more positive effects of nutrition and training. 
<br />What does it mean to Pulse cycle <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vZXBpc3RhbmUtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Epistane</a>? 
<br />Dosage something to intentionally avoid long term sides, such as suppression and liver damage ht PA. Pulses, the serious effects secondary to long-term chronic oral treatment are avoided and short term side effects such as acne and retention of minerals are softer than usual. This allows higher doses to be used. Basically, if you dosed form ED get 100% effect, 100% short term sides and 100% of the shares long term. If the dose EOD on a pulse protocol, you still get about 60% affect, 75% short term sides but only 40% long term sides. That's not a bad deal and very economical on the body and the wallet too! Of course if you would have gained 10 pounds this means that only pulse gain 6 pounds, but it also means that you can do this for 2 or 3 times longer than a normal cycle. That equals about 2 months of worry-free management, so that the net effect is a gain of about 12 pounds instead of 10 pounds more than twice the period of time, with fewer parts and a softer requirement PCT even if it is necessary at all. It's a great long-term strategy and good for new users looking to run fast cycles, clean, for 1 month with no PCT needed later. That's how I perfected it. There are two basic approaches to do it: EOD or 2on/2off according to their exercise program. Doses can be high (30-40mg) but taken together preferably before 6pm (1 dose before and after dose-w / o instead of spread out like normal) or doses can be lower (10 - 20mg) if you want to extend to 2 or 3 months instead of just one. Doses of at least 3 times a week but not more than 4. 
<br /><br />Q. Do I need to add On cycle Liver Support while I am taking Epistane? 
<br />A.  Yes, as Epistane is on the lighter side of liver harshness it is still a prohormone and it will need liver support and care while cycling epistane.  
<br />Q. Do I need to run a Post Cycle Therapy (PCT) after my cycle of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vZXBpc3RhbmUtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Epistane</a>? 
<br />A. Yes, because of the fact that your body will be used to Epistane doing all the work in creating your high test levels; it will be difficult for your body to keep its test levels as high once you stop the epistane. To boost your test levels after you will need a good natural PCT product that will help you keep your gains and repair your organs.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="595d496956e72620789c2e3f5ec612ef" url=""><![CDATA[Total Halodrol Information.....<br/><br/><strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vaGFsb2Ryb2wtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Halodrol</a></strong> exhibits an extremely high anabolic to androgenic ratio translating into hard and consistent muscle gains with No aromatization. These gains are notably extremely lean and dry in nature, making this a favorite for the pre-contest athlete, or as an anabolic addition to many stacks. Mainly used to increase muscle mass most particularly in the abdomen region and will increase muscle endurance and decrease your recovery time after workouts.
<br /><br />Q. What type of results will I see from taking a halodrol product?
<br /><br />A.  Lean Muscle Gains
<br /><br />Hard Muscles Gains
<br /><br />Increased Strength
<br /><br />Increased Vascularity
<br /><br />Q. How long does it take for halodrol to start working?
<br /><br />A. It is common for Halodrol to take a few weeks before seeing results. 
<br /><br />Q. Do I need to take On Cycle Support with <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vaGFsb2Ryb2wtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Halodrol</a>?
<br /><br />A. Yes, with any prohormone you will be effecting your liver as a result liver support/on cycle support will assist your body in dealing with  the harshness of the ph. 
<br /><br />Q. Do I need to run a Post Cycle (PCT) after I take halodrol?
<br /><br />A. Yes, Post Cycle is very important when you run a prohormone. You need post cycle to naturally riase your testosterone levels so that your body maintains most of your muscle gains. 
<br /><br />Q. What type(s) of side effects will I see on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vaGFsb2Ryb2wtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Halodrol</a>?
<br /><br />A. Halodrol produces zero aromatization, as a result you can expect to be free from estrogenic side effects (those due to increases in estrogen estradiol, progesterone or progestin) which generally include increased water retention, body fat gain, and gyno (due to the testosterone to estrogen ratio imbalance). 
<br /><br />Q. There are many halodrol products, which is the best halodrol supplement?
<br /><br />A. For the most part all halodrol products are about the same. What this means is they are the same formula and offer the same mg's per cap. However our preference here is to look at value and reviews. Based on this the best value is Halo-V by Vital Labs. Halo-V offers 80 caps, when most others offer 60. Halo-V also has good reviews as well as great results from forum loggers. Following that our 2nd pick is CEL H-drol, this is solely based on the reviews as CEL H-drol only offers 60 caps. 
<br /><br />Q. What is the chemical breakdown/description of Halodrol?
<br />A.  4-chloro-17a-methyl-androst-1,4-diene-3b,17b-diol
<br /><br />Q. What are other names for Halodrol? 
<br /><br />A. Many people refer to these names as halodrol, which is the main and usually the only ingredient in the following products: Halodrol 50, H-drol, Gaspari halodrol-50, Halo-V, Halovar,H-drol, 4-Chloro, Halo-test and halostane. 
<br /><br />Q. I'm looking for a supplement that will give me strength as well as dry gains that will not leave me with the bloated water retention look, is Halodrol right for me?
<br /><br />A. Yes, halodrol provides exactly that, lean, hard, dry gains as well as strength gains. 
<br /><br />Q. Is Halodrol safe to take if I am a beginner or I have only ran a 1-2 cycles in the past?
<br /><br />A. Yes, Halodrol is 1 step up from Epistane, which is a go to for most first timers. Many people either choose halodrol as their 2nd cycle or some choose it as their first if they think that they can handle more.
<br /><object width="336" height="295"><param name="movie" value="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4703389"></param><param name="wmode" value="window"></param><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"></param><embed src="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4703389" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowFullScreen="true" wmode="window" width="336" height="295"></embed></object>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3d01842b60d0da572606e264de193bd1" url=""><![CDATA[Total Superdrol Information.....<br/><br/><strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vc3VwZXJkcm9sLWluZm8v" target="_blank"><span style="text-decoration:underline">Superdrol Info</span></a></strong>
<br /><br />What Should I eat while taking superdrol?
<br /><br />Superdrol is the ideal product for gaining size and strength. This prohormone does best in a high caloric environment, one very high in carbohydrates. While Superdrol is a great bulking prohormone, one can easily use this product and put on little or no fat. This would require some manipulation of diet high in proteins and carbohydrates and plenty of essential fatty acids. It is also important that your carbohydrates are mostly complex carbs. Since the glycogen storage is dramatically higher while on this prohormone, the intake of complex carbohydrates should be high to both assist in gains and reduce potential lethargy and possible hypoglycaemia. It is important to have higher than normal caloric intake yet Superdrol does not protect against fat gains so it is important to slowly increase calories during start of your cycle vs sudden increase.
<br /><br />What other supplements are recommended while taking <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vc3VwZXJkcm9sLWluZm8v" target="_blank">Superdrol</a>?
<br /><br />Superdrol can put a very high level of stress on your liver during its use. The most common supplement taken by users of methylated prohormones is milk thistle and NAC. To lower blood pressure Hawthorne berry can be used. Although not common, If experiencing decrease in libido from taking superdrol users will supplement with Tribulus Terrestrials.
<br /><br />Common nutritional mistake reason why some users are not responding to superdrol:
<br /><br />Superdrol will not work if your lipid profile is out of whack. Many users underestimate the simple directions of eating heavy and eating right. It is important to be taking in 1.7-2g of pretein/lb of body weight. By week 3 of a cycle of superdrol a user should being seeing gains of 1lb per day.
<br /><br />How do I keep my gains from Superdrol?
<br /><br />First off it is important to take a good post cycle. You may lose a little bloat size from water retention. Many users report good results from taking creatine and nitrous compounds found in pre-workouts to keep gains. 
<br /><br />What is <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vc3VwZXJkcm9sLWluZm8v" target="_blank">Superdrol</a>, what does it do and what products contain it?
<br /><br />Superdrol or 2a-17a-di-methyl-etiocholan-3-one,17b-ol, also known as SD or Power Drol, is a prohormone that is good for adding bulk, muscle and strength to ones body. Users will see gains in the density of their muscle mass. Some people believe that superdrol is one of the strongest compounds available today. It is also heavily used in stacking formulas as a compliment to other prohormones like Halodrol and Max LMG.
<br /><br />The reason why superdrol is so popular is because of its inability for aromatisation to estrogen. To much estrogen in the body can create unwanted side effects.
<br /><br />Superdrol is highly anabolic, generally 400%-800% more anabolic then methyl-test. Because of how anabolic it is superdrol promotes high levels of protein synthesis and serious muscle mass gains.
<br /><br />Superdrol is a very strong prohormone and as a result can weigh heavy on the liver. As a result of this users need to up their water intake significantly. They also need to sleep a full cycle at night and increase their caloric intake. This means their diet needs to increase in quality complex carbs, high quality efa's and proteins.
<br /><br />Average cycle time 4-6 weeks.
<br /><br />Post Cycle highly recommended.
<br /><br />Here are some of the best selling <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vc3VwZXJkcm9sLWluZm8v" target="_blank">Superdrol Prohormones</a>:
<br /><br />Powerdrol-10 by Vital Labs 120CT
<br /><br />SD-PLEX 90 by Muscle Competition Labs
<br /><br />SD by Evolve
<br /><br />M-Drol by CEL
<br /><br />M-Stane by Dynamic Formulas
<br /><br />SD-10 By LGI
<br /><br />Supernova S2 by Galaxy Supplements
<br /><br />Super bolin by Myo pharma
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8c30dd186c36764b19decfe0663b0092" url=""><![CDATA[Bulking prohormones......<br/><br/>The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vYnVsa2luZy1wcm9ob3Jtb25lcy8_" target="_blank">Best Prohormone Supplements</a> for adding mass and bulking. 
<br /><br />Looking to bulk up? Read below:
<br /><br />Simply put start by eating more and training heavier so you can gain muscle weight. You could be hard gainer, an athlete looking to get into a new weight class, or simply desire a larger physique.
<br /><br />In order to gain quality mass, the nutrients intake has to be of a high quality in nature. The best way to gain weight is through a planned and controlled increase in macronutrient intake. By ensuring that the quality of the nutrients is high (such as low glycemic index carbohydrates, high quality fats and low fat proteins) muscle weight gain is accomplished and fat weight is reduced. 
<br /><br />Bulking cycles can be tricky when it comes to your diet. The diet needs to be done in a certain way otherwise; you end up gaining way too much body fat. Thus having a surplus in weight, which will eventually need to be reduced. There are some tricks that can be followed to optimize muscle gains and add the proper amount of mass to reach your desired goal. 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vYnVsa2luZy1wcm9ob3Jtb25lcy8_" target="_blank">Bulking</a> up does not consist of eating everything you can get your hands on and lifting as heavy as possible hoping that all of the increased weight gain will come in the form of muscles. This lack of a plan strategy will lead to an excess of fat gain.
<br /><br />Most of the weight that you will gain will be in the form of muscle, however some of it will be in the form of fat. The reason for this is that when you have a caloric surplus (your body has a higher caloric intake then it can use) some of those calories are stored as body fat. However, to optimize your bulking cycle, eat good foods, train hard and by starting from a low percentage of body fat, you will minimize the fat gains and maximize the muscle mass gain. 
<br /><br />Its best to increase your protein intake to 1.5 grams of protein per pound body weight, so if you weigh 200lbs, then you need to eat around 300 grams of protein per day. Some people feel lethargic if they eat more than 40 grams of protein in at once and have issues with digestion. Therefore, you can divide 300 by 40 and that will give you the amount of meals that you need to eat per day. SO to continue with the 200-lb bodybuilder he will need to eat, 7-8 meals per day spaced out with a minimum of 90 minutes in between each meal and a maximum of 3 hours. Protein sources should come from lean low fat meals including chicken, turkey, 93% lean red meats, egg whites, shrimp, tuna, tilapia, and salmon.
<br /><br />Now that your diet and work out regimen are in place correctly you can add a serious <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vYnVsa2luZy1wcm9ob3Jtb25lcy8_" target="_blank">supplement</a> that will take your body to an incredible place. It is not unusual to see gains of 10-25lbs from these supplements. Take your time and review the product descriptions, customer reviews and supplement facts.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8937428e47dd368e2769efccf2d2b351" url=""><![CDATA[Cutting Prohormones...........<br/><br/>The best prohormone supplements for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vY3V0dGluZy1wcm9ob3Jtb25lcy8_" target="_blank">cutting down</a>, leaning out and adding lean hard muscle gains. We recommend adding a On Cycle Support with the prohormone you choose. Also to retain and maximize your lean gains follow your cycle with a good Post Cycle Therapy (PCT). 
<br /><br />Need to get Cut and Shred Fat? Read Below:
<br /><br />A great way to get lean is to increase your body’s muscle mass. The more mass on your body, the easier it is to burn calories and create a calorie deficit, which forces your body to use the fat it has previously stored.
<br /><br />Body fat likes to aromatase, as a result the more over-weight you are and the more fat you have stored the more estrogen your body will convert from the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vY3V0dGluZy1wcm9ob3Jtb25lcy8_" target="_blank">prohrmone</a>use.
<br /><br />Estrogen and your body fat have a, good for them, bad for you, working relationship. We need to disrupt this relationship and make both of them move out of our space; the area where we keep our shredded muscle and veins. The best-looking muscles do not have fat and water retention over them. We want veins, and a sharp division between muscle groups, defined abs and lean hard muscle mass.
<br /><br />Now we can look at your diet. Without a good diet (and an reduction in calories), you will not lose weight at an optimal rate. For best results when running a cutting cycle one must eat minimal carbs. This however is not an easy task so many people diet 5 days of no carbohydrates followed by 2 days of free eating). As a result you will reduce your calories to 90% of your Basal Metabolic Rate. This may seem high on the calorie scale, but the cardiovascular exercise you’ll be doing will increase amount of calories you burn.
<br /><br />Cardiovascular exercise is a must for optimizing your cutting cycle. Cardio is something that creates a healthier life style and is a major factor in overall heart health. Prohormone users should pay extra attention to their heart’s health than the average man should. Testosterone is cholesterol after all. Do your cardio in the morning and on an empty stomach, you can also box, swim or play a sport or run.  Research has showed swimming, cross-country skiing, and cross training to be some of the best cardiovascular exercises.
<br /><br />Once your diet and cardio are in the right position, the next step is choosing the right <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vY3V0dGluZy1wcm9ob3Jtb25lcy8_" target="_blank">supplements</a>, after all that why you are here. Taking everything to a new place! There are many supplements you can choose from here. Take your time and review the descriptions, customer reviews and supplement facts to aid you in making the right choice. If you have further questions you can chat with us or email us. Now Make it Happen!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5370a3fd713d8617de188a937f9859cb" url=""><![CDATA[Weight loss Info.......<br/><br/>[b]<span style="text-decoration:underline"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2VpZ2h0LWxvc3MtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Weight loss Info</a>[</span>/b]
<br /><br />Not Sure which fat burner or diet pill is best for you?
<br /><br />There are many types of fat burners and diet pills available in todays market. A person needs to asses their overall goals, experience, tolerence level and daily regiment to make a decision on which type of fat burner they are best suited for. 
<br /><br />There are different methods that fat burners use to deliver their results. Some fat burners combine the methods below to optimize results. 
<br /><br />1. Appetite Suppressing <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2VpZ2h0LWxvc3MtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Fat Burners</a>
<br /><br />These fat burners aim at reducing your hunger and cutting out snacking and cravings. Good for people who know that they are over eating and sneaking in snacks between meals. This method will support your wieght loss efforts and give you the extra edge you need to ward of temptation. This will also allow for you to focus in on your diet and normalize your appetite levels. 
<br /><br />2. Thermogenic <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2VpZ2h0LWxvc3MtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Fat Burners</a>
<br /><br />Thermo means heat. Thermogenic fat burners work at burning fat by increasing your metabolism. This increases you body's heat production and as a result of this your body stores less fat and burns more calories. 
<br /><br />3. Stimulant Based Fat Burners
<br /><br />Stimulant based fat burners also work at raising your bodies metabolism and can also raise your bodies core temperature. It creates this result by using different stimulants such as caffeine. These types of fat burners are very effective in that the stimulants raise energy levels and raise your bodies calorie burning center. One will also experience a unique mental alertness and a physical energy boost that will aid tremendously in optimizing and intensifying your workout. 
<br /><br />Fat burners and diet pills will optimize a healthy diet and proper exercise regiment. The better the regiment the better results you can except. No fat burner is going to help or be healthy to take if you do not do any exercise with it. Make sure you are working at your goals of weight loss and the fat burner can help you achieve that goals much quicker then you ever thought possible. 
<br /><br />With the stronger fat burners and for beginners it may be good to start with half of the initially recommended dose to see how your body reacts to the fat burner and establish a good tolerance level. This way you can be the judge of your comfort zone and create a winning formula. 
<br /><br />Best Selling Fat Burners:
<br /><br />Black Mamba by Innovative Labs-Stimulant Based &amp; Thermogenic
<br /><br />Diabolic Eca Fire Caps by Innovative Labs-Stimulant Based &amp; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2VpZ2h0LWxvc3MtaW5mby8_" target="_blank">Thermogenic</a>
<br /><br />Asia Black by Cloma Pharma-Stimulant Based &amp; Thermogenic
<br /><br />P57 by Pharma-Stimulant Based, Thermogenic and Appetite Suppressing
<br /><br />Lean 650 by Gen X Labs- Thermogenic and Stimulant Based
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f4f299ef0a268c8a5d87981dad1e2473" url=""><![CDATA[Supplement Stacks......<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vc3VwcGxlbWVudC1zdGFja3Mv" target="_blank">YOUR FIRST SUPPLEMENT STACK</a>
<br />Don’t worry - being considered a first-time supplement user isn’t as demeaning as being considered a redneck. In fact, we’re glad you finally recognized the benefits that supplements provide as you pursue your bodybuilding goals. Allow us to walk you through the basics of supplement science to give you the know-how to build your first stack. You’ll be an expert in no time, armed with the knowledge to create more advanced stacks as you progress in ability and experience. The following seven <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vc3VwcGxlbWVudC1zdGFja3Mv" target="_blank">supplements</a> are all you’ll need to add mass, maintain energy and stay healthy. 
<br /><br />Arginine
<br />Arginine is an amino acid that’s readily converted to nitric oxide (NO) in the body. NO is involved in many physical processes, but the most vital to you is vasodilation, which is the process that increases blood flow to muscles, allowing better delivery of nutrients and oxygen. Arginine can boost growth hormone levels as well. Dose: Take 3-5 grams on an empty stomach in the morning, before workouts and before bed. 
<br /><br />Creatine
<br />We’ll keep it short since you can read everything you need to know about creatine on pages 128-129. Creatine is an amino acid-like supplement that provides the quick energy you need for powerful muscle contractions, such as when lifting weights. It also allows your muscles to hold more water, making them fuller and stronger, which ultimately stimulates additional growth.
<br />Dose: Take 3-5 grams before and after workouts. 
<br /><br />HMB 
<br />One of the best supplements for true beginners is beta-hydroxy-beta-methylbutyrate (HM<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />. It’s a metabolite of leucine, the most essential of the branched-chain amino acids (BCAAs); however, it’s considered to be a more effective form of leucine. Supplementing with HMB prevents muscle breakdown, encourages muscle growth and aids fat-burning processes in the body. Research shows it’s very effective at increasing muscle mass and strength in beginner-level trainees, but it may be less effective in more experienced lifters.
<br />Dose: Take 1-3 grams with food in the morning, before and after workouts, and before bed. 
<br /><br />Whey Protein
<br />If there’s one supplement every bodybuilder needs - regardless of experience - it’s whey protein powder. Taken before and after workouts, this fast-digesting protein provides the amino acids required to build muscle protein at the most critical time for growth. Whey is a good source of the BCAAs leucine, isoleucine and valine. Leucine, a key stimulator of protein synthesis, starts the processes for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vc3VwcGxlbWVudC1zdGFja3Mv" target="_blank">building muscle</a> protein and uses the other aminos as the building blocks for making more. Dose: Take 20 grams before workouts and another 20-40 grams after workouts. 
<br /><br />Glutamine 
<br />Glutamine happens to be one of the most plentiful amino acids found in the human body. Not only is it crucial for recovery and muscle growth, but it also buffers the fatigue-inducing chemicals that form during intense exercise. By delaying fatigue, you can bang out more reps. In addition, glutamine is essential for normal digestion and immune function. Supplementing with it protects your muscles from being broken down for fuel by your body to access the stored glutamine.
<br />Dose: Start with 2-3 grams and work up slowly to 5 grams, taken in the morning, before and after workouts and before bed. 
<br /><br />Multivitamin/Mineral
<br />Whatever your level of training experience, you must take a multivitamin/mineral supplement. It may not sound sexy, but building muscle requires adequate amounts of vitamins and minerals to do the work. Even if you eat a healthful diet, you still need to take a multi because vitamin and mineral contents of many foods have declined significantly due to modern farming practices. In addition, hard training depletes stores of certain vitamins and minerals. Choose one that contains the full spectrum of vitamins and minerals and provides 100% of the daily value (DV) of most of these. 
<br />Dose: Take one dose with food twice a day. You may also want to consider taking some extra B vitamins, such as a B complex, as well as the antioxidant vitamins C and E. The B vitamins are important for proper protein and fat metabolism, while vitamins C and E scavenge free radicals, protecting your muscles and the rest of your body from cellular damage. Try a B complex that provides 50 mg of B1 and B6, and 50 mcg of B12. Take 500-1,000 mg of Vitamin C twice a day, and 400-800 IU of Vitamin E once daily, both with food. 
<br /><br />Fish Oil
<br />Fish oil supplements containing the essential omega-3 fatty acids eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA) and docosahexaenoic acid (DHA) reduce the risk of heart disease and stroke, prevent muscle breakdown, help regenerate and grow muscle, enhance joint tissue rebuilding and encourage fat loss. Eating fatty fish like salmon several times a week may provide all the omega-3s you need, but concerns about the levels of mercury and PCBs (a mixture of individual chemicals found in the environment that are related to several health problems) in fish have caused many people to cut back on their fish intake. The good news is that a recent study found no traces of either in more than 40 brands of fish oil <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vc3VwcGxlbWVudC1zdGFja3Mv" target="_blank">supplements</a>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bbf0a94d36b176c236c90cfa2079cdbf" url=""><![CDATA[Prohormones,,,,<br/><br/>The best <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vcHJvaG9ybW9uZXMv" target="_blank">Prohormone</a> Supplements for adding mass and additionally bulking.  Looking to bulk upwards? Study below:
<br />Just put start by eating more and also training heavier so you can benefit from muscle tissue weight. You could feel hard gainer, a particular athlete looking to get into an unique body weight class, or want a heavier physique. 
<br />To be able to achieve high quality mass, the nutrients intake has to feel of a high quality in nature. The best way to benefit from weight is by way of a planned and additionally controlled increase in macronutrient intake. By ensuring that the high quality of the vitamins is high (including minimal glycemic index carbohydrates, tall high quality fats as well as low fat proteins) muscle mass weight gain is accomplished and fat weight is reduced.  
<br />Bulking cycles can be complicated in relation to your diet. The diet should be done in a certain way otherwise; you end up gaining way too much body fat. Therefore having an excess in weight, that will eventually should be reduced. There are a few tricks that can feel followed to optimize muscle tissue gains and add the proper amount of mass to reach the desired goal.  
<br />Bulking up does not consist of eating everything you are able to get the hands in and also lifting since heavy because possible hoping that all of the increased gaining weight definitely will come within the form of muscles. This lack of a plan approach will cause some kind of unwanted of fat gain. 
<br /><br />A lot of the actual load which you will benefit from is going to be in the form of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vcHJvaG9ybW9uZXMv" target="_blank">muscle tissue</a>, however some of it is within the form of fat. The factor for this might be that when you have a caloric surplus (the body has a higher caloric intake then it can use) some of those calories are really stored as body fat. Unfortunately, to optimize the bulking cycle, eat good ingredients, train frustrating and also by starting from a low percentage of body fat, you are going to reduce the fat gains as well as improve the muscle tissue mass gain. 
<br /><br />Its best to increase your protein consumption to one.5 grams of protein per pound body weight, so should you decide weigh 200lbs, then you need to eat around 300 grms of healthy protein a day. Some individuals feel lethargic if they eat over 40 grams of protein in at when as well as have problems with digestive function. Subsequently, you can easily separate 300 by 40 as well as which will give you the amount of dishes which you need to eat daily. SO to continue with the 200-lb bodybuilder he need to eat, 7-8 dinners everyday spaced away through a minimal of 90 moments in between each dish along with a the highest possible of 3 hours. Protein sources should come from lean low fat dishes such as meat, chicken, 93% lean purple meat, egg whites, shrimp, tuna, tilapia, as well as salmon. 
<br />Today that your particular diet and also work out regimen are really in spot properly you can add a serious supplement that definitely will take the body to an incredible destination. It is not strange to see gains of 10-25lbs from these supplements. Take your own time and additionally review this product explanations, customer ratings and also <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vcHJvaG9ybW9uZXMv" target="_blank">supplement</a> information.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbce164466ffc9644e8f63b868936efa" url=""><![CDATA[Best free download Motion picture legally<br/><br/>Simply since with most things, there is a right way as well as a completely wrong way to download movies from the Internet. To be able to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5maWxtbG91bmdlLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">install movies legally</a>, you must very first become a member of the reputable motion picture install site. The majority of lawful movie install sites will provide some type of free trial version to get you launched. You may find the movies that you would like to see, when you like to see them in the privacy of your own home or office. 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5maWxtbG91bmdlLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">Download Brave flick</a>
<br />One of several best things about obtaining moves legally from the Internet would be that you are not merely lucky enough to install movies to view correct in your computer, however you can furthermore observe downloaded movies on your own compact equipment, like your own iPod or smart phone, or burn the movies onto a DVD to play anywhere. 
<br />With a quick goggle search using the internet, you will find that there is virtually no lack of Film Downloads websites online. Finding the flick download site which is correct for you depends on an amount of factors, like the quality as well as selection of the movies that are available, the price of a subscription and additionally precisely what you receive for your own funds. Several motion picture download websites definitely will need you to pay a month-to-month fee, yet others merely need a one-time provider cost. 
<br />Pay attention whenever you check out film install sites to ensure you understand exactly what you will be buying. The Internet is swamped alongside unlawful bit torrent sites along with other websites which appear to have full-length movies, but alternatively just have clips as well as trailers. It is advisable to acquire a trustworthy film install site that you can trust and additionally stick with it. 
<br />Movies Capital is regarded as the greatest legitimate movie install websites currently online. For one minimal price tag, you may be able to watch the movies rather quickly streaming on your own computer, save them to the frustrating drive to view later or burn to disc and additionally observe on your DVD player. 
<br />Courageous <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5maWxtbG91bmdlLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">movie Install</a> 
<br />You are going to discover a quantity of areas for which you Download Motion picture illegally released as well as bootleg copies of some movies using the internet. You might not mind the danger of costly fines and also jailhouse time, but the high quality of the movies you get may not be worthwhile. Most video clips included on illegal flick download sites are really usually copies which were captured by way of a camcorder in a theater. Frequently online tend to be heads covering the screen, a loud potential clients and canned sound. 
<br />Whenever you signal upwards by way of a trustworthy site like Movies Capital, you receive DVD high quality movies alongside obvious visualize as well as great seem. Do not waste the time trying to save a few of dollars and additionally possibility losing a lot, significantly more. Take the time to browse online till you see a motion picture download web site which provides you high-quality copies of movies. Bid farewell to the days of ready and waiting in line to sit within a crowded theater with individuals talking in their mobile phones, slurping cola and additionally stuffing down popcorn. Now, you can watch the movies you prefer to watch, where and additionally when you like to watch them.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1609c3752c992ad8cd48475245a09bd4" url=""><![CDATA[Hemaguno 60 tablets.......!!<br/><br/>Dietary Supplement. Hematonic &amp; myogenic oral agent. (Many of these statements currently have certainly not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration or even the Japanese Ministry of Wellness. This particular product can be certainly not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or perhaps avoid any condition or alternatively disease.) Formulated within Japan.
<br />Precisely what is:2A, 3A EPITHIO-17A-METHYL-5A-ANDROSTAN-17B-OL
<br />Additionally written as: 2A, 3A-EPITHIO-17A-METHYL-17B-HYDROXY-5A-ADROSTAN 
<br />Its a prohormone or simply designer steroid regardless of what a person prefer. its a legal alternative to be able to AAS (anabolic plus androgenic steroids)
<br />Exactly what is <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VwaXN0YW5lcmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Epistane</a>?
<br />Epistane is regarded as the particular latest designer steroids about the market now, as well as it happens to be gaining attention incredibly suddenly. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VwaXN0YW5lcmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Epistane</a> is a methylated variation of the controlled substance Epitiostanol (2±,3±-Epithio-5±-androstan-17²-ol), which had been built within the 1960?s and chosen as a treatment for breast cancer. Because truly the only area Epitiostanol can be only availabe at this time is with regard to japan, chemists added a methyl group in order to the compound and the final product was a substance presently acknowledged as Epistane. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VwaXN0YW5lcmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Epistane</a> typically is a sulfur containing steroid that is recognized in order to currently have strong and also extended durable anti-estrogenic activity in addition to weak androgenic and mytropic escapades.
<br />Exactly what a person can anticipate?
<br />Since it is made with be anti-estrogenic a person can expect surprisingly dry gains from this particular compound. Epistane has low androgenic with anabolic activity. This meaning that it must be alot more anabolic consequently androgenic. Therefore making sides very minimal in order to non existant from this particular substance. Equally one of several wonderful attributes of this substance is that it does an excellent job with regard to keeping the all-natural suppression of the gonads away. Because it has anti-estrogenic attributes it keeps your own LH degrees elevated and also it really is as well said simultaneously from research and human trial that epistane could have the ability with reduce gyno. This is still a widely debated outcome of epistane however can be actually showing more and also more positive results because it becomes more popular. Despite that consumers usually see dry gains on epistane it does not signify which it would be any insufficient for a bulking cycle. In actual fact it would be beneficial considering it would certainly generate lean gains. Through research it's reported which the majority of consumers who have taken this particular substance currently have gathered anywhere from 5-12 lbs in a 3-5 week cycle. Presently with regard to my opinion epistane would certainly be better inside a cutting cycle in order to keep the actual body dry whilst preserving and in addition potentially add more lean muscles.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="45228744b6592fb3519c9f4974d5fe76" url=""><![CDATA[Halodrol 60 capsules.....!!!!<br/><br/>Halodrol from the advanced formula series of MyoPharma maximizes the actual science of performance enhancement for your fitness. Halodrol, a Halodrol 50 Clone, contains 50 mg of the beloved Halodrol Anabolic Compound! Halodrolwill lead to Huge Gains in Size &amp; Strength without Aromitization! 
<br />  [url=]Halodrol[/url] uses one of many most prevalent and also cutting edge anabolic compounds recognized in the supplement industry: “Halodrol”.
<br />“[url=]Halodrol[/url] has superior intake and bio availability and can be 10 instances more potent compared to standard Halo goods due to our very own added proprietary half lifetime enzymatic conversion accelerator compound. 
<br />With simply just a few cycles of this amazing muscle mass exploding compound, you'll receive huge and a rock hard. 
<br />Quickly receive ripped as well as lean and even transform a physique. 
<br />[url=]HALODROL Benefits[/url]: Effective Massive Pumps Performance Enhancing Longest Acting Half Life Accelerator Using 50mg per serving of this infamous compound, this Halodrol 50 Clone stands alone in very good total gains, muscle mass as well as strength gains. 
<br />    Halodrol presents Huge Gains
<br />    There is No Aromitization alongside Halodrol
<br />    Halodrol can provide massive Size &amp; Strength Gains
<br />    Halodrol typically is “The Particular Halodrol 50 Clone 
<br />Halodrol Supplement Facts:
<br />Serving Size: 1 Capsule Servings Per Container: 60 Amount Per Serving 4-cloro-17a-methyl-androst-1,4 diene-3-17b-diol 50MG. Additional Ingredients: Proprietary half everyday living enzymatic conversion accelerator, Gelatin, Di calcium phosphate plus magnesium stearate. 
<br />Halodrol Recommended Use:
<br />Take 1 capsule a day for the particular initially five days, plus in case essential grow in order to couple capsules for the actual remainder associated with the protocol. never make use of for more than 6 weeks. And in addition then take 2 weeks off cycle as well as you are able to return for another 6 week cycle. 
<br />Halodrol Product Warning:
<br />Do not employ in case beneath age of 18. Do not surpass suggested dosage during 24 hour period.These statements have not been evaluated by the particular Food as well as Drug Administration. This product is actually definitely not intended to be able to diagnose, treat, remedy, or prevent any kind of condition.”
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="56eb22a71e9abda2c055342683209d4f" url=""><![CDATA[Superdrol S2 60 capsules.........!!<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1cGVyZHJvbHJldmlld3MuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Superdrol S-2</a> typically is an anabolic compound with 2 main components, Superdrol (2a,17a-dimethyl-17B-Hydroxy-5a-androstan-3-one) and even creatine Ethyl Esther (CEE). 
<br />  The at first structural compound behind <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1cGVyZHJvbHJldmlld3MuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Superdrol S-2</a> can be 2a,17a-dimethyl-17B-Hydroxy-5a-androstan-3-one. Considering it’s 5a-reduced plus a-ring alkylated, the actual compound may not aromatize into estrogen. This has the particular positive effect of reducing side effects not to mention keeping drinking water retention/bloating to a minimal. In order to provide maximum bio availability throughout the oral form, the substance is actually methylated (the.k.a. 17-alpha alkylated) and therefore can certainly t quite easily be broken down by the actual liver and even therefore intake typically is high, ultimately resulting in greater gains. This compound binds with muscle mass mobile receptor websites and also causes a significant increase with regard to healthy protein synthesis leading to muscle cell growth/hypertrophy! Additionally, it displays anti-catabolic attributes, reducing the actual effects of cortisol, leading with less protein reduction from muscle mass cells. Muscle mass growth is actually induced given that the anabolic effects (protein synthesis) exceed the catabolic effects (cortisol induced healthy protein release from muscle cells) - and anabolic effects dramatically enhanced - this particular means muscle mass growth is a lot greater! Also, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1cGVyZHJvbHJldmlld3MuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Superdrol</a>displays qualities that aid to reduce body-fat while at the same time increasing muscle density and hardness. 
<br />  The actual 2nd structural component of Superdrol S-2 typically is creatine ethyl esther (CEE).  CEE can be a membrane permeable form of creatine that theoretically can enter the actual cells without in order to employ the “typical” creatine transporter molecules. Consumers tend to be reported in order to gain substantial increases within strength and muscle, alongside none of the gastrointestinal discomfort or simply water bloating usually associated with all the monohydrate shape. 
<br />Benefits of Creatine Ethyl Esther: 
<br />  Functions faster not to mention is a bit more efficiently absorbedThis can be likely because the esterification of creatine, CEE, will certainly heighten its lipopholic abilities, and in addition thus esterified creatine will certainly utilize fat more effectively with permeate the mobile wall not to mention exert its effects on cellular function than its unesterified creatine monohydrate counterpart.
<br />    Eliminates the particular infamous “H2O bloat” lookThus typically is probably given that creatine draws H2O into the actual cell (cell volumization), not to mention given that the majority of ingested creatine monohydrate typically is not every one of the absorbed, any kind of unabsorbed creatine usually sit out of doors associated with the target mobile alongside the water. As a result, this can result the particular dreaded “creatine drinking water bloat.” Whereas esterfied creatine can be mentioned in order to pull most of the drinking water into the muscle mobile, thereby creating a harder, more strong appearance of muscularity. 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1cGVyZHJvbHJldmlld3MuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Superdrol S-2 Benefits</a> include: 
<br /><br />Improved cell volumization
<br />    Improved vitality
<br />    Superior Mass and even Strength gains
<br />    No Negative Effects
<br />    Dry lean gains
<br />    Faster muscle healing
<br />    Improved absorption rate
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b4f4ce01047002d429a41658ac276b92" url=""><![CDATA[In which will I attain prohormones....!!<br/><br/>I grasp exactly what it feels such as, searching almost all over Gods green earth for severe <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2hlcmUtY2FuLWktZ2V0LXByb2hvcm1vbmVzLw__" target="_blank">prohormones</a> not to mention getting nowhere. I would definitely constantly ask my neighbors at the actual gym, &quot;where will likely I get prohormones?&quot;. It seemed like I would need to buy them from certain random man who was a friend of a friend and even even consequently who knows much regarding it and additionally what it does and others With regard to today's nose to be able to the grind stone world we will need to get ahead and even with regard to order that would do that some of us want severe supplements, severe prohormones that bring severe results. You as well should be able that would read information regarding the particular different kinds of prohormones for sale to locate out exactly what is the number one prohormone.
<br />  That prohomone will certainly add the actual almost all muscle, mass, strength and others Some of us built <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2hlcmUtY2FuLWktZ2V0LXByb2hvcm1vbmVzLw__" target="_blank"></a> in order to fill which will need.   StrongSupplementShop.com is the ideal spot to be able to purchase prohormones bar none. Some of us currently have an optimal prohormone selection of cutting prohormones, bulking prohormones, prohormone stacks, article cycle, about cycle as well as any alternative bodybuilding associated supplement out there. Some of us are the ideal prohormone web site online these days.  
<br />  We in addition offer the valued clients alongside a lot of information now they can result in the right decision on that prohormone typically is the greatest for them. We have detailed descriptions, videos, critiques not to mention testimonials almost all that could certainly support your needs with regard to choosing the most perfect supplement for the desired objective. Take a look then you can see why we all tend to be termed as the number one muscle building website.  
<br />In which will likely I get prohoromes? <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2hlcmUtY2FuLWktZ2V0LXByb2hvcm1vbmVzLw__" target="_blank"></a>, that's in which.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3bc37266d94429e8489ddb0552d6c8a4" url=""><![CDATA[The magic of Epistane......<br/><br/>Epi 2A3A, being completely non-estrogenic, offers an ideal composition to maximize strength and lean mass gains, with minimal side effects such as lethargy or gyno. Epi 2A3A is anti-estrogenic and produces very dry gains. The Epi 2A3A compound is very anabolic great for producing muscle growth.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VwaXN0YW5lcmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">What is Epistane</a>?
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VwaXN0YW5lcmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Epistane</a> is one of the newest designer steroids on the market today, and it is gaining attention very quickly. Epistane is actually a methylated version of the controlled substance Epitiostanol (2±,3±-Epithio-5±-androstan-17²-ol), which was created in the 1960?s and used as a treatment for breast cancer. Since the only place Epitiostanol is only available at this time is in japan, chemists added a methyl group to the compound and the final product was a substance now known as Epistane. Epistane is a sulfur containing steroid which is known to have strong and long lasting anti-estrogenic activity as well as weak androgenic and my tropic activities.
<br /><br />What you can expect?
<br /><br />Since it is designed to be anti-estrogenic you can expect very dry gains from this compound. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VwaXN0YW5lcmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Epistane</a> has low androgenic to anabolic activity. This meaning that it is much more anabolic then androgenic. Thus making sides very minimal to non existant from this substance. Also one of the great properties of this substance is that it does a great job in keeping the natural suppression of the gonads away. Since it has anti-estrogenic properties it keeps your LH levels elevated and it is also said both through science and human trial that epistane may have the ability to reduce gyno. This is still a widely debated outcome of epistane but is actually showing more and more positive results as it becomes more popular. Even though users will see dry gains on epistane it does not mean that it would be any insufficient for a bulking cycle. In fact it would be beneficial because it would generate lean gains. Through research it is reported that most users who have taken this substance have gained anywhere from 5-12 lbs in a 3-5 week cycle. Now in my opinion epistane would be better in a cutting cycle to keep the body dry while preserving and potentially add more lean muscle tissue.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8b9d037e4b8e022e53bf1682cca1087f" url=""><![CDATA[The magic of Halodrol......<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hhbG9kcm9scmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">H-Drol</a> is the ultimate repartitioning compound designed for individuals looking to achieve the most noticeable and visible gains in strength and size in the shortest period of time possible.
<br /><br />Don’t be fooled by the “new age” unreal halodrol that delivers no where near the results as the original. The new so called halodrol products use a propitiatory blend of “<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hhbG9kcm9scmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Halodrol</a>” by name only and not by ingredient product.
<br /><br />The body-composition changes seen with the use of H-Drol are dry and lean because the active ingredient in H-Drol does not aromatize to any type of estrogen. This translates into actual strength and muscle gains without the æpuffiness’ of water retention.
<br /><br />Along with excellent reports of muscle size and density, strength, and endurance, H-Drol users typically experience positive effects on energy levels, lipolysis, and libido as well.
<br /><br />Note that due to above points, H-Drol can be used for either a bulking or cutting cycle.
<br /><br />H-Drol is one of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hhbG9kcm9scmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank">strongest strength</a> and muscle building supplements available on the market today. Just two capsules per day (or in some cases, less than that) is all that most people report using in order to get them on the path towards the jaw dropping results that you deserve and crave.
<br /><br />Halo test-25 by Power-lab Nutrition will give you the size and strength gains you didn't think was possible.
<br />With the 25mg per capsule Halo test matrix, Power-lab Nutrition has taken the hassles out of scoring tablets and messing around with pill cutters by providing a dosage that can be controlled more effectively.
<br />Power-lab Nutrition has incorporated ethyl ester technology along with the sustained release formula to give maximum absorption into the bloodstream.If you’re not currently satisfied with how fast your results from training are or maybe you have hit a plateau that you need to break through then you know that if you don’t make a change things aren’t going to be any different in the future.
<br />Clearly, you must do something different – try something new – if you want a different result. A better result.
<br /><br />Warning: Do not use this product if you are at risk for or are being treated for high blood pressure, heart, kidney, thyroid or psychiatric disease, anxiety, depression, seizure disorders, strokes, or any other medical condition. Do not take this product if you are using antidepressants, MAO/MAOI inhibitors or any other prescription drugs. Do not use for more than 30 days without a 90 day break. Not for use in women or in any persons under the age of 21. Keep away from children.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="25d42b348c9cdabdc8ef2493f403316d" url=""><![CDATA[The magic of Superdrol........<br/><br/>This product is extremely powerful and is only for serious athletes and bodybuilders.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1cGVyZHJvbHJldmlld3MuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Powerdrol-10</a> is good for adding bulk, muscle and strength to ones body. Users will see gains in the density of their muscle mass.. The reason why Powerdrol-10 is so amazing is because of its inability for aromatisation to estrogen. To much estrogen in the body can create unwanted side effects.
<br /><br />Powerdrol-10 is highly anabolic, generally 400%-800% more anabolic then methyl-test. Because of how anabolic it is Powerdrol-10 promotes high levels of protein synthesis and serious muscle mass gains.
<br /><br />Powerdrol-10 is a very strong supplement and as a result can weigh heavy on the liver. As a result of this users need to up their water intake significantly. They also need to sleep a full cycle at night and increase their caloric intake. This means their diet needs to increase in quality complex crabs, high quality efa’s and proteins.
<br /><br />The first structural compound behind <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1cGVyZHJvbHJldmlld3MuY29tLw__" target="_blank">SuperNova S-2</a> is 2a,17a-dimethyl-17B-Hydroxy-5a-androstan-3-one. Because it’s 5a-reduced and a-ring alkylated, the compound will not aromatize into estrogen. This has the favorable effect of reducing side effects and keeping water retention/bloating to a minimum. To provide maximum bio availability in the oral form, the substance is methylated (a.k.a. 17-alpha alkylated) and thus can’t easily be broken down by the liver and therefore absorption is higher, ultimately resulting in greater gains. This compound binds to muscle cell receptor sites and causes a significant increase in protein synthesis leading to muscle cell growth/hypertrophy! Additionally, it exhibits anti-catabolic properties, reducing the effects of cortisol, leading to less protein loss from muscle cells. Muscle growth is induced because the anabolic effects (protein synthesis) exceed the catabolic effects (cortisol induced protein release from muscle cells) – and anabolic effects dramatically enhanced – this means muscle growth is much greater! Also, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1cGVyZHJvbHJldmlld3MuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Superdrol</a> exhibits properties that help to reduce body-fat while simultaneously increasing muscle density and hardness.
<br /><br />WARNING: Keep out of reach of children. Do not use if you are under 18 years of age, pregnant, nursing, or contemplating pregnancy. If you have any medical conditions or you are currently using prescription medications, consult your physician before using this or any dietary supplements.
<br /><br />CAUTION: Athletes or others that are tested under the International Olympic Committee or similar drug testing organizations may test positive for sports enhancing drugs. All athletes are recommended to check with their program’s rug policy regarding over the counter dietary supplements before using any of these supplements.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="225240890b4759362656b6d0dd0464fd" url=""><![CDATA[The magic of prohormones......<br/><br/><span style="text-decoration:underline"><strong>Where can I get prohormones</strong>??</span>
<br /><br />I know what it feels like, searching all over Gods green earth for serious prohormones and getting nowhere. I would always ask my friends at the gym, &quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2hlcmUtY2FuLWktZ2V0LXByb2hvcm1vbmVzLw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/183800073_15611957_49292944.jpg" /></a>?&quot;. It seemed like I would have to buy them from some random guy who was a friend of a friend and even then who knows much about it and what it does etc..
<br /><br />In todays nose to the grind stone world we need to get ahead and in order to do that we need serious supplements, serious prohormones that bring serious results. We also need to be able to read info about the different types of prohormones available to find out what is the best prohormone, which prohomone will add the most muscle, mass, strength etc.. 
<br /><br />We created <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHJvbmdzdXBwbGVtZW50c2hvcC5jb20vd2hlcmUtY2FuLWktZ2V0LXByb2hvcm1vbmVzLw__" target="_blank"></a> to fill that need. StrongSupplementShop.com is the best place to buy prohormones bar none. We have a best prohormone selection of cutting prohormones, bulking prohormones, prohormone stacks, post cycle, on cycle and any other bodybuilding related supplement out there. We are the best prohormone site on the web today. 
<br /><br />We also provide our clients with a ton of info so they can make the right decision on which prohormone is the best for them. We have detailed descriptions, videos, reviews and testimonials all that can assist you in picking the perfect supplement for your desired goal. Take a look and you will see why we are known as the best bodybuilding site. 
<br />Bulking cycles can be tricky when it comes to your diet. The diet needs to be done in a certain way otherwise; you end up gaining way too much body fat. Thus having a surplus in weight, which will eventually need to be reduced. There are some tricks that can be followed to optimize muscle gains and add the proper amount of mass to reach your desired goal. 
<br /><br />Bulking up does not consist of eating everything you can get your hands on and lifting as heavy as possible hoping that all of the increased weight gain will come in the form of muscles. This lack of a plan strategy will lead to an excess of fat gain.
<br /><br />Most of the weight that you will gain will be in the form of muscle, however some of it will be in the form of fat. The reason for this is that when you have a caloric surplus (your body has a higher caloric intake then it can use) some of those calories are stored as body fat. However, to optimize your bulking cycle, eat good foods, train hard and by starting from a low percentage of body fat, you will minimize the fat gains and maximize the muscle mass gain.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>