<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="11">
		<document id="59363a2651849e3840d460fc7bf2e339" url=""><![CDATA[wait<br/><br/>It's over, I'm leaving, Goodbye now 
<br />Yesterday I was ready to die for you 
<br />Bur now, I don't know... 
<br />Cause you promissed, to love me forever 
<br />And you told me, we'll always be dancing together, 
<br />But now I dance alone, I dance alone 
<br />I dance alone! 
<br /><br />Midnight Train, 
<br />take me away ! 
<br />Midnight Train, 
<br />just find a place for me to stay ! 
<br />Midnight Train, 
<br />I'm leaving just the way I came 
<br />Take me away from all this pain,
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="281b757123cf509dd1906f0878dc9c50" url=""><![CDATA[You never really stop loving someone, you just try to live w<br/><br/>Love…
<br />Love is a deadly sweet poison.
<br />Love is joy, somewhere there… in the chest.
<br />Love is an Angel in a beautiful sculpture. Frozen. 
<br />Or a Devil, but very seductive dressed. 
<br />Love is sleepless nights in a bed of alluring flowers,
<br />Love is the spring inside, with the bittersweet flavors.
<br />Love is the sorrow written in poems by restless authors.
<br />Love is a fabulous drawing of nonexistent colors.
<br />Love is flowers, heat, painless touches of sun,
<br />Eyes closed, warm rain crying over the town,
<br />Love is power, lordship, inescapable domination,
<br />Love is obedience, respect and self-dedication…
<br />Love is a pain for the soul, silent wounds on the heart,
<br />Loud screams from the inside. Prayers. Sins. Love is an art.
<br />Love is freedom, or a prison of all existing feelings,
<br />Love is sometimes slow, sometimes too fast heart beatings.
<br />Love is strange, overcast days. It’s an unbelievable reality,
<br />It’s when you think that dreams are real. Lies. Love is duty,
<br />Memories that last forever, sweet kisses, hugs that in a moment die,
<br />Unspoken words, secret desires, fear and dying butterflies.
<br />Mysterious glances, mysterious gestures, mysterious words,
<br />Mysterious smiles. Unbearable mystery, mystery hurts.
<br />Love unusual creates, but also unusual destroys
<br />Winged destinies, dreams and yesterday’s hopes…
<br />Love is the question without any reasonable answers,
<br />It’s the answer to the questions of incurable dreamers.
<br />Love is when you miss with all your being, but you’re not missed,
<br />When you suffer in silence, remembering when you kissed.
<br />Love is a burning Hell inside the peaceful Heaven,
<br />Love is dark days, bright nights. It’s when you’re fallen.
<br />When you’re lost in a drunken flight, you touch the sky,
<br />When you painfully hit the ground and when you cry.
<br />Love is coldness, no matter how hard you try to warm up,
<br />Love is forgotten happiness in the morning, in a coffee cup.
<br />Love is a game which you don’t know how to play,
<br />Sometimes you win, but usually lose. Love is an unknown way.
<br />Love is a gun to the temple, plumb mixed with blood,
<br />Irreparable mistakes, decision, you give up on being proud.
<br />You won’t forget what you did for love…Will you forget
<br />All the stupid things you did? When you were always upset?
<br />Love is a flower that grows quickly in your inside,
<br />But when the flower is wilting it takes all your pride.
<br />Love is a battle with yourself, when you’re fighting for life.
<br />Love is a bleeding heart that was implanted with a knife.
<br />Love is trembling, crawling under your soft skin,
<br />Stealing your life, your innocence, leaving you with its sin.
<br />Love’s dancing with the Devil, you dare to look him in the eyes,
<br />Believing he’s an Angel, believing in his lies.
<br />You know what is love, no need to write anymore, 
<br />Just look inside you. Whom do you think about after all?
<br />Who made you feel something that you never felt?
<br />Who made you feel happy? Who made you feel sad?
<br />Who did for you something that no one ever did?
<br />Who wiped your tears and kissed gently your eyelid?
<br />If you think of someone after all you read above,
<br />I assure you, that person is your Love…
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d37bd65a12374f871c371ed339a68447" url=""><![CDATA[Is life so it?<br/><br/>.............Triangle......................
<br />Jack loves Jane but Jane loves Joe
<br />But how could she ever let Jack go
<br />It’s obvious everyone can see
<br />The trouble with this trilogy
<br />Hearts don’t come…
<br />In sets of three So what do they do now?
<br />There’s only one way to find out
<br />It’s time to pick your prize and
<br />It better be right, it better be right
<br />This triangle has
<br />To untangle
<br />Got to let it go
<br />This triangle is
<br />Too much to handle
<br />Got to let it go
<br />Jane loves Joe, but Joe’s with Jill
<br />But Jane wants to be with Joe still
<br />It’s bad enough it breaks Jack’s heart
<br />It’s tearing their whole world apart
<br />But how do you stop
<br />When it’s gone so far
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e3280246fcfff4ddeec475d82b0fdc34" url=""><![CDATA[:D<br/><br/>And now you're gonna miss me 
<br />I know your're gonna miss me 
<br />I guarantee you'll miss me cuz you changed the way you kiss me
<br />cuz you changed the way you kiss me
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c8def54f95bd76b60bc3a05007117c1f" url=""><![CDATA[is it love???<br/><br/>Is it love or just a curse?
<br />Do you feel good when I hurt?
<br />I need your heart to open up
<br />If this love's not real then it's just my luck.
<br /><br />Mommy help me, I need your help
<br />This little boy, he took my love
<br />he says these things that make my body 
<br />bump up
<br />and then he runs, leaving me undone and
<br />I don't understand
<br />for sex he said he'd be my man
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fc2dd9e010e0a243b0a5ebb6327f7e33" url=""><![CDATA[Wicked games<br/><br/>Bring your love 
<br />Baby I can bring my shame 
<br />Bring the drugs 
<br />Baby I can bring my pain 
<br />I got my heart right here 
<br />I got my scars right here 
<br />Bring the cups, baby I can bring the drink 
<br />Bring your body, baby I can bring you fame 
<br />That's my muh'fuckin words too 
<br />Just let me muh'fuckin love you 
<br />.......
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6615711163e0faf351e9c746fc6cd76b" url=""><![CDATA[cam asa e in viata :D<br/><br/>Here I am again doing things I said that I wouldn't do
<br />It's 3am and I'm rushing out the door to see you
<br />Waiting all day,but now you wanna call me
<br />Why do you do this to me all the time?
<br /><br />After all the things you put me through, still I come right back
<br />But now I know the truth, I can finally see
<br />You only want me when you're lonely 
<br />If I say I'm gonna leave, that's the only time you want me
<br />Next time you need me there I won't make it
<br />Another late night call I won't take it
<br />Cos now i finally see, you only want me when you're lonely
<br />Only when you're lonely, lonely
<br />Only when you're lonely
<br />Only when you're lonely, lonely
<br />Only when you're lonely
<br /><br />Had me fooled from the start and I quickly gave my heart
<br />Cuz I loved you, loved you
<br />But this is what happens when you're a lonely girl 
<br />with no one to turn you
<br />Now I'm stronger, don't need you any longer
<br />So get off your knees, your words don't mean anything
<br /><br />After all the things you put me through, still I come right back
<br />But now I know the truth, I can finally see
<br />You only want me when you're lonely
<br />If I say I'm gonna leave, that's the only time you want me 
<br />Next time you need me there I won't make it
<br />Another late night call I won't take it
<br />Cuz now I finally see, you only want me when you're lonely
<br /><br />Nothing's ever changing, decisions you can't make it
<br />You just think of yourself and never me at all
<br />If you're with your friends, you just string me along
<br />But I won't allow it anymore, so it's time for me to move on
<br /><br />Cuz I can finally see, you only want me when you're lonely 
<br />If I say I'm gonna leave, that's the only time you want me 
<br />Next time you need me there I won't make it
<br />Another late night call I won't take it
<br />Cos now I finally see, you only want me when you're lonely
<br />Only when you're lonely, lonely
<br />Only when you're lonely
<br />Only when you're lonely, lonely
<br />Only when you're lonely
<br /><br />I can finally see, you only want me when you're lonely 
<br />If I say I'm gonna leave, that's the only time you want me 
<br />Next time you need me there I won't make it
<br />Another late night call I won't take it
<br />Cuz now I fïnally see, you only want me when you're lonely
<br /><br />Versuri de la: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.versuri.ro%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.versuri.ro/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a38ff9541a75264cd147dbd91b0108e" url=""><![CDATA[:(<br/><br/>I've been everywhere, man
<br />Looking for someone
<br />Someone who can please me
<br />Love me all night long
<br />I've been everywhere, man
<br />Looking for you babe
<br />Looking for you babe
<br />Searching for you babe
<br /><br />Where have you been
<br />Cause I never see you out
<br />Are you hiding from me, yeah?
<br />Somewhere in the crowd
<br /><br />Where have you been,
<br />All my life, all my life
<br />Where have you been, all my life
<br />Where have you been, all my life
<br />Where have you been, all my life
<br />Where have you been, all my life
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c3aa4c07cb2e3d0c212df48d6d262c1f" url=""><![CDATA[I’m giving in......<br/><br/>You’re killing me slowly, I’m giving in
<br />You’re crying me out like a violin
<br />Your words are the sweetest poetry
<br />My pleasure and pain, you’re my symphony
<br />You’re killing me slowly
<br />Killing me slowly
<br />My pleasure and pain, my electronic symphony
<br />What you do to me
<br />Hurts so good baby
<br />Can’t you see it’s getting physical
<br />Pushing me around
<br />Messing with my sound
<br />Electronic, fucking classical
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f4d328686efaf879985947140e2e1cdf" url=""><![CDATA[????????????<br/><br/>Yesterday, today, tomorrow
<br />Fade away like frozen photographs.
<br />Remember, forget
<br />The stakes, the ways you take,
<br />The ways you make the moments pass.
<br />For every regret,
<br />I tell a beautiful lie.
<br />And I would die if you find out.
<br />I tell a beautiful lie every time that I
<br />Did not open up my mouth.
<br />All the same, it’s a game,
<br />It’s a play, it’s a war,
<br />It’s a shame that we’re always fighting for.
<br />I don’t mean to cast no blame,
<br />I don’t intend to pretend that 
<br />I could never loved you more.
<br />But in the blink of an eye, 
<br />Everything you ever knew can change
<br />And it’s a beautiful lie if you think 
<br />Everything will always stay the same.
<br /><br />Babe. My babe.
<br />You got a secret – it’s starting to show.
<br />My babe. Sweet babe.
<br />How long can you keep it?
<br />How far would you go?
<br />You tell a beautiful lie.
<br />You tell a beautiful lie.
<br />And it’s going to, it’s going to drive you crazy.
<br /><br />Babe. My babe.
<br />How far would you go, go, go to tell a beautiful...
<br />Yesterday, today, tomorrow
<br />Fade away like frozen photographs
<br />Remember, forget
<br />Forever.
<br /><br />Babe. My babe.
<br />It’s starting to show.
<br />My babe. Sweet babe.
<br />How far would you go, go, go to tell a beautiful...
<br /><br />How far would you go, go, go to tell a beautiful...
<br />Yesterday, today, tomorrow
<br />Fade away like frozen photographs
<br />Remember, forget
<br />Forever.
<br />Yesterday, today, tomorrow
<br />Fade away like frozen photographs
<br />Remember, forget
<br />Forever.
<br />Lie. Lie.
<br />Beautiful lie
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="546df59aeec4d0608859eecdb2d8f3ee" url=""><![CDATA[My obsession..... my fetish<br/><br/>If you want me to listen whisper
<br />If you want me to run just walk
<br />Wrap your name in lace and leather
<br />I can hear you
<br />You don't need to talk
<br /><br />Let us make thousand mistakes
<br />Cause we will never learn
<br /><br />You're my obsession
<br />My fetish,my religion
<br />My confusion,my confession
<br />The one I want tonight
<br />You are my obsession
<br />The question and conclusion
<br />You are,you are,you are
<br />My fetish you are
<br /><br />You can kiss me with your torture
<br />Tie me up to golden chains
<br />Leave me beggin undercover
<br />Wrong or right
<br />It's all a role play
<br /><br />Let us make a thousand mistakes
<br />We will never learn
<br /><br />You're my obsession
<br />My fetish, my religion
<br />My confusion, my confession
<br />The one I want tonight
<br />You're my obsession
<br />The question and conclusion
<br />You are, you are, you are
<br />My fetish you are
<br /><br />Come to me tonight
<br /><br />You're my obsession
<br />My fetish, my religion
<br />My confusion, my confession
<br />The one I want tonight
<br />You're my obsession
<br />The question and conclusion
<br />You are, you are, you are
<br />My fetïsh you are
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>