<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="36003b3e2a7edbab7d4b940f2921469e" url=""><![CDATA[Wheel Center Caps<br/><br/>Your OEM <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTEy" target="_blank">Wheel</a> center caps may get loss after a long time drive or getting old. Then the bolts and screws on your wheel may become conspicuous and influencing the appearance of your vehicle. Wheel center caps are an important part of both the function of your vehicle and the look of your vehicle. The Wheel Center Cap, also known as the hub cap does not just cover those bolts and screws. It changes the outlook of your car. If someone installs a special and stylish cap to a car, then when you see him or her driving down the street, you will absolutely be attracted. It really does change the appearance of the overall of vehicle.
<br /><br />When you are searching the aftermarket wheel caps, please make sure that you know the proper size wheel center cap that your car requires. You can measure your OEM caps for reference. Even among the same manufacturer. (For example, Audi wheel center caps), for different types of car, the cap is different. And you do not want to get the wrong size wheel center cap and have to replace and install all over again. This will waste both you and manufacturers' time. Or you can get the information from the local car dealer or from the manufacturer website if need be. The wheel center cap comes in various colors and different material. For your preference, you can choose the style you love and make your vehicle special, with extraordinary artistic stylish. 
<br /><br />Finding the right wheel center cap style for your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTM0" target="_blank">vehicle</a> will take some searching but can be done in a manner that will completely change your vehicle. But remember it will take your time and cost money.
<br /><br />If you want, now start to do some research and find out what appeals to you. Know what size your car requires for a wheel center cap. Have fun picking out a brand new look for your car by replacing your old wheel center cap. 
<br /><br />You can view more by <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9175dc3283e4fadf5f139d7d92abf6ac" url=""><![CDATA[Attractive Carbon Fiber<br/><br/>People love <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">carbon fiber</a> very much, but most of us don’t have much knowledge about it. It is an extraordinary material, made of automotive grade premium high quality cast UV resistant vinyl that features a carbon textured finish and can be used in many place. The most importance factors is that you are willing to.
<br /><br />Most commonly use color is black, the static was known by the carbon fiber supplier and manufacturer. With its special structure and appearance, it attract many car owners, even some of the women are now chasing the carbon fiber fabric.
<br /><br />No matter where you use it, such as your car, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">home accessories</a>, motorcycle parts, mobile phone, or even your personal laptop computer. It brings a brand new look and gives you unpredicted surprise. Most people love to use it on their car, especially when they are driving in the road, it attracts the eyes from others easily and the deep impression is hard to forget. Once upon a time, I was on a bus, a car applied with black 3D carbon fiber drive pass the bus, and it quickly catch my attention, or exactly I should say it is not only me, others on the bus can’t bear to shout, “Amazing”, “cool”, “awesome”. All I heard were the praise and exciting words. And they are using the beautiful words to describe. It is really an unusual experience. 
<br /><br />With more and more widely use of 3D carbon fiber vinyl, many people apply it
<br />to wheel center caps and stickers, the famous brand car name is BMW, Mercedes Benz, this trend will become more and more popular. Now use your creativity, your personal commodity will be out of the ordinary. Another method to change the look is using various colors. As we said, black carbon fiber is universal, miraculously; it makes everything you use to special. Gold color is shiny, especially in the sun. Or choosing white and silver colors are good for you, which may fit your car’s color perfect. If you want to be the one who is different, some seldom used color may be good choice.
<br /><br />The biggest experience you cannot forget of carbon fiber is that some of them are cheap, and if it gets scratched, it can recover by using special method. The information was got through a carbon fiber supplier, you can just use a hair dryer, if the scratch is very serious, you can upgrade to High-wattage hair dryer.
<br /><br />View more at <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2edc6ec6f064724667618b4f5ccd63a5" url=""><![CDATA[The fashion trend of Carbon Fiber<br/><br/>The unpredicted fashion is that <strong>carbon fiber </strong>is becoming more and more commonly used everywhere. Most places you will hard to imagine.
<br /><br />The common sense we have for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">Carbon fiber fabric</a> is that it is an accessory that can apply on the mobile phone, vehicles, notebook computer, motorcycle, bicycle or sound box. Once upon a time, after we meet one carbon fiber supplier. We get more information about this particular vinyl material. 
<br /><br />We have a fresh knowledge about it. Now while we are using it to decorate the roof of our car, someone else has used it to cover their favorite’s guitar, for a music lover and keener, this will represent much of their image. Or for a watch and a pen, it will on behalf of your taste. This is a new inspiration of art. With this trend, people are searching more of it and try to use more widely. Not to mention hot black color, for its commonality and cool look. 
<br /><br />The use of 3D carbon fiber sheet has become a new fashion; it brings more variety and makes things say goodbye to monotonous. 
<br /><br />For more information, please view at <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5c1e87044f4f92a77fe73c74912c4e69" url=""><![CDATA[Various pattern of Carbon fiber<br/><br/>When I come across the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">carbon fiber vinyl</a>, I simply thought it is just a material, and don't know the exactly usage. Not to mention the structure of it. With more and more use of it, we found that it can use in different place and can be modified in various patterns.
<br /><br />When you see a roll of carbon fiber sheet, it looks like the shape is dull. Although it’s surface is texture, especially for 3D carbon fiber. But after the creative clipping and design, it turn out to fresh outlook, especially when apply it to cars, mobile phones, even the mouse. If you purchase a large sheet of black carbon fiber, you can use the remaining material to your mouse, just measure the size then simply tear of the backside and stick on that surface. With clipping different pattern and apply it to the surface you like, it comes out to different outlook and make the original look special and attract others’ eyes easily.
<br /><br />I will choose red <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTM0" target="_blank">carbon fiber sheet</a>, it is a bright color and can be used on the lady’s car, or a bicycle is a good choice. If we are seeking for outstanding and extraordinary taste, Gold and green color are good color. Somehow we can use mixed color and using unusual clipping. It is a brave experience and hard to miss the wide range choose and creation of this carbon fiber fabric. Car fans are always searching methods to improve and change the appearance of their car, car tail, interior car accessories and Decorations. 
<br /><br />Using Coordinative colors and apply it to your exterior car is a good method. 
<br /><br />View more items on <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1dd740f03b908a3b48634177c34d4138" url=""><![CDATA[Carbon fiber wheel center caps<br/><br/>Carbon fiber vinyl is not only used for decoration, now many people used it in some special auto car accessories.
<br /><br />Wheel Center Hub Caps is the best choice that some car lovers will apply the carbon fiber fabric. It will become a hot trend with time flies with application of the textile style material. Most people are chasing the 3D black carbon fiber look, it’s cool look that make your can stop loving it and bring a large fun and amazing feeling. Some of them are pound of their carbon fiber auto part. Obviously its catch other’s eye easily without wasting much time, afford or money.
<br /><br />There are many custom wheel center caps with carbon fiber special view in the market; you even don’t need to pay the time of apply and carbon fiber sheet to the wheel center caps. And can select the color you like to meet your requirement and fit the color of your vehicle. The commonly use of the carbon fiber is the most famous brand name, such as BMW, Mercedes’-Benz, and more and more brands will use it 
<br /><br />View more at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ed2b05bbe107c34b976370fbf72e6b62" url=""><![CDATA[The wide range of using in carbon fiber sheet<br/><br/>With the widely use of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">carbon fiber vinyl sheets</a>, many carbon fiber manufacturer attempts to put it into mass production. But at the beginning, this is wrong, for the sake of many people do not know how to use it and use it well, this is the main problem. 
<br /><br />But in these years, more and more people are searching this special material no matter in the OEM supplier or through internet. A period of time, I am so curious, and wondering the reason. By viewing many websites, I finally find out the answer and it makes me happy. That is the carbon fiber vary in 3D pattern, the appearance is attractive, it can be stronger in a certain direction or equally strong in all directions. A small piece can withstand an impact of many tons and still deform minimally. The complex interwoven nature of the fiber makes it very difficult to break. 
<br /><br />Most importantly is that this kind of material is now employed in high-quality cars, bicycles, even boats and planes, and including popular Formula One <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">racecars</a>. It is water-proof, stretchable with heat and easily to clean with water. To apply a carbon fiber in cars or popular Formula One racecars is a very exciting experiment, just imaging that people are watching the match, then a carbon fiber striking car pass, it make everyone screaming. 
<br /><br />For more information, please view <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="559b48b20f45c380cf079c6d6f108c99" url=""><![CDATA[How to clean your carbon fiber vinyl<br/><br/>We all know to apply the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">carbon fiber sheet</a> to your auto mobile is not hard, just tearing apart the backside then stick to the place or something that you extremely want to decorate, then it bring a fresh view and entirely unexpected outcome that you hardly can imagine.
<br /><br />This material is the newest and hottest used widely in auto mobiles, important vehicle, some important racing-car matches or high-tech electronic products. This is to help establish a personal style and outstanding effects.
<br /><br />But how to maintain the carbon fibre sheet well is a key question. There are many people are eager to know the method. The important method is how to clean it. As the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMjAw" target="_blank">carbon fiber vinyl film</a> is waterproof, you can simply use the water, but if you are afraid this cannot clean well the dirt, you can try adding a little car wash soap to the water. Or you can add the water to the spray then use a soft fabric and clean.
<br /><br />But don’t use a hard wax on it, the carbon fiber sheet is different from other material, if you use a wax, it will get stuck in the 3D carbon fiber vinyl patterns, and this will influence the quality and effect.
<br /><br />For more information, please view <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1221eda90b1612e87a3115301dfb3f43" url=""><![CDATA[More detail information of Carbon Fiber<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzgw" target="_blank">3D Carbon Fiber Vinyl</a>is a wrap material. For its special outlook, nowadays, many people apply it in different products or items. This material with Features:
<br /><br />3D Textured Carbon Fiber Pattern 
<br />Reflects Light Like True Carbon Fiber 
<br />Water Resistant 
<br />Advanced Air Release Technology 
<br />Pressure Activated Adhesive
<br /><br />Its <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzExMg__" target="_blank">3D textured finish</a>that simulates the carbon fiber pattern makes the vinyl wrap the most realistic looking product out there. The vinyl film includes the Air Release Technology which allows for easier installs. Specially designed micro-channels allows for air to move out of the carbon fiber vinyl wrap allowing for a clean bubble free look. Wrap everything from your mobile computer, mobile phone, car interior and exterior, hood, roof, and more places you would like to use! The Carbon Fiber Vinyl allows you to wrap anything with a smooth surface. Using a conventional hair dryer will allow you to get around medium bends and curves.
<br /><br />With more information, please view <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a80093d5f69d89aca94c74f9f9118ec" url=""><![CDATA[Apply 3D carbon fiber to make your vehicle more special<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzgw" target="_blank">3D carbon fiber vinyl</a> film is the highest grade carbon fiber product on the market. It is made with textured weave film and is the closest to looking like true carbon fiber. It is made of high performance cast vinyl made for wraps. The carbon fiber sheet is very easy to apply to everywhere you like, unlike imitation carbon vinyl that is difficult to work with and will not bend around curves easily. It is easily to adhere to rooftops, hoods, trunks, fenders, or interior parts, such as stereo bezels, dash trim and so on. 
<br /><br />With easy to clean surface, once it get dirt, you don’t need to worry much and with this material on the surface of your car, your car will be protected well. It is also easily to remove if you want to change the color or refresh the outlook. Once it was applied, your car will be more beautiful and different. Most of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzIwMA__" target="_blank">car accessories</a> are common, but once it decorates with a carbon fiber, it turns to other appearance. By apply this material, many people get the idea of cut it and apply it with various style on different place. Most important is that in this way, the touch will become special for the carbon fiber with a textured weave surface.
<br /><br />For more information, please view <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9d617dbf9a09c780aa7d06ad0a0c2def" url=""><![CDATA[Which color of carbon fiber vinyl is your best choice?<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">Carbon Fiber Vinyl</a> is the newest and hottest product. Most apply in Import Vehicle, OEM applications. It is known well for its self-adhesive backing. 
<br /><br />Use it to decorate your vehicle, door panels, kick panels, arm rests, speaker boxes, and boat seats, ATV's, personal watercraft, snow mobile or anything else you can like and enjoy the fresh appearance! 
<br /><br />Black is a universal color and has a weave patterned in high gloss finish, a reflective top coat protects from UV discoloring and gives a realistic carbon fiber sheen to any surface. It is perfect for interior and exterior applications on any flat surface, it will simply give you restyled carbon fiber look in minutes. A stylish edition to any vehicle, blue <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTEy" target="_blank">Carbon Fiber sheet</a> is very popular with motorcycle enthusiasts. This is good for motorcycle riders, ATV owners or just for people who beat on their toys. Green carbon fiber may be a little hard for you to choose. But if you mix this color with others or apply it on some place well, it brings unpredicted surprise.
<br /><br />We love red color so much. Whether you are a racing enthusiast or keep you car parked except for on the weekends, this is the color you want. Sleek is the best word to describe the Silver Carbon Fiber Film. This is a great way to add silver carbon fiber to any smooth surface. As pure as the driven snow, add this most subtle of Carbon Modifications to your ride. Carbon Fiber in White has a matte sheen, almost stealth in nature.  
<br /><br />Carbon Fiber Vinyl Film is a unique printed adhesive backed film sheet which applies like a sticker or wrap to just about any surface. It can be Customized and personalized to anything you own with the look and feel. 
<br /><br />For more information, please view <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e7b9a366309d34f44bbb123f938ffc2e" url=""><![CDATA[Key points when use carbon fiber vinyl<br/><br/>With less expensive <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">carbon fiber vinyl</a>, where do you want to apply? If you owing several cars, and keen on driving, you will definitely choose this material. Some people will think that it is the best choice to apply on cars or other vehicle. But it also can be used on musical instrument, audiophile not only emphasize the music, but only chase the unique and stylish outlook of the instrument they play.
<br /><br />Although the widely use of carbon fiber sheet, most of people will neglect the points while using it. Take note of this, this material will bring more surprise to you. 
<br /><br />Clean before applying the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTM0" target="_blank">carbon fiber film</a>. This will be easily miss, don’t forget to clean the places you are going to install it, and make sure you apply it well. In this way, it is also easy for you to remove if you want to change the outlook.
<br /><br />Cut the material if you want to. Some one will cut it to different size to meet the requirement of various places, it is easy to cut and easy to apply, with an adhesive backing, you don’t need to worry. 
<br /><br />Use special method to smooth the carbon fiber fabric. If you purchase it from a supplier and in case it is not packaged well, there will be some scratch, what to do? Don’t get down, you can simply use the air dryer to blow, then it will magically become smooth. 
<br /><br />View more <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bd35a673d3113933abceff9c5c4662a9" url=""><![CDATA[Preparation before install the carbon fiber vinyl<br/><br/>It is easy to neglect the preparation step before install a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">carbon fiber vinyl film</a>, if you pay attention to this step, the appearance of the material on the places you apply will become more satisfied.
<br /><br />With the questions of how to apply it well, you can take the below note as reference. 
<br />Firstly, don't forget to measure the place you are going to apply the carbon fiber fabric, then confirm the size and color which fit your vehicle or <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMjAw" target="_blank">car accessories</a> well. The most important point is maintained your personal fancy and style. 
<br /><br />Secondly, clean the places to make the carbon fiber stick well and with long paste.
<br />Thirdly, use proper tools while applying it to remove the bubble or crease.
<br /><br />With suitable preparation work, no matter what places you apply <strong>carbon fiber sheet</strong>, it will make it look more smooth and beautiful.
<br /><br />View more at <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42bb988be369768d0faa1f63f1f45926" url=""><![CDATA[How to remove air bubble while applying carbon fiber vinyl<br/><br/>Many people have headache when applying some stickers, no matter where they applied, the air bubble is a biggest problem. Not to mention the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">carbon fiber vinyl</a>. If there is air bubble, the appearance will be influenced and impact the entire outlook.
<br /><br />There are some ways to avoid the air bubble happen. Please pay attention to the below suggestion before your apply the <strong>carbon fiber vinyl film</strong> to your automobile. 
<br /><br />Firstly you must guarantee the surface of places is smooth and clean when you are going to apply this particular material. And make sure there is no water or other liquid.
<br /><br />Secondly it is better to apply the material in the warm and proper temperature, in this way; it will guarantee that the <strong>carbon fiber sheet</strong> is much better to stick on the place.
<br /><br />Thirdly remove the air bubble by using some tools and follow the instruction when applying it on your car or <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMjAw" target="_blank">car accessories</a>.
<br /><br />Do remember that a hair dryer or heat gun is always helpful after you finish sticking the carbon fiber sheet.
<br /><br />More information <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9f8b57b6828692761af7bd0af8a2bb36" url=""><![CDATA[The usage of carbon fiber vinyl<br/><br/>Car owners love their car very much, they will think about various ways in order to protect it well. But many of them also will think about how to protect their car and decorate so that the outlook of cars will turn out to be well or nice.
<br /><br />That is why <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODA_" target="_blank">carbon fiber vinyl film</a> becomes more and more popular. You may neglect the usage of it, but while it is universally used in many vehicles or in any of the articles in your life, you will hard to stop the trend. Especially for its optional color and easily to cut for the size you need.
<br /><br />Use the carbon fiber not only will protect your car, but it also has the function of decoration. While you are choosing and applying it, don't forget to think about the color which will be suitable and cut by yourself to the shape which you like.
<br /><br />With this fabulous <strong>carbon fiber sheet</strong>, you will have more fun and flexible use.
<br /><br />View more <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2eb5ce5e1ee424e6827c4bc182455d5f" url=""><![CDATA[Good to Select Tire Valve Stem Caps<br/><br/>Many people will neglect the important <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTM0" target="_blank">car accessories</a>; <strong>tire valve stem cap</strong> is one of the important items. Then they will miss out the function and different types of it. 
<br /><br />There are several types of <strong>tire valve stems</strong>, most of the useful type is Anti-Theft Locking Tire Valves Caps, it not only can be used as a decoration, but also comes with a locking stick and screws which can lock your valve well. In this way, you will no need to worry about it will be lost or stolen by others. 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzExMg__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/165950625_6979674_44661391.jpg" /></a>
<br />More and more people come to the after market in order to search various types of tire valve caps. BMW, Mercedes Benz, Audi and VW are the most popular brand. Car drivers can choose anti theft valve caps for safe consideration. Also they can choose without anti-theft type according to their preference and style. And can also purchase several sets at the same time to meet your requirement of changeable and different cars or brands.
<br /><br />Styles, colors, brands or types are all free to choose. View more <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a2df872fd7489f44a336ece61b5f8d9" url=""><![CDATA[Save Time and Cost by Using the Wheel Center Stickers<br/><br/>Before purchasing <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODE_" target="_blank">car accessories</a>, some people will think about the cost and usage first. Of course some auto accessories are expensive and you will worry that size or installation.
<br /><br />But if you purchase the <strong>Wheel Center Hub Caps sticker</strong>, it is no need for you to worry. These stickers are light and easy to install, by purchasing it you can use it freely and saving cost largely. It is convenient for you to replace the old or obsolete stickers. 
<br /><br />It is very easy to install, you can just slit the backside as it comes with an adhesive backing, in this way, you don’t need to replace the entire <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMjAw" target="_blank">wheel center hub caps</a>, and it will greatly save your cost and time. Before stick this item, you can just use a detergent to clean the surface of the places. Then it will make it last longer.
<br /><br />If you are worry about that the stickers are not fit to purchase from after market, you can purchase the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">custom wheel center caps stickers</a>. You are able to choose different pattern.
<br /><br />View more at <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="96773818f7b1308aa326bb50fb35bf24" url=""><![CDATA[Time to Replace Your Car Cigarette Lighter<br/><br/>The old <strong>automobile cigarette lighter</strong> is an invisible harm to your car. It is very convenience to purchase a new one if you want to replace it. Especially now there are many different pattern and brands <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">cigarette lighter</a> on the market.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzgx" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/165950625_1855695_44786613.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />A cigarette lighter is not expensive and easy to replace, now you have the chance to choose various colors with the logo you need. It also comes with no brands on the market.The reason you want to replace it is that an old one is bad to your car. If it is broken, then you will have to replace with a brand new one, then you get a chance to choose the style you like. If it get missed, it is very essential to replace.
<br /><br />You can only replace the body if you prefer the original head of cigarette lighter to the new one. Just simply screwing off the 2 heads, then installs the new head to the body of your original cigarette lighter. Then you will finish. 
<br /><br />It comes with different voltage, don’t forget to check this when you purchase, while installing, please carefully place it to your car, as an important <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTEy" target="_blank">auto accessories</a>, you can miss it.
<br /><br />View more at <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9a09948bcd3ab39aedfad12addf2eccd" url=""><![CDATA[Decorative Car Antenna or Functional Auto Antenna<br/><br/>There are decorative car antenna and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfNzc_" target="_blank">functional car antenna</a> on the market, you can choose which one is suitable for you, especially according to the brand and color of you car. It is an essential <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTEy" target="_blank">auto accessory</a>.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzc3" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/165950625_8705136_44850039.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />For an antenna as decoration, you can choose the brand, and then easily install it on the roof of your car. You can just remove the double-faced tape underneath the antenna and softly attach it. But don’t forget to use cleaner to get rid of all kinds of dirty stuffs on the surface before installing to prolong its life. It can be used freely where you would like to attach your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">Auto Antenna</a>.
<br /><br />When you are going to purchase the functional Auto Antenna, you can choose the function with FM only or TV and Radio. But you must pay attention to the voltage and current while installing.
<br />For it has been set and if it is different, the automobile antenna cannot be functioned well.
<br /><br />View more at <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c7ab8e8f79d9207bef85470755d9248" url=""><![CDATA[Choose a Car Key Ring Chain for Yourself<br/><br/>A <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xNjk_" target="_blank">car key chain</a> is not only an <strong>auto accessory</strong>; it is very common in our daily life. Although it is commonly used, many key ring chain producer or key chain lovers are chasing the outstanding one for themselves. In this way, it will show apparently different from other people.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTY5" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/165950625_10536783_45110325.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Car drivers love the key ring with the logo of famous car brand. Nowadays, there are more and more different car brand key chain available on the market, the most popular brand includes BMW, VW, Mercedes'Benz, and Chevrolet. We all know that the Brand gives the car more powerful vitality. With the car brand key chain will make our lives special and elegant. You can use it as decoration, hanging on your iphone, bag, or as a gift which will make your life full of personality and self-confidence.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTEy" target="_blank">Car key chain</a> various in styles, some with different guns, with the cool looking it attract many young people and who love weapons very much. Gun is to maintain peace weapon, it give the brave people to bring strength, it seems to be a symbol of strength, and it make your life more charming. 
<br /><br /><strong>Car key ring </strong>with lovely cartoon character is loved by young ladies, just like bring a cartoon character to real life, and to show their preference.
<br /><br />View more on <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9c96b9a26c44d645d29a0b5a333bdbd1" url=""><![CDATA[Don’t neglect the small LED Light<br/><br/>Cars can not exist if there are no <strong>auto accessories</strong>. No matter the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">car accessory</a> is big or small. LED Light is worthy of consideration, if there is no light, how can you remind other driver that you are going to turn left or right? Especially in the dark. With these small LED light, you will no need to worry much.
<br /><br />Some details car drivers seldom know is that these items with long life and low power consumption thus will save your car’s power supply, nowadays, many people purchase it as it is very easy to assemble but you don’t need to worry about the problem, it is built-in current limiting resistor and diode to protect the led from reversed polarity installation.
<br /><br />The high quality auto bulbs, such as <strong>T5 LED Light</strong>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTcz" target="_blank">Strip DRL Dayline LED</a>, Interior Dome light or T10 have a long-lasting LED in each and will give your car a unique glow whenever you use your interior, dashboard, side or license plate lights. 
<br /><br />A tip you need to know is that if there is issue of hyper flashing or malfunctioning about the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTEy" target="_blank">car LED bulbs</a>. To solve this problem, please make sure the Circuit is Built-in for standard Voltage Input, or you could add a pair of load resistors the load resistors.
<br /><br />View more at <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c944ea01e3a0396281fdaf712f5aa317" url=""><![CDATA[Different Patterns of Car Emblem Stickers<br/><br/>Do you think the outlook of you car is dull? Especially while you are driving on the road, there are passing cars one by one and most of them come with a shining or unique <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTg2" target="_blank">auto mobile badge emblems</a>. 
<br /><br /><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/165950625_3960965_45674527.jpg" />
<br /><br />Different emblems which stick on cars stand for different meaning and indicate your preference. You can use it in everywhere you like, no matter in your car window, trunk and interior. Even in
<br />motorcycle, boat, surfboard, notebook, computer case, mirror, snowboard, skateboard and so on.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">Car badge emblem sticker</a> various in brand and material. It is updated very quickly. The price is also various thus the quality is not the same. Some are made of stainless steel and metal is better than the plastic material. <strong>3D TRANSFORMERS Graphic emblem badge </strong>Autobot and Decepticon Logo is very popular. There are many emblems with brand name of BMW, Mercedes-Benz.
<br /><br />Welcome to <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="99739f3e1658bdd093ade764cb0639c9" url=""><![CDATA[Replace Your Car LICENSE PLATE BOLT SCREWS<br/><br/>We all know that there are many <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTM0" target="_blank">auto accessories</a> on the market; you can choose what you like. Nowadays, there are many <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfODQ_" target="_blank">car license plate bolt screws</a> come with branded car logo, this will make your car become stylish and look unique while you are driving. And when your original screws get old and useless, it is a good chance to use a new one.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzg0" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/165950625_15714199_45843061.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />You can’t miss out these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">Auto license plate screws</a>. With metal material made and fancy outlook, it attracts many people at a glance. It is not only useful in your Auto mobile, but also decorates your car well, such as brand name of BMW, Audi, Mercedes-Benz, Land Rover and so on. With universal standard, you even don’t need to worry about the size. 
<br /><br />With the <strong>Car license plate bolt screws</strong>, you can say goodbye to the old and dull one. It is easy to install, you can simple use a screw driver to screw off the old one, and screw your new one then stick the branded logo. It is finished! In the future, if you don’t like the logo, you can get rid of it
<br />and stick and new one.
<br /><br />View more on <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="138f3b622095e0ca78e5206f0aa52f2f" url=""><![CDATA[The benefits of 3D Carbon fiber Vinyl Sheet<br/><br/>Among the variety <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTM0" target="_blank">Auto Accessories</a>, <strong>3D carbon fiber vinyl sheet </strong>is the popular one. Not only for it’s widely use in interior or exterior, while you use this particular carbon fiber material, will you find more and more benefits.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzgw" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/165950625_10096234_45976187.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><strong>Carbon fiber sheet</strong> is a good material to decorate all the things you like, but do you know it also protect the outlook of the place you used? For example, you use it on the car exterior as decoration, sometimes when driving, the frication and scratches is hard to avoid, and then at that time, the carbon fiber wrapped plays an important role. Or use it on your car Athena, it will look extraordinary, other people may also do like you, especially there are several colors to choose.
<br /><br />If you are afraid that the dirt of carbon fiber vinyl, it is easy to clean, thus you don’t need to worry much of it. Use it on the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">Car wheel center hub caps</a> makes good-looking and protect the outer housing. Using a 3D carbon fiber vinyl sheet and enjoying the benefit.
<br /><br />View more <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8c3aa7b9996f5e374a0790aa0bd552b3" url=""><![CDATA[Apply a Shinning Car Brake Caliper Cover to Your Car<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTEy" target="_blank">Auto Accessory</a> is important; using it properly will bring a surprise view of your car. While <strong>brake Caliper covers kit </strong>is the one that many people will neglect. It is the accessory to change your normal one to shinning and racing brake caliper.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDthbXA7Y1BhdGg9MTkzXzEzNA__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/165950625_15248599_46131559.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />The first thing people want to change may be the car’s wheel, and then comes to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb3JiYW5nLmNvbS9pbmRleC5waHA/bWFpbl9wYWdlPWluZGV4JmFtcDtjUGF0aD0xOTNfMTE2" target="_blank">wheel center caps</a>. But you will lack something special. That is the brake caliper covers kit. There are after market calipers, all the four wheels can install this particular accessory. They are only different in size. But if you think it is just for decoration that may be wrong. It not only bring bright look, but also have the function of cleaning up a mostly neglected area, the covers will surely add color and aesthetic appeal behind your wheels. You may get a high-performance, unordinary look with red caliper covers or other colors of <strong>custom caliper covers</strong>, featuring the color that would perfectly match the paint job of your vehicle.
<br /><br />With more time you use it, you will find more benefits. View more <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.forbang.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.forbang.com</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>