<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="13">
		<document id="38f8c027b6be0e6a85a6632749ffb3dd" url=""><![CDATA[Horrible Day!!!<br/><br/><em>Never to think that this world is so cruel!!
<br /><br />just miss the live in the school yard, i miss u, guys.
<br /><br />even though i feel that time is so limited that i can not catch everything.
<br /><br />i thought i can handle everything.
<br /><br />but the truth always hurt me!!
<br /><br />As office girl, it is abosolute different from student's live.
<br /></em>
<br /><br />Today is really a horrible day..i hate to caculate the goods, i hate to await others.
<br /><br />i wanna more free time.
<br /><br />i need more fresh air...
<br />i still can not breath very well..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42b97b065a1a1837118d69724da8a9fa" url=""><![CDATA[pls, leave me alone<br/><br/>u always ask me: what do u love?
<br />no answer in my heart, actually.
<br />faced with all ur guys, i have  no feelings with u but just friends.
<br />i do not know what i really want. 
<br />just love to travel alone, is it a bad thing?
<br /><br />never have an ideas...
<br />sometimes, just touch the deep corner..where i feel lonely.
<br /><br />i know everything will get better just need to take a deep breath when u can not breath..
<br />comfort urself??
<br />maybe, it is my closed world....
<br /><br />pls, leave me alone...
<br />i have my own world., my minds, my sunshine......
<br />it is not everything u can give to me...
<br /><br />that is not true, one day u will leave me away...
<br />i need too take care of myself...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="75225340f2786b00a37b33fc6e12115d" url=""><![CDATA[hate u!!!<br/><br/>yes...
<br /><br />i do not wanna talk with u...
<br />when i need u, u always walk away...
<br />and when u need me, i always there...
<br />it is not fair!!!
<br />i hate this kind of friendship!!!
<br />u said i am ur dear!!!
<br />in fact, i am nothing to u...
<br /><br />i do not wanna say a word with u...
<br />let everything gone...
<br />it is the best way for us!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="afdad4ac8c3963588602e8cec5a15001" url=""><![CDATA[my world<br/><br/>When u r alone, who will you miss a lot?
<br /><br />when u wondering around the street but you are alone. how could you do?
<br /><br />even though i can tell you what i will do...
<br /><br />but i need to get usded to have this world.
<br /><br />maybe you will judge me like a wired. but i can tell you i enjoy my life alone.
<br /><br />when u always looking the contact number to find a friend who will be willing to hang out together...
<br />i was out in person.
<br /><br />that is why we are different.
<br /><br />we are not in the same world////
<br /><br />my world may not fit for you.but what i can said is that i can live in your world without any problems.
<br /><br />That is me.....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a2a57ebeeb1a427cd0f862ecf78919d" url=""><![CDATA[B'' life<br/><br/>It is hard to believe that i have been a freshman for nearly 3 months..
<br />it seems that it had been a long time since the graduation..
<br />work is a pressure...
<br />i really wanna a holiday, i wish to wonder around this world,, 
<br /><br />how could i escape away from this noise world,,
<br />every night, sitted in the sitting room, dreaming that i was in the sky, flying....
<br />how could i stand up such kind of life..
<br /><br />it is not what i want...
<br />i wanna fly high..
<br />need more breath, even though challenge filled up my whole life..
<br />nevertheness, i had stay here for another long time..
<br /><br />Freedom...where r you?
<br />i need you...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="841572e9fa4653163801df5da00edcbb" url=""><![CDATA[lost<br/><br/>u never know what will happen next second...
<br />i would like to catch every second now but the truth always hurts.
<br /><br />sometimes, i think i need take someting serious under my consideraion..
<br />but i still do not know what is real or what is fake.
<br />i know i have missed so many things in my past time..
<br /><br />i wnana make up but i know that is impossible...
<br />how could i do if i wanna find my real way...
<br />even hard, complicated, but i really want to have it ...
<br /><br />i wanna enjoy somethings that i never have...
<br />Hard, difficult. right?
<br /><br />Can you give me a hug??just a hug is perfect to me..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88b69c35925b25e4e413daba1d6c9da3" url=""><![CDATA[tough life...<br/><br/>Two days of rush trip really made me... can not have a word that can descripe how i am now..
<br />everybody thoght that i was going to enjoy...
<br />always tell my friends that they had thought too much..
<br />that is not an easy job especially being with your boss...
<br /><br />completely miss the day when in the campus...
<br />can not come back, right?
<br />whatever i can do, i can not make it up...
<br />i do not this noisy city, so many people, like a melting iron drum...
<br /><br />can enter in but can not get out...
<br />heart has been tripped, how can it run away....
<br />Life is tough but you can make it easy if you do not have dream//
<br /><br />simple life without any complains, that is a Utopia...
<br />everybody wanna but who can make it???
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="80e152a095987054baa13d5b92997ce7" url=""><![CDATA[trapped!!!<br/><br/>This world is a mess, right?
<br />when someone judge you in Twitter as: valueless, anencephalous...
<br />how could you think?
<br />Bullshit¬¬¬ my boss always says....
<br /><br />Best friend, yes, you have even you do not contact her and him frequently.
<br />but they are still your strong back...
<br />u cry, give your shoulder..
<br />you shout at this world, they hug you sliently...
<br /><br />sometimes, do not need so much words, just wait there and looking at you is the best way for you.
<br />u know, i had lost so many things now, what i wanna know is simplest..
<br />my goals, my life...
<br /><br />i miss the days that i seat in the coffee corner and have a book to read..
<br />miss the sunshine and the breath of the nature..
<br /><br />now, i am trapped in the cage_this noisy city..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ae3dc23b23e1f1857ab9683f30bff298" url=""><![CDATA[be strong<br/><br/>Night is not scared, the evil thing is that u r the single one in the world...
<br />maybe u had lost ur heart without notice...
<br /><br />actually, that is a lovely world..
<br />the one that u never get in...just standing outside to see...
<br />never to think that is tragic..no one have rights to tell you but yourself/..
<br />do not think that the world have abandoned you...
<br />but you just need a hug...
<br /><br />pls bear in mind, u r not alone, after all, u have yourself...
<br />someone who never live for others...
<br />u have to learn to shout at the world: u r the only one in this world..
<br />no one can take place of you even the God..
<br /><br />be confident to yourself, never put your head into the sand...
<br />you can charge your fate..
<br /><br />what i can do is stay here when you cry...
<br />pls be strong, i worry about you...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5d1131d85fee656c210e4bfa3087516" url=""><![CDATA[Fly again...<br/><br/>After seven hours later, i will fly again...
<br />New month, new plan...but this plan is not what i wanna.
<br />can not predict what will happen tomorrow...
<br />i scare that we will miss the flight again like last month...
<br />that will be another disaster: take train to Shenzhen and then &quot; fly to the airport&quot;..
<br />you can not image how rush it  was..
<br /><br />If you need to go one city that you have been there for 3 times, the same place, the same time even stay at  different hotels_4th stars.
<br />But you still feel boring...
<br /><br />the city is slow, small one like go to a heaven to have a holiday.
<br />but the city have been eaten by the modern culture, youngest mind...
<br />it seems that all around you are fake...
<br />you can  not find the real.
<br /><br />the night life may be colorful, charming &amp; attractive...
<br />but will you be one of them?
<br />you will get drunk in it, right?
<br /><br />OK, baby, it is time to bed or you will not catch up the flight tomorrow.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a7a5bb981e9f695e89d98df5d7ed098f" url=""><![CDATA[being out!!!<br/><br/>Wake up in the hotel so early for one just went to bed at 4am.
<br />Horrible...
<br /><br />Never image how can i keep awake today...
<br />that is the bad result from the high drink last night...
<br /><br />whatever, still can not adjust my physical clock here...
<br />i will die if i can not sleep again...
<br />really, i wanna go to bed again never though a meeting will come at noon...
<br />But one thing cheers me p is that my lunch is SEAFOOD...
<br />that is the last thing that make me a little happy.
<br /><br />Maybe go to take a hot shower will give me back a clear head...
<br />the poor thing is that the bath foam is not what i love...
<br />why a Four- star have such kind of bullshit in the washing room?
<br />even i can not find the MTV Channel...
<br /><br />Shit... had better to take a shower and then leave....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e486a97acd815f296f33da6bbfb20e69" url=""><![CDATA[no forgive<br/><br/>I hate who always eat his words...
<br />if u lie to me more than 3 times, so, sorry, i would not trust u any more...
<br />u will be in my black list automatically...
<br /><br />no way to forgive u even u r my close one...
<br />if u lie u one time, it will be have twice, three times...
<br />so, just let things move on... we can not come back...
<br /><br />no deal to solve this problem, that is your character no one can change it easily, either do i.
<br /><br />i, so tired, can not make room for u any more...
<br /><br />From now on, two worlds between u and me..
<br /><br />Say goodbye with u smile....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3c246a2095d58a94dd945706a27eae29" url=""><![CDATA[vexation<br/><br/>I miss Daddy and Mommy...
<br />why should i need to stay to work now?
<br />It is Spring Festival period now...
<br />why i need to keep working....
<br /><br />My boss is totally a bullshit,.. a ghost...
<br />Do not willing to keep moving now..
<br /><br />Tired to death, how could i have power to hang out,,.
<br />I need my bed, my puppy...
<br />I need your big, big hug...
<br /><br />how could i know that where is my limitation...
<br />what they said is extramly a bullshit...how could i do?
<br />hate them without reasons,..
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>