<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="4ea33c9c83e2eb1d7798aaf61a4a7e7b" url=""><![CDATA[Oh what to do?<br/><br/>Alrighty... I never really tell anyone how I feel about boys or anything because it alays gets over-exaggerated and turns out REALLY bad in the end. so I really like this one guy and I already know that he likes me back and all but I just can't wait for him to ask ME out and I'm too afraid to do it myself.  But I'm going to a party on friday and he's taking me and all but I just hope that he can do it then, and that we can actually make it official nd all. I just cant wait and I really want to be with him.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="261d86be53aaa7065c08ea160d87a6b7" url=""><![CDATA[Party...<br/><br/>Whoa. So I went to this party last night. It was a goodbye party for my friend Amy who is moving out of town. So I get there at 7:30 and everyone's all loud and drunk and stuff. So I give Amy the card I bought for her and she doesnt even read it! I was so mad. And then she starts to complain about how she's too tired and wasted and that she wants to go home. Actually, she didnt even go home. she went to her boyfriends house! So we were all basically mad at her. so everyone was acting all imature and me and Heather were the only non-drinkers at the party so we had to keep control over the party. The host was too sick to even stand so she was in the only washroom with another drunk sitting over the toilet and/or passed out in their own puke. We didnt end up going to sleep until around 4 in the morning and so everyone was passed out with beer bottles in their hands and just lieing on the floor or wherever they could fit. After everyone was asleep, the guy next to me started to grope me....then go up my shirt....then tried to go up my skirt but I just got up and went somewhere else. I still don't even know who it was. What a night.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1115132c6026bea541ae576a64b2ffdc" url=""><![CDATA[Oh Jeepers !<br/><br/>Wow. I havent been on facebox (pan.net in so long! Why would they change the name anyways? PAN just sounds retarded. But whatever. I should upload some new shots of me I guess eh? Well thats my plan for today. Other than going to chill with Eddie, then Shianne, then Hannah. WoOt ! Thats exciting. :|
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="49c553c29918e5c2224db06cd77563f5" url=""><![CDATA[Oh Jeepers.<br/><br/>Wow. I'm mad. My mom made us move from Huntsville lasr summer and now she wants to move back. Now that I've made new friends and have 3 jobs, am currently doing modelling and everything! Like WTF? Am I supposed to just give it all away for her? Doubt it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ad77172a5ecb788ecafea088afde2bbb" url=""><![CDATA[Pictures.<br/><br/>Almost........Done.........Uploading.........Pictures! There's only like 596 pictures. Like holy frick! Gonna take long enough!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d461f1ef19706407031fc81bc851a56b" url=""><![CDATA[Modelling?<br/><br/>so I'm gonna be modelling for Anne Hopkins! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> She saw me and my friend yesterday and was like &quot;you ladies should come to my site and drop your email addresses. &quot; Thats exciting! I cant wait for the photoshoot! Dont worry I'll upload every picture so ya'll can see my wonderfully sexy body <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f7b1e3f6f615430fe0d34ccb4740d4bc" url=""><![CDATA[My fine is 50 $... And yours ?<br/><br/>This is fun to do. Just read the “offence” and if you’ve done it, you owe that fine. Then add up your total fine. You don’t have to confess your answers, just the amount of your fine. Good luck to you all – I’m sure a couple of you are going to be broke!!!!
<br /><br />Smoked pot — $10
<br />Did acid– $5
<br />Got drunk—-$10
<br />Ever had sex at church — $25
<br />Woke up in the morning and did not know the person who was next to you– $40
<br />Had sex with someone on MySpace — $25
<br />Had sex for money — $100
<br />Ever had sex with the a Puerto Rican — $20
<br />Vandalized something — $20
<br />Had sex on your parents’ bed — $10
<br />Beat up someone — $20
<br />Been beaten up — $10
<br />Crossed dressed — $10
<br />Given money to a stripper — $25
<br />Been in love with a stripper — $20
<br />Kissed some one who’s name you didn’t know — $0.10
<br />Hit on some one of the same sex while at work — $15
<br />Ever drive drunk — $20
<br />Ever got drunk at work, or went to work while still drunk — $50
<br />Used toys while having sex — $30
<br />Got drunk, passed out and don’t remember the night before — $20
<br />Went skinny dipping — $5
<br />Had sex in a pool — $20
<br />Kissed someone of the same sex — $10
<br />Had sex with someone of the same sex — $20
<br />Cheated on your significant other — $10
<br />Masturbated — $10
<br />Cheated on your significant other with their relative or close
<br />friend– $20
<br />Done oral — $5
<br />Got oral — $5
<br />Done / got oral in a car while it was moving — $25
<br />Stole something — $10
<br />Had sex with someone in jail — $25
<br />Made a nasty home video — $15
<br />Had a threesome — $50
<br />Had sex in the wild — $20
<br />Been in the same room while someone was having sex — $25
<br />Stole something worth over more than a hundred dollars — $20
<br />Had sex with someone 10 years older — $20
<br />Had sex with someone under 21 and you are over 27 — $25
<br />Been in love with two people or more at the same time — $50
<br />Said you love someone but didn’t mean it — $25
<br />Went streaking — $5
<br />Went streaking in broad daylight — $15
<br />Been arrested — $5
<br />Spent time in jail — $15
<br />Peed in the pool — $0.50
<br />Played spin the bottle — $5
<br />Done something you regret —$20
<br />Had sex with your best friend — $20
<br />Had sex with someone you work with at work — $25
<br />Had anal sex — $80
<br />Lied to your mate — $5
<br />Lied to your mate about the sex being good — $25
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="27cae4c7d6fe29f09aeab660662d27c" url=""><![CDATA[Told to be selfish.<br/><br/>My whole life, I have done everything possible to make the people around me happy. I have been through so much stuff and so I just thought I'd let it all out while I have the chance. 
<br />If making someone smile means that I am missing out on something, I would do it. I'm the type of person that if people are happy, I'm happy. Just on a different level. 
<br />Sometimes, I would even try to make someone smile, even when they didnt. Meaning I would go through whatever I have done for nothing. Thats basically my life. 
<br />Making others happy can be so tiring and makes me really depressed. I act happy so the poeple are thinking &quot;Wow. She's happy.&quot; But really, I'm not even close to being happy.
<br /> I'm probably the most depressed person you could ever meet. But I just dont show it, for the pleasure of those around me.
<br />When people want me to do stuff, I'd do it. When I ask for someone to do me a favor, they dissapear. People just don't know what I've been through. And those that do, just stop contacting me, because I'm &quot;different&quot;. 
<br />It hurts to know that the friends you thought would always be there for you, just leave when times get rough.
<br />I, for one, am ont one of those &quot;friends&quot;.
<br />I keep my chin up, even when times get rough. I stand strong for those not strong enough. I am those who are not.
<br />Its time for me to just relax and take a break for once. Let others see what they take for granted when I'm not there for them. I know it sounds horrible of me to be saying this, but I dont want to be there anymore.
<br />I am taking a break.
<br />I am being selfish.
<br />I love it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f25c475fbc2f9a10ce2a2bf27b353b3d" url=""><![CDATA[Stupid Cassie.<br/><br/>Oh wow. I really do crack myself up sometimes..
<br /><br />Okay, so I was searching through some people and saw that there were some 14 year olds born in '93. So I was like &quot;Wtf ! I was born in '92 and I'm only 14&quot;. So I got all confused and even did the math in my head. I asked a few of my friends if I was right or wrong and they seemed confused too... So, I thought about it for a second and realized that I'm almost 15. Whoa. I definetly crack myself up. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="51804b49a6d059a24e41544447edb54c" url=""><![CDATA[Err.<br/><br/>Arggh ! Everytime I go to upload a picture, it freezes everything on my computer ! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ebb1c24b109ec5dd450e1830071d27f3" url=""><![CDATA[I WANT to make a difference.<br/><br/>WARNING : The following may be pretty lame, so you don't have to read it if you don't want to.
<br /><br />My goal in life :
<br /><br />This may seem pretty weird, but I already have my life planned out. Though, I do not have the specifics, I think I thought it up pretty well.
<br />I dont want to become a doctor, or a vet, or a social worker. I want to be a teacher. Not just any kind of teacher though. I want to teach children in 3rd world countries all around the world. I know my hopes seem pretty high, but if I continue to try my hardest and perservere, I WILL be what I PLAN to be. I THINK, THEREFORE I AM a good motto, I must say. Most people these days say that what will happen, will happen. They don't try, they don't work for it, they are just care-free and rely on fate to follow through on what they THINK should happen. I don't really know what the point of this inexplicable rant is, but I just thought I may as well voice my opinion. 
<br />So anywho, back to my goal(s)... 
<br />I WANT to make a difference. It really doesn't matter if the difference I make is as little as putting a smile on a child’s face, or as complex as building a school for those who cannot afford it. I feel as though I was brought into this world to change it. It may not be drastic, but it also could be. I don't want to be another teenage drop-out that has to live off of welfare. I want to supply for the needs of my family. 
<br />I want to be the best person I can possibly be, therefore, I will do whatever is needed to fulfill my hopes and dreams. Obviously, as most of you already know, I grew up in a broken home. It runs in my family, as sad as it may seem. But today in church, we were talking about breaking the curse, stopping the chain, and changing for the better. So my goal is to have a safe family that have what they need to survive, that know their mothers will be home when they get back from school, that know that they can always rely on their family and friends. 
<br />It really hurts to smile, even when I am hurting inside. I don't want to see others in my position. I WANT to change the way children are growing up these days. They should NOT have to deal with the things they are stuck living with. It's unfair. 
<br />It's really hard growing up in a family that doesn't support your goals in life. I was the one who took my little sister to church every Sunday. I was the one who stayed in school. I AM the one succeeding in life. 
<br />Others have the opportunity, but decline it. It seriously hurts me inside to see others turn down what could possibly be the greatest opportunity in their life. 
<br />It's only common sense. Take the opportunity of a lifetime. Don't be ridiculous. 
<br />Knowing I have made the RIGHT friends really helps when I need them most. If I didn’t meet the WRONG people, when I would ever need help, they would shun me, and until I was better, forget I even existed. 
<br />So I truly thank those that have been there for me. You have achieved MY goal in life. You HAVE changed me for the BETTER. 
<br />HAHA. I've gotten a bit off-topic... 
<br />But anyways, help. YOU taking 5 minutes out of your day to talk to a friend CAN help. It WILL help. It's really that easy. 
<br />Its not only about changing SOMEONE's life. Another one of my goals would have to be changing the WORLD. Yeah, thats right. The environment. Too much crap is going on right now, we don't need an unhealthy environment to top it all off. Grow up and Pick up. Its simple. I don't see why people don't seem to understand how what they are doing is truly affecting our health. 
<br /><br />Yeah, I have WAY too many goals in life, and WAY too many subjects to rant about. I'll just save them for another time. =]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="477064e7b9587b4906ed4f448ee13bdf" url=""><![CDATA[AnotherRandomRant<br/><br/>Boys can be so hurtful and not even know it. 
<br />I don't see how they can't understand the impact they have on us girls. I loved a guy, LOVED, we hung out, did stuff, and he told me he liked me. So, I was really excited because I thought he was a good guy, and that my chance at love has finally came. Obviously that has NOT happened, or else I wouldn't be writing this blog right now. So my bestfriend, BESTfriend, was talking to him for me on MSN, and so she asked him who he liked, and he said HER. He NEVER talks to her. EVER! Everytime I find a good guy that likes me back, she interfere's and then they choose her. I don't even understand why they can like her though. Yeah, she's my bestfriend, but she's a bitch. She treats guys like shit, and then expects them to still like her. Jeepers. It's so frustating having to compete with your friend over a guy she says she HATES. Like fuck, I hate it. She is already leading on 2 other guys, why does she have to take mine ? As soon as she got off the phone with me, I started crying. I don't cry much, but I was just so stressed. My hands are freaking shaking now, I'm so mad. And it's not even my friend. ITS LIFE. Why did I have to be born ? I know it may sound horrible, but I hate my life. Not many people would ever expect those words to come from my mouth, but I HATE my life. Whatever. I'm just going to become a freaking nun. Cupid just isn't on my side.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a544589f34fe094bc7d054a8a0c7d22" url=""><![CDATA[Holy Shyzzah.<br/><br/>Dang. I was looking at my stats yesterday, and it was like 18 for the one day. So I looked today, and it was like 130 ! I was like &quot;Holy shyzzah !&quot; <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> LOL.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13eb0ac1837b24cc2d7f5b438a085386" url=""><![CDATA[Stupid thing.<br/><br/>Everytime I go to upload pictures, it freezes and makes me mad. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/dry.gif" alt=":)" /> So the pictures I have are not as recent as possible. Work with me here.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f03eb8c416f5c7e6d9eb7efa0521a461" url=""><![CDATA[Another Statistic.<br/><br/>[Stolen from Chicken Soup For The Teenage Soul On Tough Stuff]
<br /><br />I don’t want to be another statistic
<br />Some suicidal teen
<br />Who makes a choice to kill herself
<br />When the world just seems too mean.
<br />She can’t go on with life
<br />Or so to her it seems
<br />Reality has fallen short
<br />And so have her many dreams
<br /><br />I don’t want to be another statistic
<br />Some pregnant little girl
<br />Who met this great guy
<br />And then gave sex a whirl.
<br />She was only fifteen
<br />But it felt so right
<br />She thought they’d be together
<br />For more than just one night.
<br /><br />I don’t want to be another statistic
<br />Some kid strung out on crack
<br />Who started at a party
<br />And now he can’t turn back.
<br />First cigarettes and alcohol
<br />Now meth, crack and cocaine
<br />He’s been smoking it so long
<br />That now he’s gone insane.
<br /><br />I don’t want to be another statistic
<br />Some girl left in the rain
<br />Who was walking home from school
<br />Then raped and left in pain.
<br />She can’t tell her parents
<br />And it hurts to tell her friends
<br />She doesn’t know what she’ll do
<br />To make this nightmare end.
<br /><br />I don’t want to be another statistic
<br />Some kid out of school
<br />Who dropped out real early
<br />And was acting like a fool.
<br />He thought that it was boring
<br />He thought that it was dumb
<br />He doesn’t have an education
<br />But lives on the the streets like a bum.
<br /><br />I don’t want to be another statistic
<br />Some stereotypical teen
<br />I’m gonna make a difference
<br />I’ll finish with my dream.
<br />I won’t end up pregnant
<br />On drugs or even dead
<br />I wont drop out of school
<br />Because I’ll use my head.
<br /><br />I don’t want to be another statistic
<br />To fit into some mold
<br />Of what society thinks of kids today
<br />Because it’s getting kind of old.
<br />Not all of us are bad
<br />In fact most of us are good
<br />When will the world see us
<br />And give us credit like they should ?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9b6ff6126922d4a1c7f9edd6194fcaab" url=""><![CDATA[You COULD be a hero.<br/><br/>No one sits with him, he doesn't fit in
<br />But we feel like we do when we make fun of him
<br />Cause you want to belong do you go along?
<br />Cause his pain is the price paid for you to belong
<br />It's not like you hate him or want him to die
<br />But maybe he goes home and thinks suicide
<br />Or he comes back to school with a gun at his side
<br />Any kindness from you might have saved his life
<br /><br />[Tag:]
<br />Heroes are made when you make a choice
<br /><br />[Chorus:]
<br />You could be a hero
<br />Heroes do what's right
<br />You could be a hero
<br />You might save a life
<br />You could be a hero, You could join the fight
<br />For what's right for what's right for what's right
<br /><br />[Verse:]
<br />No one talks to her, she feels so alone
<br />She's in too much pain to survive on her own
<br />The hurt she can't handle overflows to a knife
<br />She writes on her arm, wants to give up her life
<br />Each day she goes on is a day that she is brave,
<br />Fighting the lie that giving up is the way,
<br />Each moment of courage her own life she saves
<br />When she throws the pills out a hero is made
<br /><br />Heroes are made when you make a choice
<br /><br />You could be a hero
<br />Heroes do what's right
<br />You could be a hero
<br />You might save a life
<br />You could be a hero, You could join the fight
<br />For what's right for what's right for what's right
<br /><br />[Verse:]
<br />No one talks to him about how he lives
<br />He thinks that the choices he makes are just his
<br />Doesn't know he's a leader with the way he behaves
<br />And others will follow the choices he's made
<br />He lives on the edge, he's old enough to decide
<br />His brother who wants to be him is just nine
<br />He can do what he wants because it's his right
<br />The choices he makes change a nine year old's life
<br /><br />You could be a hero
<br />Heroes do what's right
<br />You could be a hero
<br />You might save a life
<br />You could be a hero, You could join the fight
<br />For what's right for what's right for what's right
<br /><br />[Rap]
<br />Little Mikey D. was the one in class who everyday got brutually harassed
<br />This went on for years until he decided that never again would he shed another tear
<br />So he walked through the door, grabbed a four four out of his father's dressing drawer
<br />And said I can't take life no more
<br />And like that life can be lost
<br />But this ain't even about that
<br />All of us just sat back and watched it happen
<br />Thinkin' it's not my responsibility to solve a problem that isn't about me
<br />This is our problem
<br />This is just one of the daily scenarios which we choose to close our eyes
<br />Instead of doing the right thing
<br />If we make a choice and be the voice for those who won't speak up for themselves
<br />How many lives would be saved, changed, rearranged
<br />Now it's our time to pick a side
<br />So don't keep walkin' by
<br />Not wantin' to intervene
<br />Cause you wanna exist and never be saved
<br />So let's wake up and change the world
<br />Our time is now
<br /><br />You could be a hero
<br />Heroes do what's right
<br />You could be a hero
<br />You might save a life
<br />You could be a hero, You could join the fight
<br />For what's right for what's right for what's right
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7c1267329f72d45c63f30becb832a719" url=""><![CDATA[I want to live<br/><br/>This is just a poem I wrote on Human Rights for my Civics class in like 10 minutes, so bare with me.
<br /><br />I want to live,
<br />I want to vote,
<br />I want to be free of racism,
<br />Sexism,
<br />Discrimination,
<br />Injustice.
<br /><br />I want to live,
<br />I want to be able to think,
<br />Without others judging who I am,
<br />Without others judging my opinion,
<br />Without others judging me.
<br /><br />I want to live,
<br />I want to live where I want to live,
<br />I want to build a house,
<br />Where my family will grow,
<br />I want to grow old, and die old,
<br />Not worrying about life.
<br /><br />I want to live,
<br />I want to live even when my body is giving up,
<br />When they think there is no other way,
<br />When they say it’s over,
<br />Because I know,
<br />I am strong enough to fight.
<br /><br />I want to live,
<br />I want to vote for whom I think should represent my country,
<br />For whom I think is capable of supplying our country with the respect it deserves,
<br />For who shall listen to our opinions, 
<br />For who shall be the best in my opinion,
<br />To run my country.
<br /><br />I want to be human,
<br />And have my rights,
<br />My rights to live,
<br />My rights to vote,
<br />My rights to live where I want,
<br />My rights to be free of discrimination,
<br />I want to be human,
<br />And have my rights,
<br />I want to live.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b510e9caf9da499a74274a1963ffd798" url=""><![CDATA[i didnt know you can do that on the internet!<br/><br/>so... my uncle came down from Alberta just to live here in G-hole and me and my sista pissed him off so much he decided to move back....he was here for like 2 weeks.... but me and my sis didnt even do shyt...he thought that we were lieing about taking the quads out at liek 4 in the morn. like we would do that in the middle of nowhere with a creaper for a neighbor and no headlights....he must be pretty freakin retarded....well anyways...back to bordom...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8514917bce16d980ded32b8b449d7d5d" url=""><![CDATA[holy chapotly<br/><br/>wow...today has been so effing boring....i've basically been on the comp since like 3 and its now 8:35.... there's like noone on msn and nobody's talking to me on facebox so i am really flipping out! plzz ppl plzz talk to me before i go and cry myself to sleep... ok maybe not but still... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a63d18e1d4ba9cbffa7f5edb2c81a31d" url=""><![CDATA[oh no :(<br/><br/>well...i am online but it says that i'm offline. So if this message actually works and all....you will know that i'm online so TALK TO ME PLZZZZ!!!! ohh... ok i see how this is going to be, now it says that i'm online....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f1c26205599133ea41ff253fb503a002" url=""><![CDATA[i'm very upset right now!<br/><br/>omg!!!! errrrr....i cant open my candycane and i REALLIIIII want it!!! i cant get it out of the wrapper andi think i might hyperventilate!!!!! man..where is someone when you need them most? and we ran out of milk so my coffees have to be black! (that was not a racial slur). sonowi dont know what to do cuz i might go legally INSANE! insane i tell you! INSANNEEEEEE!!!!!! woah....i really need to simmer down a bit...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="56516731e55eb638c40a5777da4cffd3" url=""><![CDATA[[very good title goes here]<br/><br/>umm...ya. well, i'm feeling kinda random today. probably cuz i'm jsut so effing bored outta my mind! but anyways, lets not get a lil too carried away. i think i needa HUGE coffee! i'm soooooo addicted! well anyways, there was this thing on facebook that i maid and it said to post a link on a site, so here it is &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;
<br /><br />haha....i was just kidding. but here it actually is <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />  &lt;ahref=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fp%2FCassy_Godfrey%2F504539337%26quot%3Btitle%3D%26quot%3BCassyGodfrey"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.facebook.com/p/Cassy_Godfrey/504539337&quot;title=&quot;CassyGodfrey</a>'sFacebookprofile&quot;target=_TOP&gt;&lt;imgsrc=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbadge.facebook.com%2Fbadge%2F504539337.55.1702632575.png%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://badge.facebook.com/badge/504539337.55.1702632575.png&quot</a>; border=0 alt=&quot;Cassy Godfrey's Facebook profile&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
<br /><br />holy chapotley thats a long one!
<br /><br />ohh...ok. well it doesnt work so DO NOT click on it!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="99ed5a09ca24f3951762e70590f4eff9" url=""><![CDATA[Who Wants To Own Me?<br/><br/>--------I'm for sale---------
<br /><br />Rules of FACEBOX Adoption::
<br /><br />-Put in the subject &quot;i'm for sale&quot; and see who wants to own you.
<br /><br />-The first person to send u a message saying &quot;I own you&quot; owns you.
<br /><br />It's that simple...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="759bfb8c1f3d9f412b690d7691047e59" url=""><![CDATA[What Do I Do?<br/><br/>Oh My Gosh! I just can't seem to get this one guy off my mind. I seriously think I might be in love with him. We are just starting to talk more and he makes me smile and laugh all of the time. I really hope it works out with us, but he just got out of a serious relationship and I don't know if he's ready or not. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> And the sad thing is, I can't even tell him how I fell because I'm too much of a weasle to stand up and speak my mind. God Dang it! The main reason why I think I like him is because he's a church boy and I know he would never hurt me like my past boyfriends. I really hope it works out. Wish me luck <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />Cassie ?
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>