<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="b476508d51cde6d234758026d26d2851" url=""><![CDATA[Three Ways to Rip DVD to Mac<br/><br/>Most people already have their favorite movies and television shows on DVD, but you may need to rip those DVDs to your Mac computer instead of having to purchase shows and movies again in an iPod form. Learn to transfer DVD content to your Mac computer by following methods.
<br /><br /><strong>1. HandBrake</strong>
<br /><br />Handbrake is an open source DVD ripper which can only convert DVD's to MP4 and MKV, with support for iPhone, iPods, PSPs, Apple TVs, PS3s. But it only can rip standard DVDs that can be played by your DVD player if without the help of third party software, VLC media player, not the mention the Disney new copy protections. In addition it is not stable, sometimes even crash. And if you would like to upload a commercial or home-made DVD movie to youtube.com video sharing website or to your web page or blog, HandBrake can't help at all. MacX DVD Ripper Free Edition would be the HandBrake alternative to solve this problem.
<br /><br /><strong>2. VLC Media Player</strong>
<br /><br />VLC Media Player is a powerful tool for playing digital media files. Even though it's best known for playing a wide range of file formats, it has other hidden features that boost its functionality. One such feature is the ability to rip DVDs. The player won't let you rip uncompressed video files to your hard drive, but it will compress whatever movie you're watching and save it in MPG format.
<br /><br /><strong>3. MacTheRipper</strong>
<br /><br />MacTheRipper can breaks copy protection and rips DVD content, but it doesn't encode its rips to other formats. It just rips the DVD menu and all to your hard drive in VOB file. But it also needs a third party software to convert VOB to other formats.
<br /><br />You can found more <strong>dvd ripper</strong> software at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free software download</a> website.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24f42b5ed757c5f439eaae18a7ea7eb4" url=""><![CDATA[An Efficient RAR Password Cracker You May Need Most<br/><br/>It is quite common to get a password protected RAR archive these days. You may download a game program in RAR format with password, or create an encrypted RAR file to protect its contents from the unauthorized person. But it happens that you forget RAR password and cannot access to the archive's contents. To open the password protected RAR archive, a RAR password cracker is often required.
<br /><br />RAR password recovery is a time sensitive work, thus for a WinRAR password remover, a quick cracking speed is quite important.
<br /><br />RAR Password Unlocker recovers lost passwords for RAR/WinRAR 4.11 and its previous versions. It adopts multi-core CPUs and NVIDIA-GPU acceleration technology to speed up RAR password recovery. The more CPU cores you have, the faster recovery speed you will enjoy. And the GPU can be used to greatly increase the recovery speed.
<br /><br />Before enjoying the fast speed, ensure that this RAR Password Cracker searches passwords in the right range, therefore you should set the attack mode in a right manner, otherwise, the password will never be found.
<br /><br />Three Powerful Attack Types of RAR Password Unlocker:
<br /><br />1. Brute-Force Attack. This Attack will try all possible characters combinations. Though it will finally recover RAR password, but it is not realistic at most of time, as a long time is needed. If the password is weak and short enough, this attack way is useful.
<br /><br />2. Brute-force with Mask Attack. If you remember some information of the password, even just the length range, you can set a mask in this attack mode, which will help you effectively shorten the recovery time compared with brute-force attack. The more you set, the more cracking time will be saved.
<br /><br />3. Dictionary Attack. Recover lost RAR password by trying the word combinations in the built-in dictionary. You can also add your own dictionary to the program for less time-consuming with the most possible passwords you used, such as your name, birthday, pet name, door number or others.
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free download software</a> has these additional features: Support file name encryption - Whether the archive name is encrypted or not, RAR Password Unlocker could work to recover its password.
<br /><br />Auto-save - Automatically save the recovery process every 15 minutes by default, so that you can resume the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3Jhci1wYXNzd29yZC11bmxvY2tlci01NzQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">RAR password recovery</a> project after previous interruption or stop. What's more, you can stop the cracking process at any time as you wish, and restart from the same state later.
<br /><br />No file size limitation - Recover forgotten RAR password at high speed, regardless of your encrypted RAR archive size. Free download <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3Jhci1wYXNzd29yZC11bmxvY2tlci01NzQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">RAR password cracker</a> to enjoy its time-efficient password recovery features.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31d62d507b62b34a3aacec79d8c080d6" url=""><![CDATA[What can get from WinRAR free download?<br/><br/>You may have noticed that, WinRAR free download is always on the top list in many <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free software download</a> websites, due to the usability and features this piece of program provides.
<br /><br />Winrar is the daily used program for windows users to extract RAR and ZIP archives, as well as compress files in RAR or ZIP format to backup data or reduce size of email attachments. As WinRAR integrates with windows explorer, you can easily compress and extract the file from the context menu.
<br /><br />Besides complete support for RAR and ZIP archives, WinRAR is able to unpack and convert CAB, ARJ, LZH, TAR, GZ, ACE, UUE, BZ2, JAR, ISO, Z, 7-Zip archives as well. 
<br /><br />Once free download WinRAR, you will enjoy these rich features: strong general and multimedia compression, solid compression, archive protection from damage, reconstruction &amp;repair of damaged archives, process of ZIP and other non-RAR archives, scan archives for viruses, create programmable self-extracting archives(SFX), authenticity verification, NTFS and Unicode support, multivolume archives support so as to allow the distribution easily or its storage onto several disks, interesting WinRAR themes or skins, a command line interface for MacOS X and Linux computers, drag-and-drop facility, wizard interface, theme support, folder tree panel, multithread support and Windows x64 shell integration, and other rar extras for developers and programmers. 
<br /><br />In addition to create, manage and control archive files, there are several other features like sync, encryption, security, explorer, background archiving, multi-threading, etc. 
<br /><br />WinRAR has advanced encryption algorithm, offering you the benefit of industry strength archive encryption using AES (Advanced Encryption Standard) with a key of 128 bits, making rar password is one of the most difficult passwords to be recovered.
<br /><br />How to encrypt a rar file?
<br />1. Right Click the file and press &quot;Add to Archive&quot;.
<br />2. In the pop-up window, click the &quot;Advanced&quot; tab and then &quot;Set Password&quot; on the middle-right.
<br />3. Input and reenter the password. You can check “encrypt file names” below as well, thus, openers will not see the file name.
<br />4. Click &quot;OK&quot;, now the rar file is created and password-protected!
<br /><br />WinRAR supports all windows system, including Windows 2000, XP, 2003, Vista, 2008, Windows 7. What is more, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3dpbnJhci0zMi1iaXQtOTMwMjcuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">WinRAR download</a> is available in over 40 languages, thus windows users can make use of it without any language difficulty.
<br /><br />All in all, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3dpbnJhci0zMi1iaXQtOTMwMjcuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">WinRAR free download</a> is a big benefit for you, give it a try and enjoy the powerful archive manager instantly.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c387f64710c53987c251379e261e92fe" url=""><![CDATA[Why Download Adobe Flash Player?<br/><br/>Have you ever asked to download Adobe Flash Player when browsing a webpage with a flash video in it? Flash Player enables you to view interactive web content, like flash video, games and animation in web browser. It usually happens when you browse the internet on a new PC or a portable device for the first time.
<br /><br />What is Adobe Flash Player? Adobe Flash Player, available as <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free download software</a>, is a cross-platform browser plug-in for viewing multimedia, Rich Internet Applications and streaming video and audio, on a computer web browser or on supported mobile devices. That is to say, Flash Player is a player for playing video, games, and animation embedded into web pages. If you want to watch video in the webpage, you must install Flash Player.
<br /><br />Now, Adobe Flash Player is more than just a player, it delivers beautiful HD video, faster graphics rendering, and high performance on mobile devices and personal computers, and is designed to take advantage of native device capabilities - enabling richer, more immersive user experiences.
<br /><br />What is more, Adobe Flash Player free download can be applied to major operating systems (Windows, Mac OS, Linux, Solaris), popular web browsers (Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Safari, Opera), mobile phones (Android, BlackBerry Tablet OS, Apple iOS) and portable devices (PSP).
<br /><br />After <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2Fkb2JlLWZsYXNoLXBsYXllci01MzQ0Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">Adobe Flash Player download</a>, you will enjoy these top new features:
<br /><br />* Stage 3D accelerated graphics rendering
<br />      Explore a new architecture for high-performance 2D/3D GPU hardware accelerated graphics rendering by Adobe, which provides low-level Stage3D APIs for advanced rendering in apps and gives framework developers classes of interactive experiences.
<br />    * Native 64-bit support
<br />      Flash Player can now take advantage of native support for 64-bit operating systems and 64-bit web browsers on Linux®, Mac OS, and Windows®.
<br />    * Multi-threaded video decoding
<br />      Deliver live streaming and real-time interactive video with improved playback performance and increased frame rates of high bit rate content running on Windows, Mac OS, and Linux.
<br />    * Enhanced mouse controls and relative coordinates
<br />      Create immersive, panoramic games for new classes of content, including first-person games that take advantage of infinite scrolling, mouse lock, relative mouse coordinates, and right- and middle-click events.
<br /><br />As Adobe Flash Player is so powerful and completely free, more than 99% of internet users have installed it to experience the Web at its fullest. If you are not the one of them, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2Fkb2JlLWZsYXNoLXBsYXllci01MzQ0Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">download Adobe Flash Player</a> right now to get more vivid information and entertainment from the web.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="998dcefab4c55d37dbe057cba7df4280" url=""><![CDATA[Why download Firefox instead of other web browsers?<br/><br/>Are you bothered about the slow and frequently-crashed web browser? Want to change it to another one? The competition between popular web browsers (Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Internet Explorer) is quite strong in these days, and it is a hard choice for Internet users to choose a suitable one.
<br /><br />According to many users’ experience, comprehensively speaking, Firefox is considered to be the most reliable browser at present. Let’s analyze its strong points after a quick <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL21vemlsbGEtZmlyZWZveC05MjU4OS5odG1s" target="_blank">Firefox download</a> and installation.
<br /><br />Advantage 1: User friendly interface
<br />Unlike Google chrome which removes menu bar totally, Firefox gives you the right to decide which shows in the interface. Besides the user friendly appearance, Firefox also allows you to customize the appearance on your own by changing themes and skins, making it more attractive.
<br /><br />Advantage 2: Fast webpage rendering
<br />Open this page in Firefox, it will be quickly loaded due to the great hardware acceleration technology, using less of your computer’s memory, and saving you from the bad mood after a long loading delay.
<br /><br />Advantage 3: Secure browsing
<br />Firefox makes two important security changes lately. It adopts Content Security Policy to block one of the most common types of browser threats, cross-site scripting attacks, thus enables sites to report the legitimate content to the browser when it is visited. Another security improvement is the use of HTTP Strict Transport Security, which lets Firefox automatically create a secure internet connection, preventing your log-in information from being intercepted.
<br /><br />Advantage 4: Rich add-ons
<br />Firefox has plenty of free add-ons to enhance browser function and personalize browser appearance by adding extensions, themes and plug-ins to the browser. Plug-ins and Extensions are easily available by clicking Add-ons from Tools menu in menu bar.
<br /><br />Here are several practical extensions:
<br />Google Browser Sync - allow users to sync configuration between computers through the Internet.
<br />Google Web Accelerator- accelerate website loading
<br />SeoQuake – quick review of website parameters in the search engine results pages.
<br />Wiki dictionary – online translate words or whole webpage.
<br />Adblocker plus – ward off unwanted pop up ads and other animated image ads.
<br /><br />After adding the add-ons, you are able to disable or remove them on a per-case basis.
<br /><br />These advantages make it valuable and hot to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL21vemlsbGEtZmlyZWZveC05MjU4OS5odG1s" target="_blank">download Firefox</a>, but it is not enough. Competition has forced Mozilla to put out better browser by constant updates. The latest version opens a New Tab that emulates nine most frequently visited sites for your convenience, and is able to sync your bookmarks, passwords, preferences, history, and tabs with Firefox installed on another computer.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Free download software</a> from bestdownloadreview.com, where you can get 100% free browsers without any spyware, viruses, and other malware. Moreover, relevant and reliable news, information and updates about the software are also available timely.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ebd0fc545032408c41fde8fc433214ce" url=""><![CDATA[Google Chrome Download - Get a Perfect Browsing Solution<br/><br/>You may be used to your current web browser, and do not want to change to another one, except that the new browser is more attractive. Google Chrome will give you enough reasons to change to a better browser.
<br /><br />Chrome browser developed by Google has steadily gained massive popularity since released in 2008, available for Windows XP, Vista, and 7, Mac OS 10.5 and later (Intel only), Linux, and are being developed for Win 8. It becomes the second most widely used browser at present, only after Internet Explorer. Every minute a multitude of people are hitting the Google Chrome download button. Why so many internet users choose it? The reasons are as following.
<br /><br />Reason 1: Simple user interface
<br />Launch Chrome, you will see a clean, and well organized layout, having no menus and toolbars on the interface like other browsers, as it takes efficiency and ease of use as the aim.
<br /><br />Reason 2: Advanced tab browsing
<br />From the tab context menu, you can duplicate tabs, close all other tabs, and restore the closed tab. By drag and drop, you can rearrange tab order, and even drag tab to open a new window. Tab isolation does not only mean that tabs appear separately, but also they function independently. When a troubling tab stops responding, the browser confines only the frozen tab, so that other tabs and the overall browser continue to run.
<br /><br />Reason 3: Quick loading speed
<br />The main reason to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2dvb2dsZS1DaHJvbWUtOTMwMTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">download Chrome</a> is for its unbelievably fast loading speed, which is verified to be the quickest among the major browsers and is getting faster with every new release. 
<br />Chrome shows its fast responding speed by starting up from desktop quickly, loading web pages in a snap, and running complex web applications swiftly, no matter the size of the application.
<br /><br />Reason 4: Strong Security
<br />It makes use of the built-in malware and phishing protection to secure the web, and releases new updates to make sure there is no security hole in the browser.
<br />It uses a sandboxing technique as well to block malware and isolate the related tab from others, preventing them being affected. 
<br /><br />Reason 5: Synchronization
<br />With your Google account, Chrome can sync your bookmarks, browser preferences and extensions to any computer once you sign into your account. It’s ideal for households with a single computer, and for a person with two or more computers.
<br /><br />Reason 6: More available features 
<br />Its task manager allows you to check the detailed information about browser memory usage, running processes, and provides the ability to terminate them.
<br />Thousands of apps, extensions, and themes are available in Chrome Web Store to enhance the browser function or give it a new appearance.
<br /><br />Google Chrome is unquestionably the best overall internet browser on the market - easy to use, lightning fast, secure and has thousands of applications and extensions. 
<br /><br />It is effortless to do <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2dvb2dsZS1DaHJvbWUtOTMwMTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Chrome download</a> from bestdownloadreview.com, a leading freeware and shareware download website for users to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free download software</a>. It provides the safest, fastest, most stable and comprehensive software download service, as well as the reviews about the latest version of software.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="430bbe1981b476f930c36657246ecc93" url=""><![CDATA[Internet Explorer Download - No. 1 Choice of Worldwide Users<br/><br/>Till May, 2012, Internet Explorer is still the first choice of internet users according to Wikimedia visitor log analysis report. Why Internet Explorer gained such popularity over decades? For an Internet user, fast and stable are two important features every user wants, with other requirements, like security and easy to use. But unfortunately, some browsers are fast, but take lots of system resources, and are prone to crash. While others are stable but the loading speed is not satisfying. As a browser which fits all these needs, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2ludGVybmV0LWV4cGxvcmVyLTkzMDIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Internet Explorer download</a> becomes the final solution of web browsing.
<br /><br />Let’s see how Internet Explorer outperforms in these aspects:
<br /><br />Interface
<br />The latest version - Internet Explorer 9 has a simple and minimalist interface, with all unneeded buttons and controls removed, but not bring the trouble to find the options you want with difficulty. You can only have address bar and tab there, leaving more webpage viewing area.
<br /><br />Tab
<br />Internet Explorer treats each browsing tab as its own system. If one tab crashes or freezes, it won’t crash the entire browser. And in the case of unexpected shutdowns, it will restore that tab for you automatically at next time. When you open a 'New Tab' page, you'll be able to see the most frequently visited Web sites. In addition, if you click the link from an existing one to open a new tab, the new tab is placed next to the originating tab, rather than at the end of your list of tabs. This makes it much easier to keep related tabs organized and grouped together.
<br /><br />Speed
<br />Internet Explorer 9 makes web pages fast and responsive by taking advantage of the PC resources and hardware accelerated graphics, making loading times quicker and browsing smoother.
<br /><br />Security
<br />As for safety, the new Tracking Protection and ActiveX Filtering features let you block certain sites from tracking your movements online, and switch off ActiveX elements on a per-site basis. 
<br />What is more, users are protected by SmartScreen filter to block websites and files, which are fraudulent or contain malware.
<br /><br />Compatibility
<br />IE is better compatible with some websites than other browsers. For example, when you process an online payment, IE allows the website to launch the related banking application for you. But in Google Chrome, the application cannot be started. 
<br /><br />All in all, Internet Explorer is the ideal example of how modern web browsers can and should be – take little system resources while remaining fast, feature-packed and easy to use.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2ludGVybmV0LWV4cGxvcmVyLTkzMDIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Download Internet Explorer</a> directly from the top download website – bestdownloadreview, an Internet website that provides <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free software download</a> and professional reviews. You will not have to go through the tedious processes, just one click on download button, you will instantly get IE. From the download website, you can always get the latest version of Internet Explorer and other web browsers.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="38c575bc52ae890bca6c376272ac6e77" url=""><![CDATA[How to Recover RAR Password with RAR Password Unlocker?<br/><br/>Forgot RAR Password?
<br />I created a password protected WinRAR file months ago to prevent peeping eyes, since I was sharing a computer with others, but unfortunately, I forgot the password now, what can I do to get the password? I’ve made some search and found that <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3Jhci1wYXNzd29yZC11bmxvY2tlci01NzQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">rar password recovery</a> tool may recover the password, how to use it?
<br /><br />RAR Password Unlocker Introduction
<br />RAR Password Unlocker is specially designed to recover the forgotten WinRAR/RAR password that created in WinRAR 4.11 and its previous versions. RAR archive with an encrypted file name is also supported.
<br />Key features:
<br /><br />* 3 attack options: Brute-force, Brute-force with user-defined Mask and Dictionary.
<br />    * Support multi-core CPU and NVIDIA-GPU acceleration to fasten recovery speed to a large extend.
<br />    * Save password recovery process automatically.
<br />    * Shut down computer automatically when recovery process finishes.
<br />    * 2 year free update and support.
<br /><br />RAR Password Unlocker Tutorial
<br />Download this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3Jhci1wYXNzd29yZC11bmxvY2tlci01NzQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">rar password cracker</a>, install and launch it to see the right interface. Click Open to import the locked RAR archive.
<br /><br />Attack option 1 Brute-force Attack
<br />Applicable Condition: If the encrypted rar file is created by others and you know nothing about the password, please choose this one, and it will cost a much longer time.
<br />Operation: Check the first option - Brute-force Attack, and click start button to run password cracking.
<br /><br />Attack option 2 Brute-force with Mask Attack
<br />Applicable Condition: You are the one who set rar password and can remember a bit information about the password, such as password length, uppercase, lowercase, numbers, symbols, prefix and suffix, the cracking time will be greatly shortened by Brute-force with Mask attack.
<br />Operation: Check the second option - Brute-force with Mask Attack in the first tab, and then set the information you know in second tab (the more accurate you set, the quicker you will get the password), and finally click start button to run password cracking.
<br />Note: If you set prefix and suffix, please remember to remove them from the password length. That is to say, if your forgotten RAR password contains 5-9 characters, and it starts with &quot;M&quot;, ends with &quot;n&quot;, then the min length should be 3, and the max length should be 7.
<br /><br />Attack option 3 Dictionary Attack
<br />Applicable Condition: Nowadays, there are many powerful dictionaries for password cracking, including not only the English words, but also the common used password combinations with an amount of tens of thousands. But you should know that the larger the dictionary is, the longer the cracking time is.
<br />What is more, you can set your own dictionary, if you are the one tend to use a limited range of symbols in the password, such as nickname, birthday, telephone numbers, important days or anything similar. Input them in text document by each line, and save it.
<br />Operation: Check the third option - Dictionary Attack in the first tab, import the dictionary in txt format in third dictionary tab, the default dictionary is also available, and then start password cracking.
<br /><br />You can find RAR Password Unlocker download on the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free software download</a> site.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d9205a3b27c37d354515cc9f9c602869" url=""><![CDATA[How to make full use of WinRAR?<br/><br/>What is WinRAR?
<br /><br />WinRAR is developed to extract RAR and ZIP archives, and support CAB, ARJ, LZH, TAR, GZ, ACE, UUE, BZ2, JAR, ISO, Z, 7-Zip archives as well. It can also compress and encrypt files in RAR or ZIP format for data backup and encryption, easy file transport, and saving disk space.
<br /><br />Besides that, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3dpbnJhci0zMi1iaXQtOTMwMjcuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">WinRAR download</a> offers more rich functions, such as, split file, create programmable self-extracting archives(SFX), lock archive, protect archive from damage, scan archive for viruses, convert archive to other archive types or SFX, and repair damaged archives.
<br /><br />As extraction and compression are easy and frequently used, they will not be mentioned here, let’s see how to encrypt and repair RAR archive in WinRAR.
<br />How to encrypt file with WinRAR?
<br /><br />Method 1 Though Context Menu
<br />Step 1: Right Click the file and press &quot;Add to Archive&quot;.
<br />Step 2: In the pop-up window, if you want to compress the file in ZIP, choose ZIP in Archive Format section.
<br />Step 3: Click the &quot;Advanced&quot; tab and then &quot;Set Password&quot; on the middle-right.
<br />Step 4: Input the password. You can check “encrypt file names” below as well, thus, openers will not see the file name.
<br />Step 5: Click &quot;OK&quot;, now a RAR or ZIP file is created and password-protected!
<br /><br />Method 2 Through WinRAR Wizard
<br />Step 1: Launch WinRAR program and click on Wizard from Tools menu.
<br />Step 2: On the Wizard: Choose the operation window, select Create a new archive and then click Next.
<br />Step 3: There will pop up a window, just select the file and click OK to add it to the archive.
<br />Step 4: Input an archive name and click Next button.
<br />Step 5: Click Set Password button to enter password, and press OK.
<br />Step 6: Return to the Wizard: Archive option window and just click Finish.
<br />Your password protected RAR archive will be created in your Desktop.
<br />To prevent the time-costing <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3Jhci1wYXNzd29yZC11bmxvY2tlci01NzQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">RAR password recovery</a>, keep RAR password in mind.
<br /><br />How to repair RAR archive in WinRAR?
<br /><br />Sometimes, when extracting a RAR file with WinRAR, you may encounter an error in CRC or MD5 hash check and the file is failed to open. But getting this error not mean that you can’t extract and use file anymore. As long as the file is complete, you can correct the issue using the WinRAR application itself.
<br />Step 1: Open the WinRAR application. Click on &quot;File&quot; and then &quot;Open Archive&quot; and browse to the damaged RAR file.
<br />Step 2: Press &quot;Alt&quot; + &quot;R&quot; on your keyboard, or go to Repair Archive option from Tools menu. This will bring up the WinRAR repair dialog screen.
<br />Step 3: Specify Desktop as the &quot;Folder to put the repaired archive&quot; box. Check the box that says, &quot;Treat the corrupt archive as RAR.&quot;
<br />Step 4: Press the &quot;OK&quot; button. Once it has finished repairing, a rebuilt new archive will be placed on your desktop. Open it to extract a corrupted file.
<br /><br />Download information
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Free download software</a> from bestdownloadreview.com, where you can get 100% free browsers without any spyware, viruses, and other malware. Moreover, relevant and reliable news, information and updates about the software are also available timely.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d0d619770e8cb945da5fc849fb210739" url=""><![CDATA[3 Tips to Fix Firefox Crash Problem<br/><br/><strong>Firefox Popularity</strong>
<br />For a computer, the most important application is the web browser, as you search, shopping, banking, read news, watch online videos and more, all within a browser.
<br />Firefox strives to provide the best web experience for internet users, and is the one of the three most popular browsers in the worldwide. As Millions of people around the world are using or trying to use this program, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL21vemlsbGEtZmlyZWZveC05MjU4OS5odG1s" target="_blank">Firefox download</a> are available in many websites.
<br /><br /><strong>How to Avoid Firefox Crash?</strong>
<br />In the using process of Firefox and other web browsers, the most frequently happened problem is the crash issue, though it has some relationship with the browser, other reasons can result a crash too. 
<br />Instead of changing a browser, you can do as below guides to avoid crash, not only useful to Firefox, but also applies to other browsers.
<br /><br /><strong>1. Don’t open too many tabs in a window</strong>
<br />Too many opened tabs may lead to Firefox Browser crash, the same to google chrome. Therefore try to limit the number of Firefox tabs within 10. 
<br />If you need to open more tabs at one time, try to open a new window, or drag a tab to create a new window instead of adding more tabs in one window. Certainly, avoid too many windows as well. 
<br /><br /><strong>2. Clear History, Cache and Cookies</strong>
<br />When browsing for a long time, your browser keeps caching, and stores history and cookies. Clearing the Internet cache from browser is a useful way to solve certain web page and browser problems.
<br />How to clear History, Cache and Cookies?
<br />1. Choose Tools from the menu bar, and then Clear Recent History. 
<br />2. In the Clear Recent History window, set the Time Range to Clear to Everything.
<br />3. In the list below, check Cache, History and Cookies.
<br />4. Click on the Clear Now button.
<br />Clear Recent History window disappears when the clearing finishes, restart Firefox to see if the crash problem be solved. 
<br /><br /><strong>3. Remove unneeded Add-ons</strong>
<br />One of Firefox's biggest advantages over its rivals is its vast library of add-ons, which can be used to customize the performance of your browser. After <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL21vemlsbGEtZmlyZWZveC05MjU4OS5odG1s" target="_blank">Firefox free download</a> and quick installation, you may install too many extensions and plugins. The more add-ons you install, the slower Firefox will be to start up and run. 
<br />Check all installed add-ons by opening the Tools menu, and click on Add-ons. To speed up your browser, remove or disable the unused add-ons. Restart the Firefox, you will find Firefox launches faster. 
<br /><br /><strong>Additional Information</strong>
<br />More <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free software download</a> is instantly available in bestdownloadreview.com, from which, you can get more web browsers for detailed comparison.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="971c3a23df7edcf0ddd86038bda61b43" url=""><![CDATA[What unique features you can get from Chrome browser?<br/><br/><strong>Hard to select a nice web browser?</strong>
<br />It seems to be a difficult to select the best browser from the famous ones with similar interface and function, though they look the same, actually there are differences in speed, convenience, stability, compatibility and security. Which browser or browsers would be your choice?
<br /><br /><strong>Google Chrome has 200 million active users now</strong> According to StatCounter, Chrome has been the second popular web browser used in computer from Jane to June 2012, only behind Internet Explorer, and before Mozilla Firefox. Consider that Chrome’s first stable release is in 2008, 13 years later than IE initial release, and 4 years later than Mozilla Firefox, it is easy to find out that <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2dvb2dsZS1jaHJvbWUtOTMwMTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Chrome download</a> has gained its popularity more and more quickly.
<br /><br /><strong>Why Google Chrome is so popular?</strong>
<br />The similar points, such as Synchronization, Incognito Mode, and Personalization features, with other browsers will not be mentioned here, let’s see its advantages over others.
<br />1. Fast Loading Speed
<br />This is usually the main factor for a user to decide whether use a browser or not. Google Chrome is remarkably fast to launch and load a page. In many benchmark tests, its navigation time is much swifter than all competitors, including Safari, Firefox, Internet Explorer, and Opera, and is getting faster with every new release. 
<br />2. Stability
<br />Compared with Firefox usual crash, Chrome is more stable under the same condition. In Chrome, only one tab crashes instead of the whole browser, as Chrome prevents what happens in one tab from affecting another, stops only the unresponsive tab, and other tabs continue to run. 
<br />In addition, Chrome provides a process management utility called Task Manager for users to check the memory and CPU used by each tab and plug-in, and even terminate the troubling tab. 
<br />3. Cool Interface
<br />Once <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free download software</a> and get it installed, you will appreciate this function directly. Unlike other browsers, Chrome offers a clean window without menu options and toolbars on the interface, giving you largest space to view web content. To quicken the access to your frequently visited website, you can choose Show bookmark bar from Settings icon, other options are also available there.
<br />4. Full OS Support
<br />Among the top 5 browsers, only Chrome, Firefox and Opera supports all desktop platforms, including Windows, Mac OS X and Linux.
<br /><br /><strong>Get Google Chrome Now</strong>
<br />As Chrome offers easy operation to import bookmark and other information from another browser, it is no need to worry about the old browser’s data lose.
<br />Once you <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2dvb2dsZS1jaHJvbWUtOTMwMTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">download Chrome</a> and install it, Chrome will automatically prompt you to update if there is a new stable release. So no matter what version you download, you can always get the latest version.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6b72c3955c96c537d6dbd2ab3b46f7c8" url=""><![CDATA[Reset Mac Password: What You Need to Know<br/><br/><strong>Reset Mac Password</strong>
<br />Forgot Mac password? Don’t feel frustrated and take it easy! This happens to all of us. All you need to do is calm down and check if you really cannot keep the track of your Mac password. If the answer is yes, next find the most suitable way to reset your Mac password and get back in your Mac again. Here’re some simple solutions for you.
<br /><br /><strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2UvcmVzZXQtbWFjLXBhc3N3b3JkLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Reset Mac password</a> - Try to remember it again</strong>
<br />Have you ever noticed that some things you are familiar with can be forgotten suddenly like your friend’s name and a frequently-used word? Usually, you can remember these things again. This also works for your lost Mac password. Sometimes you just temporarily forget your Mac password and it will be automatically back into your mind later. No need for you to hurry up and resort to others under this circumstance. But you can check out the places, people and other things that your password is based on and get some clues to help you recall your password.
<br /><br /><strong>Reset Mac password – with Mac installation disc</strong>
<br />Resetting Mac password is an easy job if you have the installation disc for your Mac. Just take the steps below for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2UvcmVzZXQtbWFjLXBhc3N3b3JkLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Mac password reset</a>:
<br />Step 1. Insert your Mac installation disc in your computer and hold the “C” key to boot from disc.
<br />Step 2. Select your language, and ten select Password Reset when the &quot;Utilities&quot; or &quot;Installer&quot; menu appears.
<br />Step 3. Select theMac hard disk that the forgotten password is on, and then select the username of the forgotten mac user account. And you’ll then be asked to select a new password.
<br />Step 4. Type a new password for the selected Mac user account, type it again to confirm it, and then Click &quot;Save&quot;.
<br />Step 5. Restart your Mac as usual from the hard drive and you’ll be able to log in your computer with the newly reset password.
<br />Note: Resetting the Keychain Password in OS X is also required if you reset your user account password using Mac OS X Install disc. Otherwise, you will be prompted to enter a keychain password each time an application requires authentication that your keychain would normally provide.
<br /><br /><strong>Reset Mac password – without Mac installation disc</strong>
<br />Not have the installation disc your computer comes with? Here’s another way to reset your forgotten Mac password. This method has two phases. Creating a new administrator account on Mac OS X is the first phrase, next you can use this new admin account to reset password of previous account.
<br /><br /><strong>Phrase 1.</strong> Create new admin account on Mac OS X
<br />Step 1. Restart system and hold “Cmd + S” keys from keyboard until it shows Terminal.
<br />Step 2. Type the following commands on the Terminal. Please remember to press Enter after typing each command. Your computer will restart once this is done.
<br />/sbin/mount –uaw
<br />rm /var/db/.applesetupdone
<br />reboot
<br />Step 3. When you see the Welcome wizard”, follow the wizard instructions until the Create Your Account window appears.
<br />Step 4. Type a new user name and password to create a new admin account on Mac OS X, and click Continue button.  A new Mac admin account will be created and you will automatically log into it. Next, you can go to phrase 2 to reset your lost Mac password of the previous user account with this new admin account.
<br /><br /><strong>Phrase 2.</strong> Reset the forgotten Mac password
<br />Step 5. Go to Apple icon -&gt; System Preferences -&gt; Account. You’ll see all the user accounts on your Mac.
<br />Step 6. Click on lock icon to enable your target user account and reset its password.
<br />Step 7. Enter the Password of the newly-created admin account and hit OK button
<br />Step 8. Now the target user account is enabled for changes, select this user and click the  Reset Password button.
<br />Step 9. Type a new password for the target user account, type the password again to confirm, type a password hint (optional), and click Reset Password button.
<br />Step 10. Log in your target user account with the new password, and then delete the newly-created admin account.
<br /><br /><strong>One more tip:</strong> Unlike Mac, there’s a great number of ways if you forgot login password to Windows and the most efficient solution is to get an excellent tool like Windows Password Unlocker, Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery, etc. These tools allow you to instantly reset any forgotten Windows password on all popular Windows platforms, including Windows 7. Of course, the best way for you is to create a password reset disk ahead of forgetting the password through the built-in feature of Windows.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f7fbfbfe6d566eba8a15dd6d3036b94b" url=""><![CDATA[Windows 7 Password: All You Need to Know for Better Computer<br/><br/>Everyone knows a Windows 7 password can keep your important and private data secure by stopping the unauthorized viewers. But there is something that you may still not know about this password. Here’re things you need to know for better computer life if you have little computer knowledge. 
<br /><br /><strong>Types of Windows 7 password</strong>
<br />If you have ever created a new user account on your computer, you should know that Windows 7 has three types of user accounts with different privileges: administrator, stand user and guest. So your Windows 7 password also has 3 types: administrator password, standard user password and guest password. Whether you want to download or install a new program, or change other settings affecting the computer, an administrator password is required.
<br /><br /><strong>Change Windows 7 password</strong>
<br />Changing Windows 7 password on a regular basis is highly recommended for security concerns. To do this job, just go to Start -&amp;gt; Control Panel -&amp;gt; Family Safety and User Account -&amp;gt; User Account, next you’ll find the link for changing your password. The old password of the user account you want to change password for is required to set a new password. If you forget the old password, you still can rest it to a new one by using an admin account on the same computer.
<br /><br /><strong>Windows 7 password reset Disk</strong>
<br />Today we have too many passwords to keep track of, like Gmail password, Paypal password, credit card password, etc. So it’s not surprising if you forget your Windows 7 password one day. However you can avoid this problem by creating a password reset in advance through the Windows built-in feature. With this password reset disk, you can change a lost Windows 7 password to a new one when you are locked of PC. To make such a disk, just go to Start -&amp;gt; Control Panel -&amp;gt; Family Safety and User Account -&amp;gt; User Account, next you’ll find the Create a password reset disk on the left pane.
<br /><br /><strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2UvcmVzZXQtd2luZG93cy03LXBhc3N3b3JkLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Forgot Windows 7 password</a></strong>
<br />Though Windows 7 comes with ability for creating a password reset disk, few people make full use of this feature and create such a disk ahead of forgetting their passwords. What you feel lucky is that there’re so many third-party Windows 7 password reset applications for resetting forgotten login password to Windows. Password Unlocker Bundle is a good example. This program gives you an easy and instant way to create a bootable password reset disk with CD/DVD or USB drive to reset your forgotten password and access your PC again. 100% password reset is guaranteed. In addition, this bundle also allows you to reset passwords for Office 2010/2007 word/excel/ppt files, RAR/ZIP archives, PDF files, MS SQL server, etc.
<br /><br /><strong>Dos and Don’ts for Windows 7 password</strong>
<br />1. Make a strong yet easy-to-remember <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2UvcmVzZXQtd2luZG93cy03LXBhc3N3b3JkLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Windows 7 password</a>.
<br />2. Create a password hint and password reset disk to avoid troubles caused by a forgotten Windows password in future.
<br />3. Change your Windows 7 password on a regular basis.
<br />4. Don’t use your Windows 7 password everywhere.
<br />5. Don’t tell others your password or write it on a sticky note.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="992617086a84d910d9b21db0656e67de" url=""><![CDATA[Can I Upgrade to Windows 8 without Admin Password?<br/><br/><strong>Question:</strong> I plan to upgrade my PC to Windows 8. I do not plan to download it. Rather, I will purchase the CD-ROM from my local Microsoft Store the day it comes out. Anyway, I have not had the admin password to my computer for a long time. I have been using an account that does NOT allow me to download or change anything. I cannot use those programs that break the passwords because I can't download anything! 
<br /><br />I plan on doing a CLEAN INSTALL of Windows 8 so it is like I have a brand new system. But I don't want to spent $100 on a new OS and then find out it doesn't work because I am not an admin. I don't see why I should have a problem. It is a disk! Anyway, can anyone tell me if I will run into this issue?
<br /><br /><strong>Answer:</strong> Reset Your Forgotten Windows Admin Password 
<br />Based on the description above, my suggestion is to regain admin rights of your computer by resetting your forgotten administrator password with Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery. This will only takes you a few minutes, even you are novice. 100% security and password reset rate guaranteed.
<br /><br /><strong>What you’ll need?</strong>
<br />1. Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery
<br />2. A USB flash drive or CD/DVD
<br />3. Another PC for software download and installation (You can borrow your friend’s if you don’t own another PC.)
<br /><br /><strong>What you will do?</strong>
<br />1. Download and install Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery in any PC (not a Mac).
<br />2. Burn a bootable password reset disk with CD/DVD or USB flash drive. This will cost a few seconds. It’s very easy. Only one click required for this job. Once the disk is burned, you should turn to the computer you forget admin password of.
<br />3. Insert the created bootable disk in your computer, and set BIOS of the computer to boot from CD/DVD or USB.
<br />4. Reset Forgotten Windows admin password within a few clicks. Once the password is reset, click Reboot button and your computer will restart automatically.
<br />Note: Please remove the bootable disk during restarting to ensure that your computer boot as usual form the hard disk.
<br />5. When you see the Windows login screen, log into your admin account without password.
<br /><br />Tip: Rekeysoft <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2Uvd2luZG93cy04LXBhc3N3b3JkLXJlY292ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Windows Password Recovery</a> is an easy yet powerful tool that is capable of resetting forgotten login passwords to all popular Windows versions, including Windows7, Vista, XP, 2008, 2003, 2000. And <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2Uvd2luZG93cy04LXBhc3N3b3JkLXJlY292ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Windows 8 password recovery</a> feature will be soon available in this program. It’s easy, fast and safe. Your best choice when you happen to forget Windows password.
<br /><br /><strong>One more solution</strong>
<br />Password Unlocker Bundle is a great alterative to Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery. It has all the features included in the latter, plus the ability to recover passwords for RAR/Zip archives, Office 2010/2007 files, PDF files, MS SQL server, IE, IM. GPU-acceleration and Multi-core acceleration are supported.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bd23a7fea450201f94bc1e39328053ff" url=""><![CDATA[Can I Reset Windows 7 password with Installation Disc on HP<br/><br/>Allison cannot log on HP Pavlilion dv6000 that runs on Windows 7, but she knew her password and just didn’t work. She asked if a Windows 7 installation disc would help and any other solutions would be great.
<br /><br />To be honest, the easiest way to reset a lost Windows password is to use a previously created password reset disk. You can go to Start button -&gt; Control Panel -&gt; Family Safety and User Accounts -&gt; User Accounts, and then click the Create a password reset disk on the left pane. This will cost you a few seconds. If this password reset disk is not available, a Windows 7 installation disc will be also Ok when you <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbnlwYXNzd29yZHJlY292ZXJ5LmNvbS9mb3Jnb3Qtd2luZG93cy03LXBhc3N3b3JkLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">forgot Windows 7 password</a>. All you need is to take the steps listed below:
<br /><br />Step 1.Start you locked HP from the Windows 7 installation disc.
<br />Step 2. Select your language and click Next after loading the setup files.
<br />Step 3. Select the Repair your computer link on the Install Windows screen.
<br />Step 4. Select the operating system to repair and click Next .
<br />Step 5. Click Command Prompt to open a command prompt window.
<br />Step 6. On the command prompt, type the following commands:
<br />copy c:windowssystem32sethc.exe c:
<br />copy /y c:windowssystem32cmd.exe c:windowssystem32sethc.exe
<br />Step 7. Reboot the computer.
<br />Step 8. On the logon screen, tap Shift five times and you’ll see an administrator mode command prompt.
<br />Step 9. Enter &quot;net user MyUserName MyNewPassword&quot; (replace the MyUserName and MyUserPassword with the combination you want) and press Enter.
<br />Step 10. Exit the Command Prompt, and log into the computer using your new password.
<br /><br />In my opinion, the most efficient method for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbnlwYXNzd29yZHJlY292ZXJ5LmNvbS93aW5kb3dzLTctcGFzc3dvcmQtcmVzZXQtZGlzay5odG1s" target="_blank">Windows 7 password reset</a> is to use a great Windows password reset app like Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery. This program enables you to burn a bootable Windows password reset disk in any PC in seconds. And with that burned disk, you can instantly reset any forgotten administrator and other user password for all popular Windows platforms, including Windows 7, Vista, XP, Server 2008, Sever 2003, 2000.
<br /><br />The best parts of Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery lie in that it guarantees 100% password reset rate without any data loss or damage, and it only requires 5 minutes to do the Windows password reset job. Everyone can use this program. No any special skills required. You just need to follow its instructions to do the Windows 7 password reset job within a few clicks.
<br /><br />Things you’ll need:
<br />1. A PC to download and install Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery.
<br />2. A USB flash drive(If the USB drive contains some important data, please backup at first)
<br /><br />How-to guide:
<br />1. Download and install Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery.
<br />2. Burn a bootable Windows password reset disk with USB drive.
<br />3. Start the PC you want to reset password of from the burned disk.
<br />4. Reset Windows password within a few clicks (Select the user account you want to reset password of -&gt; Click Reset button -&gt; Reboot).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb44474ddc992ed68c0b7a559e9d8f8" url=""><![CDATA[Accidentally Locked Myself out of Windows 7 Computer? What t<br/><br/>Question: I've locked myself out of my Windows 7 account with Administrator privileges. Everything I try needs me to provide an administrator password, which I used to lock myself out. Is there anything I can do?
<br /><br />Answer: Reset your Windows 7 administrator password to regain administrator privileges of your computer.
<br /><br />Taking your Windows 7 computer to a computer repair shop or calling for an IT professional can be your choice if you don’t intend to fix this problem on your own. But this will cost you a large sum of money while time-consuming. So this is not suggested. The best solution here is to reset Windows 7 admin password on your own. No special technical skill required. Everyone can do it by following the methods listed below.
<br /><br />The easiest and fastest solution – use Windows Password Unlocker
<br /><br />Windows Password Unlocker is an easy yet efficient Windows password reset app designed for personal and business users. With this simple utility, you can burn a bootable Windows password reset disk with CD/DVD or USB drive in seconds to reset the lost Windows password on locked PC. And you will be access the locked PC without password. If your PC is locked and not accessible, you can burn the bootable password reset disk in any other PC.
<br /><br />This program can reset any type of Windows password, such as Windows administrator password, standard user password and guest password. It support all popular Windows platforms like Windows 7/Vista/XP and Windows servers. And <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2Uvd2luZG93cy04LXBhc3N3b3JkLXJlY292ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Windows 8 password reset</a> feature will be soon available. 100% password reset rate and 100% safe are guaranteed. The whole Windows password reset process will cost you no more than 5 minutes, regardless of your computing level and password strength. Overall steps:
<br /><br />1. Download and install Windows Password Unlocker in any PC.
<br />2. Burn a bootable Windows password reset disk with CD/DVD/USB drive.
<br />3. Start your locked PC from the bootable password reset disk.
<br />4. Reset lost Windows 7 administrator password within a few clicks.
<br /><br />Completely free solution – use Ophcrack or Linux Live CD
<br />If you want to solve your problem without any charge, the best solution is to use Opchrack or create a Linux Live CD.
<br /><br />Ophcrack is a complete free Windows password recovery that runs on Windows 7/Vista/XP, Mac, linux. Based on rainbow tables, this free Windows password cracker allows you to recover your forgotten Windows password, not reset the password. But this freeware is complicated and time-consuming compared with Windows Password Unlocker. Most of important, the password recovery rate is not guaranteed.
<br /><br />Creating a Linux Live CD is another choice when you forgot Windows 7 password or other Windows passwords. But if you are newbie, this method is not suggested as it requires a little technique skills.
<br /><br />The last solution – Reinstall Windows
<br />Reinstalling Windows is always regarded as the last solution when it comes to bypass Windows password. This will not only erase some of your important data, but also take you much time.
<br /><br />One more tip: In reality, the best solution for resetting a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2UvZm9yZ290LW15LXdpbmRvd3MtcGFzc3dvcmQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">forgotten Windows password</a> is to use the password reset disk created through the Windows 7 built-in feature. But the presupposition is that you remember to create that disk before forgetting your computer password.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="efeb45f7883fcdf0c442c7e4a52a4011" url=""><![CDATA[Microsoft Blocks Windows 8 Start Button, Boot-to-desktop Hac<br/><br/>“Microsoft made some changes to Windows that prevent the .scf hack from working correctly,” said Rafael Rivera in an email reply to questions.
<br />The “.scf hack” Rivera referred to was first disclosed in April, and allowed users of Windows 8 Consumer Preview to circumvent the tile-based Startscreen and automatically shift to the familiar desktop after logging on.
<br /><br />Well-known ZDNet blogger Mary Jo Foley first reported Rivera’s conclusions earlier Monday. She also said other hacks, including some that restore the Start button to Windows 8, have been blocked.
<br />The changes were made by Microsoft before it announced the Windows 8 RTM, or “release to manufacturing,” milestone last week. Final copies of Windows 8 Enterprise leaked to file-sharing websites a day later.
<br /><br />Although previews of Windows 8 could be modified to insert a homemade Start button and with more work, bypass the Start screen at log on, Microsoft has invalidated those work-arounds in the RTM build, said Rivera.
<br /><br />The change wasn’t a surprise: In May, Thurrott said Microsoft had been “furiously ripping out legacy code” in the new operating system to prevent users from adding a Start button or booting straight to the desktop.
<br /><br />Microsoft pulled the Start button from Windows 8 before it shipped the Consumer Preview in late February. The Release Preview, which debuted in late May, also omitted the 17-year-old iconic user interface (UI) element.
<br /><br />The lack of the familiar Start button and the inability to sidestep the new Start screen — two separate, but intertwined issues — have been sore spots among long-time Windows users, and among the reasons why some research firms have predicted businesses will be slow to adopt the new OS.
<br /><br />Start8, a free tool released in March by Stardock, may still work in Windows 8 RTM, Foley reported. Start8 adds a Start button to the Windows desktop and optionally allowed users to skip the Start screen at log on.
<br /><br />Stardock was unable Monday to confirm that Start8 works on Windows 8 RTM, however, as legitimate copies are still a week away from release to developers, IT professionals and enterprises.
<br /><br />“The program should work, unless capability for it to function was intentionally stripped away,” a Stardock spokeswoman said in an email reply to questions. “We’re definitely excited to test with the RTM build and the new Start8 features we’ve been developing internally.”
<br /><br />Instead of a Start button, Windows 8 uses a “hot corner” at the lower left. When that hotspot is touched or clicked, the interface switches from the traditional desktop UI to the tile-centric environment, or vice versa. At boot, Windows 8 presents a log on screen where the user must enter a Windows ID; at that point, the Start screen appears.
<br /><br />By the way, as Wndows 8 is coming in next 2 months, what we prepare to do is to learn more about it, such as the interface of Windows 8, the special features. We know that Windows 8 is taken advanced graphical password logon, which is easier than a text-based password for most people to remember with using pictures instead of letters if you <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbnlwYXNzd29yZHJlY292ZXJ5LmNvbS9yZXNldC13aW5kb3dzLXBhc3N3b3JkLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">forgot Windows password</a> for Windows 8. Though there are so many <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbnlwYXNzd29yZHJlY292ZXJ5LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">Windows password recovery</a> tools to reset the password such as Ophcrack, PC Login Now, the graphical password logon will save your time.
<br /><br />Let’s pay more attention to the coming of Windows 8 and its new figure.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="148b1aa4c55b381e78326227064578d8" url=""><![CDATA[Windows 7 Password Reset Solutions You Can Use<br/><br/>A Windows login password can stop all unauthorized users from accessing your computer. However, if you forgot this password, you’ll be also be locked out of your computer. This is terrible! Here’s going to show you all the solutions you can use when you forgot Windows 7 password.
<br /><br /><strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbnlwYXNzd29yZHJlY292ZXJ5LmNvbS93aW5kb3dzLTctcGFzc3dvcmQtcmVzZXQtZGlzay5odG1s" target="_blank">Windows 7 Password Reset</a> Solutions from Microsoft</strong>
<br />Microsoft provides you 2 easy ways to reset a forgotten Windows 7 password: use another admin account on the same computer or use a password reset disk.
<br /><br />To use the admin account to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbnlwYXNzd29yZHJlY292ZXJ5LmNvbS9yZXNldC13aW5kb3dzLTctcGFzc3dvcmQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">reset Windows 7 password</a>, you just need to log into your admin account, and then just go to Local Users and Groups by clicking Start button, typing lusrmgr.msc into the Search box, and then pressing ENTER.? Next double-click Local Users and Groups, and then click Users. Right-click the account that you need to reset the password for, and then click Set Password.
<br /><br />To use a password reset disk to reset your password, you need to turn on your computer until the Windows logon screen. Type the wrong password and you’ll receive an error message. After clicking OK to close this massage, you’ll see the Reset password link. Click this link and then follow the instructions.
<br /><br />These two methods are useful. Unluckily, most users the password for the only user account on Windows 7 without creating a password reset disk in advance.
<br /><br /><strong>Windows 7 Password Reset Solutions from third-party software providers</strong>
<br /><br />Nothing to worry about if the solutions from Microsoft don’t work. There’s a great many third-party Windows password recovery tools to help you walk through this problem. Both freeware and shareware are available. For free tools, you can try Opchrack, Offline NT Password &amp; Registry Editor, Kon-Boot, Cain &amp; Abel, etc. For commercial tools, you can try Windows Password Unlocker, Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery, etc.
<br /><br />Of all the Windows password recovery tools, Windows Password Recovery is highly suggested as it can reset your forgotten Windows 7 password in a matter of minutes without any data loss or damage. 100% password reset rate is guaranteed and free technical support is available. And with this program, you can not only reset the lost Windows password, but also create a new admin account to get back in your computer again.
<br /><br />With Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery, you can reset the forgotten password in 3 simple steps: Download and install this program in any PC -&gt; Burn a bootable password reset CD/DVD/USB -&gt; Reset password with the burned disk.
<br /><br /><strong>Windows 7 Password Reset Solutions You Might Not Know</strong>
<br />Creating a Linux LIveCD is another method to bypass Windows 7 password after you forgot it. Just download the live .iso file for any Linux distribution and burn it into CD. Once this disk is created, start your computer from it and reset your forgotten Windows password. This method requires a little technical skill.
<br /><br />Another Windows 7 password reset solution you might know is to use Sticky Keys trick. The installation disc of your Windows 7 is required. Of course you can use the installation disc to reinstall Window.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f1c53329844b2c6059eff9a6f113276f" url=""><![CDATA[Password Unlocker Bundle: Recover Various Forgotten Password<br/><br/>Whether you forgot Windows password, Office password, PDF password or RAR password, you need to find some great password recovery tools to recover or reset these passwords sothat you can access the data contained in your computer, Office files, PDF files, etc. Here it’s highly recommended you to use Password Unlocker Bundle, which can help you recover various passwords.
<br /><br /><strong>What’s Password Unlocker Bundle?</strong>
<br />Password Unlocker Bundle is a 14-in-1 password recovery tool that recover passwords for more than 60 file and application types. With this tool, you can reset Windows password, change SQL server sa and other user passwords, recover passwords for Office Word/Excel/PPT 1997-2003 files, retrieve passwords for RAR/ZIP arcives, PDF files, etc.
<br /><br />This program comes with a very simple and intuitive interface and enables you to do various <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2UvYnVuZGxlLXJlY292ZXJ5LW9wdGlvbnMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">password recovery</a> jobs within a few clicks. Most important, this program uses the advanced technologies to ensure you recover passwords faster than other similar products. For Windows, MS SQL Server, IE, IM, Access, it can allows you to enjoy instant recovery when you forgot passwords for these applications and files. And GPU-acceleration and Multi-core acceleration are supported when you need to recover passwords for Office, RAR and PDF through brute-force and Dictionary attacks.
<br /><br /><strong>Reasons to use Password Unlocker Bundle</strong>
<br /><br />Reason 1. All-in-one password recovery tool
<br />Password Unlocker Bundle integrates 14 password recovery tools into one program. With this program, you can recover any password you need, including Windows password, Office password, RAR/ZIP password, PDF password, MS SQL Server password, Access password, IM Password, IE website password.
<br /><br />Reason 2. Support GPU, Multi-core and SEE
<br />This all-in-one password recovery tool recovers faster than other similar products by using its unique search algorithm and optimized SEE codes. Moreover, GPU-acceleration and Multi-core acceleration are supported for Office, RAR and PDF for significantly accelerated recovery speed.
<br /><br />Reason 3. Support latest versions of Windows, Office, WinRAR, etc.
<br />With Password Unlocker Bundle, you can reset password for the latest Windows platforms like Windows 7/ 2008 server. It also can recover passwords for Office 210/2007, RAR and ZIP archives created by any program including the latest version of WinRAR.
<br /><br />Reason 4. Recover passwords at a low price
<br />Software bundle is a great way to save your money. Password Unlocker Bundle is no exception. Integrating 14 tools into one, this bundle costs you no more than $100. And Password Unlocker Bundle Standard only costs you $39.95 but can reset or recover passwords for Windows, Office, RAR/ZIP, Access PDF, IM, IE.
<br /><br />Reset Windows Password with Password Unlocker Bundle
<br />If you <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYXNzd29yZHVubG9ja2VyLmNvbS9rbm93bGVkZ2UvZm9yZ290LW15LXdpbmRvd3MtcGFzc3dvcmQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">forgot Windows login password</a>, it’s highly suggested to try Password Unlocker Bundle Standard instead of a Windows password recovery tool. This bundle includes all the features of a Windows password recovery tool. It allows you to burn a bootable password reset disk with CD/DVD or USB flash drive to reset passwords for Windows 7/Vista/XP and Windows servers. And with more $10, you can enjoy the features of other 12 password recovery tools. If you have ever purchased any product form this Password Unlcoker Bundle, you can enjoy 50% discount on it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="26a724673fe8bbdab4470f7c5b518aeb" url=""><![CDATA[Forgot Windows 7 Password? Create a New Admin Account to Byp<br/><br/>It’s nothing to worry about when you <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbnlwYXNzd29yZHJlY292ZXJ5LmNvbS9mb3Jnb3Qtd2luZG93cy03LXBhc3N3b3JkLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">forgot Windows 7 password</a>. There’re so many Windows 7 password recovery tools to help you remove a lost Windows 7 password. But removing a forgotten Windows 7 password with these tools may cause some data loss. You might not be able to access some of your encrypted data. So here’s highly suggested to create a new admin account instead of resetting the forgotten password to access your PC again when you forgot your Windows password and be locked out of computer.
<br /><br />What needs to create a new admin account to bypass Windows 7 password?
<br /><br />Creating a new admin account on a locked PC is very simple. What you need is just a powerful tool like Rekeysoft <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbnlwYXNzd29yZHJlY292ZXJ5LmNvbS9yZXNldC13aW5kb3dzLXBhc3N3b3JkLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Windows Password Recovery</a> Enterprise. Unlike other Windows password recovery applications, this program allows you not only remove or change forgotten Windows password, but also create a new admin account to help you get back in your locked PC.
<br /><br />100% security is guaranteed. No any data loss or damage will occur. Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery Enterprise features easy and instant recovery. No matter what the level of your computing knowledge is, you can easily access your PC again in 5 minutes either by removing/changing the lost password or creating a new admin account. Even you are a novice, you can also use this application to fix your problem.
<br /><br />How to create a new admin account to bypass Windows 7 password?
<br /><br />Creating a new admin account on a locked PC with Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery Enterprise can be divided into 2 phrases. The first phrase is to create a bootable Windows password reset disk in any PC. And Creating a new admin account on the PC you forgot password for is the second phrase.
<br /><br />Phrase 1. Burn a bootable Windows password reset disk
<br />1. Download and install Rekeysoft Windows Password Recovery Enterprise in any PC.
<br />2. Launch this program and insert a CD/DVD or USB f lash drive in computer.
<br />3. Click on Burn a Bootable CD/DVD if you inserted a CD/DVD, and click on Burn a Bootable USB Flash drive if you inserted a USB drive.
<br />4. Select the target device (DVD/CD or USB drive) and click the Reset button. The bootable password reset disk will be burned in seconds.
<br /><br />Once this disk is created, you can use it to create a new admin account on the computer that you forgot password fro to bypass Windows 7 password that you lost.
<br /><br />Phrase 2. Create a new admin account
<br />1. Start your locked PC from the bootable password reset disk.
<br />2. Select the system, and then click Create a new account button when the Rekeysoft interface appears.
<br />3. Type the user name and password for the new administrator account, and then click OK.
<br />4. Click OK when the new admin account is successfully created.
<br />5. Click Reboot button to restart computer and then log into Windows with the new administrator account.
<br />Note: Please remember to remove the bootable disk before during restarting.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a97e4aaeec8216dd1a4a015344c47566" url=""><![CDATA[Carbon Copy Cloner - Secure Backup Saves Your Data and Mac O<br/><br/><strong>Lose your important data?</strong>
<br />Have you ever experienced that, computer suddenly crashed, and cannot boot normally? Your operating system or hard drive may be broken. If you have to reinstall system or change a new hard disk, what a pity that you will lose the installed programs and collected data, such as family photos, favorite videos, pictures, and other crucial information. 
<br /><br /><strong>How to avoid data loss?</strong>
<br />The answer is consistent and regular backup. Though many online data backup services are provided nowadays, they cannot be proven 100% safe, it's also a good idea to have an extra backup drive at your home to double your computer's backup security.
<br />The external hard drive backup can be scheduled and handled automatically by Carbon Copy Cloner Download.
<br /><br /><strong>Carbon Copy Cloner</strong>
<br />Carbon Copy Cloner is a tool to clone, synchronize, and backup both the operating system and file data. Different from the way to drag and drop the files you want to preserve from your main drive to the external hard drive, Carbon Copy Cloner creates images of your Mac's hard drive contents on a bootable volume.
<br />When disaster occurs, replace the failed hard drive, and simply boot the Mac machine from your backup disk to restore your data and system settings in one easy step. 
<br /><br /><strong>How to clone your hard drive to an external hard disk?</strong>
<br />Carbon Copy Cloner features a new interface to make the cloning and backup procedure more intuitive and more responsive.
<br />1. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL2NhcmJvbi1jb3B5LWNsb25lci05MjM3MS5odG1s" target="_blank">Download Carbon Copy Cloner</a> on Mac, and Launch it.
<br />2. Choose the volume that you want to clone from the Source Disk, and select the items to be copied below it.
<br />3. Choose a formatted target disk.
<br />4. Click the Clone button.
<br />If you want to update your cloned volume in the future, simply re-run Carbon Copy Cloner with the same settings, and CCC will update the backup disk with only the items that have changed since your last backup.
<br /><br /><strong>How to run the backup on a scheduled basis?</strong>
<br />To schedule a backup task, first configure CCC as if above three steps. Instead of clicking on the Clone button, click on the &quot;Save task&quot; button. 
<br />In the Scheduler window that appears, provide a name for the scheduled task and indicate when you want the task to run. In Carbon Copy Cloner, backup task can be scheduled hourly, daily, weekly, and monthly, and when source and destination is connected. Save the settings. 
<br />Note: If source and destination is not available when the backup runs, the task will run immediately when the missing volume is reconnected.
<br /><br /><strong>Summary</strong>
<br />By having a great hard drive backup tool, you can protect your system and files with extra security in case your computer's hard drive crashes or your system is ruined. Why risk losing your important files forever when you can avoid that mess with this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free download software</a>?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="567c3a6c5f4dc817b107aa7d27d7d067" url=""><![CDATA[How to create your own video with free tool<br/><br/>You must have watched many videos created by common users, either sharing their family photos as slideshow or combining their preferred movie scenes into one video, with pleasant songs and attractive visual effects. Why not create one by yourself to feel the creativity? It is easy to do that as long as you <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3dpbmRvd3MtbGl2ZS1tb3ZpZS1tYWtlci05Njk2NS5odG1s" target="_blank">download Windows Live Movie Maker</a>.
<br /><br /><strong>What does Windows Live Movie Maker do?</strong>
<br />Windows Live Movie Maker is a free video creating and editing software that allows you to easily turn photos and video clips into great-looking slideshows and movies on Vista and Windows 7. The output video file can be shared with family and friends across a TV, PC or mobile device.
<br /><br /><strong>Supported source file formats</strong>
<br />Supported image and video files include: Windows Media Video (WMV), Windows Media, DV-AVI, Microsoft Recorded TV Show, 3GP, 3GPP, MPEG-1, MPEG-2, Motion JPEG, JPEG, TIFF, GIF, Bitmap, PNG. Windows 7 users can also view QuickTime MOV and QT files, AVCHD, and MPEG-4 video formats.
<br />The source file can be your photos, collected images and video clips from your favorite movies, music videos and dramas.
<br /><br /><strong>Download and install</strong>
<br />From all download sites, even its official website, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3dpbmRvd3MtbGl2ZS1tb3ZpZS1tYWtlci05Njk2NS5odG1s" target="_blank">Windows Live Movie Maker free download</a> actually launches the installation of Windows Live Essentials. An installation window lets you choose to install Windows Live Movie Maker and any other Windows Live applications. To install Movie Maker only, deselect the other boxes.
<br /><br /><strong>How to use Windows Live Movie Maker?</strong>
<br />Step 1 Add videos and photos
<br />On the Home tab, in the Add group, click Add videos and photos to import. Or do as &quot;click here to browser for videos and photos&quot;.
<br />Step 2 Video and audio editing
<br />After importing a video, video editing tools will be added in the menu bar automatically. In terms of video editing, you can merge, trim, split, speed up or slow down video, add transitional effects, and much more. 
<br />Add music from Add group in Home tab, and then music editing tools will be added in the menu bar. In terms of music editing, you can fade music in or out, trim music, change the music volume, and much more. 
<br />Step 3 Choose an AutoMovie theme
<br />On the Home tab, in the AutoMovie themes group, click the theme you want to use. Movie Maker automatically adds titles, credits, transitions, effects, and more for you.
<br />Step 4 Save or Share
<br />Preview the movie from the option in View tab, and then save it for DVD, PC, mobile device, and more, or share it to SkyDrive, Facebook, Youtube, Windows Live Groups, etc. 
<br /><br /><strong>More tools</strong>
<br />More video creating and editing tools are available in the software <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tL3dpbmRvd3MtbGl2ZS1tb3ZpZS1tYWtlci05Njk2NS5odG1s" target="_blank">free download</a> website. Compare them and find the one that suits your needs best.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e18e20b3c7a2ecf07fd40609f45f562b" url=""><![CDATA[How to Play Counter Strike Online<br/><br/>Even a decade after its release, Counter Strike remains one of the most popular games on the Internet. Through a seemingly endless series of updates and user-created content, the game has managed to stay fresh while always sticking to its original award-winning formula. One of the biggest changes has been its integration into Steam - Valve's multiplayer match-making and content distribution service.
<br /><br />1. Download and launch Steam. It is free to <strong>download Counter Strike</strong> and is now required to access its multiplayer component.
<br /><br />2. Select the &amp;quot;My Games&amp;quot; tab in the center of the Steam Client. Click the &amp;quot;Activate a product on Steam&amp;quot; tab.
<br /><br />3. Enter the CD key when prompted. If you have a retail version of Counter Strike, enter the key that came with the packaging. If not, you will have the option of purchasing a new key.
<br /><br />4. Launch Counter Strike after it has finished installing. On the main menu, click &amp;quot;Browse&amp;quot; to see a listing of the servers available.
<br /><br />5. Double click the server you want to join. The game will start immediately if you have the necessary files. Some servers use files (maps, character skins, etc) not included with the game. The game will automatically download those files for you when you try to join.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6541ed71e7641ad7fb4a5f6c02ba53a" url=""><![CDATA[The easist way to copy files from a DVD<br/><br/>As everybody knows, Microsoft Windows Explorer is the default file management application in all versions of Windows operating system. Microsoft Windows Explorer will allow the user to copy files from a DVD and save to the hard drive, external drive or Flash drive. To copy a file, folder or a group of files or folders from a DVD, use Windows Explorer.
<br /><br />1. Right-click the &quot;Start&quot; button on the bottom left on Windows toolbar and select &quot;Explore&quot; to open Windows Explorer.
<br /><br />2. Insert the DVD into the CD/DVD drive. Allow the drive to register the DVD.
<br /><br />3. Click the &quot;Computer&quot; link in the left navigation pane of Windows Explorer. The drives, including the drive hosting the DVD, will be listed.
<br /><br />4. Click on the DVD drive. The folders and files on the DVD will list in the right navigation pane.
<br /><br />5. Right-click on a file or folder and select &quot;Copy&quot; from the context menu, or press the CRTL + C keys, to copy the file or folder to the clipboard.
<br /><br />6. Navigate to a location on the destination drive and right-click. Select &quot;Paste&quot;, or press the CRTL + V keys, to paste the folder or files into the new location.
<br /><br />If you want to copy and burn an entire DVD then, a CD/DVD burner and CD/DVD burning application, such as Roxio, Alcohol or Nero, is necessary. Just follow these steps:
<br /><br />1. Click the Windows &quot;Start&quot; button and open the CD/DVD burning software.
<br /><br />2. Click the &quot;DVD&quot; option to create a new DVD compilation.
<br /><br />3. Click the &quot;DVD-Copy&quot; option, and click &quot;Next&quot;. The application will prompt the user to insert the source disk.
<br /><br />4. Insert the DVD to be copied into the CD/DVD drive. Allow the DVD to register in the burning application.
<br /><br />5. Click the &quot;Next&quot; button. The contents of the DVD will be copied to a temporary location to be burned to the destination DVD. When the copying process is finished, the burning application will eject the source DVD and prompt the user to insert the destination DVD.
<br /><br />6. Insert the destination DVD and click the &quot;Burn&quot; button. The contents of the source DVD will burn to the blank DVD.
<br /><br />7. Test the DVD by playing in a compatible player.
<br /><br />You can download <strong>DVD copy</strong> and DVD burning software on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZG93bmxvYWRyZXZpZXcuY29tLw__" target="_blank">free software download</a> website.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>