<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="908967c83888e30a4927533b3a0200ae" url=""><![CDATA[When A Girl Misses U<br/><br/>When you catch a girl
<br />glancing at you,
<br />she wants you to look
<br />back and smile
<br /><br />When a girl bumps into your arm
<br />while walking with you
<br />she wants
<br />you to hold her hand
<br /><br />When she wants a hug
<br />she will just stand there
<br /><br />When u break a girls heart
<br />she still feels it when
<br />you run into each other 3 years later
<br /><br />When a girl is quiet,
<br />millions of things are running through her
<br />mind
<br /><br />When a girl is not arguing,
<br />she is thinking deeply
<br /><br />When a girl looks at you with eyes full of
<br />questions,
<br />she is wondering how long you will be
<br />around
<br /><br />When a girl answers, &quot;I'm fine,&quot; after a
<br />few seconds,
<br />she is not at all fine
<br /><br />When a girl stares at you,
<br />she is wondering why you are playing games
<br /><br />When a girl lays her head on your chest,
<br />she is wishing for you to be hers forever
<br /><br />When a girl says she can't live
<br />without you,
<br />she has made up her mind that you are
<br />her future
<br /><br />When a girl says, &quot;I miss you,&quot;
<br />no one in this world can miss you more
<br />than that
<br /><br />When a girl is mean to you after a break-up
<br />she wants you back, but shes
<br />scared she'll get hurt and knows
<br />you're gone forever
<br /><br />Guy Facts:
<br /><br />When a guy calls you,
<br />he wants to be with you
<br /><br />When a guy is quiet,
<br />He's listening to you...
<br /><br />When a guy is not arguing,
<br />He realizes he's wrong
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I'm fine.&quot; after a few
<br />minutes
<br />he means it
<br /><br />When a guy stares at you,
<br />he wishes you would care about him and
<br />wonders if you do
<br /><br />When your laying your head on a guy's
<br />chest,
<br />he has the world
<br /><br />When a guy calls/texts/comments you everyday,
<br />he is in love
<br /><br />When a (good) guy tells you he loves you,
<br />he means it
<br /><br />When a guy says he can't live without you,
<br />he's with you til your done
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I miss you,&quot;
<br />he misses you more than you could have
<br />ever missed him or anything else
<br /><br />repost this in 10 minutes and your true
<br />love will
<br />call you
<br /><br />someone was in your mind as you read this??
<br /><br />Post this as
<br /><br />IF YOUR A GUY &quot; When a guy misses you...&quot;
<br /><br />AND
<br /><br />IF YOUR A GIRL POST IT AS &quot;when a girl misses you...&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24c86505724908d2697e0e82b8f6591b" url=""><![CDATA[Du this plz.......<br/><br/>1. Whats your Name?
<br />2. Are we close?
<br />3. What do you think of me?
<br />4. Do you hav a crush on me?
<br />5. Would u kiss me?
<br />6. Describe me in 3 words?
<br />7. If u Had Me for 30 Mins wat would you do?
<br />8. What was ur first impression of me?
<br />9. Do u still think the same?
<br />10. What reminds u of me?
<br />11. If you could give me anything what would it be?
<br />12. How well do u know me?
<br />13. What do u like best about me?
<br />14. Ever wanted 2 tell me something u could'nt?
<br />15. Could you ever love me?
<br />16. Give me a nickname and explain why?
<br />17.R u gona put this on ur blog and c wat i say bout u?
<br />18.Anything 2 say b4 u go
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b3d286af9c26815360e06014bdecbaa2" url=""><![CDATA[Question?<br/><br/>You Can Ask Me 1 Question And 1 Question Only And I Will Give An Honest Answer Copy And Paste This To Youre Blog , You Will Be Surprised What You Get Back!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="365d68384e952eebe02eed7c14086725" url=""><![CDATA[men r like....<br/><br/>1. Men are like ........Laxatives ...... They irritate the shit out
<br />&gt;&gt;of you.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;2. Men are like ........ Bananas ...... The older they get, the
<br />&gt;&gt;less firm they are.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;3. Men are like ........ Weather ..... Nothing can be done to
<br />&gt;&gt;change them..
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;4. Men are like ........ Blenders ..... You need One, but you're
<br />&gt;&gt;not quite sure why.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;5. Men are like
<br />&gt;&gt;....... Chocolate Bars .... Sweet, smooth, &amp; they usually head
<br />&gt;&gt;right for your hips.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;6. Men are like ....... Commercials ...... You can't believe a word
<br />&gt;&gt;they say.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;7. Men are like ........ Department Stores ..... Their clothes are
<br />&gt;&gt;always 1/2 off.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;8. Men are like ........ Government Bonds ..... They take soooooooo
<br />&gt;&gt;long to mature.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;9. Men are like ....... Mascara
<br />&gt;&gt;...... They usually run at the first sign of emotion.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;10. Men are like ....... Popcorn . ..... They satisfy you, but
<br />&gt;&gt;only for a little while.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;11. Men are like ........ Lava Lamps ..... Fun to look at, but not
<br />&gt;&gt;very bright.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;12. Men are like ........ Parking Spots . All the good ones are
<br />&gt;&gt;taken, the rest are handicapped.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d718c32f9bfe702759537d9b5a0de889" url=""><![CDATA[Condoms<br/><br/>Sainsbury Condoms - making life taste better.
<br /><br />Tesco Condoms - every little helps.
<br /><br />Nike Condoms - Just do it.
<br /><br />Peugeot Condoms - The ride of your life.
<br /><br />Galaxy Condoms - Why have rubber when you can have silk.
<br /><br />KFC Condoms - Finger licking good.
<br /><br />Minstrels Condoms -melt in your mouth, not in your hands.
<br /><br />Safeway Condoms - Lightening the load.
<br /><br />Abbey National condoms - because life is complicated enough.
<br /><br />Coca Cola condoms - The real thing.
<br /><br />Ever Ready condoms - keep going and going.
<br /><br />Pringles condoms - once you pop, you can't stop.
<br /><br />Burger King Condoms - Home of the whopper.
<br /><br />Goodyear Condoms - for a longer ride go wide.
<br /><br />FCUK condoms - no comment required.
<br /><br />Muller light condoms - so much pleasure, but where's the pain?
<br /><br />Halfords condoms - we go the extra mile.
<br /><br />Royal Mail condoms - I saw this and thought of you.
<br /><br />Andrex condoms - Soft, strong and very very long.
<br /><br />Renault condoms - size really does matter!
<br /><br />Ronseal condoms - does exactly what it says on the tin.
<br /><br />Ronseal quick-drying condoms - it's dry and waterproof in 30 minutes.
<br /><br />Domestos condoms - gets right under the rim ! ! !(Please).
<br /><br />Heineken condoms - reaches parts that other condoms just cannot reach.
<br /><br />Carlsberg condoms - probably the best condom in the world.
<br /><br />AA Condoms - for the 4th emergency service.
<br /><br />Pepperami condoms - it's a bit of an animal.
<br /><br />lol hahahahahahahahahaha!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="785dd43b0d49fac8ae9b3663695a7af" url=""><![CDATA[Ask me ANYTHING!<br/><br/>You Can Ask Me 1 Question And 1 Question Only And i Promise To Give An Honest Answer Copy And Paste This To Youre Blog , U will Be surprised Wot You Get Asked.....so ask me anything!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7b6d5f0682aecadcfda106aeaa306fa0" url=""><![CDATA[Fuckable?<br/><br/>FUCKABLE PIC AWARD
<br />FUCKABLE PIC AWARD 
<br />1.) Go to the profile of the person who posted this bulletin
<br /><br />2.) Pick their most FUCKABLE picture and post a comment saying &quot;FUCKABLE PIC AWARD&quot;
<br /><br />*NOW THE FUN PART*
<br /><br />3.) Repost this bulletin and see how many comments you get on your pics
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="30bbb3b57d3444a8b2ee60ecc3048ee0" url=""><![CDATA[What am I?<br/><br/>What am i to you?
<br />1) Mate
<br />2) Best mate
<br />3) Gf/Bf material
<br />4) Shagable
<br />5) Want to go out with me
<br />6) Pritty
<br />7) Ugly
<br />8) Hate me
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c32560ad87f2018a1f78718be0f6f3ee" url=""><![CDATA[90's<br/><br/>did you experience the nineties????
<br /><br />Gordon the Gopher
<br />You owned or wanted an adidas 3 stripe tracksuit
<br />Adidas poppers remember them!
<br />now compalations when they were cool with 'rytham is a dancer', 'mr vain', 'what is love' and 'how bizarre how bizarre'
<br />Girls thought blue mascara was cool
<br />You owned a pair of nike air max and wore them to death
<br />Adidas predator football boots were a must have
<br />Mr Motivator (what happened to him?
<br />Girls fancied Gary Barlow more than Robbie Williams
<br />You used the phrase 'its a free country' every day
<br />you taped the pepsi chart show n tried in vain to stop it before that annoying bloke started talkin n ruined it all
<br />Cans of coke were 25p
<br />Fruit of the loom jumpers were a must have item
<br />You knew the dance to saturday night and the macerana
<br />Shellsuits n bumbags
<br />Strike It Lucky with Micheal Barrymore
<br />Family Fortunes with Les Dennis
<br />Generation Game - Brucie
<br />You lost or nearly lost a tooth eating a wham bar cola bar or iron bru bar!
<br />Lads collected premier league stickers n swapped them at playtime
<br />You wore kickers with the tags hangin out
<br />You thought saying i know you are you said you are so what am i??' to every cuss that came your way was cool
<br />Shouting 'LEGGGIIITTTT' when you ran away from something
<br />'i am rubber n you are glue, whatever you say bounces off me n sticks to you' was probably the ****iest thing girls said in the playground
<br />CK1 (probably from the market)
<br />Collecting pogs n slammin them all around the playground
<br />Walkers Tazos
<br />Knowing all the words to 'Fresh Prince of Bel Air' and Saved by the bell
<br />Playing kurby in the street
<br />British Bulldogs
<br />Levis 501s
<br />Eclipse jeans with the smiley yellow face on the back
<br />Opel Fruits, now called starburst.
<br />Original tamogotchi
<br />NOKIA 3210 The phone of all phones
<br />Power Rangers - Everyone had a favourite who was yours
<br />Mini punch
<br /><br />if you can think of any more then mail them to me, if not, 'its a free country'
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fcf1b88a2246007257675a505f840f14" url=""><![CDATA[be honest plz!!<br/><br/>POST THiS iF YOU AREN'T SCARED TO SEE HOW PEOPLE THINK OF YOU
<br /><br />0 = ewwwwwwwwwwww!
<br />1 = Definetly not attractive.
<br />2 = Decent
<br />3 = Fine
<br />4 = Fine as hell!
<br />5 = I'd do you.
<br />6 = Pretty damn sexy!
<br />7 = Lovable, I LOVE YOU!!!
<br />8 = I wanna make you my man/girl.
<br />9 = Just a friend.
<br />10 = Sexiest person I know!
<br />11 = Fuckin beautiful
<br />12 = Ya, I've checked you out a few times.
<br />13 = i wanna fuck u
<br />14.= Let's get married!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12f3dc2a8fb85c788eb1466163a3b9e2" url=""><![CDATA[Do this plz!! xx<br/><br/>Name:
<br /><br />Age:
<br /><br />Height:
<br /><br />Weight:
<br /><br />Location:
<br /><br />Interests:
<br /><br />Occupation:
<br /><br />NOW THE RUDE ONES!!
<br /><br />How many people have you slept with?:
<br /><br />Have you ever cheated on a partner?:
<br /><br />If so was it a one night thing or an affair?:
<br /><br />Ever paid for sex?:
<br /><br />Ever slep with more than one person in 24 hours?:
<br /><br />Like oral sex?:
<br /><br />Anal?:
<br /><br />Ever had had sex with a member of the same sex?:
<br /><br />Had sex outdoors? (if so where):
<br /><br />Had a threesome?:
<br /><br />Foursome?:
<br /><br />Fivesome (if your lucky!):
<br /><br />Ever regretted sleeping with someone?:
<br /><br />Will you repost this so i can do it for you?:
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b50a21da22a842b9846956d8b9a85bc0" url=""><![CDATA[Spin the bottle ne1??<br/><br/>Body: The rules are that you post this and wait for someone to send you a message telling you what they would do with you. All you have to do is repost this with the subject &quot;SPIN THE BOTTLE''
<br /><br />1.I Would Feel your ass
<br />2.I Would kiss you on the cheek
<br />3.I Would kiss you on forehead
<br />4.i would just give you a hug.
<br />5.i would give you a kiss on the lips
<br />6.i would french kiss you
<br />7.i would make out with you
<br />8.i would try and feel you up
<br />9.i would try and fuck you
<br />10.i would shag you all night long
<br /><br />If you do not repost this you will have bad relationships for the rest of your life!!! SPIN THE BOTTLE
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8e85ac3daea98cb5a56899430ca7ab97" url=""><![CDATA[Men r like<br/><br/>1. Men are like ........Laxatives ...... They irritate the shit out
<br />&gt;&gt;of you.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;2. Men are like ........ Bananas ...... The older they get, the
<br />&gt;&gt;less firm they are.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;3. Men are like ........ Weather ..... Nothing can be done to
<br />&gt;&gt;change them..
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;4. Men are like ........ Blenders ..... You need One, but you're
<br />&gt;&gt;not quite sure why.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;5. Men are like
<br />&gt;&gt;....... Chocolate Bars .... Sweet, smooth, &amp; they usually head
<br />&gt;&gt;right for your hips.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;6. Men are like ....... Commercials ...... You can't believe a word
<br />&gt;&gt;they say.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;7. Men are like ........ Department Stores ..... Their clothes are
<br />&gt;&gt;always 1/2 off.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;8. Men are like ........ Government Bonds ..... They take soooooooo
<br />&gt;&gt;long to mature.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;9. Men are like ....... Mascara
<br />&gt;&gt;...... They usually run at the first sign of emotion.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;10. Men are like ....... Popcorn . ..... They satisfy you, but
<br />&gt;&gt;only for a little while.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;11. Men are like ........ Lava Lamps ..... Fun to look at, but not
<br />&gt;&gt;very bright.
<br />&gt;&gt;
<br />&gt;&gt;12. Men are like ........ Parking Spots . All the good ones are
<br />&gt;&gt;taken, the rest are handicapped.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e3a28d2fd2b2362bf9a5c395d7694aa8" url=""><![CDATA[hmmmmmmmmm?<br/><br/>Here are some weird and funny questions that get you thinking, what the fcuk
<br /><br />Why did Sally sell seashells on the seashore when you can just pick them up anyway?
<br /><br />Why do people constantly return to the refrigerator with hopes that something new to eat will have materialized?
<br /><br />Can you read a picture book?
<br /><br />How come Superman could stop bullets with his chest, but always ducked when someone threw a gun at him?
<br /><br />Did you ever notice when you blow in a dog's face he gets mad at you? But when you take him in a car, he sticks his head out the window!
<br /><br />Why do they call it an asteroid when its outside the hemisphere but call it a hemorrhoid when its in your ass?
<br /><br />If Barbie is so popular, then why do you have to buy her friends?
<br /><br />Why do the ABC song, Twinkle Twinkle Little Star, and Baa Baa Black Sheep all have the same tune?
<br /><br />Why is it that when a person tells you there's over a million stars in the universe you believe them, but if someone tells you there's wet paint somewhere, you have to touch it to make sure?
<br /><br />If Americans throw rice at weddings, do the Chinese throw hamburgers?
<br /><br />Why do banks leave the door wide open but the pens chained to the counter?
<br /><br />Where in the nursery rhyme does it say humpty dumpty is an egg?
<br /><br />Why doesn't Tarzan have a beard?
<br /><br />If Practice makes perfect, and nobody's perfect, then why practice?
<br /><br />Why is the time of day with the slowest traffic called rush hour?
<br /><br />Who was the first person to look at a cow and say, &quot;I think I'll squeeze these dangly things here, and drink what ever comes out&quot;?
<br /><br />Why can't women put on mascara with their mouth closed?
<br /><br />If Dracula has no reflection, how comes he always had such a straight parting in his hair?
<br /><br />Why does blow and suck mean the same thing when we describe something being crap?
<br /><br />Why do people say heads up when you should duck?
<br /><br />Tell me what you thought of these crazy thought, also repost this bulletin if you want, thanks
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="385dc267f1974588441d67290d245f1f" url=""><![CDATA[HEHE<br/><br/>A man escapes from prison where he has been for 15 years. He breaks into a house to look for money and guns and finds a young couple in bed. 
<br /><br />He orders the guy out of bed and ties him to a chair, while tying the girl to the bed he gets on top of her, kisses her neck, then gets up and goes into the bathroom. While he's in there, the husband tells his wife:
<br /><br />&quot;Listen, this guy's an escaped convict, look at his clothes! He probably spent lots of time in jail and hasn't seen a woman in years. I saw how he kissed your neck.&quot; If he wants sex, don't resist, don't complain, do whatever he tells you. Satisfy him no matter how much he nauseates you. This guy is probably very dangerous. If he gets angry, he'll kill us. Be strong, honey. I love you.&quot;
<br /><br />To which his wife responds: &quot;He wasn't kissing my neck. He wwas whispering in my ear. He told me he was gay, thought you were cute, and asked me if we had any vaseline. I told him it was in the bathroom. Be strong honey. I love you too!!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1ebf73264c84d5dc32140b394d9cca11" url=""><![CDATA[17 signs of really having feelings for some one<br/><br/>17 signs of really having feelings for someone
<br />SEVENTEEN:
<br /><br />U LOOK AT THEIR PROFILE/PICTURE CONSTANTLY
<br /><br />SIXTEEN:
<br /><br />WHEN YOUR ON THE PHONE WITH THEM LATE AT NIGHT AND THEY HANG UP, YOU STILL MISS THEM EVEN WHEN IT WAS JUST TWO MINUTES AGO.
<br /><br />FIFTEEN:
<br /><br />YOU READ THEIR TEXTS or IMS OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
<br /><br />FOURTEEN:
<br /><br />YOU WALK REALLY SLOW WHEN YOU'RE WITH THEM
<br /><br />THIRTEEN:
<br /><br />YOU FEEL SHY WHENEVER YOU'RE/THEY'RE AROUND.
<br /><br />ELEVEN:
<br /><br />WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THEM, YOUR HEART BEATS FASTER AND SLOWER AT THE SAME TIME
<br /><br />TEN:
<br /><br />YOU SMILE WHEN YOU HEAR THEIR VOICE.
<br /><br />NINE:
<br /><br />WHEN YOU lOOK AT THEM, YOU CAN'T SEE THE OTHER PEOPLE AROUND YOU, All YOU SEE IS HIM//HER.
<br /><br />EIGHT:
<br /><br />YOU START LISTENING TO SLOW SONGS, WHILE THINKING OF THEM
<br /><br />SEVEN:
<br /><br />THEY'RE ALL YOU THINK ABOUT.
<br /><br />SIX:
<br /><br />YOU GET HIGH JUST FROM THEIR SCENT.
<br /><br />FIVE:
<br /><br />YOU REALlIZE THAT YOU'RE AlWAYS SMILING TO YOURSELF WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THEM.
<br /><br />FOUR:
<br /><br />YOU WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR THEM, OR ANYTHING TO SEE THEM.
<br /><br />THREE:
<br /><br />WHILE READING THIS, THERE WAS ONE PERSON ON YOUR MIND THE WHOLE TIME...
<br /><br />TWO:
<br /><br />You were so busy thinking about that person, you didnt notice number twelve was missing
<br /><br />ONE:
<br /><br />You just scrolled up to check &amp; are now silentely laughing at yourself.
<br /><br />NOW MAKE A WiSH. YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO.......
<br /><br />*
<br /><br />**
<br /><br />***
<br /><br />****
<br /><br />*****
<br /><br />******
<br /><br />*******
<br /><br />********
<br /><br />*********
<br /><br />********
<br /><br />*******
<br /><br />******
<br /><br />*****
<br /><br />****
<br /><br />***
<br /><br />**
<br /><br />*
<br /><br />*
<br /><br />**
<br /><br />***
<br /><br />****
<br /><br />*****
<br /><br />******
<br /><br />*******
<br /><br />********
<br /><br />*********
<br /><br />********
<br /><br />*******
<br /><br />******
<br /><br />*****
<br /><br />****
<br /><br />***
<br /><br />**
<br /><br />*
<br /><br />**
<br /><br />***
<br /><br />****
<br /><br />*****
<br /><br />******
<br /><br />*******
<br /><br />********
<br /><br />*********
<br /><br />********
<br /><br />*******
<br /><br />******
<br /><br />*****
<br /><br />****
<br /><br />***
<br /><br />POST THIS AS: &quot;17 signs of really having feelings for someone&quot;
<br />*AND SOMETHING GOOD WILL HAPPEN TO YOU TONIGHt
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bae11ea42767141d98d08c156cee0224" url=""><![CDATA[Add yours!<br/><br/>FEEL FREE TO ADD YOURS!
<br />Quote of the week:
<br />&quot;And when I woke up old ladies where pointing at me.&quot;
<br />&quot;Even Tesco's wont employ me!!&quot;
<br />&quot;I read the globe does that count?&quot;
<br />&quot;Im not stupid, im just slow&quot;
<br />&quot;Do it Dad, Travolta's ur bitch&quot; 
<br />&quot;Hel get up, i get up we'll all get up. itl be anorchy!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="102735776d6d8f3eac6e3f4f96145dae" url=""><![CDATA[Rough Sex Facts<br/><br/>rough sex facts!!!!
<br />send this right after u read it, something good will happen at 2:25 tomorrow. Get ready for the biggest shock in your life!!
<br />Whoever breaks this chain will be cursed w/ relationship problems 4-10 years.
<br />If you send this in 15 mins. your safe. Something good will happen tonight at 11:11pm.
<br /><br />Giving .........head....... massages the jaw....while burning 32 calories.
<br /><br />Swallowing foreign body juices is actually like taking vitamins and it whitens your teeth
<br /><br />The American Dental Association says that semen cuts plaque better than mouth wash, so suck a dick and save a smile.
<br /><br />Having nice sex burns 358 calories.
<br /><br />Having rough sex [make it hurt] burns 543 calories.
<br /><br />Take off her clothes
<br />with her consent.........................12 cal
<br />without......................187 cal
<br /><br />Take off her Bra
<br />With two hands..........................8 cal
<br />With one hand.........................12 cal
<br />With mouth.............................85 cal
<br /><br />Put on Protection
<br />hard .......................... 6 cal
<br />soft..........................315 cal
<br /><br />Foreplay
<br />Looking for target...................8 cal
<br />Finding G spot ......................92 cal
<br />I don't F***ing care.....................0 cal
<br /><br />Entry
<br />Holding her..................12 cal
<br />On the floor.................8 cal
<br /><br />With Different Position
<br />Missionary..........................358 cal
<br />Doggy...........................316 cal
<br />69 lying...............................286 cal
<br />69 standing.............................512 cal
<br />Italian hanger.........................912 cal
<br /><br />Orgasm
<br />Real................................112 cal
<br />Faking................................315 cal
<br /><br />After &quot;O&quot;
<br />Lying in Bed............................18 cal
<br />Hop off the bed............................36 cal
<br />Wondering why she left pissed off...........816 cal
<br /><br />Get dressed
<br />Quiet and calm...........................32 cal
<br />Rushing.........................98 cal
<br />Heard her boyfriend opening the door.............1218 cal
<br />Heard her dad at the door.............1942 cal
<br />Her mom walking in..............................Priceless!!!LOL
<br /><br />IF YOU BREAK THIS YOU WILL HAVE THE WORST DAY OF YOUR LIFE TOMORROW AND AWFUL SEX FOR A YEAR! REPOST THIS AND YOU WILL FIND AMAZING SEX WITHIN ONE MONTH
<br /><br />REPOST THIS WITH THE TITLE: rough sex facts
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2ce5e2b1f4d1172581ff75eab6e53ef0" url=""><![CDATA[SEX<br/><br/>... A smile leads to a laugh
<br /><br />... A laugh leads to a high 5
<br /><br />... A high 5 leads to a hug
<br /><br />... A hug leads to a kiss
<br /><br />... A kiss leads to a makeout
<br /><br />... A makeout leads to a feel up
<br /><br />... A feel up leads to a finger
<br /><br />... A finger leads to a hand
<br /><br />... A hand leads to a lick
<br /><br />... A lick leads to a suck
<br /><br />... A suck leads to a fuck.
<br /><br />So tell me how many people are you gonna smile at after you heard this because sex is like math.
<br /><br />... You add the bed
<br /><br />... You subtract the clothes
<br /><br />... Then you divide the legs
<br /><br />... And leave your solution
<br /><br />... But pray you dont multiply
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5a36146133c3e031ae9b43482861c248" url=""><![CDATA[HAHA!! So true!<br/><br/>to make a women happy a man has to be:
<br /><br />1) a lover
<br />2) a friend
<br />3) a companion
<br />4) a chef
<br />5) passionate
<br />6) strong
<br />7) tender
<br />8) clean
<br />9) a fan of shopping
<br />10) generous
<br /><br />to make a man happy a women just has to...
<br /><br />1) show up naked
<br />2) bring food
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="18df1dc0ec5ca43872ae4e5bf5e4606a" url=""><![CDATA[A True Boyfriend<br/><br/>• Grab her neck when you kiss her, it's a real turn on.
<br />Not her butt//boobs.
<br /><br />• Stay on the phone with her even if shes not saying anything.
<br /><br />• When she's mad hug her tight and don't let go then kiss her
<br /><br />• When she says she's ok don't believe it talk with her
<br /><br />• Never cheat on her because 10 yrs later she will remember you &amp; what you did.
<br /><br />• Call her at 12:00am on her birthday to tell her you love her
<br /><br />• Call her before you sleep and after you wake up
<br /><br />• Treat her like a person and not something to show off for
<br /><br />• Tease her and let her tease you back.
<br /><br />• Stay up all night with her when she's sick.
<br /><br />• Watch her favorite movie with her.
<br /><br />• Give her the world.
<br /><br />• Let her wear your clothes.
<br /><br />• When she's bored and sad, hang out with her.
<br /><br />• Let her know she's important.
<br /><br />• Kiss her in the pouring rain.
<br /><br />• When she runs up at you crying, the first thing you say is;
<br />&quot;Who's ass am I kicking babe?&quot;
<br /><br />If you do post this in the next four minutes the one your love will :
<br />•Call you.
<br />•Kiss you.
<br />•Love you.
<br />•Text you.
<br /><br />Guys post as: I'd be this boyfriend
<br />Girls post as: A true boyfriend
<br /><br />* No one can be the perfect boyfriend but as long as you treat her right and remind her how much you care none of the things above really matter if you truely love her
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be390b63869dfecd2e349b0a59ba8fce" url=""><![CDATA[CHINESE HOROSCOPE (Freakishly Correct)<br/><br/>DO NOT CHEAT
<br />OR IT WON'T WORK AND
<br />YOU WILL WISH YOU HADN..T.
<br /><br />TAKE 3 MINUTES
<br />TRY THIS - IT WILL FREAK YOU OUT.
<br /><br />THE PERSON WHO SENT THIS TO ME SAID
<br />HER WISH CAME TRUE 10 MINUTES AFTER SHE FORWARDED THE EMAIL
<br /><br />NO CHEATING!!!!
<br /><br />THIS GAME HAS A FUNNY / CREEPY OUTCOME.
<br /><br />DO NOT READ AHEAD, JUST DO IT.
<br /><br />IT TAKES ABOUT 3 MINUTES - WORTH A TRY
<br /><br />1st. Get PEN and PAPER
<br /><br />2nd. WHEN CHOOSING NAMES, MAKE SURE THEY ARE REAL PEOPLE THAT YOU ACTUALLY KNOW
<br /><br />3rd. GO WITH YOUR FIRST INSTINCTS !!!!! Very important for good results.
<br /><br />4th SCROLL DOWN
<br /><br />ONE LINE AT THE TIME
<br />DON..T READ AHEAD
<br />otherwise
<br />YOU WILL RUIN THE FUN.
<br /><br />1. On a blank sheet of paper, WRITE NUMBERS 1 through 11 in a COLUMN on the LEFT.
<br /><br />2. Next to the NUMBERS 1 &amp; 2,
<br /><br />WRITE DOWN ANY
<br />2 NUMBERS YOU WANT.
<br /><br />DO YOU HAVE A FAVORITE NUMBER?
<br /><br />3. Next to the NUMBERS 3 &amp; 7,
<br /><br />WRITE DOWN THE NAMES OF TWO MEMBERS
<br />OF THE OPPOSITE SEX. SAME SEX IF GAY
<br /><br />CAUTION: DO NOT LOOK AHEAD or IT WILL NOT TURN OUT RIGHT
<br /><br />4. WRITE ANYONES NAME
<br /><br />(like FRIENDS or FAMILY...)
<br />next to 4, 5, &amp; 6.
<br /><br />DON..T CHEAT OR YOU..LL BE UPSET THAT YOU DID
<br /><br />5. WRITE down FOUR SONG TITLES in 8, 9, 10, &amp; 11
<br /><br />6. Finally,
<br /><br />MAKE A WISH
<br /><br />ARE YOU READY?
<br />HERE IS THE
<br /><br />KEY TO THE GAME
<br /><br />1. THE NUMBER of PEOPLE THAT LIKE YOU is found in
<br /><br />SPACE 2
<br /><br />2. THE PERSON IN SPACE
<br /><br />3 IS THE ONE YOU LOVE
<br /><br />3. THE PERSON YOU LIKE but your relationship CANNOT WORK is in
<br /><br />SPACE 7
<br /><br />.
<br /><br />4. YOU CARE MOST about the PERSON you put in
<br /><br />SPACE 4
<br /><br />5. THE PERSON YOU NAME IN NUMBER 5 IS THE ONE WHO
<br /><br />KNOWS YOU VERY WELL.
<br /><br />6. THE PERSON YOU NAMED IN 6 IS YOUR
<br /><br />LUCKY STAR
<br /><br />7. THE SONG IN 8 IS THE SONG THAT MATCHES WITH THE
<br /><br />PERSON IN NUMBER 3
<br /><br />8. THE TITLE IN 9 IS THE SONG FOR THE
<br /><br />PERSON IN 7
<br /><br />9. THE 10TH SPACE IS THE SONG THAT TELLS YOU MOST ABOUT
<br /><br />YOUR MIND
<br /><br />10. AND 11 IS THE SONG TELLING HOW YOU
<br /><br />FEEL ABOUT LIFE
<br /><br />11. NUMBER 1 IS YOUR
<br /><br />LUCKY NUMBER
<br /><br />repost this
<br />WITHIN AN HOUR OF READING THIS.
<br /><br />IF YOU DO, YOUR WISH WILL COME TRUE.
<br /><br />* REPOST WITH
<br />CHINESE HOROSCOPE (Freakishly Correct)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="922bf063d395da7eab87a8aaccf28c89" url=""><![CDATA[DO IT u no u want to! :P<br/><br/>Would you kiss me?
<br />[] Hell Yea
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br />[] Maybe
<br />[] already did
<br /><br />Would you do me?
<br />[] In an instant!
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br />[] Maybe
<br />[]you look to sweet to screw
<br />[] already did
<br /><br />Am I attractive?
<br />[] Heck no
<br />[] hot as Hell
<br />[] Fine
<br />[] Cute
<br />[] Okay I think ur pretty
<br />[] Sexy
<br />[] Ugly!
<br /><br />Do you think im a virgin?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br />[] Don't know
<br /><br />Name one thing you would like to do to me...
<br />________________________
<br /><br />I look like..
<br />[] A player
<br />[] One time thing
<br />[] Next bf/gf
<br /><br />If you saw me for the first time would you talk to me?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br />[] maybe
<br /><br />Would you rather..
<br />[] Fuck me with me
<br />[] Cuddle with me
<br />[] Date me
<br />[] Marry me
<br />[] Friends
<br /><br />What kind of underwear are you wearing right now?
<br />[] boxers
<br />[] whitie tighties
<br />[] thongs
<br />[] granny panties
<br />[] boy shorts
<br />[] none
<br /><br />On a scale of 1-10 (10 being the highest), rate me..
<br />[] 1
<br />[] 2
<br />[] 3
<br />[] 4
<br />[] 5
<br />[] 6
<br />[] 7
<br />[] 8
<br />[] 9
<br />[] 10
<br /><br />Are you going to repost this so i can answer for you?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br /><br />What would you want me to be to you?
<br />[] Friend
<br />[] girlfriend/Boy friend
<br />[] Friend with benefits
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4447d92b862882a144e93c4054b9be8a" url=""><![CDATA[do this plz<br/><br/>01 I____ Alice
<br /><br />02 Alice is _____.
<br /><br />03 If I were alone in a room with Alice, I would _____.
<br /><br />04 I think Alice should _____.
<br /><br />05 Alice needs _____.
<br /><br />06 I want to _____ Alice 
<br /><br />07 Someday Alice will _____.
<br /><br />08 Alice _____.
<br /><br />09 Without Alice ___.
<br /><br />10 My memories of Alice are ____.
<br /><br />11 Alice can be _____.
<br /><br />12 The worst thing about Alice is _____.
<br /><br />13 The best thing about Alice is _____.
<br /><br />14 I am _____ with Alice 
<br /><br />15 One thing i would like to know about Alice is _____. 
<br /><br />16 Alice should go and _____.
<br /><br />17 Alice _____ me
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>