<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="538c4e9af4ccd5eaf40a7cbc623906ae" url=""><![CDATA[....<br/><br/>im not here for any special reason ....just a nice friendship in net and no other thing...
<br />if u r a nice and  polite person u can send me message...otherwise im sorry ....
<br />all the best ....
<br />Helen...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2b4bc4634082d17b2fcfac552d1e0e54" url=""><![CDATA[..........<br/><br/>im an polite&amp;easy going&amp;kind heart girl..........
<br />if ur nice &amp;polite person   u can be my friend,,,,,,,,,
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e3ef4dd19076eb385eda890e5d48640e" url=""><![CDATA[boys vs girls<br/><br/>1. Guys don't actually look after good-looking girls. they prefer neat 
<br />and presentable girls. 
<br /><br />2. Guys hate flirts. 
<br /><br />3.When a guy says he doesn't understand you, it simply means you're not 
<br />thinking the way he is. 
<br /><br />4. Guys may be flirting around all day but before they go to sleep, 
<br />they always think about the girl they truly care about . 
<br /><br />5. When a guy really likes you, he'll disregard all your bad 
<br />characteristics. 
<br /><br />6. Guys go crazy over a girl's smile. 
<br /><br />7. Guys will do anything just to get the girl's attention.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12d366f76f2d90b22c4cc199cbd49770" url=""><![CDATA[boys vs girls<br/><br/>8. When you touch a guy's heart, there's no turning back. 
<br /><br />9. When a girl says &quot;no&quot;, a guy hears it as &quot;try again tomorrow&quot;. 
<br />.... so true. 
<br /><br />10. You have to tell a guy what you really want before he gets the 
<br />message clearly. 
<br /><br />11. Guys love their moms. 
<br /><br />12. A guy would sacrifice his money for lunch just to get you a couple 
<br />of roses. 
<br /><br />13. A guy often thinks about the girl who likes him. But this doesn't
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6c2a43d2a7ab64728296351a2a1fef09" url=""><![CDATA[Friends<br/><br/>Friends love unconditionally. They have there little angry moments but what's done is done and all is forgive and forget. Why let something that happened in the past ruin what happiness you could have in the future? 
<br /> Believe in love at first sight because there is the equivalent in friendship. Some people think that you have to know someone really well to become good friends. Trust me, it's not true. If the first time you really spend time together you talk for 25 hours straight until 4:30 in the morning about some topic you thought no one else in the world understood, hun, that's real love at first sight.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="11b4c40ee83c6ccb3732b71c2520cd53" url=""><![CDATA[Rabindranath Tagore<br/><br/>This is the life.
<br />***Life's errors cry for the merciful beauty,.... that can modulate their isolation into a harmony with the whole.....by Rabindranath Tagore.***
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fa5cc9a9b15b1bbbad23afc4bd490a8b" url=""><![CDATA[isobella<br/><br/>Ophelia
<br />OH the green glimmer of apples in the orchard ------ Lamps in a wash of rain ------ Oh the wet walk of my brown hen through the stack-yard---- Oh tears on the window pane------ Nothing now will ripen the bright green apples ------ Full of disappointment and of rain ------ Brackish they will taste, of tears, when the yellow dapples----- Of autumn tell the withered tale again.******** D.H.LAWRENCE 
<br /><br />..im tryin to cool maself...in de stream...coolin off ma steam...let alone lie...let me cry...let de singin birds sing...ma songs of gloom...how sorrow i feel...de flowers still bloom...let de rain fall...upon ma hearts call...notink will eva change...it shall still remains de same...so darlin...im tryin to cool maself...in de stream...coolin off ma steam...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3141b6eeec115ca850f518118e1e05d2" url=""><![CDATA[.....................<br/><br/>Raindrops on our dresses, 
<br />Sunshine on our face, 
<br />No matter what the weather, 
<br />The look of love won't be replaced.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="25c893e9e114f776d667e44f619db32f" url=""><![CDATA[...............<br/><br/>For My Dad
<br />For the father that you are,
<br />and the father that you've been,
<br />If I had a choice to make,
<br />I'd choose you, Dad, again.
<br />For the trials I put you through,
<br />and for the times I let you down,
<br />I'm proud you've finally seen,
<br />how God turned my life around.
<br />You never ran away,
<br />when the times were tough to take...
<br />instead you gave me courage,
<br />to face my own mistakes.
<br />Thank you for your strength,
<br />and the faith to see me through...
<br />the love you gave to me,
<br />is the love I'm sending you!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5195c2808fb642d816ffe9e96b8c7b4e" url=""><![CDATA[ur welcome to my page.....<br/><br/>•	One evening an old Cherokee told his grandson about a battle that goes on inside people. 
<br /><br />He said, &quot;My son, the battle is between two wolves inside us all. 
<br /><br />&quot;One is Evil - It is anger, envy, jealousy, sorrow, regret, greed, arrogance, self-pity, guilt, resentment, inferiority, lies, false pride, superiority, and ego. 
<br /><br />&quot;The other is Good - It is joy, peace, love, hope, serenity, humility, kindness, benevolence, empathy, generosity, truth, compassion and faith.&quot; 
<br /><br />The grandson thought about it for a minute and then asked his grandfather: &quot;Which wolf wins?&quot; 
<br /><br />The old Cherokee simply replied, &quot;The one you feed.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1ef3133711879b1104b2445c264a4a5c" url=""><![CDATA[dictionary<br/><br/>Hi,
<br /><br />Ever you have come across a word in economy or politics text, that no dictionary come in handy, even the up-to-date one at hand!  It seems kinda usual with the rush of change in the globalism today.  Well, as I believe, there's an answer where there's a question!  Check out the following link you'll see what I mean.
<br /><br />cheers!
<br /><br />&lt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flexicon.ft.com%2F%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lexicon.ft.com/&gt</a>;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="100b6e361d13221483d8b27b28746051" url=""><![CDATA[the ship<br/><br/>Hi,
<br />I did not check the translation with the original, it may have something for the Observant eyes.
<br /><br />?? ???? ???????? ??????????? ????? ? ??? ??  . ???? ?? ??? ?? ?? ???? ??? ???? ??? ???? ? ?? ??? ? ????? ????? ??? ?? ?? ????? ?? ???? ? ????? ??????? . ??? ?? ??? ???? ?? ?????? ??? ???? ?? ? ???? ?? ????? ??????? ??? ???????  ? ????? ???????? ?? ???? ????? ????? ? ?? ???? ?? ?? ??? ????? ??? ? ???? ???? ?? ?? ????? ? ????? 
<br /><br />????? ????? ???? ??? ? ???? ???? ??? ?? ?? ????? ??? ? ???? ???? ????? ??? ? ???? ???????? ??? .  ????? ??? ?? ????? ??? ???? ????? ???????? ??? ???? ????? ?? ?? ?? ????? ??  ??? ????? ? ?? ???? ????? ???? ?? ?? ?? ???? ? ?? ????  ????? ??? ? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ??? ??? ?? ??? ????? ??? ? ??? ?? ????? ????? ?? ??? ? ??? ?? ??? ??? ????? ?? ????? ????? ??? 
<br /><br />?? ?? ?????? ???? ? ???? ?? ??? ?????? ? ????? ???? ?? ?? ??????? ? ??? ??? .  ????? ?????????  ???? ?? ????? ?? ????? ?????  ? ?? ???? ????  ????? ???? ?? ???????  ?? ???? ??? ? ????? ????  ?? ???? ?? ????? ???? ??? ????? ???? ??? 
<br /><br />?? ?? ???? ????? ?? ?? : &amp;quot; ??? ???? ??? ????? ????? ??? ? ?? ??????? ??? ????? ?? ????? ??? ??? ????? ????? . ;  ????????  ???? ????? ????? ?? ?? ???? ????  ??? ???? ???? ???? ?? ??? ?????? ???? ?? ?? ???? ?? ????? ?? ?? ?? ????? ????? ? ???? ???? ? ??? ????? ?? ?? ????? ??? ????? . ??????  ???? ????? ??????????? ???? ????? ???? ????? ????? ??? 
<br /><br />?? ???? ?? ???? ????? ???? .  ????? ??? ? ?????? ?? ???? ????? ?????? ????? ? ??? ?? ??? ?????? ? ????? ???? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ???? ????? .  ?? ??? ? ????? ??????? ???? ????? ?? ?? ????? ??? ?? ? ?? ?? ??? ???? ??? ?? ?? ????? ? ???? ??  ????? ?? -  ????? ?? ????? ??? ??? - ????? ? ??? ???? ?????? ???? ??? 
<br /><br />????? ????? ??? ?????? ?? ???? ??? ? ????? ? ?????? ? ????? ? ???? ?????? ???? ????? ???? ? ??? ????? ????? ?? ??? ???? ? ?? ???? ??? ?? ????? ??????? ????? ?????????? ?? ????? ?????  ? ?? ???? ?????? ??? ?? ?????? ????? ??? ??? . ??? ?????? ??? ?? ??? ???? ????? ?????? ???? ????? ??? 
<br /><br />??????? ????? ??? ?? ????? ???? ?? ?? ????? ?????? ???? ?? ?? ??? ?? ??? ?????? ? ??? ???? ?? ?? ????? ????? ?? ???? . ????? ????? ?????? ?? ? ???? ????? ??????? ?? ???? ??? ?? ?? ???? ?? ?????? ???? ????? ? ???? ?? ????? ????? ?? ??  ?? ????? ??? ?  ???? ??????? ??? 
<br /><br />?? ???????? ??? ????? ?? ????? ? ???????? ????  ???? ???? ?? ????? ??? ?? ????? ?? ???? ????? ?????? ? ?? ???? ????? ??? ???? ??? ? ????? ????  ? ??? ??? ??? : &amp;quot;  ??? ??? ??? ??? ??? ????? ???? ????? ??? ?? ?????? ?? ??? ??????? ????  . &amp;quot;  ???????? ?? ?? ?? ??? ??? ?????? ? ???? ?? ???? ?? 
<br /><br />???? ?? ???? ?? ?? ???? ???? ????? ?? ??? ????? ? ????? ?????? ????? ???? ?? : &amp;quot; ??? ???? ????  ?? ?? ????? ???? ??????? ? ! &amp;quot; 
<br /><br />????? ??? ???? ??? : &amp;quot; ????? ? .... ?? ?? ???????  .  &amp;quot;  ?????? ?  ????? ??? 
<br /><br />?? ???? ??? ??? ?? ?? ???? ?????? ?????? ? ?? ???? ????? ???? ?? ?? ???? ??? ? ??? : &amp;quot; ?????? ?????? ?? ?? ????? ?????? ?????? ? ?? ???? ??? ??? ?? ????? ????? ?? ! &amp;quot; 
<br /><br />????? ??? ?? ???? ????? ??? ??? ?  ?? ???? ????? ??? ? ?? ???? ??? ????? ??? ? ?? ?? ?? ???? ????? ??? ? ??? : &amp;quot; ????? ??? ?? ?? ????? ???????? ?? ???? ?????? ?? ??????? ??? ? &amp;quot; 
<br /><br />???? ?? ?? ?????? ? ?? ???? ?? ?????? ?? ????? ???????? ??????  ?? ???? ????? ??? : &amp;quot; ?? ??? ?? ???? ???  ?????? ? ?? ??? ??? ??  ????? ????? ???????? ????? ?? ??????? ?? &amp;quot; 
<br /><br />???????? ?? ?? ?? ?????? ??? ? ???? ????? ????????? ?????? 
<br />???? ????? ?????? ?????? ???????? 
<br /><br />* * * 
<br />?? ???? ???   
<br />* * * 
<br /><br />THE SHIP 
<br /><br />A voyaging ship was wrecked during a storm at sea and only two of the men on it were able to swim to a small, desert like island. 
<br />The two survivors not knowing what else to do agree that they had no other recourse but to pray to God. However, to find out whose prayer was more powerful, they agreed to divide the territory between them and stay on opposite sides of the island. 
<br />The first thing they prayed for was food. The next morning, the first man saw a fruit-bearing tree on his side of the land, and he was able to eat its fruit. The other man’s parcel of land remained barren. 
<br />After a week, the first man was lonely and he decided to pray for a wife. The next day, another ship was wrecked, and the only survivor was a woman who swam to his side of the land. On the other side of the island, there was nothing. 
<br /><br />Soon the first man prayed for a house, clothes, more food. The next day, like magic, all of these were given to him. However, the second man still had nothing. 
<br /><br />Finally, the first man prayed for a ship, so that he and his wife would leave the island. In the morning, he found a ship docked at his side of the island. The first man boarded the ship with his wife and decided to leave the second man on the island. 
<br /><br />He considered the other man unworthy to receive God’s blessings, since none of his prayers had been answered.  As the ship was about to leave, the first man heard a voice from heaven booming, “Why are you leaving your companion on the island?” 
<br />“My blessings are mine alone, since I was the one who prayed for them,” the first man answered. 
<br /><br />“His prayers were all unanswered and so he does not deserve anything.” 
<br />“You are mistaken!” the voice rebuked him. “He had only one prayer, which I answered. If not for that, you would not have received any of my blessings.” 
<br /><br />“Tell me,” the first man asked the voice, “What did he pray for that I should owe him anything?” 
<br />“He prayed that all your prayers be answered.” 
<br /><br />For all we know, our blessings are not the fruits of our prayers alone, but those of another praying for us.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>