<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="20">
		<document id="43b8f8f134d12bd39c2ce2b9ad013dd0" url=""><![CDATA[PCCSB-------WANNA MAKE IT<br/><br/>PC Chandra School of Business
<br /><br />The PC Chandra School of Business is a newly established business school in Salt Lake, Kolkata. This business school has been set up with a determined initiative of making tomorrow’s leaders. In fact, the PCCSB is successfully trying to act as a beneficial medium between the academics and the industries. In order to produce future managers and leaders equipped with the ultimate managerial skills, the PCCSB is offering effective modern facilities and curriculum to its students. The PC Chandra School of Business has a noble vision to get recognized as India’s best institution in the field of specialized education. This apart, this B-school also has a prudent mission to equip its students with the right attitude and the latest skills to suit the demands of the various types of industries.
<br /><br />The PCCSB firmly believes that giving emphasis on areas like Academic Enlightenment, Attitudinal Development, English Language Skills Development and Personality Development can give an additional benefit in building up tomorrow’s leaders today. The well defined and the specialized courses in Retail, Advertising, Sales Management, Human Resource Management, Banking and Mutual Fund, Insurance and Family Business etc are prepared keeping in mind the requirements of the industries. These courses aim at building up budding young business minds and making them shine in their chosen fields. The Summer Internship Programme and guest lectures from various domain of the industries are some of the salient features of PCCSB, which help in creating true leaders of tomorrow.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4ed1332e615a2303fa8386d33917a5cc" url=""><![CDATA[CORP CONNECT<br/><br/>CORP-CONNECT AT PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS
<br /><br />Corp Connect is an important medium which, connects the students of PC Chandra School of Business with the corporate world. It provides them a suitable platform to get the maximum benefit from the industry. The Corp Connect session offered by PCCSB help the students to have a realistic view of the market scenario, an opportunity to interact with the corporate honchos from various sectors and confidence to voice their opinion and queries in a packed session. The Corp Connect of PC Chandra School of Business has five major sub-divisions. These are: Corp Talk, Corp Exposure, Corp Associates,  Corp Research and Corp Cetera. 
<br /><br />Corp Talk:  The Corp Talk implies guest lectures by eminent personalities from the industry where the students have the full freedom to have a share of the corporate happenings through verbal interaction. 
<br /><br />Corp Exposure:  It helps the students to put into practice the theoretical aspect of management education.
<br /><br />Corp Associates:  The Corp Associates facilitates the students to get associated with apex business bodies like the CII, FICCI etc. 
<br /><br />Corp Research: It emphasizes upon carrying out live projects by the students which are being given by the esteemed faculties of the institution.
<br /><br />Corp Cetera:  It includes other subsidiary activities like that of Mall Visit and industry visit.
<br />The Corp Connect session is held every Friday evening in the college premise. Various facets of management like the HRM, Finance, Marketing, IT etc are covered in this comprehensive programme of preparing tomorrow’s leaders today. Some of the topics covered in this programme are CRM, Financial Sales and Management, Future Role of HR Professionals etc. The Corp Connect enable the students to become confident and quality management professionals in their respective areas, which can really change the corporate world. 
<br /><br />Some of the renowned speakers of the Corp Connect are Mr. Rajiv Soni (Head Marketing Communication- Tata Steel) others.Mr. Gautam Roy Choudhury ( AVP-Axis Bank), Mr. P.S.Paul(D.G.M.-H.R-IOCL), Mr. Susanta Bandopadhyay (Executive-Director-HR- Vesuvius India), and few others.
<br /><br />Few students opine that the sessions are good, interesting and even they are willing to take more such classes. Some are of the view that the good learning atmosphere and quality teachers help them to grab things better and faster. Some of them said that the lecturers demonstrated practical simulated sessions which help them to have a deep insight into the practical problems of the industry. Finally, it can be said that majority of the students expressed their eagerness and enthusiasm to have more of corporate interactions and lively classroom session.
<br /><br />PCCB WEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="159831107cde8e72d8c429eb785dbcc4" url=""><![CDATA[PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS<br/><br/>PC Chandra School of Business
<br /><br />The PC Chandra School of Business is a newly established business school in Salt Lake, Kolkata. This business school has been set up with a determined initiative of making tomorrow’s leaders. In fact, the PCCSB is successfully trying to act as a beneficial medium between the academics and the industries. In order to produce future managers and leaders equipped with the ultimate managerial skills, the PCCSB is offering effective modern facilities and curriculum to its students. The PC Chandra School of Business has a noble vision to get recognized as India’s best institution in the field of specialized education. This apart, this B-school also has a prudent mission to equip its students with the right attitude and the latest skills to suit the demands of the various types of industries.
<br /><br />The PCCSB firmly believes that giving emphasis on areas like Academic Enlightenment, Attitudinal Development, English Language Skills Development and Personality Development can give an additional benefit in building up tomorrow’s leaders today. The well defined and the specialized courses in Retail, Advertising, Sales Management, Human Resource Management, Banking and Mutual Fund, Insurance and Family Business etc are prepared keeping in mind the requirements of the industries. These courses aim at building up budding young business minds and making them shine in their chosen fields. The Summer Internship Programme and guest lectures from various domain of the industries are some of the salient features of PCCSB, which help in creating true leaders of tomorrow.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f1a63c9127a7832001c07b679e5e1cfc" url=""><![CDATA[MBA'S 4 EXECUTIVES<br/><br/>Evening MBA in PCCSB
<br /><br />The main objective of the evening MBA course in PC Chandra School of Business (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> is to enable the working executives to earn add-on qualifications to enhance their professional career. The evening MBA in PCCSB is aptly tailored to meet the needs of its takers who actually do not have time to get into a full time MBA. This course is of two-year duration and is held three days a week in the evening. Punjab Technical University (PTU) conducts the exams every six months. It comprehensively covers all the basic management subjects in its curriculum. This course conducted by PCCSB is broadly categorized into four semesters and offers the following support to its takers. These are :
<br /><br />i)	Affordable Course Fee
<br />ii)	Free Net-Book Computer
<br />iii)	Free access to Library
<br />iv)	Free access to Computer Lab
<br />v)	Free access to Gymnasium
<br /><br />The required qualification to undergo this module is a normal graduation from any UGC recognized universities in any discipline. The students who want to apply to PCCSB can either apply online or can avail the prospectus from the institute. The main streams included in this curriculum are HR, Finance, Systems and Marketing. 
<br /><br />The evening MBA of the PC Chandra School of Business is made in accordance with the demands of today’s industry and hence is aptly capable of making tomorrow’s leaders. This course helps its takers to implement rational but innovative work methodology in order to make the industry think in a lateral way. 
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7bee1d5ec4116b6161ec1688b8ea18b2" url=""><![CDATA[CORPORATE XPOSURE AT PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>CORP-CONNECT AT PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS
<br /><br />Corp Connect is an important medium which, connects the students of PC Chandra School of Business with the corporate world. It provides them a suitable platform to get the maximum benefit from the industry. The Corp Connect session offered by PCCSB help the students to have a realistic view of the market scenario, an opportunity to interact with the corporate honchos from various sectors and confidence to voice their opinion and queries in a packed session. The Corp Connect of PC Chandra School of Business has five major sub-divisions. These are: Corp Talk, Corp Exposure, Corp Associates,  Corp Research and Corp Cetera. 
<br /><br />Corp Talk:  The Corp Talk implies guest lectures by eminent personalities from the industry where the students have the full freedom to have a share of the corporate happenings through verbal interaction. 
<br /><br />Corp Exposure:  It helps the students to put into practice the theoretical aspect of management education.
<br /><br />Corp Associates:  The Corp Associates facilitates the students to get associated with apex business bodies like the CII, FICCI etc. 
<br /><br />Corp Research: It emphasizes upon carrying out live projects by the students which are being given by the esteemed faculties of the institution.
<br /><br />Corp Cetera:  It includes other subsidiary activities like that of Mall Visit and industry visit.
<br />The Corp Connect session is held every Friday evening in the college premise. Various facets of management like the HRM, Finance, Marketing, IT etc are covered in this comprehensive programme of preparing tomorrow’s leaders today. Some of the topics covered in this programme are CRM, Financial Sales and Management, Future Role of HR Professionals etc. The Corp Connect enable the students to become confident and quality management professionals in their respective areas, which can really change the corporate world. 
<br /><br />Some of the renowned speakers of the Corp Connect are Mr. Rajiv Soni (Head Marketing Communication- Tata Steel) others.Mr. Gautam Roy Choudhury ( AVP-Axis Bank), Mr. P.S.Paul(D.G.M.-H.R-IOCL), Mr. Susanta Bandopadhyay (Executive-Director-HR- Vesuvius India), and few others.
<br /><br />Few students opine that the sessions are good, interesting and even they are willing to take more such classes. Some are of the view that the good learning atmosphere and quality teachers help them to grab things better and faster. Some of them said that the lecturers demonstrated practical simulated sessions which help them to have a deep insight into the practical problems of the industry. Finally, it can be said that majority of the students expressed their eagerness and enthusiasm to have more of corporate interactions and lively classroom session.
<br /><br />PCCB WEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dc5a02d81f7363af95b1d507d9c8d9a3" url=""><![CDATA[LIBRARY OF PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>Library of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />The Library of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS is an indispensable part for its management students as it helps them by selecting, acquiring and disseminating appropriate management information. The Library of PCCSB has adopted the Open Access System, which enables its members (students and faculties) to avail books of their choice. The unique features of the Library of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS are as follows:
<br /><br />a)	Current Awareness Services: This service helps to keep its members update about the recent happenings in our country and abroad.
<br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />	Selective Dissemination of Information: This service helps an individual or a group to have relevant information to his/her/their topic of interest.
<br />c)	Information Retrieval System: It helps the members to get quick access to the bibliographical information of books and CD’s.
<br />d)	Print Media: The Library of PCCSB has vast collections of books, periodicals, journals and magazines of varied genres to suit the diverse needs.
<br />e)	Non-Print Media: This Library has a good collection of educational CD’s, which help the students through its unique audio-visual features.
<br />f)	Reprographic Service: This service comes free for the staff members and nominal fees are charged for the students. The students and the staff members can avail the scanning facility whenever necessary.
<br />g)	Micro- Documents: These documents refer to the discussion papers, case studies, journals, articles, instructors manual etc for reference purpose by the students and the faculties.
<br /><br />The timing of the Library is from 10.00 am to 7.00 pm. The people coming to the Library should keep the place clean, handle the books and papers carefully and should maintain silence. Any damage to the Library should be borne by the concerned person. The Library should be used for the sole purpose of studying and not for informal discussion.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="130e89fc9c3b8696aa5bcc79ff781f90" url=""><![CDATA[FEST IN PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>Fest of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />A fest in a b-school is generally held to assess the managerial acumen of the students and to have an informative and an educational interaction among them. This apart, a fest also involve lot of cultural activities and business games, which exhibit the creative sides of the future mangers
<br /><br />The Fest of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> is a noble initiative to provide a platform to the future managers of our country to exhibit their managerial skills. D Fiestta, the fest of PCCSB was organized on 1st and 2nd of May, 2009. The business quiz and the various management games were the main attractions of the fest. 
<br /><br />The first day had the debate judged by Godhuli Mukherjee, Director of Election Planning Commission and Mr. Rajiv Soni, Head of Marketing Communication at Tata Steel. This event was followed by an Impromptu where two different slides were shown and the participants had to link them through lateral thinking. This event was judged by Prasenjit Ukil, VP of HSBC and Jaybrata Ghosh, associate consultant of TCS.
<br /><br />The HR Game asked the participants to pick a chit and act accordingly. The Finance Game had business related queries and an offline Stock Exchange, where the participants was told to sell virtual shares. The Marketing Game was no less fun where the participants had to sell lipsticks for men. This was evaluated by Mr. Abhijit Roy, Senior Vice president of Berger Paints. 
<br /><br />The Fest of PCCSB was indeed a successful event as it involved whole hearted participation from the students and it was also an interactive way to treat the seniors. The Fest of PCCSB was also a learning part as it unfolds many interesting information pertaining to management studies to the students. Students were of the view that the Fest of PCCSB will be much more innovative and informative in the coming future and will attract many more business schools to participate.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fe9b7063662e4f427d4f40021dec6371" url=""><![CDATA[PLACEMENT SCENARIO IN PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>Placement scenario in PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />The purpose of placements is an integral part of any and every b-school of a country. This is also very much true for PCCSB. The main advantage of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS is that, it has got a very industry related course structure, highly educated and experience faculties and strong training and placement department. Moreover, rigorous exam schedules also help sharpen the abilities of the students to make a place for themselves in the corporate world. This apart, the special emphasis on personality development and grooming part plays a pivotal role in complete change of personality of the students to make them smart enough to get placed in the corporates.
<br /><br />Top recruiters of this b-school are
<br /><br />a)	SUPER RELIGARE LABORATORIES LTD.,
<br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />	DUNLOP INDIA LTD.,
<br />c)	SAJ INDUSTRIES LTD.,
<br />d)	DREAMMAKER CAREER SOLUTIONS PVT. LTD.,
<br />e)	CIPLA,
<br />f)	TARINI PVT.LTD.,
<br />g)	YES BANK,
<br />h)	TRADEINDIA.COM,
<br />i)	KOMBENCH FINANCIAL SERVICES LTD.,
<br />j)	HSBC
<br />k)	KOTAK MAHINDRA
<br />l)	ABC INDIA LTD.
<br />m)	BERGER PAINTS
<br />n)	BOC
<br />o)	IMRB
<br />p)	LENOVO
<br />q)	HCL
<br />r)	PANTALOONS
<br />s)	METRO CASH AND CARRY
<br />t)	SPENCER’S
<br />u)	TATA INDICOM
<br />v)	GENIUS CONSULTANTS
<br />w)	NEROLAC PAINTS
<br />x)	ITC
<br />y)	INDIAN OIL
<br />z)	TATA AIG
<br />aa)	PEPSI
<br />b<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />	ULTRA TECH
<br />cc)	BIRLA TYRES
<br />dd)	BARISTA
<br />ee)	BHARTI AXA
<br /><br />The PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS is flawlessly catering to the needs of the students by providing the best learning ambience and at the same time meeting the industry demands by supplying the best manpower. Even in recession stricken corporate world, PCCSB has very well managed to place its students successfully. By determination, goodwill and commitment, PCCSB has become the ULTIMATE MBA junction for MBA aspirants.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8564768b244a33e89a3271665d9a53b3" url=""><![CDATA[GYM IN PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>Gym in PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />The Gym in PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> offers the facility of keeping and maintaining body fitness of the students and the staffs alike. The Gym of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> is highly equipped with all modern machineries and equipments. The students of PCCSB can even engage themselves in yoga, free-hand exercises and aerobics apart from rigorous body-workouts. The audio-visual effect in the Gym enables them to concentrate in performing the exercises. These equipments are periodically maintained and even upgraded when required under the esteemed supervision of our qualified trainer.
<br /><br />The Gym of PCCSB has the following machines to suit the varied needs of our students. PCCSB firmly believes that “ A Healthy Mind Resides in A Healthy Body”. Hence it has created a modernized gym with the following instruments. These are:
<br /><br />a)	Corporate Motorised Treadmill (01)-  Used for running, jogging, walking and cardio- workouts.
<br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />	Mannual Treadmill (02)-  Used for running, jogging, walking and cardio-workouts.
<br />c)	Lat Pully Machine (01)-  Used for improvement of Latissie Massdorsi Muscle.
<br />d)	Cycle (01)-                       Used for cardio- workouts.
<br />e)	Preachurecurl Machine-    Used for biceps muscle.
<br />f)	Leg-Extention Machine-    Improves quadrishape muscle.
<br />g)	Butterfly Machine-            Improves shape of chest muscle.
<br />h)	Chest press Machine-        Improves chest muscle.
<br />i)	Parallel Bar along with  -   Improves chest , Deltroid, Trapezious muscle, 
<br />             Vertical Leg Rising       -  Reduces lower abdominal fat
<br />And Wrist Rolling    -         Improves Upper and Lower forearms
<br />Machine and Trunk   -        Reduces inter-coastal zone fat
<br />Twisting Machine
<br />j)	Decline Sit-ups Board (02)-  Improves upper abdominal muscles
<br />k)	Cross Trainer-                        Used for cardio-workouts
<br /><br />Thus it can be said that the Gym of PCCSB benefits the students to maintain strong body and mind in ways more than one. The cost of using the Gym is included with the course fee. This Gym truly enhances the enduring capacity of our future managers produced by PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cd704a571c3ac8663076fc7c17bedab9" url=""><![CDATA[CORP TALK IN PRODUCT MANAGEMENT IN PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>Corp Talk on Product Management in PCCSB
<br /><br />Corp Talk on Product Management in PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> is a significant event on the part of the management students who dream to become the future leaders of our country. This topic was briefly explained to the students of PCCSB by Mr.L.S.S Lal,  National Head of Sales (Rupa and Co.) on the 5th of February, 2010. He has got 29 years of relevant experience in Sales and Marketing and also other allied domain. 
<br /><br />During his stipulated duration, Mr. Lal has demonstrated abilities in market expansion, brand building, generating new business and targeting potential customers. The students were highly engrossed by his dynamic personality and interactive nature in depicting marketing managerial skills. The thought of considering marketing as a sole professional career came as an instant choice to many of the students of PCCSB because of the valuable session rendered by Mr. Lal.
<br /><br />At the end of the session he was presented a memento and the students’ representatives delivered a vote of thanks. The students were of the view to attend such more sessions during their courses.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ec46caae702b47bdbabd3d1fd5f4adb6" url=""><![CDATA[FEEL PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>Feel PCCSB
<br /><br />“ The Feel PCCSB” is a unique concept adopted by the PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />. This initiative enables its students to have an idea about the campus life, the faculties, the teaching methodology and last but not the least, the placements. 
<br /><br />The PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS allows its students to have a glimpse of true management education through this programme. This facility is however, applicable to the students of the Post Graduate Programme in Management.  “ The Feel PCCSB” initiative continues for fourteen days and comes free of cost. In these fourteen days, the students utilize the maximum available resources like the well stocked library, the hi-tech grooming lab and well equipped gymnasium to satisfy their thirst for management education. This programme ensure that the students can fulfill their curiosity before investing their money and precious time in shaping their professional career.
<br /><br />This unique concept adopted by the PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS makes it stand uniquely among even the best b-schools of the city. Not only that, it also exhibits the confidence and vision of institution authorities. This programme of PCCSB also depicts the fact that no matter what, quality always comes first. This unique idea has really helped this b-school in obtaining quality students and hence premium placements.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="814465b923faf66ab06be7eb40e51aff" url=""><![CDATA[INDUCTION IN PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>The Induction Programme of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />The Induction programme of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> is very unique of its kind. This programme welcomes the students to get associated and be indispensable members of PCCSB family during their stay period. The senior batch students offer grand welcome to the fresher’s batch through this Induction programme. Apart from the students, the administrative staff, the faculties, the placement and the marketing departments are also cordially invited to make this programme a grand success. This event is generally initiated by the campus Director, Mr. Avishek Auddy by a welcome speech. This is then followed by an interactive speech from the representatives of the senior batch. The freshers are then directed to introduce themselves. 
<br /><br />The main purpose of the Induction programme in PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS is to know the future managers in a deeper way. Secondly, the students are made conscious about their role as business students. 
<br /><br />Finally, both the senior and the junior batch students end up in having gala celebration with mouth watering food, snacks, tea and coffee at the campus. This programme truly unfolds the social and inter-personal skills of the future leaders of our country.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c65dc515d70e34cc2838b7958792aa32" url=""><![CDATA[INTERNSHIP IN PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>Internship in PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />Internship programme in PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> is an integral part of its management courses. Unlike any other B-schools, which provide only one internship, PCCSB allocates three separate internships for individual student in three different companies during his/her two-year PGPM course duration. This is mainly done with the aim to make the students gradually adapted to the competitive market scenario and for practical corporate exposure. This is because PCCSB believes that practical experience is the best learning process. 
<br /><br />The duration of the first internship is of one month, the second is of one and half months and the third is of three months. Each student of PCCSB is individually evaluated after each internship he/she completes.  The students mainly face problems during internships in three important areas. These are: communication skill, work profile/ambience and finally the inter-personal skills. Afterwards, the concerned students are given adequate attention to upgrade him/her in accordance with the corporate demand. The internship programme in PCCSB continues for five and half months and within this period, the students are exposed to the industry for experiencing the on-job training so as to have an idea of the actual work environment. This concept really helps to bring the best out of the management students of PCCSB so that they can bring changes and innovation in the corporate scenario.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="105058de6667f82bf5f91988db3ce5dc" url=""><![CDATA[POST GRADUATE EXECUTIVE PROGRAMME IN MANAGEMENT IN PCCSB<br/><br/>Post Graduate Executive Programme in Management of PC CHANDRA    SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />The main objective of the Post Graduate Executive Programme in Management of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> is to make the students aptly equipped with right sets of skills and attitude to rule the corporate world. This course of PCCSB is a part time and its duration is one year. It mainly caters to the working executives who literally have no time to invest in their academics. The Post Graduate Executive Programme in Management consists of four specialized streams. These are: Financial Sales and Management, Retail Management, Human Resource and Corporate Intelligence and Advertising and Marketing Communications. 
<br /><br />The PGEPM in PCCSB aims in structuring the thought process of the individuals to enable them think the business way. The working executives who will be going for this course, will be immensely benefited as they will be enriched with the modern business approaches to deliver customized results. 
<br /><br />The Post Graduate Executive Programme in PCCSB offers the following facilities:
<br /><br />Classroom Sessions using electronic delivery media
<br />Case Studies
<br />Presentations and Project Work
<br />Flexible timings
<br />Free Access to Guest Lectures
<br />Free Internet Access
<br />Free Library Access
<br />Free Access to Gymnasium
<br />Specially designed course materials
<br /><br />People with a graduation degree in any discipline and at least two years of post qualification work experience is a pre-requisite  to be eligible. This apart, they have to sit for CAT/MAT/XAT or PCCSB autonomous exam to qualify.
<br /><br />People successfully completing this course become highly efficient and capable in delivering solutions fast and in a unique way. Not only that, they also become indispensable for the industry because they exhibit qualities necessary to become tomorrow’s leaders.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1ae2784eafafb103e5641e964cad3a9b" url=""><![CDATA[BUDGET DAY IN PCCSB/PCCSOB<br/><br/>Budget Day of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />The Budget Day at PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> was held this year on the 26th of February, 2010 in the college campus. This is the second year that the Budget Day is being observed in the college. The students of the college, the faculties, and eminent personalities were present at the programme. The Budget Day was observed in a spacious hall in the 1st floor of the building. The budget was shown live on a big projector. Everybody listened the budget in wrapped attention.
<br /><br />Our college students made a brief introduction before the starting of the session. The renowned personalities who were present in the programme include Mr. Asim Ranjan Manna (Director of Dalmia Securities Pvt. Ltd.) and Mr. Debapriya Ghosh ( Guest Faculty of J.U.). 
<br /><br />The Budget Day of PCCSB mainly emphasized upon the importance of knowing the budget and its merits and demerits. Our esteemed panelists analyzed a comparative study of the budget. This was then followed by an interactive question-answer session between our students and the dignitaries. Some of the questions were also brilliantly explained through verbal illustrations by our faculty Mr. Gautam Sinha and campus Director, Mr. Avishek Auddy.
<br /><br />The Budget Day immensely made the students aware about the supposed economic developments in our country. This in turn helps them to get educated about the market scenario so that they can become able and efficient managers of tomorrow. 
<br /><br />Finally, the session was concluded with a vote of thanks and the students were more than happy as their doubts were made crystal clear by our eminent panelists. They clearly expressed their views that they are really interested in becoming a part of this event next year too.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3f8e15c75b484ee5ef4369622d7a10e0" url=""><![CDATA[Post Graduate Programme in Management in PCCSB<br/><br/>Post Graduate Programme in Management in PCCSB
<br /><br />The Post Graduate Programme in Management in PC Chandra School of Business has been designed keeping in mind the demands of the industry and the ingredients needed by the students to match up the demand. In fact, this course aptly suit the needs of those who want to make business management as their profession. Post Graduate Programme in Management in PCCSB is a two year full time course offering dual major specializations in two consecutive years.
<br /><br />In this course the students will be receiving two management degrees. One is the PGPM conferred by the PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS and the other is the MBA degree given by Punjab Technical University (PTU). The PGPM programme offers Cafeteria specializations in either of the domain mentioned below:
<br /><br />Retail Management
<br /> Advertising and Marketing Communications
<br /> Banking and Mutual Funds
<br /> Insurance
<br /> Family Business.
<br /><br />On the other hand, the MBA degree enables the students to go for general specializations in any one of the following:
<br /><br />HR
<br /> IT
<br /> FINANCE 
<br /> MARKETING. 
<br /><br />The students undergo three separate internships of five and a half months duration in total during this course. The dual specialization offered in this course immensely help our students to be the future leaders of our country.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fd394f2ca4969141fdaffbe5a7d9b38b" url=""><![CDATA[CORP TALK ON RETAIL MANAGEMENT IN PCCSB<br/><br/>CORP TALK ON RETAIL MANAGEMENT IN PCCSB
<br /><br />An interactive session on Retail Management was organized in the campus of PCCSB in the month of January. The speaker of the session was Smita Chakravorty, Head of Marketing East and Hyderabad, at Planet M Retail. The session started with a welcome speech by the students.
<br /><br />The session on Retail Management in PC Chandra School of Business was highly interesting as well as informative as the speaker shared her experience in the field of sales, marketing and advertising. She gave vivid virtual description of the actual work ambience in the Advertising and Marketing domain. She also highlighted the multiple job responsibilities and strategies one have to handle and execute to penetrate deep into the market. This was followed by the question-answer, which literally made the students glued to the session. 
<br /><br />This session at PC Chandra School of Business concluded on a positive note and vote of thanks by the students. The speaker was presented a memento and the students being highly motivated are eagerly willing to attend more such lectures during their academic session.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="db953a1c8d0679e78063173d42bfc5d" url=""><![CDATA[ADMINISTRATION IN PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCSB)<br/><br/>ADMINISTRATION IN PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />The Administration in PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS is an integral part in smooth running of this business school. The Administration Department is run by qualified and experienced professionals who efficiently look after verticals like procurement, student services, infrastructure, systems and other allied domains. All types pf queries on the part of the students is effectively taken care of by this department. Mr. Avishek Auddy, the Director of PCCSB keeps a close watch in the functioning of the Administrative Department.
<br /><br />All types of official requests/proposals by the students, faculties and the employees need to be approved by the Administration Department before being taken to the supreme authority. The apex authority in consultation with the Administrative Head of PCCSB makes all important decisions or amendments.
<br /><br />Lastly, this wing of PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS is also responsible to put a check on any type of misdoings or fraudulent activities by the students or their accomplice.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
<br /><br />.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="26faceeccc1cd1b4f223b5aec7088b5" url=""><![CDATA[A Knowledge Initiative by PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS(PCCS<br/><br/>A Knowledge Initiative by PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS(PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS(PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />,a newly born business school in Salt Lake, Kolkata organized a Knowledge Initiative Programme on the 7th of September, 2009. The venue was Shibnath Shastri College, Kolkata. The participants included the under graduate students. The time duration of the programme was of two hours.
<br /><br />The main objective of the programme was to emphasize upon two aspects, namely Effective Communication and Choosing the Right Career. PCCSB firmly believes that  effectual communication skills and opting the right professional career are the hallmark of any successful professionals. The discussion on the aforesaid topics was made effective and informative through the slide presentations. The Director of PCCSB, Mr. Avishek Auddy took an active part in the programme. Students participated in large numbers and the seminar ended with interactive question-answer session.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fe1f85398d6eb50ca805307be5cda008" url=""><![CDATA[Seminar by PCCSB at Calcutta Stock Exchange(CSE)<br/><br/>Seminar by PCCSB at Calcutta Stock Exchange(CSE)
<br /><br />YO !! CAP M, 2010 is a seminar on youth opportunities in the Capital Market, which was jointly organized by PC CHANDRA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (PCCS<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> and CALCUTTA STOCK EXCHANGE on Saturday, April 24th, 2010. The main objective of the seminar was to provide a synoptic overview of the Capital Market amongst the youth and the opinion leaders dealing with them. The seminar highlighted on the market mechanism so that budding investors or entrepreneurs can prudently utilize their money for steady growth of our industries.
<br /><br />The target audience in the gathering comprises of the undergraduate and post- graduate students, faculties from reputed institutions and young professionals. The facilitators include the MD and CEO of the Calcutta Stock Exchange, Manager of SEBI, GM of Calcutta Stock Exchange, Ex-banker and faculty of PCCSB and Ex-Director of Calcutta Stock Exchange and also the Director of PCCSB, Mr. Avishek Auddy.
<br /><br />PCCSBWEBMASTER
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>