<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="15">
		<document id="5c42d2c786bbc26501d086716d00326" url=""><![CDATA[well, is it so hard to conceive nowadays??<br/><br/>nowadays, people are more career-minded and stress has become an enemy to a family of bliss.. why do people procrastinate when they are of conceivable age? are people becoming more and more selfish, just because they are daunted by the trouble of upbringing their offsprings? To be frank, even if you are potent, it doesnt necessarily mean that you can conceive at the end of the day.. regular body checkups are essential to assure yourself. It's sometimes best to equip oneself with significant knowledge that can nourish one's mind throughout the rest of one's life.. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bestlifeyouwant.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.bestlifeyouwant.com</a> is 1 website that equips you with a better tomorrow, especially when you feel lonely in the absence of your spouse. I really feel very blissful upon encountering this website, the world will definitely benefit too! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e6994acc8f9a2769c76a1dc3ada34c17" url=""><![CDATA[Affairs of the heart..<br/><br/>Have you ever been troubled in love? Is your relationship the one you want or you are just not ready to take on 1? Sometimes it's just a matter of how each individual think.. You got hurt in relationships and you wont want to commit to 1 so easily because you are daunted by the setbacks suffered or you may suffer again. Love is an intangible element which you cant measure with how much you did for your love and how much you get in return. Ultimately it is the perseverance, consistency, patience and sincerity (most important factor) that counts. Communication and mutual trust are significant as well. Always let your love know what you are thinking in every moment, so he or she can be assured. To be able to get together is a chance of a lifetime and we do have to cherish each other no matter what may happen in your journey.. a TRUE LOVE is hard to come by, though. Sometimes it's obstination in someone that causes commotion or avoidable conflicts. Give and take is the key to a better tomorrow. A strong relationship is bound to have storms and hurdles preventing someone from going forward. It applies to all situations in life.. to be able to succeed in something, determination (the will to do something) and keeping on to the direction you are facing are essential. A strong person is someone who disregards and braves all the 'high tides', to get to his goal. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.couples.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.couples.hop.clickbank.net</a> is indeed a link to all bliss.. somewhere that you will be able to find the key to your happiness..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4b91d0f369ab1d90a2e7f0c27eb9435d" url=""><![CDATA[Losing weight to stay healthy?<br/><br/>Do you lose weight just because you want to be healthy, to please your mate or simply just to look good? People are not fat by nature, but family background as well as parents' genes play a part.. Bingeing on food indeed, do fattens a person to his/her irregular shape. So long as you can control your food-craving, embark on an exercising lifestyle and taking stress under your control. Maintaining a good attitude towards life is essential as well. Have you ever wondered why fat people get fatter? They have a poor control over their craving for good food though sometimes it's tormenting to refrain yourself from eating good food when they are just right in front of your eyes!! Utter determination is required in getting yourself toned up.. no one is able to help but YOU yourself!! <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.turbulence.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.turbulence.hop.clickbank.net</a> is a link that shows you around the process of getting yourself the confidence you yearn for. No regrets after all..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31df3234d965a11baf0911adad891148" url=""><![CDATA[women's greatest concerns in this era..<br/><br/>Hiding your cellulite legs is much harder to do than hiding a cellulite butt or belly. Unlike with your stomach or buttocks, it's not as though you can just cover them up all year round. At one point or another, someone is going to see your cellulite legs and you're going to be horribly embarrassed. Honestly, are you really going to just sit around and wait for that to happen? Or, are you going to do something about it with these simple home remedies for cellulite. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.reneecel.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.reneecel.hop.clickbank.net</a> is all you need to find out in order to regain the past confidence lost..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a078f446f49be00e6d4ef0607458d851" url=""><![CDATA[david copperfield or criss angel?<br/><br/>A talent indeed, is not self-acquired but in-born nature. To be able to perform magic tricks needs a lot of practice and skills but not just talent. With talent, it helps one to pick up the skills much easily and faster. People said, 'there's more to it than meets the eye'.. Magicians are indeed too discreet not to reveal the essence of magic tricks to the audience, to be able to live up to this standard requires full concentration as well as determination to improve after every failures or setbacks. That's the spirit! David Copperfield and Criss Angel are definitely the mascots of the magic industry.. We are fortunate to learn some first-ever uncovered magic tricks from <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.magicsi25.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.magicsi25.hop.clickbank.net</a>. Indeed an eye-opener..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cce6ecb12e0c50cebb20a5aa40d4a6ab" url=""><![CDATA[Cars, an asset or liability?<br/><br/>What if there is a way to buy a car and increase your standard of living simultaneously? Well, my partner and I bought a brand new car because we wanted to increase our monthly income. That doesn’t make sense! Buy a brand new car to increase your income? Usually buying a brand new car means that your disposal income goes down not up. Hmm, financial illiteracy is a dangerous thing. Everything starts with a shift in thinking. The key is to understand the difference between assets and liabilities and to have your assets PAY for your liabilities, so you don’t have to. Have you ever noticed that when you apply for a loan, the bank tells you that your car is an asset? Under the true definition of assets and liabilities, anything that takes money out of your pocket is a liability. Henceforth, not only were our cars liabilities, but they were extracting more money out-of-our-pockets every month just to keep them running. Both my partner and I owned older vehicles, which were starting to break down more often. Then an idea struck. What if we could unlock the money we had tied up in our cars and buy a brand new car without lowering our lifestyle but actually increasing it? That’s exactly what we did. We sold our cars and used the money to buy income-producing assets, which covered most of the payment on our brand new car. It is a sweet little car that comes loaded including leather interior. Not only is the payment covered, but we also managed to take advantage of the 0% financing for five years deal, so every dollar goes towards paying the car off. At the end of five years:
<br />The car will still be paid off. 
<br />We will still have the money from the sale of our older cars, which may even have INCREASED in value. 
<br />We will have an income stream in addition to our existing income.  
<br />We did not have to lower our standard of living or work harder or longer to come up with the car payment month after month. What else could you apply this strategy to - anything that you would spend a chunk of money for. So, the next time you’re thinking about buying a car or some other 'liability', consider if there might be a better way. 
<br />To know more in details, you can refer to: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.jamaco.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.jamaco.hop.clickbank.net</a>
<br />&lt;Photo 1&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8822fc93bd1370465530411db7233654" url=""><![CDATA[Training your diaphragm to STARDOM?<br/><br/>Can anyone learn how to sing? It always amaze me when I am asked this. Yes, anyone can learn how to sing. Most people have the false belief that singers are born with the singing talent. You either have it or you don't. Nothing could be further from the truth. With the proper singing instructions anyone can learn how to sing. There are a few people who, through trial and error, happen to stumble upon the proper singing techniques. These people are referred to as natural born singers, but in reality, they learned how to sing using the same techniques that can be taught to anyone. Provided that you receive the proper vocal training. Learning how to sing does not involve learning, and practicing boring scales or breathing exercises. Learning how to sing properly is a natural systematic process to building a powerful singing voice without any injury or stain. With the proper singing instructions you can learn how to sing, and should see dramatic improvements to your singing voice literally overnight.
<br />The professional trainer, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.ric1312.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.ric1312.hop.clickbank.net</a>, is one of the three judges of AMERICAN IDOL, who are definitely here to bring you to stardom.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="999830c60f03b53ada9f46f0a8296f54" url=""><![CDATA[We definitely can't do WITHOUT $$$ in this world!!!<br/><br/>Have you ever wondered why some people can make a lot of money in all affiliate programs and some don't...even though they are given the same product, compensation plan and training information, and Are DOING it the same way they have been taught? In our quest for financial success we typically make the same mistakes, over and over again. STOP! It really is not necessary to continue down thesame path as you've always gone. Your birth certificate doesn't come with a guarantee of financial success, but when you were born you came fully equipped with talents, abilities, desires, and choices. Now you need to make sure you are fullyutilizing those talents, abilities, and desires... and that you are making the right choices to create the BIG Money for you from <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.ssw01.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.ssw01.hop.clickbank.net</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="302040238ea7179b6d4a7cd43d52400d" url=""><![CDATA[Is hair so important?<br/><br/>With the hormonal changes of aging comes a decrease in the number of active hair follicles. Though this is an essentially universal change in all of us, a number of hormonal, genetic, or disease states make some of us lose hair earlier in life. The most common cause of hair loss is known as androgenetic alopecia, or male pattern baldness (in men), and female pattern baldness (in woman). Stress from work and studies as well as unhealthy food consumption are the main trigger to hair loss. Other drugs also can cause hair loss. Many medicines used to treat even common diseases can cause hair loss. Most do so by unknown mechanisms, and most of the drugs known to do this only cause hair loss in a small minority of patients. Obviously, be sure to ask your doctor before discontinuing a medication as some of these medicines require a slow taper to avoid complications. Click this link, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.hairebook.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.hairebook.hop.clickbank.net</a> for more insights
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="54c286ae87640abef5b842d78128c237" url=""><![CDATA[Symptoms of AGEING<br/><br/>One of the things that we are most concerned about as we start to age is that our bodies and / or our minds are going to give out on us. One of the best ways to prevent this type of physical or mental deterioration is to stay as active as possible into our later years. One of the things that has taken place as humans start to live longer and longer is that they are more likely to die of specific diseases than of &quot;old age&quot;. As a result, the majority of medical research that is done to improve the quality of life for aging adults is focused on how to cure specific diseases related to aging (such as Alzheimer's or diabetes). It can be argued, however, that it would be more effective to combat the general health issue of aging rather than trying to fight specific diseases. The basic sentiment behind this argument is the belief that curing individual diseases has a limited effect on the number of lives that are going to be improved as a result of success. In contrast, delaying or reversing aging altogether would have a widespread effect and could ultimately lead to the avoidance or reduction of a multitude of the different diseases that are impacted by aging. For more details, feel free to click on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverstrong.antiwrink.hop.clickbank.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everstrong.antiwrink.hop.clickbank.net</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d0a24d38c9ad9a33da5728e25368ee7" url=""><![CDATA[Smoking KILLS..<br/><br/>We hear a lot about the relationship between tobacco and cancer. Everyone knows that you shouldn't smoke because smoking leads to cancer. So wouldn't you be shocked to find out that researchers are working on a vaccine for cancer which actually includes tobacco as one of the ingredience in the vaccine? The truth is that this isn't so shocking after all. Many times the ingredients used in a product don't really have the same effect as they would when used in an entirely different product. What's interesting here is really that researchers even thought to try this! And what's really important to take away from it is the fact that there could one day be a cancer vaccine out there.  is definitely a saviour to most compulsive smokers..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f52c3d658ba43c99f1d3eeda0f0197c1" url=""><![CDATA[Men's 'best friend'..<br/><br/>Dogs, like people respond better to praise than anger. If you spend all afternoon struggling with a naughty dog, you should make sure to let him know how good he is when he finally &quot;gets it&quot;. Make sure you use a &quot;happy&quot; tone. Dogs can tell an angry tone form a pleased one and saying &quot;Good boy&quot; in a tone that implies you want to attack him with a hatchet isn't going to work. Ultimately, he did what you wanted so let him know you're happy with him. Without that reinforcement he won't understand or remember to do it again. Give your dog affection and praise when he's sitting at your feet watching TV. I know it's easy to forget they're there sometimes, but chances are you're the dogs primary source of entertainment and affection. Let him know he's loved and that sitting quietly while you're focusing on something else can earn him rewards just as much as obedience or performing a trick.  is bound to make your dog an independant breed..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f12db073f7b35549945989bf05a5cb0b" url=""><![CDATA[Earning thru processing EMAILS? Is it possible for someone e<br/><br/>Here’s a little opportunity to share with my dear friends.. I can’t believe this initially till I keep getting real income! If you can process 30 a day, 
<br />you'll earn $750.00 every day! 
<br />Earn $25.00 For Every Email You Process! 
<br />You Are Guaranteed To Get Paid Instantly For Each Email You Process! 
<br />This is an easy, profitable opportunity to earn $1000's every week from home. 
<br />No experience required. 
<br />Your Earnings Are Unlimited... Below are your potential earnings!!! 
<br />5 e-mails processed 5x$25.00 = $125 Per Day!
<br />10 e-mails processed 10x$25.00 = $250 Per Day!
<br />25 e-mails processed 25x$25.00 = $625 Per Day!
<br />30 e-mails processed 25x$25.00 = $750 Per Day! 
<br />$273,750 a year income! 
<br />Hurry now!! Take action and Alertpay $25 to <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=fuhao82@hotmail.com">fuhao82@hotmail.com</a> and I'll show you the way.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="210f0cbc83eec25f82824e02946919d8" url=""><![CDATA[Economic Recession is bogging the whole world...<br/><br/>As many industries suffer during the US economic downturn, some workers are looking for jobs in sectors that are continuing to grow. Figures show that one of the most recession-proof industries is healthcare. US government statistics show the healthcare industry added more than three-quarters of a million jobs last year. And one internet job site, Jobfox, ranks nursing and medical administrative services as two of the safest careers to have during a recession. Despite promises to tackle recession together, EU governments are scrambling each in their own corner to come up with new measures to revive their economies, threatening the bloc's unity. However, the new wave of government actions since then has left some worried that EU states risk causing more harm than good by failing to coordinate. The banking sector is once again at the centre of governments' attention, with Britain announcing earlier this month an insurance scheme to relieve banks of the impact from the toxic assets ravaging their balance sheets. After Europe saw the weakest new car sales in 15 years in 2008, governments including France, Germany, Portugal, Spain and Sweden are mulling measures for the auto industry, one of the biggest employers on the continent. Measures under consideration range from incentives for scrapping old cars to encourage purchase of new vehicles, to tax breaks, public procurement initiatives and outright state investment in carmakers. On the economic front, government are also taking up different approaches, with London cutting value added tax to boost consumption, Berlin mulling big infrastructure investment and Paris looking into aiding companies. WASHINGTON - The economy shrank at a 3.8 percent pace at the end of 2008, the worst showing in a quarter-century, as the deepening recession forced consumers and businesses to throttle back spending. American consumers and businesses cut back everywhere in the final three months of 2008. Shoppers chopped spending on cars, furniture, appliances, clothes and other items. Businesses dropped the axe on equipment and software, home building and commercial construction. And overseas sales of U.S.-made goods and services tanked as foreign buyers grappled with their own economic woes. Meanwhile, U.S. exports, whose growth earlier last year helped to keep the economy afloat, turned negative. Economic slowdowns in other countries has cut into demand for U.S goods and services. Trying to survive the downturn, businesses are scrambling to cut costs and that's taking a painful toll on the nation's labor market. The unemployment rate jumped to a 16-year high of 7.2 percent in December and could hit 10 percent or higher at the end of this year or early next year. A staggering 2.6 million jobs were lost last year, the most since 1945, though the labor force has grown significantly since then. Another 2 million or more jobs will vanish this year, economists predict. New York's main futures contract, light sweet crude for March delivery, was up 26 cents to 41.94 dollars a barrel. The gains followed wildcat strikes at oil refineries in Britain, as well as data showing a milder-than-expected economic contraction in the United States. The Japanese data came a day after the United States said new home sales plunged almost 15 per cent in December to the lowest monthly level on record, while the number of people seeking unemployment benefits hit a record high. South Korean exports suffered their biggest-ever drop in January, adding to market expectations that the central bank will cut interest rates by at least half a percentage point to shore up Asia's fourth-largest economy. The country is home to the leading producers of computer chips, mobile phones and ships and is the first big Asian exporter to report trade data each month, providing an early indication of the state of global demand. Japan, China and a number of other export-reliant economies have also reported a collapse in trade in recent months, with the technology industry hit especially hard by worsening consumer demand in the United States and Europe. The benefits of an economic recession can be painful to admit. When capital flows freely, entrepreneurs and non-entrepreneurs alike get to start companies - much like walk-ons get to chase their dreams of playing big league. In a downturn, those not favored by the market get the boot. That is the benefit of a recession. We cull the herd of would-be entrepreneurs. It's like cutting the 6th string on the football squad. The bus can't hold that many kickers AND the soccer team needs that talent. So, talent gets redeployed as it is fit. Sure there are very real consequences, and those who can shake off the rejection to move on will flourish in their new environment. Our economy depends on the flexibility and variability - without it, innovation and incentive to innovate would die. It is no easy task to redeploy yourself, particularly if you must retrain yourself, but it is your ability to be flexible, adapt and embrace that promises you long term stability. For more updates in depth on how you can survive the crisis, visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.savings.bestlifeyouwant.com%2FIndex.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.savings.bestlifeyouwant.com/Index.html</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e571b942c33ff978dfbc774a88d9ce9a" url=""><![CDATA[Good resumes guarantee you a JOB?<br/><br/>Retrenchment is all over the world and unemployment rate is, nevertheless, kept at the high level. People are finding hard to seek for jobs in order to survive. Polishing up your resume is an essential thing to do, first of all. A good resume is the one that get you interviews, no more, no less. Although this is obvious and simplistic, it is surprising how many job seekers don’t have it clear enough.A good resume must fit the personality of its owner, tempered as well by the expectations of the industry. That means that there are as many good resumes as there are several kinds of people and kind of jobs. A good resume must be tailored to your exact needs and also to employer’s expectations. Guidelines are important to lead you back to the right track. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fresume.bestlifeyouwant.com%2Fhomepage.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://resume.bestlifeyouwant.com/homepage.html</a> is definitely the wise choice for helpless retrenched out there.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>