<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="2fd0d0d3d041a7e4073b6c6bc47196b7" url=""><![CDATA[Charges Against Muslim Students Prompt Debate Over Free Spee<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0aWNsZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtpZD03Mzg6Y2hhcmdlcy1hZ2FpbnN0LW11c2xpbS1zdHVkZW50cy1wcm9tcHQtZGViYXRlLW92ZXItZnJlZS1zcGVlY2gmYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9NjE6aXNsYW0mYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7SXRlbWlkPTQ4" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bid%3D738%3Acharges-against-muslim-students-prompt-debate-over-free-speech%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bcatid%3D61%3Aislam%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3BItemid%3D48"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;amp;id=738:charges-against-muslim-students-prompt-debate-over-free-speech&amp;amp;amp;catid=61:islam&amp;amp;amp;Itemid=48</a></a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO2FtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7YW1wO2lkPTczODpjaGFyZ2VzLWFnYWluc3QtbXVzbGltLXN0dWRlbnRzLXByb21wdC1kZWJhdGUtb3Zlci1mcmVlLXNwZWVjaCZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9NjE6aXNsYW0mYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7YW1wO0l0ZW1pZD00OA__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_11518704_34015157.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />When administrators at the University of California, Irvine, decided to suspend the Muslim Student Union for a quarter over the disruption of a speech last year by the Israeli ambassador to the United States, most thought the latest controversy on campus had ended.District Attorney Tony Rackauckas of Orange County, however, disagreed — and filed misdemeanor criminal charges last week against the 11 student protesters, accusing them of disturbing a public meeting and engaging in a conspiracy to do so.
<br /><br />The charges have not only reignited campus debate about the event but have also prompted a feisty argument about the role of free speech on a college campus, in this case one whose politics can seem as complicated as peace negotiations in the Middle East.
<br /><br />When the ambassador, Michael B. Oren, came to speak last February, several students stood up, one at a time, and interrupted him with shouted complaints about Israel. When the repeated outbursts continued deep into Mr. Oren’s speech, the ambassador huddled with his security aides to decide whether to continue speaking. He did, but by the time the speech was over, 11 Muslim students had been arrested. The group became known as the “Irvine 11,” although three were students from University of California, Riverside.
<br /><br />As students walked through campus one recent afternoon, most hardly batted an eye at the colorful fliers advertising some coming campus events. They may have missed the lecture “Islam the Misunderstood Religion.” But they could pick up a pamphlet about Islamic philosophy from a nearby table — where signs proclaimed “Free Egypt.”
<br /><br />During the fall quarter, while the suspension was in place, none of this kind of activity by the Muslim Student Union had been allowed.
<br /><br />Over the last decade, the university has become a symbol of what some Jewish groups say is a growing anti-Israel sentiment on campuses. But for others, the school is quickly becoming a symbol of problems Muslim students face when they are viewed as too outspoken.
<br /><br />“People are afraid to be seen as with us,” said Hamza Siddiqui, a senior and a leader of the Muslim Student Union. “It’s like they went after them, how do we know they aren’t going to come after us next? Everyone is afraid and looking over their shoulder.”
<br /><br />Mr. Siddiqui, 22, said even his parents have warned him to keep quiet and not involve himself too closely with the student group, worrying that he could get suspended or jeopardize his prospects for law school.
<br /><br />Because university officials are prohibited from asking about religion, it is impossible to know how many students are Jewish or Muslim. Many Muslim students come from the surrounding cities in Orange County, where there are vibrant Middle Eastern communities.
<br /><br />For years, Jewish and Israeli advocacy groups have said that the Muslim Student Union has fostered a hostile environment on campus. In 2007, the Office of Civil Rights of the federal Department of Education examined complaints from the Zionist Organization of America that the university was not doing enough to respond to the problem. The investigation cleared the campus administration of any wrongdoing. In 2009, the same organization complained that an event sponsored by the Muslim Student Union was used to raise money for an organization that helps Hamas, the Islamic militant group, in Gaza. The university asked the F.B.I. to investigate, but no charges were ever filed.
<br /><br />Much of the controversy on campus centers on Palestinian Awareness Week, which the Muslim Student Union has sponsored each spring. In the past, the week has included bloody Israeli flags and speeches delivered under signs that read “Holocaust in the Holy Land” and “Israel — the Fourth Reich.”
<br /><br />Many students came to dread the events, which some began to refer to as “hate week.” A few students have said they felt uncomfortable walking across campus wearing a Star of David or any other overtly Jewish symbol during the week. Some have had loud shouting matches, while others have chosen to stay home and avoid campus altogether.
<br /><br />By last winter, it seemed that the talk had been toned down and that much of the discomfort for Jewish students had subsided. But students said they caught wind of plans to interrupt Mr. Oren’s speech. The students who were arrested said that the protest had not been a Muslim Student Union activity, but an investigation by university officials concluded that that the group had coordinated the protest in an effort to shut down the event.
<br /><br />Similar outbursts have occurred during speeches by Israeli officials on other college campuses. But it appears that none prompted disciplinary actions from either the college or law enforcement officials.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4fd40cbe4e8721af2412c27389459471" url=""><![CDATA[Copts and Muslims worship side by side<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2lkPTc0Mjpjb3B0cy1hbmQtbXVzbGltcy13b3JzaGlwLXNpZGUtYnktc2lkZSZhbXA7Y2F0aWQ9Njk6Y3VycmVudC1hZmZhaXJz" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bid%3D742%3Acopts-and-muslims-worship-side-by-side%26amp%3Bcatid%3D69%3Acurrent-affairs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=742:copts-and-muslims-worship-side-by-side&amp;catid=69:current-affairs</a></a>[nick<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Fimages%2Fstories%2FFeb-11%2FCopts_and_Muslims_worship_side_by_side.jpgname"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/images/stories/Feb-11/Copts_and_Muslims_worship_side_by_side.jpgname</a>][object Object][/nickname] 
<br /><br />GROUPS of Egyptian Copts and Muslims conducted acts of worship side by side in Tahrir Square in the centre of Cairo on Sunday. They were among the hundreds of thousands of mainly young people who have occupied the square as part of continuing calls for the immediate removal from power of President Hosni Mubarak. Cordoned off by troops, the Copts held a mass, while Muslims conducted their midday prayers. This brief display of harmony contrasts with the bigger political picture in Egypt, which is becoming increasingly chaotic and difficult to read. Demonstrations and mounting pressure from Washington have failed to force Mr Mubarak out of his palace.
<br /><br />Because of the general uncertainty, foreigners continue to leave. Among them was the Revd Paul-Gordon Chandler, of St John the Baptist’s, in the Maadi district of Cairo, who flew out at the request of the Episcopal Church in the USA.
<br /><br />Mr Chandler said that most expatriates have been evacuated. “Unpredictability right now is the only known, it seems.” The un­predictability stems from the fact that although the uprising was people-led and spontaneous, those opposing the Mubarak regime lack a unified ideology.
<br /><br />A large number of Egyptians want Mubarak to go, but they cannot agree about the timing and manner of his departure. While the protesters in Tahrir Square are refusing to hold a dialogue with the government as long as the President is still in office, others have begun such consultations.
<br /><br />For the population at large, the euphoria is increasingly offset by the difficulties of coping with everyday life while businesses remain closed. But opposition leaders fear that if life becomes too normal, the momentum of the protests will be lost.
<br /><br />The President-Bishop of the Episcopal Church in Jerusalem and the Middle East, the Most Revd Mouneer Anis, told the American Anglican Council last weekend that Western governments did not appreciate that, “if the president left suddenly, there would be a vacuum, like what happened in Iraq, and this will give an opportunity for extreme groups to fight and divide and play around.”
<br /><br />Preliminary talks between opposition leaders and the Vice-President, Omar Suleiman, made little headway. But the first meeting was historic for two reasons: there was no one present from the ruling National Democratic Party, which has had Egyptian politics in a strangle­hold for decades; and representatives from the banned Muslim Brother­hood attended. This group, although banned, has a huge public following.
<br /><br />The potential is there for a new political landscape. But the wheels of the revolution are turning slowly, so it could be weeks — or months — before we see who is given the task of leading the new Egypt.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b5df06cacfb2eb00d307315cad14f00" url=""><![CDATA[Copts and Muslims worship side by side<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO2FtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7YW1wO2lkPTc0Mjpjb3B0cy1hbmQtbXVzbGltcy13b3JzaGlwLXNpZGUtYnktc2lkZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9Njk6Y3VycmVudC1hZmZhaXJz" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bid%3D742%3Acopts-and-muslims-worship-side-by-side%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bcatid%3D69%3Acurrent-affairs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;amp;amp;id=742:copts-and-muslims-worship-side-by-side&amp;amp;amp;amp;catid=69:current-affairs</a></a>[nick<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Fimages%2Fstories%2FFeb-11%2FCopts_and_Muslims_worship_side_by_side.jpgname"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/images/stories/Feb-11/Copts_and_Muslims_worship_side_by_side.jpgname</a>][object Object][/nickname] 
<br /><br />GROUPS of Egyptian Copts and Muslims conducted acts of worship side by side in Tahrir Square in the centre of Cairo on Sunday. They were among the hundreds of thousands of mainly young people who have occupied the square as part of continuing calls for the immediate removal from power of President Hosni Mubarak. Cordoned off by troops, the Copts held a mass, while Muslims conducted their midday prayers. This brief display of harmony contrasts with the bigger political picture in Egypt, which is becoming increasingly chaotic and difficult to read. Demonstrations and mounting pressure from Washington have failed to force Mr Mubarak out of his palace.
<br /><br />Because of the general uncertainty, foreigners continue to leave. Among them was the Revd Paul-Gordon Chandler, of St John the Baptist’s, in the Maadi district of Cairo, who flew out at the request of the Episcopal Church in the USA.
<br /><br />Mr Chandler said that most expatriates have been evacuated. “Unpredictability right now is the only known, it seems.” The un­predictability stems from the fact that although the uprising was people-led and spontaneous, those opposing the Mubarak regime lack a unified ideology.
<br /><br />A large number of Egyptians want Mubarak to go, but they cannot agree about the timing and manner of his departure. While the protesters in Tahrir Square are refusing to hold a dialogue with the government as long as the President is still in office, others have begun such consultations.
<br /><br />For the population at large, the euphoria is increasingly offset by the difficulties of coping with everyday life while businesses remain closed. But opposition leaders fear that if life becomes too normal, the momentum of the protests will be lost.
<br /><br />The President-Bishop of the Episcopal Church in Jerusalem and the Middle East, the Most Revd Mouneer Anis, told the American Anglican Council last weekend that Western governments did not appreciate that, “if the president left suddenly, there would be a vacuum, like what happened in Iraq, and this will give an opportunity for extreme groups to fight and divide and play around.”
<br /><br />Preliminary talks between opposition leaders and the Vice-President, Omar Suleiman, made little headway. But the first meeting was historic for two reasons: there was no one present from the ruling National Democratic Party, which has had Egyptian politics in a strangle­hold for decades; and representatives from the banned Muslim Brother­hood attended. This group, although banned, has a huge public following.
<br /><br />The potential is there for a new political landscape. But the wheels of the revolution are turning slowly, so it could be weeks — or months — before we see who is given the task of leading the new Egypt.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3294608771d71b6529d2111b8837b3e4" url=""><![CDATA[Afridi eleven departs for World Cup show<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bid%3D741%3Aafridi-eleven-departs-for-world-cup-show%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bcatid%3D70%3Asports%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3BItemid%3D27"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;amp;id=741:afridi-eleven-departs-for-world-cup-show&amp;amp;amp;catid=70:sports&amp;amp;amp;Itemid=27</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Fimages%2Fstories%2FFeb-11%2FAfridi_eleven_departs_for_World_Cup_show.jpg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/images/stories/Feb-11/Afridi_eleven_departs_for_World_Cup_show.jpg</a>
<br />National cricket team, led by Shahid Khan Afridi, has flown for Bangladesh to partake in cricket World Cup. The mega event is scheduled to kick off on February 19, Geo News reported.Earlier, Afridi eleven arrived Lahore airport from National Cricket Academy where the boys flew for Bangladesh.A large number of cricket fans thronged Allama Iqbal airport to see team off in shadow of prays but players did not talk to media on the occasion.Earlier, skipper Pakistan team Afridi told a press conference that players had developed good winning-combination, which, according to his experience, would help Pakistan in mega event.
<br /><br />He said he was watching Pakistan team competing in semi-final in the mega event, adding that he was satisfied with the performance of his side.
<br /><br />“Pakistani team is capable of wining world cup,” wicket keeper Kamran Akmal said.
<br /><br />The fifteen-member squad include Shahid Afridi (Captain), Misbah-ul-Haq (Vice-Captain), Muhammad Hafeez, Kamran Akmal, Younis Khan, Asad Shafiq, Umer Akmal, Abdul Razzaq, Abdul Rehman, Saeed Ajmal, Shoaib Akhtar, Umer Gul, Wahab Riaz, Junaid Khan and Ahmed Shehzad.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3b901d1ff8bedf716eeafb0e2848b03a" url=""><![CDATA[Prize-winning art is kids' stuff<br/><br/>Section: Fashion &amp; Lifestyle	 - Category: Family &amp; Kids
<br />LOOK closely in the bottom corners of Tim Johnson's painting Community base, which last night won the $50,000 Arthur Guy Memorial Guy Painting Prize, and you'll see two small stencils of choo-choo trains.These were applied by the Sydney artist's three-year-old twins, Leo and Dion, who the 63-year-old artist says are dragging him into new territory. Johnson, who also has two adult children, has explored a lot of artistic territory since he began painting in the early 1970s.
<br /><br />He has moved from the wild and wacky performance art of that explosive era, moved on to the more cerebral post-modernism of the '80s, and then delved into notions of ''cultural identity'' in the '90s as he explored Buddhism and various aspects of Asian and Native American art while also experimenting with photography and computer imagery.
<br /><br />''I was thinking about that question of what the 'next thing' might be on the way up on the bus to Bendigo,'' Johnson said yesterday at the Bendigo Art Gallery, which administers the biennial prize and is showing an exhibition of works by the 37 finalists from the 330 artists who entered this year's competition.
<br /><br />''But I don't think I can predict what the next thing will be until it happens. I don't think you can move on to the 'next' or 'new' thing but add to what you already know. And at the moment I think I'm probably adding my kids' perspective at how I look at things.''
<br /><br />Perspective is at the heart of Johnson's winning painting, which he painted in his Newtown studio over two weeks in preparation for a Sydney show, where it failed to sell.
<br /><br />Community base's aerial perspective is a view of Western Desert artists working alone or gathered at humpies in family groupings in the early 1980s when Johnson travelled to Papunya to work with its artists, who included the revered Clifford Possum and Charlie Tarawa. They are two of the 40 or so real people depicted in the painting and re-created on canvas from photographs Johnson took at the time.
<br /><br />So is Johnson also in the painting? ''No,'' he said. ''Hang on, I might be,'' he interrupted himself, pausing to looks at the 150-centimetre by 180-centimetre painting. ''No, I'm not because I was usually behind the camera.''
<br /><br />The painting uses Aboriginal dot patterns as well as what the artist describes as ''multiple vanishing effects''.
<br /><br />''And it has imagery from other sources - there's Asian bits and imagery from Chinese embroidery,'' he said, explaining that the multiplicity of motifs is a reflection of the world. ''Life is so much more complicated today and there's a lot of influences and imagery coming at us all the time and I tried to reflect that.''
<br /><br />The painting also provides Johnson's perspective on a life spent making art.
<br /><br />''They [the Western Desert artists] were a model to me of how you can work just living in their own community doing their own work and getting recognition from their community,'' he said.
<br /><br />It's a model Johnson has followed, which is probably why he is not as well known as many artists of his generation.
<br /><br />''I have never really promoted myself too much,'' he said, though he admitted that he had noticed an increase in attention since 2009 when a retrospective, Painting Ideas: Tim Johnson, organised by the Queensland Art Gallery and the Art Gallery of New South Wales, toured east-coast capitals and showed at Melbourne's Ian Potter Museum of Art.
<br /><br />''Sometimes good things happen when you don't need them and when you do need them they tend not to happen. I think the flow-on effect of the retrospective has helped me,'' said Johnson, whose paintings sell from $5000 for small works to about $60,000 for large multi-panelled works.
<br /><br />Bendigo Art Gallery director Karen Quinlan chose Johnson's work for the $50,000 cash prize ''unanimously'' with four other judges in a two-hour session on Thursday. She said that not even some of the judges had a thorough knowledge of Johnson's work but it was first on each of their list of favourites.
<br /><br />The Bendigo Art Gallery gets to keep the painting for its collection while the Guy family provides the $50,000 prize to the artist.
<br /><br />Given that artists who have won the previous three Arthur Guy Memorial Prizes can command more than $50,000 for large works, Ms Quinlan said it was time to consider increasing the prizemoney for the 2013 award
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9d90ebfdccc803d1bfeb5983683704d2" url=""><![CDATA[PIA’s head resigns to end strike<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0aWNsZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtpZD03NDQ8aW1nIGNsYXNzPSJzbWlsZXkiIHNyYz0iaHR0cDovL3YxLm5ldGxvZ3N0YXRpYy5jb20vdjYuMDAvNDIwOS8vcy9pL3NtaWxpZXMvdG9uZ3VlLmdpZiIgYWx0PSI6KSIgLz5pYXMtaGVhZC1yZXNpZ25zLXRvLWVuZC1zdHJpa2UmYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9Njk6Y3VycmVudC1hZmZhaXJz" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_12573429_34071338.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Employees of Pakistan’s state airline have called off a four-day strike that crippled air travel in the country after the resignation of the top company official. The leader of the employee union for Pakistan International Airlines (PIA) said their major demand was the resignation of the company’s managing director. The managing director of the airline resigned Friday to end the strike, Defence Minister Ahmad Mukhtar said.
<br /><br />“Managing director, PIA, Aijaz Haroon has resigned,” Mukhtar told a press conference in Islamabad, with Interior Minister Rehman Malik and union representatives alongside him.
<br /><br />The resignation prompted celebration among the strikers.
<br /><br />Union leader Sohail Baloch said they hope to have flights running again after midnight. The strike grounded more than 200 flights
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="387f2b79508baa23ed1f61596335e73f" url=""><![CDATA[Switzerland freezes any assets tied to Mubarak<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0aWNsZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtpZD03NDM6c3dpdHplcmxhbmQtZnJlZXplcy1hbnktYXNzZXRzLXRpZWQtdG8tbXViYXJhayZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_5300629_34071652.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />The Swiss government on Friday froze any assets belonging to former Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak or his family in Switzerland. Foreign Ministry spokesman Lars Knuchel said the order to block any bank accounts takes effect immediately but gave no details on the family’s assets.Swiss Finance Minister Widmer-Schlumpf was asked earlier this week by Swiss national TV station SF whether Mubarak or his family had any money in Switzerland.
<br /><br />”We don’t have any very clear indications that anything is here, but of course we’re in the process of clarifying this and we’ll act appropriately,” she said.
<br /><br />She said the Foreign Ministry was investigating the matter.
<br /><br />At the end of 2009, Egyptian deposits in Swiss bank accounts totaled 3.6 billion Swiss francs (about $3.5 billion), according to the Swiss National Bank.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9f790360ae2bea52fdd61a3cd07eebbe" url=""><![CDATA[Malaysian Muslims warned against Valentine’s Day<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2lkPTc0ODptYWxheXNpYW4tbXVzbGltcy13YXJuZWQtYWdhaW5zdC12YWxlbnRpbmVzLWRheS0mYW1wO2NhdGlkPTcxPGltZyBjbGFzcz0ic21pbGV5IiBzcmM9Imh0dHA6Ly92MS5uZXRsb2dzdGF0aWMuY29tL3Y2LjAwLzQyMDkvL3MvaS9zbWlsaWVzL3Rvbmd1ZS5naWYiIGFsdD0iOikiIC8-cmVzcy1yZWxlYXNlJmFtcDtJdGVtaWQ9Njc_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bid%3D748%3Amalaysian-muslims-warned-against-valentines-day-%26amp%3Bcatid%3D71"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=748:malaysian-muslims-warned-against-valentines-day-&amp;catid=71</a><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />ress-release&amp;Itemid=67</a>
<br /><br />Malaysian Muslims warned against Valentine’s Day
<br /><br />Section: Local Communities	 - Category: Press Release<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9NzQ4Om1hbGF5c2lhbi1tdXNsaW1zLXdhcm5lZC1hZ2FpbnN0LXZhbGVudGluZXMtZGF5LSZhbXA7YW1wO2NhdGlkPTcxPGltZyBjbGFzcz0ic21pbGV5IiBzcmM9Imh0dHA6Ly92MS5uZXRsb2dzdGF0aWMuY29tL3Y2LjAwLzQyMDkvL3MvaS9zbWlsaWVzL3Rvbmd1ZS5naWYiIGFsdD0iOikiIC8-cmVzcy1yZWxlYXNlJmFtcDthbXA7SXRlbWlkPTY3" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_3183902_34135191.jpg" /></a>
<br />As couples around the world mark Valentine’s Day, Islamic officials in Malaysia have warned Muslims against celebrating something “synonymous with vice activities”. The warning follows plans announced last week by several Malaysian states who are planning a crackdown on “immoral acts” during Valentine’s Day as part of a campaign to encourage a sin-free lifestyle.
<br /><br />“In reality, as well as historically, the celebration of Valentine’s Day is synonymous with vice activities,” Mr Wan Mohamad Sheikh Abdul Aziz, head of the Malaysian Islamic Development Department (JAKIM), which oversees the country’s Islamic policies, told state media.
<br />“Islam would reject anything, even from the Eastern culture, if it contravenes the Islamic teachings,” he added. Wan Mohamad said a fatwa (ruling) issued by the country’s top clerics six years ago noted the day “is associated with elements of Christianity,” and “we just cannot get involved with other religion’s worshipping rituals.”
<br />Trap’ campaign
<br />JAKIM officials will carry out a nationwide ‘Mind the Valentine’s Day Trap’ campaign, he said, aimed at preventing Muslims from celebrating the day.
<br />Nasrudin Hasan Tantawi, head of the Islamic party PAS’s youth wing said Wednesday that authorities in the opposition-controlled northern states of Kedah, Penang and Kelantan as well as central Selangor state will also carry out “immorality checks” on February 14.
<br />PAS is part of the opposition alliance that won control of the four states in 2008 elections.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="44a3b6133d46278a2f4e4f1245e138b6" url=""><![CDATA[Pawlenty hits Obama on Muslim Brotherhood<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnQ_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bamp%3Bview%3Dart"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=art</a></a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_9931687_34135206.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />Tim Pawlenty accused President Barack Obama on Sunday of not being clear enough in opposing the Muslim Brotherhood taking over in Egypt. Pointing to the president's interview ahead of last Sunday's Super Bowl on Fox News, Pawlenty said Obama should have been firm in stating that the United States does not want the group to gain power. &amp;quot;The president of the United States ducked the question on whether the Muslim Brotherhood should be running Egypt,&amp;quot; Pawlenty said on ABC's &amp;quot;This Week.&amp;quot; &amp;quot;And I’m telling you they should not be running Egypt.&amp;quot;
<br /><br />Pawlenty also attacked the administration for cutting aid to non-governmental organizations in Egypt, as well as the policy of past administrations of propping up ousted leader Hosni Mubarak.
<br /><br />&amp;quot;History shows that authoritarian regimes offer only a false stability,&amp;quot; said the former Minnesota governor, who's weighing a bid for the Republican presidential nomination
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="56e67a72bfe31bc9fdc75e290d81ef00" url=""><![CDATA[Mubarak's last-minute rush to hide his billions<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9NzQ2Om11YmFyYWtzLWxhc3QtbWludXRlLXJ1c2gtdG8taGlkZS1oaXMtYmlsbGlvbnMtJmFtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9Njk6Y3VycmVudC1hZmZhaXJz" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bamp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bamp%3Bid%3D746%3Amubaraks-last-minute-rush-to-hide-his-billions-%26amp%3Bamp%3Bcatid%3D69%3Acurrent-affairs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=746:mubaraks-last-minute-rush-to-hide-his-billions-&amp;amp;catid=69:current-affairs</a></a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0aWNsZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtpZD03NDY6bXViYXJha3MtbGFzdC1taW51dGUtcnVzaC10by1oaWRlLWhpcy1iaWxsaW9ucy0mYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9Njk6Y3VycmVudC1hZmZhaXJz" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_5642376_34135212.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />Hosni Mubarak used the 18 days it took for protesters to topple him to shift his fortune into untraceable accounts, Western intelligence sources said. The former Egyptian president is accused of amassing as much as $64 billion during his 30 years in power. It is believed his wealth was tied up in foreign banks, investments, bullion and properties in London, New York, Paris and Beverly Hills. In another move, Egypt's chief prosecutor banned the sacked prime minister Ahmed Nazif from leaving the country the day after Mr Mubarak was overthrown.
<br /><br />The prosecutor also banned the widely despised former interior minister Habib al-Adly from travelling and froze his assets on Saturday, the state news agency MENA said.
<br /><br />In the knowledge that his downfall was imminent, Mr Mubarak was understood to have attempted to place his assets out of reach of potential investigators. On Friday night, Swiss authorities announced they were freezing any assets Mr Mubarak and his family may hold in the country's banks, while pressure was growing for Britain to do the same.
<br /><br />A senior Western intelligence source said Mr Mubarak had begun moving his fortune in recent weeks. ''We're aware of some urgent conversations within the Mubarak family about how to save these assets. We think their financial advisers have moved some of the money around. If he had real money in Zurich, it may be gone by now,'' the source said.
<br /><br />Demands were growing among protesters in Cairo on Saturday night for Mr Mubarak, who was at his family villa in the resort town of Sharm El Sheikh, to be put on trial for corruption.
<br /><br />There were unconfirmed reports that he was effectively under house arrest, as the focus of protesters moved from toppling the hated ruler to seizing his fortune, although the army's ruling council said Mr Mubarak was being treated with respect.
<br /><br />During the protests last week, Ibrahim Yousri, a former deputy foreign minister, and 20 lawyers petitioned Abdel Meguid Mahmoud, the prosecutor-general, to put Mr Mubarak and his family on trial for stealing state wealth.
<br /><br />''There's no doubt there will have been some frantic financial activity behind the scenes,'' a US official said.
<br /><br />''They can lose the homes and some of the bank accounts, but they will have wanted to get the gold bars and other investments to safe quarters.''
<br /><br />The Mubaraks are understood to have wanted to shift assets to Gulf states where they already have considerable investments.
<br /><br />The United Arab Emirates and Saudi Arabia have frequently been mentioned as likely destinations for Mr Mubarak and possibly his family.
<br /><br />Reports from Egypt suggest Mr Mubarak had accounts with the Swiss bank UBS as well as with HBOS, now part of Lloyds Banking Group, which is 41 per cent owned by the British government.
<br /><br />But it is understood Lloyds officials have so far found no evidence that Mr Mubarak had secret accounts with them.
<br /><br />Quite how much he has stashed away - and where it is hidden - is open to speculation.
<br /><br />His wife Suzanne is half-Welsh, while it is thought the couple's two sons, Gamal and Alaa, may even have British passports.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8511185c58d21107833a35cb4ca8bef3" url=""><![CDATA[Anti-Muslim immigration petition stirs community anger in Au<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2lkPTc2MDphbnRpLW11c2xpbS1pbW1pZ3JhdGlvbi1wZXRpdGlvbi1zdGlycy1jb21tdW5pdHktYW5nZXItaW4tYXVzdHJhbGlhJmFtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bid%3D760%3Aanti-muslim-immigration-petition-stirs-community-anger-in-australia%26amp%3Bcatid%3D69%3Acurrent-affairs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=760:anti-muslim-immigration-petition-stirs-community-anger-in-australia&amp;catid=69:current-affairs</a></a>
<br /><br />Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />A new petition in the Australian Federal Parliament for a ten-year moratorium on Muslim immigrants is drawing the fury of the Muslim community in the country. “That’s hardly a loving Christian to be very selective in whom you want to enter in your home,” Ikebal Patel, president of the Australian Federation of Islamic Councils, told the Herald Sun on Tuesday, February 15. ACT Liberal Senator Gary Humphries presented a petition calling for a 10-year suspension of Muslim immigration into Australia and for a review of the country’s immigration policy to ensure priority is given to Christians.
<br /><br />“For God’s sake we’ve gone beyond the white Australia policy and now we are talking about … a policy that only allows Christians,” said Patel.
<br /><br />The petition cites the constitution, the founding fathers and the currently parliament prayer to insist that Australia is a Christian commonwealth.
<br /><br />It also insists on rejecting what it describes as ‘attempts to establish a Muslim nation in Australia’.
<br /><br />Senator Humphries said the petition expresses a view about Australia’s immigration policy and wasn’t racially vilifying.
<br /><br />“A number of senators had refused to do so and having read the content I can understand why,” he told the Canberra Times.
<br /><br />“But my long-standing position on petitions is that it is the right of every Australian to put their point of view to the Australian Parliament.”
<br /><br />Muslim immigration and multiculturalism have become a heated debate in Australia, a country where one quarter of the population is immigrants and one that was long celebrated as a melting pot for immigrants.
<br /><br />Australia Muslims have been haunted with suspicion and have had their patriotism questioned in post 9/11.
<br /><br />A 2007 poll taken by the Issues Deliberation Australia (IDA) think-tank found that Australians basically see Islam as a threat to the Australian way of life.
<br /><br />A recent governmental report revealed that Muslims are facing deep-seated Islamophobia and race-based treatment like never before.
<br /><br />Abhorrent
<br /><br />Senator Humphries insisted that his petition was not against Muslims, but should be accepted in the frame of free speech.
<br /><br />“I certainly don’t agree with what’s in the document,” he told ABC Radio on Tuesday, February 15.
<br /><br />“I don’t agree with the sentiments expressed by the petitioners.”
<br /><br />He, however, insisted that he was a friend of Canberra’s Islamic community.
<br /><br />“Many Muslims are my friends and I hope they’ll remain my friends,” he said.
<br /><br />“But I believe that they have the right to put that point of view in front of the members of the Federal Parliament.”
<br /><br />But ACT Labor senator Kate Lundy, who is also parliamentary secretary for immigration and citizenship, criticized the anti-Muslim petition.
<br /><br />“I would not have tabled this petition,” she said.
<br /><br />“All citizens are entitled to request that their petitions are tabled in the Parliament and all senators exercise their own judgment.
<br /><br />“The Government is committed to Australia’s brand of multiculturalism which has seen the integration and the peaceful settlement of 7 million migrants since the Second World War.”
<br /><br />Disappointed by the position, Patel, the Muslim leader, said he would write to the senator for explanation.
<br /><br />“The least we would have expected from him is to let us know what he was going to do,” Patel said.
<br /><br />“It is just quite disappointing to have something as despicable as this and for him to put it in [the Senate]. And then it makes the world stage by being discussed in the Senate.
<br /><br />“You either put it in and back it or you take Senator Kate Lundy’s view that…she chose not to put it forward because it was an abhorrent position.”<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9NzYwOmFudGktbXVzbGltLWltbWlncmF0aW9uLXBldGl0aW9uLXN0aXJzLWNvbW11bml0eS1hbmdlci1pbi1hdXN0cmFsaWEmYW1wO2FtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_15223385_34239271.jpg" /></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1e11c34c003aae50296ac5a86198b863" url=""><![CDATA[Muslim American Congressman Hails Egyptian Protests as Rebuk<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2lkPTc1OTptdXNsaW0tYW1lcmljYW4tY29uZ3Jlc3NtYW4taGFpbHMtZWd5cHRpYW4tcHJvdGVzdHMtYXMtcmVidWtlLXRvLWFsLXFhaWRhJmFtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bid%3D759%3Amuslim-american-congressman-hails-egyptian-protests-as-rebuke-to-al-qaida%26amp%3Bcatid%3D69%3Acurrent-affairs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=759:muslim-american-congressman-hails-egyptian-protests-as-rebuke-to-al-qaida&amp;catid=69:current-affairs</a></a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9NzU5Om11c2xpbS1hbWVyaWNhbi1jb25ncmVzc21hbi1oYWlscy1lZ3lwdGlhbi1wcm90ZXN0cy1hcy1yZWJ1a2UtdG8tYWwtcWFpZGEmYW1wO2FtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_1347316_34239409.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />Muslim American U.S. Congressman Keith Ellison has hailed the protests that began in Tunisia and spread to Egypt and are now radiating out to a whole list of countries.  Ellison praises President Obama for his handling of the crisis in Egypt, and says the United States must continue to be on the right side of history. Congressman Keith Ellison says the Egyptian protesters have delivered a stunning and stiff rebuke to al-Qaida and religious extremism.  He said al-Qaida leaders have long made false claims that America is at war with Islam, and that violence is the way to attain political goals.
<br /><br />&quot;They also say that the only way to achieve change is through violence and terrorism and murder,&quot; said Ellison. &quot;Well the people in Tahrir Square showed that if you stick, and you stay, and you stand up for what you believe in, that you will be successful and you don’t have to harm anybody to do it.&quot;
<br /><br />Ellison said the Egyptian protesters refused to be provoked into responding to violence from pro-government thugs, although some were beaten, jailed and even killed.  The Democratic lawmaker from Minnesota said the credit for Hosni Mubarak’s resignation belongs to the people of Egypt.  But he says he is also proud of President Barack Obama for laying out universal principles in his Cairo speech two years ago.
<br /><br />&quot;But I am proud of a few things, one is that President Obama, a couple of years before this revolution made comments in Cairo which were nothing short of prescient&quot; said Ellison. &quot;[He was] talking about people’s desire to have a voice in their own governance, freedom of expression, freedom of inquiry, freedom of faith.&quot;
<br /><br />Some Republican lawmakers, such as House Foreign Affairs Committee Chairwoman Ileana Ros-Lehtinen, have accused the Obama administration of having a rollercoaster policy on Egypt.
<br /><br />&quot;First it was negotiate with the opposition, then it was orderly transition,&quot; said Ros-Lehtinen.
<br /><br />Ellison said the president was right to be cautious in the beginning and was phenomenal in making clear where Washington stood in the end.
<br /><br />Ellison also said concerns expressed by some Republican lawmakers about the prospect of the opposition Muslim Brotherhood group playing too big of a role  in the transition are “overblown.”
<br /><br />‘My view is that the Muslim brotherhood is a part of the fabric of Egyptian society,&quot; he said. &quot;Democracy means that we don’t get to decide who runs that country, the people of that country decide that.  The Muslim  brotherhood, by the way, has never polled at more than 22 percent.  The population is really not calling for more religion, they are calling for bread, peace, freedom and dignity.
<br /><br />Ellison said as protests for democracy spread to Iran and to a number of Arab-speaking countries, the United States should take note of which countries allow for peaceful freedom of expression.
<br /><br />&quot;And I hope the United States gets on the right side of history,&quot; said Ellison. &quot;I believe we should reorder our priorities in the Middle East, and things like human rights and development and diplomacy ought to be our primary tools, and things like guns, bombs and warfare ought to be used as a last resort.”
<br /><br />At a news conference Tuesday, President Obama drew a contrast between the protests in Egypt and the protests in Iran, which have been violently put down by the government.  The president said the United States is sending a strong message to its allies in the region that they should look to Egypt’s example and not Iran’s.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="10c3ba4b3a0907c0eb4dbfb35924cb3d" url=""><![CDATA[Muslim Brotherhood plans political party<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0aWNsZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtpZD03NTg6bXVzbGltLWJyb3RoZXJob29kLXBsYW5zLXBvbGl0aWNhbC1wYXJ0eSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bid%3D758%3Amuslim-brotherhood-plans-political-party%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bcatid%3D69%3Acurrent-affairs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;amp;id=758:muslim-brotherhood-plans-political-party&amp;amp;amp;catid=69:current-affairs</a></a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO2FtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7YW1wO2lkPTc1ODptdXNsaW0tYnJvdGhlcmhvb2QtcGxhbnMtcG9saXRpY2FsLXBhcnR5JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_7471480_34239488.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />The long banned Muslim Brotherhood said Tuesday it will form a political party once democracy is established in Egypt but promised not to field a candidate for president, trying to allay fears among Egyptians and abroad that it seeks power. Still, the fundamentalist movement is poised to be a significant player in the new order. Egypt’s new military rulers gave a strong sign they recognize that the Brotherhood, which calls for creation of an Islamic state in the Arab world’s most populous nation,
<br /><br />can no longer be barred from politics after the mass popular uprising that forced out President Hosni Mubarak with 18 days of protests.
<br /><br />The Armed Forces Supreme Council included a former Brotherhood lawmaker to an eight-member panel tasked Tuesday with amending the constitution enough to allow democratic elections later this year.
<br /><br />The panel is comprised of legal experts of various ideologies, including secular liberal scholars and three judges from the current Supreme Constitutional Court, one of them a Christian, Maher Sami Youssef.
<br /><br />The changes aim to open the field for political parties to form, loosen restrictions on who can run for president and write in guarantees to prevent the rampant election rigging that ensured Mubarak’s ruling party a lock on power.
<br /><br />The panel’s head is Tareq el-Bishri, considered one of Egypt’s top legal minds. A former judge, he was once a secular leftist but became a prominent thinker in the ”moderate Islamic” political trend.
<br /><br />He is respected on both sides as a bridge between the movements. Sobhi Saleh, the Brotherhood representative, was jailed for three days during the protests.
<br /><br />The military is pushing ahead with a quick transition. Generals from the Armed Forces Supreme Council said Tuesday the military wants to hand power to a government and elected president within six months, the firmest timetable yet outlined. The constitutional panel has 10 days to propose its changes to be put to a referendum.
<br /><br />I
<br />”If the freedom to create political parties is seriously allowed, the Muslim Brotherhood will be part of the scene, but just not all the scene as they were in the past regime,” said Ammar Ali Hassan, an Egyptian expert on Islamic movements.
<br /><br />Last week, Obama played down the Brotherhood’s power, calling it only ”one faction in Egypt” that does not enjoy majority support.
<br /><br />The wave of protests that ousted Mubarak may have hurt the Brotherhood’s popularity, as well.
<br /><br />The group initially balked at joining the demonstrations when they erupted Jan. 25, until its younger cadres forced its leadership to join fearing they would be left behind. Hundreds of thousands from across the spectrum of Egyptian society joined the protests.
<br /><br />Brotherhood youth were a major source of manpower and organizational experience, but they never became the majority.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c33dd6aa987f64d319ec49e0dda8b49" url=""><![CDATA[Religion News Coverage Doubled, Focused On Islam Controversi<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9NzgzOi1yZWxpZ2lvbi1uZXdzLWNvdmVyYWdlLWRvdWJsZWQtZm9jdXNlZC1vbi1pc2xhbS1jb250cm92ZXJzaWVzLWluLTIwMTAtJmFtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9NjE6aXNsYW0mYW1wO2FtcDtJdGVtaWQ9NDg_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_8486114_34518719.jpg" /></a>Section: Local Communities	 - Category: Islam
<br />Islam dominated religion news coverage in 2010, a year that also saw religion reporting double to 2 percent of all news, according to a new study from the Pew Research Center's Project for Excellence in Journalism and the Pew Forum on Religion &amp; Public Life.
<br />The so-called &quot;Ground Zero mosque&quot; and threat of Quran burning from a Florida pastor helped bring coverage of Islam and related controversies to 40 percent of all religion news last year.
<br /><br />From 2009 to 2010, religion-related reporting increased from 1 percent to 2 percent of all news coverage in the U.S. media. And for the first time since 2007, when Pew began tracking such coverage, neither the Catholic Church nor religion's role in American politics were the most reported topic.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ec9b6b71347b14a7e0c9cbe83146ea5d" url=""><![CDATA[4G iPhone won’t arrive until 2012 according to analyst<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9NzgxOjRnLWlwaG9uZS13b250LWFycml2ZS11bnRpbC0yMDEyLWFjY29yZGluZy10by1hbmFseXN0JmFtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9MzQ6bGF0ZXN0LXRlY2gtbmV3cw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_8376148_34518768.jpg" /></a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0aWNsZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtpZD03ODE6NGctaXBob25lLXdvbnQtYXJyaXZlLXVudGlsLTIwMTItYWNjb3JkaW5nLXRvLWFuYWx5c3QmYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9MzQ6bGF0ZXN0LXRlY2gtbmV3cw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_8376148_34518768.jpg" /></a>It’s the year 2011, 4G is the “in” thing and everybody seems to be hopping onto the bandwagon this year. Well, everybody except Apple. According to an analyst from Telecom Pragmatics, Sam Greenholtz, the iPhone 5 that will be launching later this year, will not pack any LTE radios and that the iPhone 6 (which will be released in 2012) will be the one supporting LTE instead. According to another analyst, when Apple locked down the specs for the iPhone 5, they didn’t expect this level of hardware competition. Sounds like a reasonable explanation, but if past iPhone models are of any reference to how Apple designs their phones – the exclusion of 4G this year might have been done on purpose. Well, the year is still young and you can expect a lot more iPhone 5 rumors to surface before we actually get the real deal, so stay tuned and we’ll keep you posted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ceb2c60b738feac106c190b1bbd6ec4f" url=""><![CDATA[American man sentenced 25 years for Facebook and ‘South Pa<br/><br/>Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />Zachary Chesser of Virginia, who converted to a militant form of Islam, had pleaded guilty to three charges, including threatening the lives of ‘South Park’ writers and participants in ‘Everybody Draw Mohammed Day.’ This undated file picture released by the SITE Institute on July 21, 2010, shows Zachary Adam Chesser standing in front of the White House in Washington. Mr. Chesser was sentenced Thursday, having pleaded guilty in October to providing material support to a US-designated terrorist group and making threats against the writers of the ‘South Park’ TV show and other cartoonists.
<br /><br />A Muslim convert and college dropout was sentenced to 25 years in prison on Thursday after pleading guilty to attempting to provide material support to a Somali-based terrorist group and threatening the lives of the writers of the “South Park” satiric television show for portraying the prophet Muhammad in a bear suit.
<br /><br />Zachary Adam Chesser, 21, of Fairfax, Va., had also posted on a militant Islamic website the names and addresses of participants in another satiric effort, an “Everybody Draw Mohammed Day” sponsored by a group of artists on Facebook. He advised the militant Muslim followers of the website: “Just a place to start.”
<br /><br />Lawyers for Mr. Chesser portray him as a confused, immature person who tended to dive wholeheartedly into new experiences. In an 18-month period in 2009 and 2010, he went from being a student at George Mason University to converting to Islam and becoming a close follower of radical Muslim cleric Anwar al-Awlaki. In the process he came to embrace the most violent form of Islam advocated by Al Qaeda and other Muslim terror groups.
<br /><br />Since his arrest last year, Chesser has repudiated violence and says he feels remorse for his earlier conduct. His lawyers had urged that he receive a 20-year sentence.
<br /><br />Federal prosecutors asked the judge to send Chesser to prison for 30 years.
<br /><br />In court filings, prosecutors argued that the injury Chesser caused to the nation is ongoing and open-ended. “There is nothing that Chesser can ever do or say that will remedy the tremendous harm he has already caused to our society as a whole,” Assistant US Attorney Gordon Kromberg wrote in a brief.
<br /><br />He said Internet-based threats Chesser placed on militant websites made “people shrink back from expressing their opinions – or even telling a joke – lest they be accused of being an enemy of Islam for whom beheading is the only appropriate punishment.”
<br /><br />The prosecutor added that Chesser’s victims “will continue to be at risk of kidnapping and beheading for years (if not the rest of their lives) because of his actions.”
<br /><br />Chesser’s lawyer, Federal Public Defender Michael Nachmanoff, acknowledged that his client’s threats were serious, but he said they did not carry the weight of similar pronouncements made by Ayatollah Khomeini against author Salman Rushdie.
<br /><br />“Unlike threats from deviant Islamic leaders who arguably possess religious credentials and who, as leaders of countries or mosques also have adherents to their teachings, Mr. Chesser’s call to violence, thankfully, appears to have received little attention, which is not surprising given its source,” Mr. Nachmanoff wrote in his brief to the court.
<br /><br />Chesser pleaded guilty in October to three federal charges. He attempted to provide material support to the Somali-based al-Shabaab organization, which has been designated a foreign terrorist group by the US government.
<br /><br />He has admitted that he tried to board a plane from New York to Uganda with the intent of eventually joining members of al-Shabaab in Somalia. He said he brought his infant son on the journey in an effort to disguise his intention of traveling overseas to engage in what he considered a holy war.
<br /><br />Chesser was intercepted before his plane could depart. He later told investigators that he planned to walk across the border from Uganda into Kenya and then across the Kenyan border into Somalia.
<br /><br />Chesser also admitted that he used militant websites on the Internet to urge Muslims in the US to leave suspicious packages in public places to desensitize US law enforcement officials to the threat of small bombs. The effort was part of a plan to increase the carnage during a presumed future campaign involving real bombs.
<br /><br />The defendant also pleaded guilty to soliciting violence from fellow Muslims against those he perceived as insulting the dignity of Islam. The threats were issued over the “South Park” program and the Draw Mohammed Day effort on Facebook.
<br /><br />“Zachary Chesser will spend 25 years in prison for advocating the murder of US citizens for engaging in free speech about his religion,” said US Attorney Neil MacBride in a statement.
<br /><br />“The fact that a young man from northern Virginia could support such violence and terror is a sobering reminder of the serious threat that home-grown jihadists pose to this country,”<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2lkPTc5NTphbWVyaWNhbi1tYW4tc2VudGVuY2VkLTI1LXllYXJzLWZvci1mYWNlYm9vay1hbmQtc291dGgtcGFyay1kZWF0aC10aHJlYXRzJmFtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bid%3D795%3Aamerican-man-sentenced-25-years-for-facebook-and-south-park-death-threats%26amp%3Bcatid%3D69%3Acurrent-affairs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=795:american-man-sentenced-25-years-for-facebook-and-south-park-death-threats&amp;catid=69:current-affairs</a></a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9Nzk1OmFtZXJpY2FuLW1hbi1zZW50ZW5jZWQtMjUteWVhcnMtZm9yLWZhY2Vib29rLWFuZC1zb3V0aC1wYXJrLWRlYXRoLXRocmVhdHMmYW1wO2FtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_5878597_34694397.jpg" /></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b675f12ad1c48f6cc4f5ae930629ad3" url=""><![CDATA[Mosque for Chinese Muslims nears reality<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bid%3D794%3Amosque-for-chinese-muslims-nears-reality%26amp%3Bcatid%3D69%3Acurrent-affairs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;view=article&amp;id=794:mosque-for-chinese-muslims-nears-reality&amp;catid=69:current-affairs</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9Nzk0Om1vc3F1ZS1mb3ItY2hpbmVzZS1tdXNsaW1zLW5lYXJzLXJlYWxpdHkmYW1wO2FtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_13458887_34694476.jpg" /></a>
<br />Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />Chinese Muslims in the city are one step closer to having a mosque they can call their own.
<br />The mosque, which will be run by the Malaysian Chinese Muslim Association (Macma), will feature Chinese architecture but would be open to everyone, demonstrating the universality of Islam.The mosque complex, which also includes an Islamic cultural centre, will be built on a 1.8ha plot in Jalan Davis here. “The mosque will promote a better understanding of Islam, especially among the Chinese community,” said Macma president Datuk Dr Mustapha Ma at a presentation ceremony for the Macma Mosque architecture competition.
<br /><br />Dr Mustapha said the mosque’s construction would begin once Macma had decided on a final design from the competition’s 58 entries.
<br />He said Macma would raise its own funds but hoped the Government would honour its RM1mil pledge made in 2009 by then Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Datuk Seri Ahmad Zahid Hamidi.
<br /><br />“Some non-Muslim friends like the Federation of Chinese Associations Malaysia (Hua Zhong) have also pledged their assistance,” Dr Mustapha added.
<br /><br />The competition’s five-member jury awarded honourable mention prizes to entries from two architecture firms.
<br /><br />The Prime Minister’s wife Datin Seri Rosmah Mansor presented two cheques worth RM30,000 to the firms at a ceremony yesterday.
<br /><br />In her speech, Rosmah said the mosque was strategically located and would be a major tourist attraction.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="63ede1e160cd835ea04bdf74162e92c6" url=""><![CDATA[Lasith Malinga — first man to two World Cup hat-tricks<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Falmuslim.com.au%2Findex.php%3Foption%3Dcom_content%26amp%3Bamp%3Bview%3Darticle%26amp%3Bamp%3Bid%3D793%3Alasith-malinga--first-man-to-two-world-cup-hat-tricks%26amp%3Bamp%3Bcatid%3D70%3Asports%26amp%3Bamp%3BItemid%3D27"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://almuslim.com.au/index.php?option=com_content&amp;amp;view=article&amp;amp;id=793:lasith-malinga--first-man-to-two-world-cup-hat-tricks&amp;amp;catid=70:sports&amp;amp;Itemid=27</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0aWNsZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtpZD03OTM6bGFzaXRoLW1hbGluZ2EtLWZpcnN0LW1hbi10by10d28td29ybGQtY3VwLWhhdC10cmlja3MmYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9NzA6c3BvcnRzJmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO0l0ZW1pZD0yNw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_2835547_34694511.jpg" /></a>
<br />Wednesday, 02 March 2011 13:55
<br />Written by Muslim News Magazine
<br />Sri Lanka’s Lasith Malinga became the first man to pick up two hat-tricks in World Cups when he skittled out three Kenyan tail-enders in their Group A match on Tuesday. Malinga, who missed his side’s opening two matches with a sore back, fired back with the wickets of Tanmay Mishra (0), Peter Ongondo (0) and Shem Ngoche (0) with successive, full deliveries, the latter two clean bowled. He finished with a career best six for 38 as the Africans were dismissed for 142. In 2007, Malinga grabbed four in a row against South Africa.
<br /><br />It is the second hat-trick of the 2011 World Cup after Kemar Roach took the last three Dutch wickets in West Indies’ victory in Group B on Monday.
<br /><br />Kenya crumbled from a respectable 102-2 to 142 all out in 43.4 overs after choosing to bat first, with the Obuya brothers the only batsmen to reach double figures.
<br /><br />A 94-run partnership between Collins Obuya (52 off 100 balls) and his elder sibling David (51 off 106 balls) raised hopes that Kenya might cross the 200-run mark but Malinga turned into a one-man hit-squad.
<br /><br />He got rid of Collins with a toe crushing yorker in the 32nd over before returning for his final spell to flatten the Kenyans with breathtaking pace as he bagged four wickets in five legal balls.
<br /><br />Malinga trapped Mishra lbw with the final delivery of his seventh over and then returned to knock over the stumps of Ongondo and Ngoche with the first two balls of his next over.
<br /><br />Sri Lankan fans were already dancing in the stands to celebrate the achievement and when Malinga grounded Elijah Otieno’s leg stump to grab his sixth victim of the day, a deafening roar reverberated around the R Premadasa Stadium.
<br /><br />Malinga could only shake his head in disbelief as he looked up to the arena’s giant scoreboard which displayed a sign reading 6-38 underneath a picture of the man of the moment.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cc2e830a940d68901e73a1439ed2d44d" url=""><![CDATA[Pakistan survive scare from Canada<br/><br/>Friday, 04 March 2011 13:42
<br />Written by Muslim News Magazine
<br /><br />Shahid Afridi took his wicket tally in the 2011 World Cup to 14 as Pakistan saw off a spirited Canada by 46 runs. Pakistan were skittled out for 184 after 43 overs, indebted to a stand of 73 from Misbah-ul-Haq and Umar Akmal. Umar fired four fours and a six in his 48 but swing bowler Harvir Baidwan took 3-35 as the final four Pakistan wickets fell for three runs in 14 deliveries. Jimmy Hansra made a valiant 43 but Afridi struck twice in two balls and snared 5-23 as Canada were 138 all out.
<br /><br />The day after England's shock defeat against Ireland, Pakistan, who were beaten by the Irish themselves at the 2007 World Cup, needed a superb performance from their skipper to avert a similar embarrassment.
<br /><br />Resting paceman Shoaib Akhtar and without injured spinner Abdur Rehman they opted to bat first in cloudy conditions but Baidwan caused problems after coming into the attack as second change, claiming two wickets in his first three overs, including the prize scalp of Younus Khan.
<br /><br />Younus, who scored half centuries in Pakistan's previous victories over Kenya and Sri Lanka, played across one and was lbw for six.
<br /><br />A rescue operation was needed and after Umar drove his first ball sweetly for four, there was a period of consolidation with six overs elapsing without a boundary.
<br /><br />Umar slog-swept Balaji Rao for six but the burly spinner broke the partnership as a defensive prod by Umar saw him adjudged lbw, while four overs later, Misbah, who took 60 balls to hit his first boundary, nudged a wide delivery to the wicketkeeper for 37.
<br /><br />Five umpiring decisions were proved incorrect after referral in the Canadian innings, four by Daryl Harper and one by Nigel Llong.
<br /><br />After two wickets fell for no runs in six deliveries, umpire Harper, who had inexplicably given Ruvindu Gunasekera not out when the ball was arrowing in to middle stump on a full length, was involved in another moment of controversy.
<br /><br />The Australian deemed that Ashish Bagai was lbw to Umar Gul on the back foot when replays projected the ball passing comfortably over the stumps.
<br /><br />Pakistan fielders pointed out to the officials that the batsmen had sought advice from the balcony before deciding to ask for a review - both against the rules and surprising as it appeared obvious that the decision should be queried.
<br /><br />A referral can be quashed under such an infringement but the umpires deemed that a stern warning was sufficient.
<br /><br />Bagai put on a painstaking 28 in more than 12 overs with Zubin Surkari before he was given out lbw to Afridi after a review following umpire Harper's initial rejection.
<br /><br />Surkari was reprieved when a review showed the ball would have clipped leg-stump so umpire Harper's not out verdict stood, but in Saeed Ajmal's next over, Pakistan risked their final review and the official's rejection of the lbw appeal was proved incorrect.
<br /><br />Rizwan Cheema fell to an ugly swipe at Afridi in the next over as the spinners began to exert pressure and the Canadians were reduced to 111-5.
<br /><br />The captain's next over all but ended Canada's hopes, with Hansra - who had batted for almost 20 overs - undone by one that nipped back and Baidwan still playing his defensive shot when a fearsome quicker ball had already shattered his stumps.
<br /><br />Afridi, who moved six clear as the tournament's leading wicket-taker, became the first man in World Cup history to take four or more wickets in three consecutive matches.
<br /><br />Even after completing his spell his inspiration continued when he dismissed Rao with a stunning direct hit from mid-off, the big Chennai-born Canadian resembling an old steam puffer as he jogged forlornly against the throw and was run out by three yards.
<br /><br />Wahab Riaz thudded a delivery into the middle stump to complete a fine comeback from Pakistan, who head into Tuesday's match against New Zealand with their 100% record still intact.
<br /><br />Unsurprisingly Afridi was named Man-of-the-Match but warned improvements needed to be made against the Kiwis. &amp;quot;We did not have good shot selection and I think it's a very good wake-up call for us for the next game,&amp;quot; he said.
<br /><br />&amp;quot;Myself and coach Waqar Younis will definitely talk to the boys and this will not happen again. We needed some partnerships and that's what we were missing and that's what the coach was saying. Partnerships are very important.&amp;quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="87095eb96b67b26ddbd77f3f871498f7" url=""><![CDATA[National focus on Muslim radicalization debate<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9ODEwOm5hdGlvbmFsLWZvY3VzLW9uLW11c2xpbS1yYWRpY2FsaXphdGlvbi1kZWJhdGUtJmFtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9Njk6Y3VycmVudC1hZmZhaXJz" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_6091519_34856256.jpg" /></a>Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />The White House on Sunday praised American Muslims for helping fight violent extremism, but a House leader on terrorism issues said they aren't cooperating enough with law enforcement to counter the radicalization of young followers by al-Qaida-linked groups.
<br />Deputy National Security Adviser Denis McDonough, speaking at an interfaith forum at a Northern Virginia mosque, commended its members for taking &quot;an unequivocal stand against terrorism.&quot;&quot;You've sent a message that those who perpetrate such horrific attacks do not represent you or your faith, and that they will not succeed in pitting believers of different faiths against one another,&quot; McDonough said.
<br /><br />But Rep. Peter King, chairman of the House Homeland Security Committee, re-asserted warnings about al-Qaida terrorists targeting Muslim youth in this country.
<br />&quot;The overwhelming majority of Muslims are outstanding Americans, but at this stage in our history there's an effort ... to radicalize elements within the Muslim community,&quot; he said in a preview of his hearing Thursday on the extent of the problem and the Muslim community's response.
<br />&quot;It's there and that's where the threat is coming from at this time,&quot; King said in an interview broadcast Sunday.
<br />&quot;I don't believe there is sufficient cooperation&quot; by American Muslims with law enforcement, King said. &quot;Certainly my dealings with the police in New York and FBI and others say they do not believe they get the same — they do not give the level of cooperation that they need.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cbcf5d48d5f5899523a7a2ac3c84c3d8" url=""><![CDATA[Australia's second wettest summer on record<br/><br/>ONE of the strongest La Niña's on record has ensured summer 2010-11 has been the second wettest on record for Australia.
<br />Tom Saunders, meteorologist at The Weather Channel, said above average rain has been recorded across most of Australia this summer.
<br />&quot;Nationally we averaged 354.7mm, 70 per cent above normal and second only behind the infamous summer of 1973-74 when 419.8mm was recorded,&quot; said Saunders.
<br />&quot;This will be no surprise to most Australians considering the flooding which occurred over large parts of the east and north.&quot;
<br /><br />All states and territories recorded above average falls. Out of 111 years:
<br /><br />-    Victoria recorded its wettest summer on record
<br />-    Western Australia recorded its second wettest summer
<br />-    South Australia recorded its third wettest summer
<br />-    New South Wales recorded its fifth wettest summer
<br />-    Queensland recorded its sixth wettest summer
<br />-    Northern Territory recorded its eighth wettest summer
<br />-    Tasmania recorded its seventeenth wettest summer
<br /><br />&quot;After a decade of drought, The Murray Darling Basin also recorded its third wettest summer on record,&quot; said Saunders.
<br /><br />&quot;Looking ahead into autumn, the La Niña is now past its peak and has been weakening since early January. However, until the Pacific Ocean returns to neutral in winter we can expect above average rain to continue over most of the country.&quot;
<br /><br />&lt; Prev	  	Next &gt;
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7dmlldz1hcnRpY2xlJmFtcDthbXA7aWQ9ODA5OmF1c3RyYWxpYXMtc2Vjb25kLXdldHRlc3Qtc3VtbWVyLW9uLXJlY29yZC0mYW1wO2FtcDtjYXRpZD02OTpjdXJyZW50LWFmZmFpcnM_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_13592406_34856294.jpg" /></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b10a491ae7cf464499f988490ce514fd" url=""><![CDATA[White House Seeks to Allay Muslims’ Fears on Terror Hearin<br/><br/>Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />Article Index
<br />White House Seeks to Allay Muslims’ Fears on Terror Hearings
<br />Page 2
<br />All Pages
<br />Page 1 of 2
<br />As a Republican congressman prepares to open hearings on the threat of homegrown Islamic terrorism, President Obama’s deputy national security adviser visited a mosque here on Sunday to reassure Muslims that “we will not stigmatize or demonize entire communities because of the actions of a few.” The White House billed the speech by the adviser, Denis McDonough, as a chance for the administration to lay out its strategy for preventing violent extremism. But the timing was no accident;
<br /><br />Mr. McDonough was in effect an emissary from the White House to pre-empt Representative Peter King of New York, the House Homeland Security Committee chairman, who has promised a series of hearings beginning Thursday on the radicalization of American Muslims.
<br /><br />“In the United States of America, we don’t practice guilt by association,” Mr. McDonough told an interfaith, but mostly Muslim, audience of about 200 here at the All Dulles Area Muslim Society, known locally as the Adams Center. “And let’s remember that just as violence and extremism are not unique to any one faith, the responsibility to oppose ignorance and violence rests with us all.”
<br /><br />Mr. McDonough made no explicit mention of the hearings or Mr. King. But his speech came on a day when the back-and-forth over Mr. King’s plans crescendoed, from the airwaves of Washington’s Sunday morning talk shows to the streets of Manhattan to this northern Virginia suburb, a region packed with Muslim professionals, many of whom are extremely wary of Mr. King and his plans.
<br /><br />In Washington, Mr. King, who represents parts of Long Island, faced off on CNN with Representative Keith Ellison, the Minnesota Democrat and the only Muslim in Congress. Mr. Ellison said he would testify at Mr. King’s hearing on Thursday despite his deep conviction that it is wrong for Congress to investigate a particular religious minority.
<br /><br />In New York, 500 people demonstrated near Times Square to protest the hearings and call on Mr. King to expand his witness list to include other groups. 
<br /><br />“That’s absolute nonsense,” Mr. King said in a telephone interview, adding that Al Qaeda is trying to radicalize Muslims and that that effort is the leading homegrown terrorism threat. “The threat is coming from the Muslim community,” he said, “the r<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsbXVzbGltLmNvbS5hdS9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDthbXA7YW1wO3ZpZXc9YXJ0aWNsZSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtpZD04MDg6d2hpdGUtaG91c2Utc2Vla3MtdG8tYWxsYXktbXVzbGltcy1mZWFycy1vbi10ZXJyb3ItaGVhcmluZ3MmYW1wO2FtcDthbXA7Y2F0aWQ9Njk6Y3VycmVudC1hZmZhaXJz" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/157293505_10006796_34856317.jpg" /></a>adicalization attempts are directed at the Muslim community. Why should I investigate other communities?”
<br /><br />As the Times Square demonstrators held up placards declaring “Today I am a Muslim Too,” Rabbi Marc Schneier, president of the Foundation for Ethnic Understanding, and Feisal Abdul Rauf, the imam who is a co-founder of a project to develop a mosque near ground zero, addressed the crowd.
<br /><br />“To single out Muslim Americans as the source of homegrown terrorism and not examine all forms of violence motivated by extremist belief — that, my friends, is an injustice,” Rabbi Schneier said.
<br /><br />Mr. King and Mr. McDonough each took pains on Sunday to say that he had no quarrel with the other. “We welcome any involvement in the issue,” Mr. McDonough said of the hearings. “It’s an important issue.”
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fd0803532a85f61109136b78f74e7d21" url=""><![CDATA[Olive Web - A Web Design Company<br/><br/>Section: Business &amp; Finance	 - Category: Career
<br />Olive Web – Company Structure
<br /><br />At Olive Web Design we believe in matching the right skills to the right project. We feel that by having a large in-house development team we would be leaving ourselves in the position that we had to assign an individual to a project because they were short of work, rather than because they were the right person for the job. We feel that this is not in our best interests or in the best interests of our customers. Web projects can require skills from a diverse range of areas, including:
<br /><br />Graphic and web design
<br />Client side development
<br />Server side development
<br />Content writing and editing
<br />On-line and off-line marketing
<br />Usability assessments and testing
<br />Accessibility assessments and testing
<br />Security
<br />Information architecture
<br />Many of the above skills can be broken down further into smaller groups. We evaluate each project based on our knowledge and experience and then source the necessary skills from our pool of partner companies and freelancers.
<br /><br />We are always on the lookout for talented freelancers to join us which is why we have spent time optimizing our jobs page to be highly ranked on Google for ‘Web Design Jobs’ and ‘Design Jobs’. We have also developed links with other prominent companies and individuals within a number of on-line communities including Web Standards and Accessibility ‘gurus’.
<br /><br />When you bring your project to us you can be sure of the highest quality of service delivered through individuals whose skills and experience are well matched to your project.
<br /><br />Olive Web Philosophy
<br /><br />We design web sites that focus on usability. This means web sites that are simple to use, easy to navigate, and that help the user to find information and products quickly. We work hard to create design that is elegant, timeless and compelling. Yet, we never allow our desire for great art to overwhelm the need for good function.
<br /><br />As the web moves away from being the “cool new toy” to a tool for information and research, web design must change with it. Web design must support your message, not overwhelm it. Therefore, web design must be done with restraint. Visual toys such as animation and sound must be used only when the content or product warrants it, not simply as useless decoration.
<br /><br />Why must web design face this new reality? The Web is not television (despite efforts to make it so). It is currently an information resource for most users, not an entertainment medium. Therefore, web design must make information easily accessible. That is its core responsibility. Additionally, e-commerce is about meeting the needs of diverse customers quickly. Simplicity, ease of use and clear navigation are powerful web design tools that enhance the customer experience, and your bottom line as a business owner.
<br /><br />Mr.Wasif Jones, the creative force behind Olive Web, not only Design web sites, but helps businesses by designing web sites intelligently. I avoid the fads that quickly go out of style and focus on what matters most to the customer. Anything that hinders your ability to communicate clearly to your customer is left out. That is what good web design is all about. We invite you to CONTACT US when your business needs a web site. We can help you to make the Internet a hard-working part of your business toolkit.
<br /><br />Olive Web Profile
<br /><br />Interactive Web Design Company provides high quality, reasonable priced products and service, including web design, web program, design, SEO and other web service. It is convinced that it is a good investment using our services. Client using our service are increasing in the past year. Our Mission is to satisfy our clients.
<br /><br />Olive-Web Design Services Includes:
<br /><br />Website Design | Flash,PHP,ASP,etc.
<br />Web Programs | CMS,CRM
<br />Domain Registration
<br />Web Hosting
<br />Flash Website Design | Flash Web Program
<br />Graphic design | Corporate Identity, Visual Identity
<br />Print Media Design | Logo Design, Business Card Design, Name Card Design, Letter head Design, Envelope Design, Leaflet Design
<br />Web Promotion, Google Promotion, Yahoo Promotion
<br />SEM (Search Engine Marketing)
<br />SEO (Search engine optimization) for website design
<br />W3C Compatible Website Design
<br />Business Programs – Online Payment, Online Shopping, Email Marketing
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9fdf547504321b00c93c852dac156647" url=""><![CDATA[WikiLeaks revelation precedes home secretaries’ talks<br/><br/>Section: Current Affairs	 - Category: Current Affairs
<br />Home secretaries of India and Pakistan will begin wide-ranging talks on Monday, including cross-border terrorism, smuggling of narcotics, inflow of fake Indian currency notes and the progress in the Mumbai terror attack trial in Pakistan, Indian news reports said on Sunday.
<br />However, a WikiLeaks revelation in The Hindu on Sunday concerning India’s diplomatic engagement with the world and with Pakistan to move against alleged terror mastermind Hafiz Saeed and his associates over the Mumbai terror attack may have queered New Delhi’s pitch on the key issue.
<br /><br />Fresh US cables published coincidentally on Sunday, the day Pakistan’s home secretary crossed the Wagah border into India, indicate that New Delhi’s case for Pakistan to act against alleged terrorists of Lashkar-e-Taiba (LeT) was based primarily on the statements of three men, two of whom were later acquitted.
<br /><br />While Ajmal Kasab, a Pakistani gunman, was sentenced to death, the other two — both Indian Muslims — were acquitted in the case. The fact that the Indian dossier on Hafiz Saeed was corroborated by the condemned man — Ajmal Kasab — with the statements purported to have been given by Messrs Fahim Ansari and Sabahuddin seems to have been implicitly rejected by both the trial court and the Bombay High Court.
<br /><br />According to one US embassy cable, the Indian dossier “is drawn almost entirely from the confession of the surviving gunman, Ajmal Amir Kasab, and statements by Fahim Ansari and Sabahuddin (Shaikh)”. The three are accused in the 26/11 Mumbai attacks case. National Security Adviser M.K. Narayanan described the material in the dossier as “Grade-1 evidence”.
<br /><br />The cable noted that while “Kasab was eventually sentenced to death by the Mumbai trial court, the other two were acquitted as the court found the evidence against them to be insufficient and wanted to give them the ‘benefit of doubt’.”
<br /><br />Both Ansari and Sabahuddin are involved in other cases. Sabahuddin is facing charges for the 2008 attack on a Central Reserve Police Force camp in Rampur, Uttar Pradesh, and the 2005 blast at the Indian Institute of Science in Bangalore. Fahim has a case pending against him in Rampur for alleged forgery and possession of a weapon.
<br /><br />Details of how Kasab was indoctrinated and prepared by the LeT, specifically by Hafiz Saeed and an unnamed “Major General Saab” emanated from Kasab’s statement, and corroborated by the other two. According to the Indian dossier, “Hafiz Saeed fixed the time as 7.30pm to carry out the attack and justified the time by saying ‘at this hour there is considerable crowd at the places of our target’.” While acquitting the two Indian accused, the judges discarded a portion of Kasab’s confessional statement which referred to the involvement of the duo. “We find no difficulty in excluding that part of the confessional statement which refers to the duo’s involvement as there is no sufficient corroboration to that part,” they said.
<br /><br />The court also noted that the prosecution had not established beyond doubt the handing over of maps of 26/11 targets by Fahim to Sabahuddin in Kathmandu in January 2008.
<br /><br />Indian reports at the time said that Mumbai police’s elite crime branch was again left red-faced after Bombay High Court dismissed its appeal challenging the acquittal of the Indians as co-conspirators.
<br /><br />Next &gt;
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>