<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="13">
		<document id="89f983a3bcdce370068ae4ee20e6a157" url=""><![CDATA[Four Aspects To Keep In Mind Before Making A Smartphone Purc<br/><br/>We do not know, of course, why you need to learn more about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.e-mobilguide.dk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.e-mobilguide.dk</a></a>, but sometimes people needed to learn tough lessons like we did. Obviously, looking at search numbers, this is one area that attracts the attention of a lot of people.<br /><br />Sure, maybe you can find people to help you with certain aspects, but we always like to do as much as possible ourselves. Remember though, that you have to take everything into consideration and go with what works best for you.<br /><br />Which of the following will be directly applicable to you is something we cannot say, so you need to think about that as you read along.<br /><br />Really, that is about what anybody can or should do, and it makes perfect sense when you read the following article.<br /><br />Owning a smartphone has become one of the necessities in today's fast moving life. The reasons for their popularity is that they can carry out a lot of functions at one go. It is very helpful for today's fast paced lifestyle. The functionality of these smartphones differ with the brands and other aspects like the OS present in them. Any smartphone review site will tell you to think about certain aspects before you can select one among them. Here is some information on the aspects you have to look at before making a purchase.<br /><br />1) OS of the phone<br /><br />Mobile operating systems are used to power smartphones. Windows has introduced windows 7 platform to tackle competition like android, iOS, RIM and Symbian. These OSs of well known brands change based upon the purposes they serve. Nokia Symbian has been one of the most used OSs along with android and iOS. When you look through a smartphone review site, you can know more about the smartphones so that you can pick the one that best matches your tastes.<br /><br />2) Smartphone's battery life<br /><br />Talk time and standby time should be measured if you want to check the life of the battery of the phone. Standby time refers to the amount of time the battery will remain on when the phone is not in use. Different phones have various levels of battery life; including standby time and talk time. Talk time refers to the length of time the phone battery will work when making phone calls. Some of the best smartphones today give you a talk time of five hours on an average. On an average you will need a talk time of four hours a day. Pick a phone that can give you more talk time if you use more features.<br /><br />3) Memory<br /><br />One of the best things about smartphones is that they can be used to store several things from music to documents. You can use the storage space for pictures, videos, bookmarks, applications and games. If you are a user who stores more than just pictures in your phone, then get a phone that has more storage space. Make sure the phone has a memory of over 4GB. Your phone needs to have a slot to incorporate a storage card for any future use.<br /><br />4) Look of the phone<br /><br />Various brands of smartphones have their own exclusive phone designs that make them stand apart from each other. The design elements that add a touch of exclusiveness to a phone are its screen, its size and its keyboard. Buttons keyboard refers to the one that is normally found in all kinds of cell phones. Sometimes, the size of the screen depends upon the keyboard type. If it is a touchscreen keyboard, you can see that the size of the screen is much bigger to incorporate it. Large screen is for those users who prefer to watch movies and live television on their mobiles.<br /><br />These are some of the aspects that will help you to pick a phone that suits you. A smartphone review site can be useful to you in that it provides you more details on aspects. Examine other aspects and capabilities of a smartphone like Bluetooth capable printing and faxing.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dab33b2898caef4ed87eb5457e0f4e32" url=""><![CDATA[Smartphones: Pre Purchase Considerations To Be Made<br/><br/>Only you know the reasons for wanting to discover more on the topic of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">visit</a>, but we are happy you are here, nonetheless. Obviously, looking at search numbers, this is one area that attracts the attention of a lot of people.<br /><br />We do have a preference for taking care of things on our end, even though you can certainly talk to experts on the subject. As for us, we like to be hands-on and learn how to manage and take care of it for ourselves.<br /><br />Which of the following will be directly applicable to you is something we cannot say, so you need to think about that as you read along.<br /><br />We all proceed at a pace that is comfortable for us, and you will have the best results that way, anyway.<br /><br />You can see that smartphones are used by almost everyone today. The reasons for their popularity is that they can carry out many functions at one go. For the 'on-the-go' lifestyle of today, smartphones can be very beneficial. Numerous leading brands offer top of the line smartphones with different functions for specific purposes. Read the reviews of these phones on a smartphone review site to make an informed decision. Here are some pointers.<br /><br />1) Operating System<br /><br />Mobile operating systems are used to power smartphones. Apart from Apple's iOS, more OSs are becoming well known, like Google's Android and Nokia's Symbian. These various OSs are appropriate for different purposes. Nokia Symbian has been one of the most used OSs along with android and iOS. A smartphone review site will Provide you information on smartphone comparisons that will be useful for you.<br /><br />2) Smartphone's battery life<br /><br />Talk time and standby time should be measured if you want to check the life of the battery of the phone. Standby time refers to the amount of time the battery will stay on when the phone is not in use. Some of the well known smartphones have a standby time of up to four hundred hours. Talk time is the more important battery life aspect when compared to a phone's standby time. When compared to the average standby time of 300 hours given by the smartphones of today, average talk time comes to around 5 hours. If you do not use any additional aspects, you need around 4 hours of talk time everyday. Besides talk time, more features like web browser functioning and others need to be looked at before buying a smartphone.<br /><br />3) Phone's storage capacity<br /><br />Unlike other phones, smartphone memory can be used to store documents, music and more. Storage space in a smartphone is used to store bookmarks, games and other applications. If you store only music and images in your phone, a smartphone with lesser memory capabilities is for you. To store a vast range of media files, select a phone with 4GB minimum memory. If your favorite phone has less than that capacity, make sure that it can accommodate external storage cards.<br /><br />4) Phone design<br /><br />You can see that one smartphone does not look like another because of its unique style. Some of the design factors that you need to look into are screen size, device size and keyboard kind. While some people like technologically forward touchscreen keyboards, some like the conventional button ones. The screen size of your phone relies on the type of the keyboard it has. While a Samsung galaxy touchscreen phone has a large screen, a blackberry phone has smaller one. If you want to watch movies, write documents or play games, go for a big screen phone.<br /><br />There are more aspects of a phone that you can assess to make the best purchase. If you browse a smartphone review site, you will see that more features like Bluetooth technology, camera capacity, GPS features, etc will be reviewed. Some of the other features that you can think about are conference calling abilities, personal reminders, etc.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4a9bb1c60e4d0bac7a71a898e34a469c" url=""><![CDATA[What Can You Expect From Smartphones Of The Future<br/><br/>You are obviously looking for something about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">more info</a> that can help you, and it seems many others are, too. While that is all happening, maybe people are becoming more aware of what is going on and why it matters so much. The devil is in the details - that is extremely true in our experience, and apparently the same in many people who have come before us. We know the value of what you are about to read, and while it may not all be directly applicable we are confident some of it will be.<br /><br />Just like many other subjects, a few details might seem to not apply to you - but the majority or maybe all of it will.<br /><br />Sometimes it is difficult to keep track of the ever changing world of smartphones. Firms try and make their smartphone stand out from the rest to catch the customer's eye. Anyone who has been making use of a mobile phone for a decade will realize the changes that have been happening over that span. Customers now are looking for the next large change. Here are certain changes that you can expect in the future. Keep in mind that some of these aspects might never make it to a smartphone while some might be available within a few months.<br /><br />Flexible smartphones.<br /><br />Over the last few years chips used in smartphones have become a lot faster and a lot smaller. This frees up a lot more space for battery and allows changes to be made to the display. So, you might soon come across smartphones whose screen can be folded. You can feast your eyes on this new variety of screens by the end of 2012 when Samsung launches it. In the beginning you will not be able to do over bend the screen. But, soon nano-technology will be used and you will be able to convert your phone from a wrist watch to a full sized QWERTY phone.<br /><br />Impact of Near Field communication.<br /><br />Near Field communication (NFC) is a great way of connecting with other smartphones because all you need to do is touch the other device and you are ready for data transfer. Android 2.3 Gingerbread, which is one of the most commonly used Android OS has support for this technology.<br /><br />The technology has not been adopted widely because the main use is to make payments and customers are not very sure about that. You will get a lot of more features with the improved NFC in Android 4.0 Ice cream Sandwich. One such aspect that Google plans on introducing is called 0-click interaction. Users will be able to establish a peer-to-peer connection by keeping their phones back to back. For those who do not like using apps for transferring data and contacts, this is the perfect solution.<br /><br />Greater influence of augmented reality apps.<br /><br />You might have seen some augmented reality apps but in the future these apps will become the norm in smartphones. Google Goggles is one such app which can search information about an image that you click. You can also use the Layar browser and Bing visual search in Windows phone 7 to get an idea about augmented reality. It is quite possible that in time these apps evolve into a lot more powerful tools.<br /><br />GPS.<br /><br />GPS has become very well known with drivers as a navigational tool. But people are coming up with exclusive ways to use a GPS. It can be tough at times to find a restroom in crowded places. With the advanced GPS systems and smartphones you will not have this problem. If you are in Disneyland then you would be able to use your GPS to find out the queue at a specific ride.<br /><br />Computing chips.<br /><br />Nvidia's quad-core Tegra 3 (nickname Kal-el) chips are already available in smartphones and are 5 times faster than the previous Tegra 2 models. This is only the begin as the next two years will see Nvidia coming up with Logan, Wayne and Stark models which will be a lot faster.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eeea7f3af8832ad2e34b5e81c1cc8a1e" url=""><![CDATA[Evolution Of Smartphones<br/><br/>The topic of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">website</a> is highly relevant in associated markets as well as the parent market and for good reason. While that is all happening, maybe people are becoming more aware of what is going on and why it matters so much. One thing we do not see talked about much is how important it is to pay attention to things that may initially appear to be less important - often times they can be very important. It is unknown to us what exactly you are searching for in terms of the wider scope of this topic, and that is why this will touch on a few points that you can easily delve deeper into.<br /><br />But with all that said, our knowledge of this subject is pretty solid which allows us to feel confident the following will be of service to you.<br /><br />You can see that the area of telecommunications has been making consistent technological advancements. Some years back, some of the daily business tasks had to be carried out with the help of complicated machines. But, the scenario is not the same anymore. You now have smartphones that can carry out the functions of a pager, a fax machine, an alarm clock and a calculator, all in one package. With them, you can save your time and efforts. Here is some information on the history of smartphones.<br /><br />1) IBM Simon<br /><br />History of smartphones starts with the launch of IBM's Simon. This was truly the first attempt at bringing a handheld device that performed more functions than one. Besides the basic mobile phone abilities, this phone had more aspects like calendar, email client, address book, faxing ability, note pad and world clock. The predictive keypad that can be virtually seen in almost all mobiles today was first adopted into this phone. Simon was big and weighed more than other mobile phones. It could not fit into your pocket. And the phone didn’t cost any less ($899).<br /><br />2) Nokia's first smartphone<br /><br />The Nokia communicator models of phones can be called the next large step in the smartphones history. Nokia 9000, which was released in the year '96, looked like a palmtop computer. Besides the aspects of a mobile phone, it had a physical QWERTY keypad, a feature phone Personal Digital Assistant interface (powered by Hewlett Packard) and text based web browsing. Some of the phones from Nokia that were launched after Nokia 9000 have better web browser features in them.<br /><br />3) Smartphone by Ericsson<br /><br />'Smartphone' was a term that was first used to describe GS88 communicator introduced by Ericsson. At the beginning of the millennium, another smartphone by Ericsson made its way to the market, Ericsson R380. This phone was powered by the Symbian mobile OS that is used in some of the best selling smartphones of today. It performed functions of a personal digital assistant along with the functions of a mobile phone. This smartphone was smaller and lighter compared to the other smartphones before it.<br /><br />4) Another Nokia smartphone<br /><br />Nokia 9210 Communicator was launched in the same year. The phone was definitely an improvement over the previous communicator phones, in terms of features. There are several additions to the list of firsts for the communicator phones. Through these phones open symbian mobile operating system made its way to popular phones. Nokia N95 was a smartphone that provided 3G, TV- out, GPS and a 5 mp camera.<br /><br />5) The next generation smartphones<br /><br />The phase that comes next in the history of smartphones is more interesting. The phones that came later brought in quality along with affordability to everyone. Blackberry company started manufacturing e- mail capable mobile phones that became an instant hit with businessmen. It is said that the launch of Apple iPhone can be held possible for the rise in the number of smartphone users. More companies like Windows, HTC, Samsung and others followed in the footsteps of Apple in providing their customer with top notch smartphones. Also, iOS (previously called iPhone OS), Android, Blackberry OS, Bada and other better mobile OSs were introduced.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8e93284d17a43f0bb76d8e09527f7b0b" url=""><![CDATA[What To Look For When Buying Smartphones<br/><br/>No kidding at all - <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">visit our website</a> is something that you perhaps never thought you would be actively looking for more information on.<br /><br />The best way to effectively deal with new issues is to gain some helpful knowledge before proceeding. All those unknown reasons as to why we look to something with the feeling of interest are often impossible to discern and that is really all right. Our needs are as diverse as we are as individuals, and so no matter about all of that because we are glad you are here.<br /><br />This article has an introductory treatment on the subject matter, and you can take that and expand it in just about any direction you choose.<br /><br />There are so many smartphones in the market today offering a multitude of features. It becomes difficult for a first time user to understand all of them. Once you take a pick, there is no looking back as these phones are costly, so it is critical that you analyze the attributes of the smartphones before you go ahead and make a purchase. Buying a smartphone that fails to serve your purpose because of lack of information can cost you a lot. So here is a simple buying guide to smartphones to help you to make an informed decision.<br /><br />1) Camera resolution<br /><br />Analyze the reason you want to buy a smartphone first. This buying guide to smartphones will help you analyze it. See what feature of a smartphone you will use the most when you buy one. If you are keen on photography, then you can go for the smartphones that have high resolution camera. Some cameraphones come with extra features including IR filter, extra lens, LED flash, Image Signal processor, etc. Some of the phones that can provide you good quality cameras are HTC Amaze 4G, iPhone 4S and others. More phones like Motorola Droid Razr, HTC Sensation 4G, Motorola Photon 4G also have good cameras to provide. Your smartphone needs will differ based on if you are a photographer or a videographer.<br /><br />2) Multimedia<br /><br />If you want to purchase a smartphone for entertainment purposes, there are a host of phones with unique multimedia capabilities. While entry level smartphones have an internal storage of 512 MB, the best selling ones have about 32GB. You can carry your extensive media libraries on these smartphones. Music apps can be downloaded online too based on the smartphone you have. What's more, smartphones can be played in many audio formats too. If you are looking for a phone that can perform as a good quality music player, you can opt for phones like Xpress Music range from Nokia, Samsung Galaxy S or Sony Xperia X10. Your smartphone alerts you when you have received a message or a mail even when you are playing music on it.<br /><br />3) Take a look at the smartphone style<br /><br />You also have to evaluate the designs of the smartphones before zeroing in on one. Almost all the smartphones of today come with a sleek and slim look. Touchscreen phones have long screens to accommodate the keypad and other features too. Samsung Galaxy phones are examples of long and touchscreen smartphones. It is also important to take a look at the keypad of the smartphone you want to purchase. Because, sometimes people who have been using regular keypads can find it very hard to get used to other keypad versions. You should have noticed that a lot of of the smartphones that were released within last year have touchscreen keypads on them. See that whichever phone you get has a keypad of your preference.<br /><br />4) More smartphone aspects<br /><br />Apart from the ones discussed above, you can also look into certain other aspects. See how much talk time and standby time a smartphone can offer you. If you like listening to music or watching videos on your smartphone, think about getting one that has high battery life. You can also buy the phone based upon the operating system it is powered by; some of the popular ones are Android, Symbian, Blackberry OS and iOS. Use this buying guide to smartphones and buy a smartphone that you won't regret having bought later.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eb84aa4ecd706929419c41c28456d207" url=""><![CDATA[Different Features Of Smartphones Compared<br/><br/>It can be frustrating when you are just getting started in your search to understand <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">click here</a>, but do not feel alone in that regard. It is easy to look at others who are where you want to be and have negative feelings, but just try to avoid that because there was a time when they were just like you.<br /><br />What you will find here is well-researched information that you can trust and build upon and go forward with. Even the old pros still take the time to try to learn more, and that is how they became old pros. Challenges to your forward movement can always be present, it just depends, and that is when a wide base of knowledge can be very helpful.<br /><br />Continue on reading and you will widen your knowledge or start building it from the ground up if you are new to this.<br /><br />Smartphones have put feature phones behind them in terms of popularity. Their multi- tasking abilities and other reasons have made them so popular with people. You can see that a lot of smartphones have been introduced within the past five years. The unique functionalities on smartphones are designed in order to meet specific purposes. Compare smartphones to understand their working and features so that you buy one that matches your preference. Here is a comparison of some features of different smartphones.<br /><br />1) Mobile Operating Systems<br /><br />Operating Systems used on smartphones are different from those on computers, so take a look at them when you compare smartphones. Mobile OS is the software platform on your smartphone that is responsible for the smooth functioning of your phone. It not only manages all the softwares but also the hardware resources. Read on to know about the most widely- used operating systems on smartphones.<br /><br />a) Google's Android<br /><br />Android is currently the world's most popular linux- based mobile operating system. The Open Handset Alliance led by Google has been developing it. Around three hundred million android devices are being used the world over. When compared to any other mobile OS, you can see that Android has the highest percentage of third party apps running.<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> Apple's iOS<br /><br />iOS is the multi- tasking multi- touch operating system by Apple company. iPad, iPod touch, iPhone, Apple TV and any other products by Apple use the OS. It is one of the easiest operating systems to work with. Some of the default apps available on this operating system are YouTube, Google Maps, Clock, Game Center, Siri (iPhone 4S only), etc.<br /><br />c) Symbian Operating System<br /><br />This is an OS specifically created for smartphones. It is maintained by Accenture. Symbian is more popularly associated with Nokia phones. Initially, the OS enabled simple functions like messaging, gaming and basic media running. From sending and receiving emails to running apps, the OS can multi- task easily. Apart from Nokia phones, Symbian has been used on Sony Ericsson phones.<br /><br />2) Types of Keyboards<br /><br />Mobile phone keyboards had some basic features upon their introduction. See that you are comfortable using the keyboard on the smartphone you want to buy. QWERT keyboards typically found on computers can be found on smartphones too. Kinds of keyboards used on smartphones are explained here.<br /><br />a) Touchscreen enabled keyboards: <br /><br />With touchscreen keyboards, you don’t need physical keyboards. The way this works is that you have to touch the virtual keys with your fingertips. If you are a user of regular keyboards, wanting to purchase a touchscreen phone, be prepared to experience an interface shock. Use it periodically to become the 'master of touchscreen typing'.<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> QWERTY keyboards<br /><br />QWERTY keypads are physical keyboards on which letters are arranged in a way that is typical of regular computer keyboards. Blackberry most popularly makes use of this keyboard form. Computer users might still find this type a bit tough to use as the spacing is different.<br /><br />3) Other comparisons<br /><br />There are more features that make the smartphones different from each other; to know them compare smartphones. Device size and screen size are distinctive. Small screens are typically seen on smartphones that have QWERTY or other types of physical keyboards. Besides the screen size, the size of the device is another aspect that makes it exclusive. You can see that the various models of Blackberry itself have many ranges and styles. These aspects of smartphones must be evaluated and compared so that you make the best selection.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d82a68b81cd4b72632e7e2987748196" url=""><![CDATA[Top 10 Smartphones Of 2012<br/><br/>Any time you are looking for the most reliable information concerning <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">visit</a>, you really have to pay attention to the various supporting issues surrounding it. But that is the common effect, we think, because it is so easy to go along being blissful in ignorance. The bottom line is that you do not want to deprive your self of critical information that could be exactly what you need to know. You always want the best possible outcomes with something like this, and so you generally know what needs to be done. While some information can look a little intimidating at first, depending on what you bring to the table, you are of course more than capable of understanding the issues involved.<br /><br />The smartphone market has been growing over the years. Every year, mobile companies launch new phones. While some become successful, the others disappear into oblivion. Watch out for the top 10 smartphones of 2012.<br /><br />1) iPhone 4S<br /><br />If you are looking for the latest phone from Apple, it is iPhone 4S. It is said to have the slickest iPhone design. iPhone 4S has topped the top 10 smartphones of 2012 list mainly because of its A5 dual core processor. If you are a &quot;gaming freak&quot;, this processor will not seize to amaze you with its PowerVR SGX GPU.<br /><br />2) Samsung's latest Smartphone<br /><br />Samsung phones are known for their technologically advanced touchscreen capabilities. Samsung Galaxy S2 is the new phone in the galaxy that is running on android OS. It comes with a considerably enhanced hardware. second with the 8 MP camera on this phone. Some of the optional accessories for this phone include the stylus pen, dock connector, MHL cable and others.<br /><br />3) The latest smartphone from HTC<br /><br />HTC, a fairly new mobile company has been known for its smartphones. HTC One X is its latest smartphone. It is expected to be released in 2012 and has some amazing smartphone features. 2.<br /><br />4) Sony's Xperia Ion<br /><br />Sony Xperia Ion, the latest smartphone from the Sony stable is expected to be released in 2012. From music to videos, you can save any multimedia file on Sony Xperia Ion. With LCD display of 4.55&quot; and a camera of twelve megapixel, this is one of the best smartphones from Sony. A 1.5 gigahertz Qualcomm CPU will power the smartphone.<br /><br />5) Addition to Nokia's Lumia series<br /><br />There is a lot that Nokia has to learn from competitors Samsung, Sony and Apple about smartphones. In order to combat its rivals in the smartphone scene, Nokia is releasing its latest in the Lumia series, Lumia 900. It is said to have adopted the saying, &quot;big is beautiful&quot;. With its 4.3&quot; AMOLED display technology, you can expect crisp and exciting graphics on it. It is powered by Windows Phone 7 OS.<br /><br />6) Blackberry Bold Touch<br /><br />Blackberry Bold Touch is the blackberry phone with enhanced multimedia aspects. The best thing about this smartphone is that this is one of the first blackberry phones to adopt touchscreen technology in it. This phone consist of a camera of 5 megapixel power. For browsing the web and viewing media files, this is the right blackberry smartphone for you.<br /><br />7) New smartphone from LG<br /><br />LG Optimus 4X HD is the new smartphone from LG with HD 720p screen. It has a rear 8mp camera and a secondary 1.3 mp camera. To cover your requirements, you get a battery of 2000mAh battery with this phone. Android Ice Cream Sandwich OS powers this device.<br /><br />The other phones on the list<br /><br />The 3 phones that complete the list of top 10 smartphones of 2012 are Huawei Honor, Panasonic Eluga Power and Motorola Razr. You can see that the Chinese Huawei Honor and the American Motorola smartphones have great functionalities to offer. Panasonic's efforts at bringing out a successful smartphone can be seen with Panasonic Eluga Power.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="19db47e94c49bad36521ae0d3e4864a8" url=""><![CDATA[Why Should You Purchase A Smartphone?<br/><br/>Once in a while you come across a topic, like <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">for more information click here</a> for instance, and it will be instrumental for you to realize there are related areas that it would be very good for you to explore. That is just the way some things go, it seems, and one can easily get led into a false sense of information security. If you are not ever quite satisfied with what you know or have just read, then that should compel you to keep digging. So just do not allow your self to assume too much or get too comfortable with what you know. Everything is connected in one way or another, and that is why we warn you about today's subject and the idea that it may be a shallow subject.<br /><br />The iPhone has had a huge influence in the evolution of mobile phones. It was the first real smartphone. Various versions of iPhone and several Android based phones are being used the most today followed by Symbian, RIM and Windows mobile phones. Many conventional mobile phone users are not very keen on switching to a smartphone. The major reason for this apprehension is the feeling that smartphones are complicated devices. Those who already have a smartphone do not want to buy a new one because they think it will be a waste of money. These people should remember that there might be aspects associated with the new phone that warrant the price.<br /><br />Portable internet<br /><br />The most important impact of smartphones has been on how quickly and easily you can access the internet. You could use the internet with earlier mobile phones as well, but the restricted screen size would be a hindrance. Most of the smartphones available today have big touchscreens through which you can view content. This makes watching YouTube content and photos a lot richer experience. You will find that the connection alternatives and speed improves with upgrades in smartphone models. Those who have used 3G on phones will realize the Importance of such technologies. But, with newer models, you can access 4G which is a lot faster.<br /><br />The APP market<br /><br />The applications and developer community support available to both iPhones and Android phones has played a crucial role in their success. Both the AppStore by Apple as well as the official Android market place provide number of programs that significantly enhance the performance of the phone. This is one of the biggest disadvantages of old devices. When applications are made, the purpose is to make them run on the most popular phone models. This means that older models of smartphones will not support the app.<br /><br />Portable gaming console<br /><br />The quality of hardware used has improved significantly. The processor chips in some of the smartphones today are as fast as last generation PCs. Gaming firms keep making better games to utilize the touch interface, accelerometer and gyroscope offered by new smartphones. You can go through various app market and you will realize that they are dominated by game apps. New games keep coming up at a rapid pace and most of them will not run on the hardware present in older smartphones.<br /><br />Music players<br /><br />Earlier mobile phones neither had the storage capacity nor the cap to offer good quality music playback. Smartphones today are equipped with SD card slots that are compatible wit 32 GB memory cards. Phones which do not offer SD slots have an internal memory of 8GB or more. The quality of music playback has improved greatly along with media player software. This has been one of the main reasons for iPods not getting new releases as most people prefer using iPhones for listening to music.<br /><br />Stay in touch making use of social media apps<br /><br />Many businesses and people like to maintain their profiles on social media. Newer smartphones come with better integration with social media platforms. Whether it be managing the account or simply sharing content, every job is made easy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e8a48b68cccc4be5fbee053dc1eaf7c9" url=""><![CDATA[What Can You Expect From Smartphones Of The Future<br/><br/>If you started doing some serious searching, you will see the numbers of discussions centered on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">website</a>. You are smart to be here reading on this subject matter only because of course it is relevant to you, but knowing more can potentially help in other ways. While we cannot be sure about you, we do tend to think you will discover this on your own. One of the great aspects of the net is you read this article, for example, and then can pick and choose what is most relevant and immediately gain additional knowledge.<br /><br />There is bound to be a minimum of several points well worth reflecting on, so maintain a positive mindset.<br /><br />The smartphone industry is always on the move. You will find companies coming up with unique features to broaden their customer base. Anyone who has been using a mobile phone for a decade will realize the changes that have been happening over that span. It is very common to expect a revolutionary feature with every new smartphone. So, mentioned below are changes you might see in smartphones in the coming years. Keep in mind that some of these features might never make it to a smartphone while some might be available within some months.<br /><br />Flexible smartphones.<br /><br />The processors used for smartphones are not only a lot smaller now, they are a lot faster as well. This frees up a lot more area for battery and allows changes to be made to the display. This has meant that it is possible that future screens are flexible. In fact, Samsung is preparation to launch flexible screen smartphones as soon as 2012. In the beginning you will not be able to do more than bend the screen. But when nano-technology is also introduced in the mix, your phone may take the shape of a wrist watch or a full sized phone.<br /><br />Near Field communication.<br /><br />Near Field communication (NFC) is a great way of connecting with other smartphones because all you need to do is touch the other device and you are ready for data transfer. Android 2.3 Gingerbread, which is one of the most commonly used Android OS has support for this technology.<br /><br />Since NFC can mainly be used for making payments through your smartphone as of now, the customers are not very keen on the technology. Google plans on increasing the abilities of NFC with Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich. Google is calling the new feature as 0-click interaction. This new ability allows you to establish a connection with other smartphones by simply keeping two devices back to back. This will aid in sharing YouTube videos, web pages and contact information without using any app.<br /><br />Greater impact of augmented reality apps.<br /><br />As of now there are very limited apps that work upon augmented reality which is bound to change in the coming years. One of the apps where you can see many improvement is Google Goggles that searches information about an image you take. The Layar browser and the visual search choice provided by Bing are also examples of augmented reality apps. In the future you might find these apps to grow a lot more.<br /><br />Making Use Of GPS with future phones.<br /><br />GPS has become very well known with drivers as a navigational tool. But, there are a lot more applications for this technology. It can be tough at times to locate a restroom in crowded places. You can hope to use GPS to solve this issue in the future. The improved GPS will also help you in figuring out how long a queue is present at various location.<br /><br />CPU chips will become powerful.<br /><br />Smartphone processors like the Tegra series are always getting better with the latest Tegra 3 being 5 times as fast as Tegra 2. By 2014, Nvidia plans to release the Stark series which will be 100 times faster than the Tegra 2 chips.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="318cb28754f65f793791137948137673" url=""><![CDATA[Tips For Buying A Smartphone<br/><br/>It is exciting for us to report that <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lLW1vYmlsZ3VpZGUuZGsv" target="_blank">visit</a> is really commanding a lot of attention over the net space. It is important for all this dialog to be happening because of the implications. We understand there can seem to be a wealth of information you have to absorb, so just take your time with it. As you know, this is a broad topic of discussion, and that is why it will be helpful for you to think in broad terms.<br /><br />There is bound to be a minimum of several points well worth reflecting on, so maintain a positive mindset.<br /><br />The popularity of smartphones has been growing over the years, what with all the options. It can be a challenging task to choose one among them. It is essential that you evaluate the attributes that each of these phones has to provide so that you can make the best selection. If you went ahead and bought a smartphone 'impulsively', you have not really made a smart decision. A buying guide is given here to make you comprehend the features you need to analyze before buying a smartphone.<br /><br />1) Evaluate the camera on the smartphones<br /><br />You need to evaluate the purpose for which you want a smartphone. Every buying guide to smartphones tell you this. Various types of smartphones are made to Provide you various particular features. If photography is the reason you want to buy a smartphone, there are several of those with the best quality in the market today. The VGA features, extra front facing camera, LED flash and other such features on these cameraphones can even help in videoconferencing. If you want to take photos of the highest quality, you can go for some of the best cameraphones like Apple iPhone 4S and Samsung Galaxy series. Another smartphone with great camera abilities is Nokia N8 with which an entire movie 'The Commuter' was filmed. So, you can make a selection based on the type of photography that you are into.<br /><br />2) Multimedia abilities of smartphones<br /><br />Smartphones of today can double as small cinema screens with improved multimedia and display capabilities. A few of the best smartphones provide you an inbuilt memory of 8GB that is sufficient for an average user. You can store your entire song collection on these phones. You can download and use many music apps directly. Smartphones have no limitations when it comes to playing varied formats of audio files. Blackberry has recently made foray into music phones, you can browse through their site and choose a smartphone that appeals to you. You don’t have to fret about the audio and video quality on these phones because they provide you value for your money.<br /><br />3) Appearance of the smartphone<br /><br />If you have a smartphone that has everything but you don’t like the look of it, you know where you went wrong. While some smartphones are small and bulky, the others have a long and sleek appearance. Also, the flip smartphones are also not being manufactures anymore to make way for touchscreens. Variations in design can be seen on smartphone models of the one company; for instance, while iPhone 4S has a flat back, its predecessor iPhone 3GS has a semi- curved back. Keypads of smartphones are another style aspect you have to think about. Because in case you want to send an email or a text urgently, using a keypad that you are not familiar with can be extremely frustrating. Apart from virtual keypads and regular numeric keypads, more kinds are being introduced like the QWERTY keyboards. If you are not good at handling virtual keyboards, go for the physical ones.<br /><br />4) Other smartphone features<br /><br />There are certain other features that you can assess. Battery life of a phone is as important as any other smartphone aspect. If someone is talking about total talk time, it means they are talking about the number of hours the phone will stay switched on until when in use. Mobile Operating System have an effect on smartphones, for instance, there are Android phones and then there are Symbian phones; make sure you know which one you want. Use the buying guide to smartphones and you can make a 'smart' decision on your 'smartphone' purchase.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c686f97396c54d09cb54961aa2a4c002" url=""><![CDATA[Why Smartphones Are Popular<br/><br/>You can find so many conversations about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2tpdGNoZW5hcnQtaXN0LmNvbS8yMDEyLzA0LzA5L2V2b2x1dGlvbi1vZi1zbWFydHBob25lcy8_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.e-mobilguide.dk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.e-mobilguide.dk</a></a> on the web; we know because we have been in enough of them. We will talk more about some of the reasons why this topic of discussion needs to be taking place. That is what we found out, and it is good to know, plus discovering the nuances will essentially be an empowering experience. It is unknown to us what exactly you are searching for in terms of the wider scope of this topic, and that is why this will touch on a few points that you can easily delve deeper into.<br /><br />Just like many other subjects, a few details might seem to not apply to you - but the majority or maybe all of it will.<br /><br />These days you can see that virtually everyone around you has abandoned the regular phones and has switched over to smartphones. From Nokia to Microsoft, you can see that these phones are being manufactured by some of the best mobile companies. Several sites on the internet have tried to answer the question why you need a smartphone, and so have we in this article. They can perform many tasks at a time. Here are 5 reasons to why owning a smartphone makes sense.<br /><br />1) Keep in touch with people<br /><br />Communicating with smartphones can be exciting as there are several alternatives to do so. Not only can you call or text your friends, you can email them or get in touch with them over social media. With instant messaging, now you can ping your friends and have conversations with them. You can see that mobile phone communication technology has evolved from 2G to 4G. Apart from this, you will find more reasons why you need a smartphone.<br /><br />2) GPS and music<br /><br />You can see that many music player handheld devices have been launched in the market. But there is a reason why smartphones are preferred over them by several people. You can save a lot of money because you won't be spending anything extra on a separate music player. With a storage space of 32 GB inbuilt in some of these phones, you carry your entire song selection on them. Radio and music put aside, GPS is another helpful feature on smartphones. With Global Positioning System integrated into these phones, you don’t have to fret about getting lost anywhere. If you are late to work, you can use GPS to find the shortest route to your workplace.<br /><br />3) Smartphones and internet<br /><br />Emailing and web browsing are some of the best aspects that a smartphone provides you. You can watch YouTube videos on your smartphone and while away your time. With your smartphone, playing angry birds has never been this much fun. These phones have features that serve specific purposes, for instance, blackberry phones with corporate email service help speedy business transactions. With smartphones, you can access internet even when there is no wi- fi network around because of the 3G technology.<br /><br />4) Smartphone cameras<br /><br />Camera- equipped smartphones are taking away the market share of cameras today. If you have an Apple iPhone, you can make use of the VGA camera (front facing) for videoconferencing. With a nokia smartphone that has a camera of 12mp autofocus lens, shooting clear videos is a breeze. iPhone 4S, Nokia 800, Samsung Galaxy and other smartphones come with an 8 megapixel camera. It is easier to get a smartphone with additional camera features like LED flash, IR filter, added lens, etc.<br /><br />5) More reasons to own a smartphone<br /><br />To know other reasons why you need a smartphone, read on. With the calendar on this phone, you can organize your work. With smartphones, shopping is more fun, because there are so many things you can do including redeeming your discount coupons. Among other things, you can also prepare a shopping list on your smartphone. Smartphones are more an investment than an expenditure. Businesses can make exclusive use of smartphones. So far, you have discovered a few things concerning <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dhbGxpcG9saXRvdXIubmV0LzIwMTIvMDQvMDkvaGlzdG9yeS1vZi1zbWFydHBob25lcy8_" target="_blank">website</a> along with the significance it has for you. We encourage you to seriously look at the backdrop of your own life and how what you are reading about will help. That is really in your best interest only because you know your situation better than anybody else. You will be best served if your knowledge is broad, and then you can fill in any details with further research. That is would be the ideal scenario, here, but you will not always have the time to do what is necessary for that to happen. So just find what ever spare time you have, and be sure you pay attention to the most important issues. As always, take care of your self or perhaps someone else if you are helping them with this research. For instance, if the sales executive of a company owns a smartphone, he can make presentations with the help of the phone and a projector. Also, you can have all your business contacts saved on these phones.<br /><br />The feedback about this is typically along the lines of surprise reactions when people read about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hcnllbGxlbmZvcm9oaW8uY29tLzIwMTIvMDQvMDkvaGlzdG9yeS1vZi1zbWFydHBob25lcy8_" target="_blank">website</a>, here. You can pick one of the supporting sub-topics and still find even more about this.<br /><br />Do pay close attention as you begin to move from one topical area to another. But do not feel shy about exploring anything that you feel may shed more light on this. Then, since you know it is important, simply drill down to discover more about it.<br /><br />Then it is up to you as to move forward with a linear consideration to the topic, or in any other direction.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="30edefb4b8224c6635686975e2b318b" url=""><![CDATA[Smartphones Features Comparison<br/><br/>There really is a lot more to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGFyYXRzdHVkZW50LmNvbS9ibG9ncy92aWV3YmxvZy5waHA/YmxvZ2lkPTQ4MDk5JmFtcDthbXA7bW9kZT1ibG9n" target="_blank">for more information click here</a> than what you will find in this article, we know, but we can add to what you already know, for sure. Well, welcome to the club because you are absolutely not alone with that feeling of needing to know more.<br /><br />It is always your call as to whether or not to gain outside help with some things. We are different from some folks, we think, because we would not call someone to offer their expertise.<br /><br />The most important thing to keep in mind is what will be comfortable for you and be able to work the best for you.<br /><br />We all proceed at a pace that is comfortable for us, and you will have the best results that way, anyway.<br /><br />Smartphones have put feature phones behind them in terms of popularity. Their multi- tasking abilities and other reasons have made them so popular with people. Various brands of smartphones have been launched into the market in the past ten years. The exclusive functionalities on smartphones are designed in order to meet specific purposes. In order to select one that is suitable for you, you need to compare smartphones. Here is a comparison of some aspects of different smartphones.<br /><br />1) OS on smartphones<br /><br />Compare smartphones and understand the OSs powering them because they make a lot of difference. Other application programs and softwares on smartphones run on the operating systems. Some of the advanced functions of your phone have been made possible due to OS. Here is a look at some of the most popular mobile operating systems.<br /><br />a) Android<br /><br />Some of the biggest smartphone brands run on the linux kernel powered Android operating system. It was introduced by Google in 2007. Some of the smartphones that use Android are Samsung Galaxy Nexus, HTC Dream and more. You are not quite finished learning about   <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BwaWR1bmlhLm9yZy8yMDEyLzA0LzEwL2EtZ3VpZGUtdG8tYnV5aW5nLXNtYXJ0cGhvbmVzLTIv" target="_blank">visit our website</a> and all that it means in your life. We encourage you to seriously look at the backdrop of your own life and how what you are reading about will help. We do make the effort to help you as much as possible since this is all about you. Having a wider perspective is to your advantage as well as an open mind. So, just take it a little at a time and learn from the best sources which is always best. Perhaps the most critical aspect is understanding your own situation as much as possible, and then find the most salient information. What we mean by that is some aspect will have greater meaning for each of us, and then you can go off and discover more for your self on that one thing. There are about ninety thousand applications available for Android.<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> Apple phones run on iOS<br /><br />iOS is another well known mobile operating system introduced by Apple Inc. This operating system is exclusive to Apple devices like iPad and iPhone. It is said that working with iOS is simple when compared to other mobile operating systems. Some statistics on the internet show that iOS applications have been downloaded more than twenty billion times till date.<br /><br />c) Symbian by Nokia<br /><br />Symbian OS does not run on any other device except phones. The interface component included in this OS is S60 (5th edition) based. Qt framework has been included in the Symbian OS. Apart from clicking photos, playing videos and other basic functions, the OS has been technologically updated to do carry out more complex tasks. You can also carry out tasks like editing suite with this OS. With shortcuts and widgets, customizing the downloaded apps is simpler on this Symbian.<br /><br />2) Keyboards on smartphones<br /><br />If you notice, smartphones have very different keyboards on them when compared to the other phones. See that you are comfortable making use of the keyboard on the smartphone you want to buy. QWERT keyboards typically found on computers can be found on smartphones too. Here is more information.<br /><br />a) Touchscreen smartphone keyboards: <br /><br />These keyboards eliminate the need for physical keyboards. To enter a number, say 1, you have to touch the number 1 on your touchscreen and voila! It is entered. If you are not used to this keyboard type, it might be frustrating to type texts or dial numbers quickly. However, like every other technology, you need to use it to comprehend it.<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> QWERTY keyboards<br /><br />QWERTY keypad is the one that has physical keys on it; the sequence of which follows the sequence of keys on a computer keyboard. Motorola and Blackberry smartphones use this kind of keypad. Computer users might still find this kind a bit difficult to make use of as the spacing is different.<br /><br />3) More differences<br /><br />When you compare smartphones, more distinctions can be spotted between the various brands. Screen and device sizes of one phone are different from that of another. Small screens are typically seen on smartphones that have QWERTY or other types of physical keyboards. You can see that not all phones have the same design and size when it comes to the structure of the devices. You can see that the various models of Blackberry itself have several ranges and styles. These aspects of smartphones must be evaluated and compared so that you make the best selection.<br /><br />If you have done even a little reading on  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Rpbmd3YW5nNzg5LmNvbS8yMDEyLzA0LzEwL3doYXQtdG8tbG9vay1mb3Itd2hlbi1idXlpbmctc21hcnRwaG9uZXMv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.e-mobilguide.dk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.e-mobilguide.dk</a></a> thus far, you know it involves so many people, everywhere. You know how it is with folks because you are probably the same; no attention is paid unless there is an issue.<br /><br />So what we recommend is that you start paying closer attention and be mindful about it. We are much more reactive to things because we tend to wait until it is happening, and there is less thought about preventing something. You know what tends to happen, it is only post-event or knowledge that action is taken. That is why we always urge those we communicate with to become knowledgeable and keep learning.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="98b78edb90e38702f1858417d1facce2" url=""><![CDATA[Smartphones: Pre Purchase Considerations To Be Made<br/><br/>Join in the conversation about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zcXVpZG9vLmNvbS9ndWlkZXRvcHVyY2hhc2luZ3NtYXJ0cGhvbmVzNDU4" target="_blank">read more</a> because it is popular in certain niche markets. It is tough to say with certainty how many people understand its importance, today. The devil is in the details - that is extremely true in our experience, and apparently the same in many people who have come before us. This article was produced from the perspective of looking at the overall which should at least touch on some of your concerns.<br /><br />There is bound to be a minimum of several points well worth reflecting on, so maintain a positive mindset.<br /><br />Smartphones are the mobile phones that have seen faster growth than any other phones in the recent past. The reasons for their popularity is that they can carry out a lot of functions at one go. They are more useful these days than they were a decade ago because they help cope up with the speedy living of today. The functionality of these smartphones differ with the brands and other aspects like the OS present in them. The details on the working of these phones can be found on a smartphone review site. Read on to know more.<br /><br />1) Operating System<br /><br />When you are looking for a smartphone, consider the OS that is used in it. Some of the most well known mobile OSs in the market today are iOS by Apple and Android by Google Even though we are offering a solid overview with some pertinent details about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2d1aWRldG9wdXJjaGFzaW5nc21hcnRwaG9uZXMyNzAud2V0cGFpbnQuY29tL3BhZ2UvQStHdWlkZStUbytCdXlpbmcrU21hcnRwaG9uZXM_" target="_blank">click here</a>, there is much more than you may realize. <br /><br />All you need to do is follow along because we have this plus much more in store. You may think something could not be directly applicable in your situation, but just be a little careful about overlooking anything. <br /><br />Everything is related in one way or another, and that is part of the beauty of it all. <br /><br />The best results will be from taking action on hard core facts, and then also seeing what can be done in other ways in a creative fashion. In the rest of our discussion, we will offer more information that will reinforce what you have already learned, and then you will be better equipped to understand. We always think that it is always all good, and it just needs to percolate a little bit in your mind.. These various OSs are suitable for different purposes. For example, Blackberry OS is more business focused while iOS is more popular with gamers. Go through a smartphone review site to know more about these operating systems so that you know which one is appropriate for you.<br /><br />2) Standby time and Talk time<br /><br />You can measure the battery life of a smartphone in two ways, standby time and talk time. According to mobiledia.com, standby time is the &quot;amount of time you can leave your fully charged cell phone turned on before the phone will completely discharge its batteries&quot;. Some of the popular smartphones have a standby time of up to four hundred hours. Apart from standby time, you should also think about the talk time that the battery of the phone provides. The average talk time of any popular smartphone today is around 5 hours. On an average you will need a talk time of four hours a day. If, besides calling and sending messages, you use the phone for more purposes, then 4 hours talk time is not sufficient for you.<br /><br />3) Phone's storage capacity<br /><br />Smartphones can be picked based on the storage capacity they provide the user. You can use the storage space for pictures, videos, bookmarks, applications and games. If you are a user who stores more than just photos in your phone, then get a phone that has more storage space. To store a vast range of media files, choose a phone with 4GB minimum memory. You can get a memory card to be inserted into the phone, if your smartphone does not have enough memory of its own.<br /><br />4) Phone design<br /><br />You can see that one smartphone does not look like another because of its unique style. Check the size of the device, kind of the keyboard and size of the screen of the phone. While some people like technologically forward touchscreen keyboards, some like the conventional button ones. The kind of the keyboard used has an impact over the size of the smartphone screen. If your phone has button keyboard, the size of the screen is more compressed to allow for the keyboard space. Big screen is for those users who prefer to watch movies and live television on their mobiles.<br /><br />These are some of the aspects that will help you to pick a phone that suits you. Go through a popular smartphone review site so that you can gather better details about a phone you want to purchase. Some of the other aspects that you can think about are conference calling abilities, personal reminders, etc.<br /><br />Of course <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb29kcmVhZHMuY29tL2V2ZW50L3Nob3cvMzEyNDI2LXdoYXQtdG8tbG9vay1mb3Itd2hlbi1idXlpbmctc21hcnRwaG9uZXM_" target="_blank">visit</a> is important to you otherwise you would not have been searching for it. But it really can easily go far beyond the obvious since it is tough to know all about what is possible. Naturally, that is when things can begin to get a little complicated. You have read the three points we have discussed, and it of course is prudent that you investigate further. But as you well know, the internet is so huge that you can do that with no problems. In order to protect your best interests, be wary of where you get your material and what you believe. After all this much time has passed, we all know what things are like on the web.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>