<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="492a063748d629b9f28f3124fae2d2f6" url=""><![CDATA[Tours to Kerala-The Joy of Kerala Tour Packages<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXZhY2F0aW9ucy5odG1s" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_11875176_29428777.jpg" /></a>
<br />Kerala has been accredited as one of the ten paradises on Earth by National Geographic. The demography and the diversified cultural background of Kerala is an ideal blend for a holiday destination. <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmc_" target="_blank">Kerala tour packages</a> </strong> usually comprise of visit to Lush hill stations, Sandy beaches of Kerala, Unique Kerala backwaters, Religious, Heritage &amp; Cultural sights, Kerala Ayurveda treatment. Kerala has been named suitably as The Gods’ Own Country and Venice of East. Kerala now has become one of the most visited holiday vacation destinations in India.
<br /><br />Kerala, The Venice of the East is pregnant with picturesque beauty of nature and prosperous culture and tradition. It is a place of spirituality and grandeur. A tourist can have the joy of Kerala tour packages through a range of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLWhvbGlkYXkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala holiday tour</a> </strong> packages which offer numerous options to explore the prosperous Kerala’s tradition and culture of Kerala and picturesque natural beauty of Kerala.
<br /><br />Kerala is loaded with various tourist destinations which are visited by a large number of tourists from all over India and abroad. In Kerala a traveler can make tours to destinations such as Trivandrum, Munnar, Alappuzha, Thekkady, and Palakkad etc. All these holiday destinations in Kerala are well-known for their rich charisma and culture and packed with lots of mind-blowing must see attractions. 
<br /><br />When you pay visit to the tranquil backwaters of Kerala during your <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcvdG91cnMtdG8ta2VyYWxhLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Tours to Kerala</a> </strong>, the Venice of the East, the first thing that catches your sight the Kerala houseboats. The houseboats of Kerala are pretty alike, the gondolas in the Venice. Most of the tourists, especially the honeymoon couples, love to stay overnight in a luxury Kerala houseboat. It could be a pretty extraordinary experience for the first time travelers in Kerala. The backwater tour packages in Kerala are mostly offered as Kottayam Backwater tour packages, Kozhikode Backwater tours, Alleppey Backwater tour package; Kochi Backwater tours packages, Kumarakom Backwater tour packages.
<br /><br />The sandy sun-kissed beautiful beaches of Kerala are also very famous amongst the tourist on a tour package to Kerala. The beautiful coastline of Kerala comprises of abundance of attractive &amp; clean sandy beaches such as Kappad Beach, Kappil Beach, Kovalam Beach, Alappuzha Beach, Cherai Beach, Marari beach and Beypore Beach etc. You can select your choice of beach tour package from the wide range of beach tour packages available in Kerala. Just leave the rest of the world behind and enjoy to the fullest and have a nice time on your holiday to the beaches of Kerala. 
<br /><br />Kerala has got a wide range of scenic verdant hill resorts also. The hill resorts in Kerala are perfect destination to explore the idyllic atmosphere and nature at its best. Some of the most visited hill stations in Kerala are Munnar, Thekaddy, Wayanad, Rajamala, Ponmudi and Ramakalmedu. These attractive marvelous hills resorts are well-known for its peaceful environment and scenic beauty. Moreover, your tour to Kerala is never completed without visit to the popular wildlife destinations like Chinnar wildlife Sanctuary, Eravikulam wildlife Sanctuary and Periyar wildlife Sanctuary. 
<br /><br />A tour package to Kerala will always let you realize and feel the splendid beauty of nature. Travel to Kerala and enjoy the quietness of temples, admire the ancient Hindu architecture and grant peace for the human body. It is an idyllic destination that gives total pleasure for your mind, body and soul.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="60d25d92a2ddad9cec5bee49e143afd1" url=""><![CDATA[Kerala Vacation and Tours<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmc_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_6684495_31056125.jpg" /></a>Welcome to Kerala the land of ever green beauty. Globally acclaimed for the scintillating beauty of the hill stations, mesmerizing charm of the backwaters and stunning beaches with ever-ending palm trees, Kerala beauty is hard to define. It is seen to be believed.  National Geographic Traveler Magazine one of the leading travel magazine in the world today have also named Kerala as one of the Ten Paradise in the World and 50 Must Visit Destination of Lifetime. 
<br /><br />On you <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLWhvbGlkYXkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala holiday</a>  </strong> you have wonderful opportunity to enjoy each and every attractions which has made Kerala the featured destination on the World Tourist Map today. Tourists from all over the world and holiday makers come here to enjoy their holidays to experience the serenity of nature and the unparallel beauty of the backwaters that is truly unmatched by any other tourism destination in the world. Apart from all these the world class accommodation facilities, warm hospitality and peaceful ambiance have truly made Kerala the most sought after tourism destination in the world today. 
<br /><br />The state of Kerala is blessed with some of the most magnetizing attractions among which the backwaters are the prominent. Beaches, hill stations and the exotic wildlife parks and sanctuaries also supplements in the boom of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXJpc20uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tourism</a>  </strong>. These are some of the feature attractions that one can visit or explore on their <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXZhY2F0aW9ucy5odG1s" target="_blank">Kerala vacations</a>  </strong>. 
<br /><br />Key Attractions of Kerala Tourism  
<br />•	Kerala Backwaters 
<br />•	Kerala Hill Station 
<br />•	Kerala Wildlife Parks and Sanctuaries
<br />•	Kerala Beaches 
<br />•	Colorful Fairs and Festivals 
<br />•	Rich Culture and Heritage Attractions 
<br /><br />Well plan for holiday in Kerala and explore the fascinating attractions and enigmatic charm of Kerala tourism and relish in forever. Surely you will cherish each and every moment spent here in this beautiful state of Kerala –the God’s Own Country.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a40d7fcc44991691178e61e509ce05d" url=""><![CDATA[Kerala Tours and Travels – Awesome Experience to Cherish F<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21vaGR6YWhlZXJ1bGhhc2FuLmJsb2dzcG90LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_6388024_31338278.jpg" /></a>
<br />Have you ever experienced the beauty of nature in their refreshing form? Have you ever enjoy a cruise over the scenic backwater or played with the romancing waves or enjoyed safari in the exotic forest packed with colorful birds or animals or ever experience the power hidden in the ayurveda herbal care? If you have not experienced all these, come for <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXJzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Kerala tours</a>  </strong> and you surely have the flavor and enjoy the hidden delights in all these beautiful tourism attraction of Kerala India. 
<br /><br />Every year thousands and thousands of tourists from all over the world come for <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcvaG9saWRheS1pbi1rZXJhbGEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Holiday in Kerala</a>  </strong> to explore the scintillating beauty of the nature and the blissful ambiance that is truly incomparable and enchanting and beyond visual and verbal descriptions. Kerala has some of the most beautiful backwater destinations and are the most preferred destinations by the tourists for tours and travels. Endowed with scintillating charm and refreshing beauty, the backwaters of Kerala are the lifeline of the state tourism that appeals tourists from all over the world. Tourists love to stay over the houseboat and enjoy the beauty of the backwater that slowly moving take to the world of scenic beauty that offers vistas hard to forget. 
<br /><br />Apart from the backwater there are amazing hill stations with well organized tea gardens, cascading waterfall and lovely mist kissed hills. Kerala also has globally famous beach destination that are the major holidaying destination in the state and the featured attraction of Kerala tourism. More of all the lush green beauty and the rich flora and fauna preserved by the wildlife parks and sanctuary add additional beauty to Kerala that grab the attention of the nature lovers and well as Widlife enthusiasts for <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXZhY2F0aW9ucy5odG1s" target="_blank">Kerala vacations</a>  </strong> in India. 
<br /><br />Come for Kerala tour and treasure remarkable holidaying experience exploring the charm and beauty that are truly magnetizing attractions. Truly speaking you will cherish each and every moment spent here in this evergreen paradise for lifetime.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71950d62afc4543a1fe100b5aa4c163e" url=""><![CDATA[Darjeeling Tours – Key Attractions to Explore<br/><br/><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_8340334_31438238.jpg" />
<br />Refreshing air, exotic natural beauty, blossoming flowers, mist kissed hills, gorgeous looking tea gardens, tumbling waterfalls, sun-kissed mountain peaks, exciting tourists attractions, Darjeeling a beautiful town located in the lap of the Kanchan Junga is world famous hill station. Its magnetizing charm of the scenic natural beauty with refreshing air and marvelous countryside with lovely view of the people in traditional dress wearing smiles on their face truly make Darjeeling a wonderful holidaying destination of North East India tours. The scenic town is blessed with amazing beauty and blissful ambiance with cool amiable climate that attracts tourist all the year round, winter and summer being the peak season of tourists. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling also dubbed as the Queen of Hill station is one of the most desired destination of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East India tours</a>  </strong> and provide wonderful opportunity for tourist to delight in adventure tour, leisure tour, nature tour and more of all family vacation. <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Darjeeling tours</a>  </strong> take you to the major tourist’s destination that will offer you amusing experience to delight in. Some of the major attractions of tourists that you most not miss to visit are listed below: 
<br /><br />•	Darjeeling Zoo, Darjeeling Museum
<br />•	Botanical Garden, Chowrashta 
<br />•	Mall Road, Darjeeling Monastery 
<br />•	Batasia Loop, Rock Garden
<br />•	Tiger Hill, Darjeeling Ropeway
<br />•	Lebong Race Course (Highest Race Course in the World)
<br />•	Ghoom Railway Station (Second Highest Railway Station in the World)
<br /><br />Apart from all these the Darjeeling Railway also dubbed as the Toy Train is part of the World Heritage Site and is one of the main attractions of Darjeeling Tourism, which grabs the attention of tourists from all the nook and corner of the world. Beside these one can enjoy the memorable journey in fact journey of lifetime and enjoy the scenic beauty and the people busy in their daily life as you pass through the town.  Surely you will cherish the moment of tour to Darjeeling for lifetime.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="19987629fa7470c2e11faa1cb922ddcb" url=""><![CDATA[Reasons to Plan for Kerala Tours<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXJpc20tcGFja2FnZS5odG1s" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_6388024_31338278.jpg" /></a>
<br />Some call it astonishing, some call it marvelous, some call it awesome, some call it enchanting beautiful, some call it paradise on earth, some call it God’s Own Country. Truly speaking Kerala is beyond all these and its refreshing beauty and awesome tourism attractions fade the importance of all these adjectives. So instead of describing the beauty of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank">Kerala tour Package</a>  </strong> with simple words, or going along with the words of the writers and poets, experince the beauty of this heavenly state of India in its true form planning <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour</a>  </strong> with the leading tour operator. 
<br /><br />Kerala has some of the world’s most beautiful attractions which are beyond visual and verbal descriptions. Here you can enjoy cruise over the breathtakingly beautiful backwaters fringed by the costal palm trees, exotic wildlife parks and sanctuaries, stunning beaches and exciting cities blessed with rich culture and traditions. Beside these you have wonderful opportunity to experince the world class hospitality of Kerala, delicious delicacies prepared in the melting pot, rejuvenating ayurveda therapy and many more. Truly speaking you will cherish each and every moment spent here in Kerala for lifetime. 
<br /><br />Some of the Prime attractions of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXJpc20uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala Tourism</a>  </strong> are listed below: 
<br />•	Kumarakom Backwater
<br />•	Alleppey Backwater
<br />•	Cochin Beach 
<br />•	Mirimar Beach
<br />•	Periyar Wildlife Sanctuary
<br />•	Thekkady Wildlife Sanctuary
<br />•	Parimbikulam Wildlife Sanctuary
<br />•	Trivandrum 
<br />•	Wayand 
<br />•	Idduki Hill Station
<br />•	Munnar Hill Station 
<br /><br />Beside all these there are many other tourism attractions in Kerala which are worth a visit. Well if you want to explore the splendor of this wonderful state of Kerala plan your holiday with one of the leading tour operator. So from the many <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour packages</a>  </strong> book one of your choice and enjoy your holiday in this evergreen paradise on earth in a delightful and memorable way.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9166f0b2e98df4ccad82455f39421949" url=""><![CDATA[Enjoy Delightful Holiday in Kerala with Kerala Tour Package<br/><br/><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_6141108_32382941.jpg" /></a></span>
<br />Holiday destinations are known for their specialties and their tourism attractions make it special. While Kashmir and Himachal Pradesh are known for their snow capped Himalayas, Darjeeling is known for its scintillating beauty of nature, Goa is known for its serene beaches and Rajasthan for its magnificent forts and palaces. Like wise Kerala a beautiful state located in the south western part of India is known globally famous its magnetizing beauty of the backwaters and the scintillating natural attractions. Due to the enigmatic beauty of natural attractions and blissful climatic conditions, Kerala is lovingly called God’s Own Country. 
<br /><br />Kerala has some of the finest tourism attractions that include the famous hill stations of Munnar, breathtakingly beautiful backwaters of Kumarakom and Alleppey, serene and magnetizing beaches and on top the exotic wildlife parks and sanctuaries. Apart from these, there are colorful cities and hill towns which are known for their exciting tourism attractions and magnificence, truly unmatched and found no where else in the world. So if you want to explore the magnetizing beauty of these favored attractions, plan for <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXJzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Kerala tours</a>  </strong>. Truly you will have wonderful time in Kerala which you will love to cherish and relish in forever. 
<br /><br /><strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank">Holiday in Kerala</a>  </strong> is made delightful and memorable by the tour operators who provide several tailor made <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour packages</a>  </strong> with all the facilities, services as well as proper guidance that makes the tour truly an experince of lifetime. Your visit to Kerala offer you to see and explore the astounding beauty of nature, rich culture and traditions, fairs and festivals, ruins and temples, forts and palaces, historical caves and many other tourism attractions. All these attractions will keep you engross you for more that and week and offer you enjoy memorable time in Kerala, the God’s Own Country. 
<br /><br />In additional, Kerala is also famous for its rejuvenating ayurveda therapy which is one of the oldest ways to treat skin diseases, imbalance of the body, mind and soul. Kerala Ayurveda is holistic science which helps to retain to retain the lost health, peace of mind and soul and more of all skin diseases. More of all ayurveda therapy don’t have side effect and cures the root cause of the diseases. Beside that one can also enjoy mesmerizing Kathakali Dance performed by the great artists, taste the delicious delicacies prepared in the hot melting pot, experince the warm hospitality of the people who never let you feel away from home and much more. Kerala is sheer wonder and offer you enjoy holiday in a delightful and memorable way treasure remarkable experince of lifetime. 
<br /><br />Well if you want to experince the magnificence of all these wonderments of Kerala, plan your vacation with one of the leading tour operator and management companies. Tour Operators provide several tailor made <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXBhY2thZ2UtdG91cnMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala package tours</a>  </strong> with customize prices and services. Book one of your choice and experince the splendor on nature and its magnetizing attractions in a delightful and memorable way. 
<br /><br />You are most welcome to Kerala, the God’s Own Country.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="582add9963abc3e15d87642261fb1323" url=""><![CDATA[Top Tourist Attractions to See on Kerala Tours<br/><br/><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_332116_32442045.jpg" /></a></span>
<br />Sandwiched between the azure Arabian Sea and the Western Ghats, Kerala is a beautiful state globally famous for its scenic natural beauty. It is endowed with scintillating beauty which comprise of beautiful backwaters, secluded beaches, refreshing hill stations and more of all exotic wildlife parks and sanctuaries packed with varied species of birds and animals. Apart from natural beauty it is also known for its rich culture and traditions, forts and palaces, ethnic caves and on top warm hospitality that makes <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXJzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Kerala tours</a>  </strong> an affair to remember and cherish forever.
<br /><br /><strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXBhY2thZ2UtdG91cnMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala package tours</a>  </strong> provide you wonderful opportunity to see and explore the magnetizing beauty of some of the most beautiful holiday destinations that include the
<br /><br />Kumarakom
<br />Kumarakom is a scenic village located along the bank of the picturesque Vembanad Lake, which is famous for its backwater destination. Most of the tourist who visits Kumarakom never misses the opportunity to length the beauty of its backwater cruising over the houseboat which slowly moving takes them to the world of wonderments. It is also famous for its exotic bird sanctuary where one can see some varied species of birds and small creatures enjoying their time freely in the open environment of Kumarakom Bird Sanctuary.
<br /><br />Cochin
<br />Lovingly called the Queen of Arabian Sea, Cochin is a natural harbor which is famous for its magnetizing beauty of nature and historical charm which are beyond visual and verbal descriptions. Here one can see some of the most beautiful attractions for which Kerala is known that include the heritage Chinese Fishing Net, Bolghatty Palace, Mattancherry Palace, Cherai Beach, Santa Cruz Basilica and many  others. Surely these wonderful attractions will keep you engross for more a week and offer you remarkable experince of Cochin tour in Kerala in India.  
<br /><br />Munnar
<br />Munnar lovingly called Kashmir of the South is blessed with outstanding beauty of nature. It is one of the most beautiful destinations and feature attractions of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXJpc20uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tourism</a>  </strong> which attracts tourists from all the nook and corner of the world. Here one can see exciting range of tourism attractions that include well organized tea gardens, Attukal, Devikulam, Pallivasal, Nyayamakad, Rajamala, Echo Point, Mattupetty Lake &amp; Dam and the Eravikulam National Park.
<br /><br />Beside these you can also enjoy visit to several other tourism destinations on your <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank">tour to Kerala</a>  </strong> which offer you an opportunity to enjoy vacation amidst the serenity of nature in a delightful and memorable way.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8fba041d1b0d5385284bc60bb7f80c5" url=""><![CDATA[Darjeeling Tours Visit to Scenic Hill Station of India<br/><br/><span class="textAlign" style="text-align: right;"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_8340334_31438238.jpg" /></a></span>Darjeeling also known as the ‘Queen of Hills’, is the most popular hill station in India. It is located on the border of Nepal and India and is very much known for its scenic natural beauty. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling is mostly famous for its well organized Tea Gardens, scenic surroundings with lively green living Mountains and many more attractions. On your <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tours to Darjeeling</a>  </strong> you can see and visit to some wonderful attractions like the “The Japanese Temple, The Observatory Hill, The Charming Rock Garden and the most attractive The Tiger Hill” and many more like this. Darjeeling is a sheer wonder and being here on your holiday will truly be a lifetime experince which you will love to share with your beloved one with much pride and delights.
<br /><br />The best time to be here is in the spring season, when whole Darjeeling bathes in the beauty of the Rhododendrons and lush greenery which adds magical colours to this Hill Town. It seems all the Darjeeling people after the very busy day comes to get refresh themselves to the most fascinating and to the busiest place in the town known as the beautiful Chowrasta. This is the place where you get to see every kind of people in the evening the students, businessman, the couples and some young guys enjoying their life living behind all the worries, which will tempt you for the same. Here enjoy the stimulating hot tea in the bliss of the surrounding viewing the magnetizing mist kissed hills with blossoming flowers and cascading waterfalls.
<br /><br />Apart from the tourist attractions <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tourism</a>  </strong> also offer world class accommodations facilities, which is very easily available in the town. Especially this Hill Stations is also famous for its beautiful Hotels which have all kinds of accommodations for every class of people. On stay in any of the hotels in Darjeeling, tourists can experince the rich culture and tradition as well as the warm hospitality of the welcoming people of Darjeeling. Taste the delicious delicacies, mood making Tongba and cuisines of your choice during your stay in Darjeeling. Truly you will have memorable <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Northeast tours</a>  </strong>, which you will love to treasure as a lifetime experience.
<br /><br />So what are you waiting for pack your bags and be here and explore the beauty of the charming Hill Station Darjeeling, lovingly called as Queen of All the Hill Stations.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="162b3d034e42f87518e035eee7567ec8" url=""><![CDATA[Kerala Holiday Treasure Remarkable Experience of Lifetime<br/><br/>Kerala is no wonder the most sought after holiday destination in India. It is amazingly blessed with astounding beauty of nature and tranquility that offer an ultimate holiday experience. Well if you are planning to enjoy holiday in this nature blessed Kerala, located in the south Western part of India, you are most welcome. 
<br /><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_6141108_32382941.jpg" /></a>
<br /></span>
<br />Kerala is a sheer wonder and is one of the most enticing tourism destinations in India visited by tourist from all the nook and corner of the world. It is magnificently blessed with astounding charm of nature in the form of backwaters, hill stations, fascinations wildlife parks and sanctuaries, bewitching beaches, inspiring temples and forts, rich culture and traditions and much more. Truly Kerala is a sheer wonder and is one of the most favored and sought after holiday destinations in India. Visit to this serene strip of land and enjoy holiday in the bliss of Mother Nature in a delightful and memorable way. Holiday in Kerala is made more delightful and memorable by the tour operators who provide several <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour packages</a>  </strong> to offer tourists and holiday seekers an ultimate travel experience.  
<br /><br />Truly Kerala is amazingly blessed by astounding charm of nature, but amongst all the most favored and visited by the tourists are its scintillating nature blessed backwaters, which needs no descriptions about its magnetic charm and beauty. Its very first sight is enough to leave even the sternest tourists spell bound. Some of the most visited backwaters by the tourists are Kumarakom, Kuttanad, Kollam, Kasargod and Cochin. These backwaters of Kerala are sheer wonder and the major attraction of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank">Kerala tourism</a>  </strong>. So what are you waiting for? Plan for tours to Kerala and enjoy holiday in this beautiful state of Kerala in a delightful and memorable way. 
<br /><br />Kerala is the land of astonishments and is one of the most favored and sought after holiday destination in India. So enjoy vacation availing the right package <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank">tours to Kerala</a>  </strong> and explore the magnetic charm of the nature in a delightful and memorable way.  
<br /><br />Welcome to Kerala the God’s Own Country.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8e8cfc984f51645c8fe5a0e2ee6eabe3" url=""><![CDATA[Kerala Tours for Remarkable Vacations<br/><br/><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_16655_33376738.jpg" /></a></span>
<br /><br />Kerala is amazingly beautiful and is one of the few states in India where you will find the nature at its best. It is one of the states in South India where one can see and explore lots of amazing attractions and destinations that are one of its kinds in the whole world. 
<br /><br />Kerala has lots of amazing tourism attractions among which the natural attractions magnets huge number of tourists from all the nook and corner of the world. Here one can see and explore huge number of attractions among which the most popular ones that one can afford to miss are listed below: 
<br /><br />Backwaters of Kerala
<br />Backwaters of Kerala are the prime attractions among all and are visited by thousands and hundreds of tourists from all the nook and corner of the world. The scintillating backwater dotted by the swaying coconut trees, paddy fields and lush green surrounding never fails to grab the heart of the nature lovers or the tourists on board. Here one can enjoy houseboat cruise on the famous backwater destinations of Kerala that include the famous Kumarakom Backwater, Alleppey Backwater, Kuttanad Backwater, Kollam Backwater, Cochin Backwater and Kasargod Backwater. 
<br /><br />Wildlife Parks of Kerala   
<br />Kerala Wildlife Parks and Sanctuaries are globally famous and are home to varied species of birds, animals and creatures. Here one can plan for jungle safari on <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour</a></strong> and see the various species of animals and birds in their natural home. Some of the famous and most visited wildlife parks in Kerala are Begur Wildlife Sanctuary, Chinnar Wildlife Sanctuary, Eravikulam Wildlife Sanctuary, Idduki Wildlife Sanctuary, Periyar Wildlife Sanctuary, Peechi Vazhani Wildlife, Parambikulam Wildlife Sanctuary, Peepara Wildlife Sanctuary etc. 
<br /><br />Beside these town tourism attractions, on your <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank">tours to Kerala</a></strong> you can see and explore the magnetizing charm of the scintillating hill stations, beguiling beaches, rustic villages, inspiring temples, ethnic caves in Wayanad, magnetizing waterfalls and much more. Come for Kerala tour availing tailor made <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour packages</a></strong> from the leading tour operator and explore the fascinating charm and splendor of the Kerala tourism in a delightful and memorable way. 
<br /><br />For more information about Kerala tourism, holiday in Kerala and Kerala package tours please visit our site <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.keralatourpackage.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.keralatourpackage.org/</a></a></strong>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="863e8cca2e35c53d0d05990846161279" url=""><![CDATA[Enfold Kerala Splendor with Kerala Tour Packages<br/><br/><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_9855736_33805011.jpg" /></a>
<br /></span>
<br />Kerala tour packages are gaining high importance in the world market today and especially when it accounts for tours and travels in India, Kerala is outstanding. It is the destination of all season and so it gathers the attention of tourists from across the world. It is amazingly beautiful blessed with scintillating beauty of nature, with beguiling beaches, picturesque hill stations, enchanting backwaters, fascinating wildlife parks and bird sanctuaries, inspiring temples, exotic Ayurveda Resorts and much more. Kerala due to all these wonderments is remarked as God’s Own Country. More of all you will find the blessing of nature and the cool amiable climatic conditions all the year round. 
<br /><br />Come to Kerala booking <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcvcGFja2FnZS10b3VyLXRvLWtlcmFsYS5odG1s" target="_blank">package tour to Kerala</a></strong> and take back home remarkable memories to relish in forever. Here you can experience the sheer magical charm of the evergreen natural beauty with rich flora and fauna. Most of the tourism destinations of the state Kerala are blessed with awesome beauty of nature that mesmerizes the heart of the visitors and tourists. Come to Kerala and take back home remarkable memories to relish in forever. 
<br /><br />Well on your <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour</a></strong> you cannot afford to miss to enjoy houseboat cruise over the scintillating and picturesque backwater which is said to be the lifeline of the Kerala tourism. Houseboats and the backwaters make the perfect combination and this may be the reason why both of them are considered to be the wonder of the state that enchants thousands and hundreds of tourists from across the world. Some of the favored backwater destinations in the state are Kumarakom, Kasargod, Kollam, Kuttanad, Cochin and Alleppey. 
<br /><br />Apart from all these there are many other tourism destinations in Kerala which are worth to visit and explore. Scintillating hill stations, fascinating wildlife parks and sanctuaries of Periyar and Thekkady and the beguiling beaches are many other tourism destinations in Kerala which are worth to visit and explore. So what are you waiting for? Book one from the many <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXBhY2thZ2UtdG91cnMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala package tours</a></strong> and enjoy holiday in this nature blessed Kerala also referred as God’s Own Country in a delightful and cherishable way. 
<br /><br />Know more about Kerala packages, holiday in Kerala, Kerala tourism packages and Kerala holiday packages please visit our site <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.keralatourpackage.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.keralatourpackage.org/</a></a></strong>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="44311a3419d796cf585bdd02e8c930ff" url=""><![CDATA[Kerala the Sheer Wonderments of India<br/><br/><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/129266265_14928404_34492404.jpg" /></a></span>
<br />Kerala fondly called God’s Own Country is blessed with astonishing tourism attractions and sightseeing spots which seems it is crafted with immense care. It is one of the most enticing tourism attractions in India which is blessed with astounding tourism attractions which is a sheer wonderment beyond words to describe. 
<br /><br />Located in the south western part of India, Kerala in India is visited by millions and millions of visitors for holidays and tours and travels. Most of the tourists who come for <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXJzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">tours to Kerala</a></strong> love to explore the soul beauty of this enigmatic state cruising over the houseboat, which is truly one of the most amazing wonderments that one can hardly love to miss out. Its sheer wonderments and the enticing charm have left one and all spell bound and offer tourists to enjoy memorable vacations in a delightful and memorable way. 
<br /><br />The state of Kerala is not only known for its enigmatic charm and splendor of the backwaters but is also famous for its evergreen natural surrounding of the hill stations which is blessed with astounding charm of the scintillating attractions and sightseeing spots. Some of the popular hill stations that you can hardly miss to visit are Munnar, Wayanad, Idduki, Devikulam, Chembara Peak, Idduki, Ponmudi, Palakkad, Vogamon, etc. All these hill stations are amazingly beautiful and so it is visited by thousands and hundreds of tourists from across the nook and corner of the world. 
<br /><br />Beside all these <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour packages</a></strong> also offer visitors to delight in the delicious delicacies, world class accommodation facilities, and sightseeing spots and on top blissful ambiance. All these well organized tourism attractions and pleasant climatic conditions truly make <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcva2VyYWxhLXRvdXIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Kerala tour</a></strong> truly remarkable, memorable and cherishable. 
<br /><br />So come to this very beautiful Kerala and take back home lots of memorable memories to relish in forever. Know more about Kerala holiday packages, Kerala tourism, holiday in Kerala and affordable Kerala packages please visit our website <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZXJhbGF0b3VycGFja2FnZS5vcmcv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.keralatourpackage.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.keralatourpackage.org/</a></a></strong>.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>