<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="11">
		<document id="e328b87d71bc8efa8f6d1ffe7046270e" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>Traditional Muslim Clothing is Being Redesigned With Style by Famous Designers<br /><br />Traditional Muslim clothing covers a person's body from head to toe, especially a woman. You can easily spot a burqa-clad woman in a heavy crowd. It is necessary for Muslim women to abide by the Islamic guidelines on modesty in dressing. Today Muslim garments are being added as a part of designer's collection by top notch designers. Famous designer Domenico Vacca has redesigned the traditional Abaya in his own style and added it to his own collection. There are some basic requirements that the traditional Muslim garments must comply with. Some of these requirements are listed below.<br /><br />*Traditional Muslim clothingrequires that men and women alike should decently cover their body parts in public. Most women find it necessary to cover their heads and faces too. They do so to comply with the traditional fact that they should not display their beauty in front of men with whom they can marry. According to the tradition, men must compulsorily cover their body from navel to knee.<br /><br />*According to the Islamic convention clothes must not cling to the bodies, especially for women. Women are required to wear loose fitting clothes. Women wear cloaks, like Abaya and Jilbab, in public to hide their body curves. In several Islamic countries men wear loose fitting robes that cover the body from the neck to the ankles.<br /><br />*Another important aspect is that the garments worn should be thick enough to cover the body entirely. In other words, wearing see-through garments is a strict no. Neither skin nor the shape of the body should be seen through the clothes.<br /><br />*The overall appearance of a person should decent. One should look dignified in the clothes he or she is wearing. Shiny or flashy clothing should be avoided because they defeat the above stated requirements for dressing modestly in public. People should wear neat, clean and sober clothes. They should not wear ragged or flashy clothes to attract the admiration or sympathy of other people.<br /><br />Thus, we see that how traditional Muslim clothing sets apart the Islamic people from the rest. Their religion encourages them to look like Muslims and not try to imitate the style statements of other regions and religions. Women are discouraged from dressing like men. Today these garments are easily available endowed with all kinds of embellishments in intricate patterns and vibrant colors.<br /><br />If you are looking for such items of dressing or their modern stylized versions, you can drop into the East Essence store and select the garments that suit your style the best.<br /><br />Muslim Clothing - Bringing together the finest in Islamic clothing, East Essence is proud to serve a diverse array of customers with its broad variety of Islamic apparel for women.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="74112971640040094530ef648d2421ca" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>Kids Hijab - Beautiful Designs and Styles to Choose<br /><br />These days, Muslim or Islamic children have a wide range of choices when it comes to Kids hijab. There are innumerable styles to select when it comes to the fabric choices. There are the gorgeous pashmina shawls to the relatively modest wholesale shawl versions as well. Whatever it is, your child is sure to look very cute when they wear the hijab.<br /><br />Ethereal white<br /><br />There are beautiful combinations available these days in the variety of kids hijabs. These range from classic white pieces available in a one piece with a fabric like georgette shawl and devoid of any lace. Though these look relatively simple they are the classic styles and will never go out of fashion.<br /><br />Black versions<br /><br />Then, there are the more common black kids hijabs, which range from the plan black chiffon shawls worn as hijab to small designs woven or painted on the black hijab. Some of the children's pieces have a single piece of hijab and do not contain any lace on the edges. However, most young girls will love to have a bit of intricate lace edging on their gorgeous black silk shawl and hence these are very much in vogue nowadays.<br /><br />Colorful variations<br /><br />There are also various colorful combinations when it comes to kids hijabs. After all, all kids like a bit of color in their garments so why not in the hijab as well? These days, you can find classic sober pink combinations with delicate designs on them to intense maroon and red variations of the hijabs. Many of these hijabs are made of a silk shawl or sometimes have more expensive pashmina shawls used. There are also unusual green blends when it comes to color in kids hijabs. These range from jungle green color combinations to classic green color variants. Then, there are the classic brown combinations as well where both light as well as darker brown colors in the kids hijabs are available. Light grey is also a very common choice.<br /><br />Kids look cute in hijabs!<br /><br />You will definitely agree that kids hijabs are very much in demand because they look so cute wearing them! Little girls bundled up in their cute colorful hijabs are a joy to behold! In addition, with so many beautiful designs, styles, colors and cuts to choose, it can be difficult to choose the perfect one for your little darling!<br /><br />Where to buy<br /><br />If you are looking for affordable kids hijabs, the best place to buy them would be on an online site that sells wholesale shawls. In this manner, you can get access to reasonable prices and good quality at the same time. Online stores are more convenient because shopping happens instantly and you do not have to visit a store to buy the hijab. If you are looking for more high-end and expensive kids hijabs, these are also typically available in such online stores. The typical shawls used for such hijabs range from pashmina shawls, classic chiffon shawls to even silk shawls. Whatever your requirement is, you are sure to find these kids hijabs in such stores.<br /><br />Thesa is an experienced writer and publicist. She have 12 years experience in writing well-researched articles of various topics, SEO web content, marketing and sales content, press releases, sales scripts, academic essays, E-books and news bits.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="35f6d79cd564cce2a0160ec218ff9888" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>Muslims Dating Online - A Modern Approach To Marriage<br /><br />Muslims have a hard time finding love and romance. They have either the choice of an arranged marriage or finding a partner on their own initiative. When we talk of arranged marriages then it usually means that parents are involved and the potential newly weds would be able to meet each other and give their feelings if they are happy to go along with the wedding or to carry on looking. However, arranged marriages are becoming less and less popular in the West.<br /><br />Young Muslims today have turned to other mediums to find love. Asking friends to match you up is fine but you never really know who that other person is. Many Muslims feel uncomfortable about dating as some young men and women are only interested in casual dating and nothing more serious or committed.<br /><br />Muslim matrimonial sites have sprung up in response to the demand for a safe way for Muslims looking for marriage can meet. There is anonymity so all of your personal details are secured away from prying eyes. You will be able to view thousands of other Muslims profiles and can narrow your search down to find someone who fits your lifestyle and criteria exactly. Something that would be very difficult to do if you are relying on family to do. Let's say for example that you are a practicing Muslim who prays 5 times a day and want to find someone who is equally committed to Islam. By viewing other members profiles you will be able to see what type of Muslims they are i.e. do they wear a hijab, niqab, have a beard, do regular prayers, etc.<br /><br />One common misconception is that everyone on these types of meeting sites are lying or embellishing their profiles to make them more appealing. This may be true to a certain extent, but remember that these Muslims want to meet other Muslims for possible marriage, they would be deceiving themselves if they were to embellish their profiles.<br /><br />Are 'matrimonial sites' permitted in Islam? Casual dating without the purpose for marriage is not permitted in Islam. Online matrimonial sites allow the users to speak with other members without having to go out with them. Parents can always play an active role in the search online too.<br /><br />Online Matchmaking removes the awkwardness of meeting other single Muslims. No feelings are hurt and no one has traveled many miles to meet. There is an understanding that is shared on these Muslim matrimonial sites that is not felt on other dating sites. As an Islamic matrimonial site it is instantly viewed as a site where being a Muslim is the first criteria for all.<br /><br />Living in a modern society where an estimated 50% of all marriages are destined to end in divorce, surely any advantages that can help us find a life long match is worth considering. There is no longer a need for Muslims to feel that only the desperate use Muslim Matrimonial sites as these sites have proved themselves to be very appealing to Muslims from all around the world.<br /><br />Shazia Shah has been a driving force behind the Free Muslim Dating website Muslim Engagement and Free Muslim matrimonial website Unattached Muslims, with Muslim Members from all over the UK<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="87ce066061fdb4132a94018894715d16" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>The History of the Abaya<br /><br />The traditional abaya is a plain black robe worn by Muslim women to cover their regular clothing, It could be described as a long-sleeve robe-like dress and it is the traditional form of dress for many countries of the Arabian peninsula including Saudi Arabia and United Arab Emirates. In Iran the abaya is referred to as a chador and in South Asia a burqa.<br /><br />The abaya covers the whole body except the face, feet, and hands. It can be worn with the niqab, a face veil covering all but the eyes.<br /><br />The origins of the abaya are vague. Some think that it existed as long as 4 000 years ago in the ancient civilizations of Mesopotamia and when Islam arose in the seventh century C.E., the religion absorbed local veiling practices into its culture, probably due to the dressing traditions of the women of Arab Jahiliya.<br /><br />In those days women wore dresses that revealed their necks, chests, even breasts as well as other parts of their bodies. They also drew their veils backwards while leaving the front parts wide open (understandable in the crushing desert heat). Consequently, when Islam arrived, they were ordered to draw their veils forward to cover their chest and to protect women from acts of disrespect.<br /><br />Some think that the idea of 'the covering' was more about class than it was about religion. In pre-Islam urban centers of the Arabian Peninsula veiling was seen as a sign of privilege and a luxury afforded to women who didn't have to work. They were distinguished from slave girls and prostitutes, who were not allowed to veil or cover, and nomadic and rural women too busy working to be bothered with something so impractical as a face veil and extra layer of clothing.<br /><br />Source: Laura of Arabia, women24.com<br /><br />Today, the strictest interpretations of Islamic Shari'a law dictate that Muslim women should wear full body coverings in front of any man they could theoretically marry. This means that it is not obligatory in the company of father, brothers, grandfathers, uncles or young children and does not need to be worn in front of other Muslim women.<br /><br />Abayas come in a multiplicity of types and design, and different styles and colours are favoured by women from particular regions according to specific religious and cultural interpretations.<br /><br />A Head abaya rests on top of the head and extends below the ankles, ensuring that a women's body stays completely hidden.<br />    Black abayas are more commonly worn in Middle Eastern countries, especially Saudi-Arabia, Kuwait and Qatar.<br />    White abayas are populary worn in Far Eastern Muslim countries.<br />    Coloured and embroidered abayas are becoming increasingly popular in Jordan, western countries and now also in Middle Eastern countries too. <br /><br />Although black is the preferred colour in some countries Muslim women can generally wear whatever color they like as long as it does not generate unnecessary attention. For this reason earth-tones are popular choices.<br /><br />Muslim women often wear designer labels underneath their outer garments and increasingly they want to wear fashionable outerwear too. Fashion designers are waking up to this and specialised stores, websites and fashion shows are springing up, top European fashion labels including John Galliano and Blumarine have recently showcased models wearing couture abayas.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1fa47b3705536ca06ed9e384f296861" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a><br /><br />How to Wear a Hijab Properly<br /><br />There are many different ways to wear a Hijab properly. When it comes to Islamic clothing, though, a lot of modernization has taken place; there are essentially five styles to wear the Hijab and these are underlined below.<br /><br />First style<br /><br />In this technique of wearing the hijab, a pashmina shawl is placed over the head with one side shorter than the other side. Then, using a safety pin, the two edges are folded back behind the neck and pinned together. When pinning, the scarf front should look smooth and neat. Then, take the longer scarf edge and bring it around under the chin and take the scarf all the way to the other end. The hijab should fall evenly around your shoulders and there must be no creases on the front portion of the scarf. Once the placement is satisfactory, you should pin the other edge of the hijab to the portion around under the neck.<br /><br />Second style<br /><br />In this technique, the method of wearing the hijab is the same as the first style. However the difference is that in here, the finish is smoother and neater in appearance. The hijab front portion is pinned onto the back of the person's head instead of in the front as in the first method.<br /><br />Third style<br /><br />This is a very popular and smart style of wearing the hijab. These days there is a wide range of oblong hijabs available at various stores selling wholesale Islamic clothing. You can use such hijabs or a scarf in this third style. In this method, place the Pashmina shawl on the head with one side long and other short. Fold the scarf behind the head and pin the two edges at the nape of your neck behind the head. As in the earlier methods, ensure the hijab front is smooth with no creases. Take the longer scarf edge and bring it around under the chin all the way to the other side. You can now pin the hijab under your ear or on the head side as per your individual preference. You can also pin the hijab at the back of the head for a cleaner and smarter appearance.<br /><br />Mona Hijab<br /><br />This is a new kind of hijab style, which is only available online. Thus, the best place to get such hijabs would be in online shops which specialize in wholesale Islamic clothing. This is a single-piece hijab comprising of underscarf with stretch material and a scarf attached to it. Once you place the underscarf on the head, the attached hijab will fall smoothly and naturally around the head so you only have to wrap it once and pin it on the front or back of the head.<br /><br />Turban styled<br /><br />This is a very new design when it comes to wearing hijabs. In these exclusive designs, the Kuwaiti Amira is a good choice. In such a style of wearing hijab, the person has to tie the hijab ends on the back of the head and bring the edges again to the front, fold the sides and swing all around the head. All excess parts of the scarf have to be tied underneath or the other end can be tucked at the side.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7330cb09d7803ae6969f818aa84c2f00" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>Here is a guide on how you want to properly accentuate using one of the most diverse accessories in the planet.<br /><br />Scarfs are a great thing to purchase because they are one of those things that never go out of style no matter how different trends seem to change. They allow you to get new wardrobe without having to buy new clothes. These are high quality accessories that should be found in your closet along with ties and bows. This way, you don't have to spend your savings on every fad.<br /><br />When you are considering color, you should think of how it will compliment your skin tone. If you have a light complexion it wouldn't be wise to buy something too bright. Same thing goes if you have a darker complexion. Also, it has to go well with your coat or jacket. At first, it'll be difficult to find a color to balance out the two, but you'll eventually find one.<br /><br />Think about opposites when matching your coat with scarfs. The coarser and thicker the coat, the finer or thinner the math should be, vice-versa. It is just a matter of how you mix and match it. For example, a black one would go well with a brown coat. Or a black leather jacket with a thick white one. Both looks are great for males and females.<br /><br />This tip is for the ones who love to wear suits. The rare three piece suit which has recently been popularized, works really well with scarf. A trench coat on top of a cashmere-made accessory makes a man look really good and made up. Pair a black suit with green one, blue suit with red one, and a gray suit with blue one.<br /><br />If you are the type of person who enjoys the simplicity of casual clothes then a short or medium piece is the one for you. There's nothing like seeing a man/woman walking down the street wearing jeans, a leather jacket and triangle-folded scarfs wrapped around their neck. Women can pull off wearing bold colors that are brighter, while men may want to wear more subdued colors.<br /><br />Come winter time, hand knitted sweaters and thick jackets are the basis on which type you'd want to match it with. The main reason people wear these clothes are to keep their body temperate, but if you look hard enough you'll find some products with the same quality for winter but with fantastic designs. What better way to get warm than with a designer made scarf.<br /><br />When it comes to which style you want to purchase that all depends on you. There is a wide selection of styles on which you can choose from. You can retro and buy the 80's or 70's items or go for a more formal one like a Pashmina. Make sure that what you purchase is one you'd like to wear for more than one occasion.<br /><br />Scarfs are made to enhance the beauty that each person possess, so don't be afraid to try out new things even if you're the only one who seems to be doing it. Creativity needs to be played out whenever you dress, especially when you're dealing with designs and colors as each one has something to offer. Go and find out which you like best that'll best suit your disposition and lifestyle.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="216e3130987e6de071ce8fa285d859cd" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>Jilbabs are a wonderful blend of fashion and modesty for Muslim sisters. All over the world Muslim women are donning them to ascertain their own identity. They come in a variety of colors with intricate embroideries, laces and trimmings suitable for various events. Even the fabric used in their making can be light and breezy cotton apt for hot weather, or smooth and elegant chiffons and silks appropriate for a formal gathering. These graceful articles of clothing are also available in a large range of colors and designs; for day-wear, you can choose lighter shades in beige, off- white, sky blue or olive green, whereas for night-wear, black, chocolate brown or navy blue would be an ideal choice.<br /><br />Jilbabs will not only protect and cover you according to the decorum of Islam; they will also help you establish your femininity and beauty in a trendy manner. You do not have to appear dowdy wearing them as they can be made to vary in their stitching to suit your figure. A slim figure can be adorned with pleats and gathers and kimono-style very loose sleeves, while a heavyset built can be given a sleeker look with a front open garment with panels. Necklines too dictate fashion and form and help in getting the look you prefer; you can definitely choose your own style and get these loosely-fitted outer clothes with bans, Vs or boat neckline.<br /><br />Simplicity is most appropriate when dressing for work or attending other daily chores; here your selection of jilbabs should be plain ones with simple cuts and in neutral colors; no fancy lace or frill. Wrinkle-free, easy to wash fabric like cotton or denim can be used to make them. Printed fabric too can be used to make daily wear jilbabs; stripes, polka dots, tiger prints can be utilized creatively to produce attractive pieces. When getting ready for a wedding or a party, you can opt for silks and chiffons in colors of your preference. Sequins and stones weaved into elaborate embroidered patterns will make dazzling jilbabs; frills, laces and ribbons can further enhance the beauty of your garment.<br /><br />Reversible jilbabs also look good and are a handy and useful addition to your wardrobe. The two colors used in making them not only complement each other but also extend your options in wearing them going well with your mood, time of the day and the occasion. Pick up jilbabs that compliment your figure and style, slip into one and you are ready for any occasion.<br /><br />Sohail Khan works for Islamic Impressions which specializes in retail and wholesale products for the Islamic market and stock a wide range of jilbabs and abayas for the discerning Muslim woman.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dbe6bb42ecdfad745096db1ea5663d0e" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>How many of you have shopped at that big box store, purchased a shirt or some other item of kids clothing only to see the hem or other stitching start to unravel before it's even washed the first time?<br /><br />Or, perhaps you've purchased clothes that have buttons - and the button thread doesn't even have a knot in it, so the minute you tug at that stray thread, the whole button pops off (that's my personal pet peeve).<br /><br />Now that's &quot;cheap.&quot; As in &quot;cheaply made.&quot;<br /><br />I know... I know... you don't want to use the word &quot;cheap&quot; when you're looking for your children's clothes. No one wants to appear cheap. But, what is a parent to do? Of course all parents would love to drape their children in the most beautiful of designer kids clothes, but let's face it. The reality is that today's parents are usually looking for bargains. Cheap kids clothes.<br /><br />Because the fact of the matter is a lot of parents are feeling... well... a bit &quot;cheap&quot; these days. But, they don't necessarily want to shop at that large well-known box store that I don't need to name. And I don't blame them.<br /><br />So here is a quick tip for all you parents who are looking for cheap kids clothes! Let's start with some of the more obvious suggestions like &quot;shop at yard sales&quot; or &quot;shop at thrift or consignment stores.&quot; All cities have them, and a lot of people are selling their kids' clothing for rock-bottom prices. A lot of these clothes are barely worn since kids grow so fast.<br /><br />But, rather than waste hours chasing down just any yard sale, shop smarter. Here's an example: Get on CraigsList in your area and find the &quot;For Sale&quot; section of the page. Scroll down, and click on the &quot;Garage Sale&quot; tab. However; instead of wildly writing down every yard sale you see listed, go to the top of the page, and in the little search window, pop in the term &quot;clothes&quot; or &quot;kids clothes.&quot; You will very quickly narrow down your choices.<br /><br />For example, using the strategy I just discussed, I went to the New York City section of CraigsList, and clicked on the &quot;garage sales&quot; tab. I immediately saw numerous pages of listings. Who wants to plow through that many listings? So, I then typed &quot;Clothes&quot; in the search bar at the top of the page, and the results were filtered to 99. I then tried &quot;kids clothes&quot; in the tab, and wound up with 12 listings. Isn't that a lot easier to sift through?<br /><br />But don't stop there! Under the same &quot;For Sale&quot; heading of the page, you'll see the &quot;clothes &amp; accessories&quot; tab (it is abbreviated &quot;clothes&amp;acc&quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />. Once you click on that tab, you'll wind up with a whole new set of options. Again, you'll likely be faced with numerous pages (especially if you live in a large city). Using the New York City example again, I typed in &quot;kids clothes&quot; which filtered all but 11 listings.<br /><br />Also try the &quot;household&quot; section since people will list kids clothes there as well. Be creative!<br /><br />As a quick word of caution, be prudent when responding to ads on line. Be careful about giving out your contact information. And, no one will know you were &quot;feeling cheap!&quot;<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3430b5b206236fe821a416934712dcd3" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>However, here are some helpful tips that will guide you while buying your kids' clothes.<br /><br />It's essential to buy items, which will make the child feel comfortable. Don't go for the clothes, which will stick tight to the body. Purchase the one's that have wide neck and are made up of stretchable material so that the child doesn't have difficulty in putting on and taking off the dress.<br /><br />The fabric that you opt for your kids should make your little one feel comfortable. Children's clothes are made up of various fabrics ranging from lace to tulle and satin to cotton. However, soft cottons are the most preferred ones for all the seasons, especially the summers. Make sure your kid wears fleece or woolen clothes in winter.<br /><br />Buying right size kids' clothes is very important. Don't opt for clothes that are too small or too large. Buying small size clothes may create breathing problems for your child; buying clothes, which are large, put your kids in danger of getting hurt by stumbling.<br /><br />Avoid buying children's clothing with buttons and opt for zippers. Children generally have a tendency to swallow buttons. Don't even opt for clothes, which have ties. Ensure that the clothes are easily washable.<br /><br />While buying your kids clothing, keep the costs low. Purchase clothes during off-season sales because it is during this time that the stores offer highest discounts. You can also go for mix and match clothes to save some pounds. The best way of saving money without compromising on the design and the quality is by visiting online stores to shop for your kids' clothes.<br /><br />With the growth of kids' clothing industry, the fashion designers are dedicated to work exclusively on designing outfits for toddlers and teenagers. The clothing stores and the supermarkets are being filled up with colorful and ingenious clothing items for young ones. Lots of shops are specializing in selling only kids wear.<br /><br />In contract to the children's clothes that were designed few decades back, the children's clothes of the present days are a lot more stylish and appealing. Ranging from a few month's old girl's dress and a few month's old boy's suit to superhero outfits and mix and match clothing's, nowadays all kinds of kids wear are manufactured just to satisfy the desires and needs of the young population.<br /><br />There are a number of online clothing websites that specializes in kids clothing. They offer fashionable kids wear at affordable prices. Consider few things before choosing the online clothing website for buying the kids clothing.<br /><br />Check out the website's credibility. Make sure that the site is secure because while purchasing online you need to pay money through the credit card. Take a quick look in the feedback section to understand the viewpoints of the customers. Finally, while placing the order online, note the transaction number and the confirmation number that's been provided. These numbers help to trace the order and check out the status from time to time.<br /><br />Are you looking for an online store for kids' clothes? Visit thecarouselhalifax.com to get the most stylish and attractive kids wear for your little one. Clothes of different brands are available at the right price at The Carousel Halifax<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5d7518340818a606fe466e22f4adaefa" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>In fact, the shirts Mandela proudly sports have their origins halfway across the world, on the islands of the Malay archipelago, where the cloth is known as batik. The tradition of producing batik cloth was brought to South Africa by Javanese laborers forcibly transported by the Dutch East India Company to the Western Cape. The Madiba shirt (named after Mandela's clan name) adapts traditional batik using African colors and motifs and demonstrates its versatility and widespread appeal.<br /><br />Batik is probably the most famous of the resist methods of dyeing cloth. Resist dyeing involves applying a substance that stops dye from reaching certain parts of the fabric in order to create a pattern. This method can use wax (as in Javanese batik), rice paste (Japanese tsutsugaki) or can tie off a section of the fabric ('tie-dye' or Indian bandhani). In most parts of South-East Asia, the wax is applied using a copper spout allowing the craftsman to create intricate patterns and differing width of line. New areas of wax can be applied and the cloth which is usually cotton or silk, can be re-dyed allowing for greater complexity in design and color. After the design and coloration are finished the wax is removed and the cloth is ready for use. These traditional methods of creating batik are extremely time-consuming and require a high level of skill so various labor-saving devices have been introduced to the process including brushes for the wax and copper stamps that apply the wax. Any hand-produced batik takes a long time and can be very costly, so much of modern batik cloth is in fact batik print, retaining the patterns and colors of batik but without using the wax dying technique.<br /><br />There are batik making traditions in many parts of South-East Asia, particularly in Indonesia and Malaysia, each with varying designs, colors, and cultural influence. Perhaps the most famous and influential however is the batik of Java and specifically that originating in the royal cities of Yogyakarta and Solo. This batik is often produced in the traditional colors of black, brown, indigo and dark yellow, uses patterns representing folklore, tradition, and nature, and is of huge cultural importance to the Javanese. Batik cloth is worn at weddings, funerals, to carry babies, and is integral to Javanese cultural traditions such as dancing and puppetry. The vital influence batik has on the cultural life of Indonesia has been recognized by UNESCO which in 2009 declared Indonesian batik as part of the Intangible Cultural Heritage of Humanity: a living, cultural tradition, closely linked with the local community. UNESCO acknowledges Indonesian batik as a craft '...intertwined with the cultural identity of the Indonesian people and, through the symbolic meaning of its colors and designs, expresses their creativity and spirituality.' (Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.unesco.org%2Fculture"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.unesco.org/culture</a> )<br /><br />In modern-day Indonesia, batik has become a stylish and popular part of cultural life, vital to the creative economy, an important draw for tourists, and a key aspect of national identity. The flight attendants for Indonesia's national airline Garuda wear batik print as part of their uniform, as do those from the Singaporean and Malaysian national carriers. It is increasingly popular worldwide too, and is used for furnishing, decorative purposes, tablecloths, and as a medium for painting and other artworks.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3c7d9780a53495ca12aeb2095c1a16b1" url=""><![CDATA[Baju Muslim | Busana Muslim | Jilbab<br/><br/>The sheath dress has long been a staple in the closets and wardrobes of women everywhere. Many have come to love the body hugging silouhette so much that they've acquired quite a collection. These smart dressed women know that the sheath is the one dress that will take them anywhere they need to go and will have them looking and feeling stunning when they get there.<br /><br />Along with a figure and curve enhancing cut, are some other fabulous features that make women love the sheath such as: Versatility - whether it's an afternoon of strolling through downtown for shopping, snacking and chatting with friends or a formal evening event, the sheath dress is the perfect option. They're available in so many different fabrics, necklines and hemlines that there's a sheath dress for absolutely every occasion.<br /><br />Details - The devil might in the details but when it comes to this must have fashion piece, the details are what makes each one different from the next. With buttons, ruffles, pearls, crystals, sequins and countless other design features, it's no wonder a woman could have several sheath dresses in her closet without any single one looking anything like another. For this reason, it's so easy to always have something to wear! Along with those all important little details are the countless patterns and prints to choose from. Spring, summer, winter or fall - there's a color, pattern, cut and perfectly detailed sheath dress to take you through the entire year of fashion.<br /><br />Budget - Here's the best thing of all about the sheath dress - you don't have to be rich to own one. The cut is available in budget ranges from as low as $20 on up to the thousands of dollars. It all depends on the brand, designer and of course fabric. But even if your sheath dress only cost you $30, it's such a classic and sophisticated design that no one will ever know! Wear it with a great pair of strappy heels and a fabulous handbag and a few key pieces of jewelry and for as little as $100 you can look like a million bucks!<br /><br />Pair your sheath dress with all of your feminine favorites such as scarves, shawls, waist enhancing belts and any height heel from flats to stilettos. It's versatility and chic design makes it the perfect garment to go with all kinds of fantastic fun to wear accessories.<br /><br />When looking for sheath dresses, be sure to visit the sheath dress guide for lots of great information!<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3NpcmxlbmdrYXAubmV0Lw__" target="_blank">busana muslim, baju muslim, jilbab, mukena, baju koko, gamis</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>