<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="18">
		<document id="be6561111ee37928f9cdaef475c03522" url=""><![CDATA[At Rainbow's End<br/><br/>At Rainbow's End I'll find her
<br />She'll be there waiting for me
<br />Don't ask who she is 'cos I don't know
<br />But I'm sure she'll be there
<br /><br />At Rainbow's End I'll see her
<br />She'll be there smiling at me
<br />Her hair'll be long, her smile'll be pure
<br />It's not much to ask, to be sure
<br /><br />At Rainbow's End I'll touch her
<br />And feel her sweet caress
<br />A touch so soft to make angels weep
<br />If you get there first, tell her I'll be late
<br /><br />At Rainbow's End I'll talk to her
<br />You know, she'll talk to me
<br />Her voice so sweet and innocent
<br />A man I may be but still I'll cry
<br /><br />At Rainbow's End I'll kill her
<br />A fate she deserves I'm sure
<br />A being so pure, so good, so right
<br />Cannot be allowed to exist
<br /><br />At Rainbow's End it's lonely
<br />Here I am again on my own
<br />Perhaps I brought it upon myself
<br />Given the choice, I'd repeat
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7416f6ce314650b374c9d03cc8d3683b" url=""><![CDATA[Forever Isn't Such a Long Time<br/><br/>Forever isn't such a long time
<br />If that time is spent with you
<br />Seconds turn to minutes and those minutes to hours
<br />Before I know it, we're outta' time
<br /><br />Forever isn't such a long time
<br />Or so I'm told
<br />Each time we say goodbye I see that single tear in your eye
<br />It's like you cry until you're found
<br /><br />Forever isn't such a long time
<br />Unless we're talking death
<br />Finally feeling that sweet embrace
<br />Only able to imagine the look upon your face
<br /><br />Forever isn't such a long time
<br />But you gotta' spend it alone
<br />It sounds cruel I know and to be fair it probably is
<br />I guess that's just the way it goes
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cdbb130c147a83c73220bc523b8c6cf7" url=""><![CDATA[Pills, Weed, and Coke<br/><br/>Forget your pills, your weed and your coke
<br />There's nought I like better than having a smoke
<br />Cigarette or cigar, I really don't mind
<br />Nothing else on me will you find
<br /><br />Forget your pills, your weed and your coke
<br />There's nought I like better than having a smoke
<br />I swear it's the truth, and it's not like you'll listen
<br />There's worse things believe me, you don't know what you're missin'
<br /><br />Forget your pills, your weed and your coke
<br />There's nought I like better than having a smoke
<br />In the morning, a cigarette and a mug of sweet coffee
<br />Sets me up just right for what the day offers
<br /><br />Forget your pills, your weed and your coke
<br />There's nought I like better than having a smoke
<br />I know it's a bad habit, I know the risks
<br />But what's the point of life, if not to enjoy it?
<br /><br />So you can keep your pills, your weed and your coke
<br />'Cos there's nought I like better than having a smoke
<br />Cigarette or cigar, I really don't mind
<br />Only one thing that matters; the choice is mine
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4af0a454486328bf32d9fc6aef77fba8" url=""><![CDATA[The Vampirate<br/><br/>Lost at sea without a map
<br />Just the stars as yer guide
<br />Ye come across a body afloat
<br />The driftwood t'keep 'im alive
<br /><br />Ye take 'im in the goodness o' yer heart
<br />Shines thru' for all t'see
<br />An act o' kindess ye'll live t'regret
<br />To be sure, yer gonna' die
<br /><br />He starts with those ye'll not notice
<br />The kitchen boy and 'is dog
<br />Pretty soon he'll think bigger
<br />An' ye'll be 'is final meal
<br /><br />Ain't a thing ye can do about it
<br />'Cos ye know not what demon ye face
<br />Soon ye'll be just the same as he
<br />A vampirate; cursed for eternity
<br /><br />Cursed to sail the seven seas
<br />To only make berth at night
<br />Ye'll feast on the blood of innocents
<br />An' make merry as ye do
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="462b6a079b0e46027a6b4dae9ab7a73f" url=""><![CDATA[My links<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zbWFzaHdvcmRzLmNvbS9wcm9maWxlL3ZpZXcvQW5ndXNFY3JpdmFpbg__" target="_blank">Smashwords - About Daniel Greathead, author of 'Love: Blood: Death: Revenge'</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N0b3Jlcy5sdWx1LmNvbS9Qcm9qZWN0X1RlcnJvcg__" target="_blank">Daniel Greathead's Storefront - Lulu.com</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3V0dWJlLmNvbS91c2VyL0RlYXRoUmFnZVJhZGlvP2ZlYXR1cmU9bWhlZQ__" target="_blank">DeathRageRadio</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXR0cGFkLmNvbS91c2VyL0FuZ3VzRWNyaXZhaW4_" target="_blank">AngusEcrivain - Wattpad</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6667539f39333339a46e7714601d2383" url=""><![CDATA[Two Mums<br/><br/>My Mum used to be my Dad
<br />And when she gets home late from work it's not so bad as
<br />It would be if she was still a man
<br />She had his dick cut off and her lips implanted
<br />Up until that point she was definitely a man but
<br />Now I got two Mums and they eat each other all the time
<br /><br />Two Mums
<br />Two Mums
<br />Lick her out
<br />Lick her out
<br />Two Mums
<br />Two Mums
<br />Lick her out
<br /><br />After the operation
<br />She came home to me
<br />I wondered what happened to her
<br />Weenie...
<br /><br />There's a moral to this story and I know you want to hear it
<br />Doesn't matter if you don't understand it
<br />He went through that pain so she could have good times
<br />It's like Romeo and Juliet without romance or killing
<br />This story's sick and it doesn't have a meaning
<br />How d'you know your Mum's not your Dad? It could happen to you
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2941bda26c55eecc4ee360651c26284f" url=""><![CDATA[That's What She Said<br/><br/>That's what she said
<br />Chained to the iron bed
<br />Calling out my name
<br /><br />Yesterday you were pretty
<br />Now? I feel shitty
<br />I think you know who's to blame
<br /><br />That's what she said
<br />Gonna' dye your hair red
<br />Blood red; come and see
<br /><br />So come and get your fill
<br />Should you take the blue pill?
<br />C'mon... what's it to be?
<br /><br />Lost in a world of my own creation
<br />Shouting out across the nation
<br /><br />But I don't think there's anyone home
<br />I'm left here on my own
<br /><br />That's what she said
<br />Gonna' wind up dead
<br />I guess that awaits us all
<br /><br />Cryin' ain't a sin
<br />It's like pissin' in the wind
<br />Futile, after all
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="993b5991440a1694cf99e9998d7ba560" url=""><![CDATA[The Last Vampire<br/><br/>As he stared at the thick oak door, the light that filtered through around it's edges stung his aged eyes. It was late in the evening and soon night would fall. He longed for the darkness and the sanctity it offered for he was a vampire, the last of his kind. He had lived for thousands of years and for the majority of that time he and his kind had been worshipped but the last four hundred years had seen every other of his race hunted and killed.
<br />	His body was not what it used to be. His skin was leathery in both appearance and feel, and it hung from his weak, brittle bones. His eyes were almost hollow, sunk into his skull so deep that it was a wonder he could see. The skin around his eyes, nose, and mouth was sore, red in colour.
<br /><br />Some time later when darkness had fallen, he struggled to open the heavy door, and made his way outside. He was in a cemetery, and the building in which he had taken refuge was an old outhouse on the church grounds. He would not normally have visited such a place because churches and the like made him nervous, uncomfortable almost, as if he had an itch that no matter how hard he tried, he simply could not scratch.
<br />	There was a reason for his being there. He was waiting for someone.  Back when he was human, he had a brother. He had long ago lost all feelings of family and love, but upon his turning his brother had made him a solemn promise, one that each and everyone of his descendants had been raised to honour. That promise was simple. Each first born child would be fed to him providing that child was male, and he would drain their blood yet in every generation the first born child had been female, until now.
<br />	Finally there was a first born male child, and he was going to savour every drop that child's blood as if his very life depended upon it.
<br />	What he did not know but would soon discover, is that once he drank from the child, it would give him strength and life anew. He would regain his long-absent youth and thus be able to create more of his kind, and once again the vampire race would assume its rightful place, as deities.
<br />	He heard someone approaching, footsteps crunching upon the gravel of the path that ran through the cemetery, and he sniffed hungrily at the air. He picked up the scent of a man, thirty-eight years old, and the newborn male that he cradled in his arms, protecting the child from the chill night air.
<br />	He made his way slowly to the end of the path and waited. The man was hesitant, hardly surprising under the circumstances. He held out an arm and beckoned to the man, that simple act causing him great pain, and the man approached, still clutching the child tightly.
<br />	“Give... the boy... to... me...” it had been years since he had last spoken, decades in fact, and his voice was little more than  a hoarse whisper. Reluctantly the man held the child towards him, as if his actions were not his own. “Go...” he hissed as he took the child from his unresisting grasp. Looking into the man's eyes he saw sadness and fear, and both emotions stirred something inside of him, something he had not felt for a long time; lust for the kill.
<br />	With a final, longing glance at his child, the man turned and ran, and he did not stop. The man gone he looked down at the child and smiled. The child did not appear to be afraid, in fact he smiled back.
<br />	He tilted the child's head gently to the side and lowered his mouth to the exposed skin of the boy's neck, and breathed deeply the sweet aroma of untainted innocence before he bit into the skin, his pointed teeth easily breaching the meagre defences offered by the child's epidermis.
<br />	Fresh blood flowed into his mouth, coating his tongue and throat as he gulped it down eagerly. It had been an extremely long time since he had fed upon a human, and never one so young. The blood offered him new life, and he welcomed it. The child was not yet half-drained and already he could feel the benefit.
<br />	He drank yet more of the child's blood, until the body was dry. During the ordeal the child had not made a sound, as if he knew that with his death, a once great and powerful race would be so again.
<br />	He dropped the lifeless body to the floor as the blood coursed it's way around his body, giving him strength and clarity. He raised his head to the stars and let out a scream, primal in origin, a scream that had been brewing for hundreds of years.
<br />	The scream subsided and he lowered his head. The transformation was complete, and once again he was youthful in appearance, and he felt incredible. Dawn was but a few minutes away and he did not have time to find anywhere else to take refuge during daylight hours, so he picked up the child's corpse and with more assurance and confidence then he had felt in centuries, he stalked back to the outhouse and entered, closing the door gently behind him. He threw the tiny body to the floor where it landed awkwardly.
<br />	For the daylight hours he would rest, and head out at dusk to feed and begin the long but worthy process of re-birthing his kind for he was the last vampire but soon, that would change.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="853c43b7e612c4ccea9b2f667615b2a5" url=""><![CDATA[One Last Time<br/><br/>You come in you screw up you scream wreck the party
<br />Time takes it's toll all the time
<br />Your life is all f*cked up and I get the blame but
<br />I can't get into your head
<br />You try to have fun with what may become
<br />You make yourself feel warm inside
<br />When all's said and done then whatever is left
<br />F*cks the rest of us up way too much
<br /><br />Can't you wait a little bit longer
<br />Why can't you give something back
<br />You said I'm running outta' chances
<br />So tell your story one last time
<br /><br />Your head isn't messed up you just like to think it is
<br />So there's an excuse to behave as you do
<br />What dreams may come when you're laying in wait to see
<br />A big red fat man with wings
<br />You say you can't see you'll never be me
<br />I hope that you speak the truth
<br />Does it hurt every day won't the pain go away
<br />Like a battering ram through your skull
<br /><br />You f*cked me over and over again
<br />You wanted me to believe in you
<br />You f*cked me over and over again
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="daa8aea66cf4f0f01000acb692a9e2b7" url=""><![CDATA[Don't Eat the Peanuts - A SurprisePunk/PeanutPunk Poem<br/><br/>&quot;Don't eat the peanuts!&quot; She cried out loud
<br /><br />As I made my way towards her, pushing through the crowd
<br /><br />Too late was her warning as I'd already placed
<br /><br />My hand in the bowl, and brought salty snacks to my face
<br /><br />It was only then I noticed she was not of the norm
<br /><br />From her cheeks grew whiskers, a downy fur adorned
<br /><br />Every inch of her body and from the top of her head grew ears
<br /><br />As she changed before my very eyes, I cowered back in fear
<br /><br />I raised my hand to shield my eyes, but stared at it aghast
<br /><br />As my bones began to break through skin, someone somewhere laughed
<br /><br />I whipped my head around to see who'd dared to make a sound
<br /><br />Unable to control the anger inside, I waited for him to sit down
<br /><br />&quot;What the f*ck is wrong with me?&quot; I turned to ask at the bar
<br /><br />&quot;No need for language like that mate, I can have you barred!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Just tell me what I need to know.&quot; I said as calmly as I could
<br /><br />&quot;You're mutating mate,&quot; the guy replied. &quot;Toxic waste... it's all good!&quot;
<br /><br />So there I was a mutant freak, surrounded by my kind
<br /><br />Unable to leave but why would I want to, unless I was out of my mind
<br /><br />But if you find yourself alone, if you've failed to make the cut
<br /><br />Come on down we'll welcome you, but you might want to avoid the nuts
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d3eb8064944eca53ae06dd4e618a4d5f" url=""><![CDATA[Job Done - A Nanopunk Poem<br/><br/>She strode into the room, everybody stared
<br />Without exception not a single person dared
<br />To move, for fear of what she'd do
<br />She's been here before y'see, and the carpet was new.
<br /><br />She flung her jacket high, upon the hook it fell
<br />Her arms were of metal, ready to raise Hell
<br /><br />She scanned the room quickly, and soon located her target
<br />She raised her right arm and pointed, the man he was a Sergeant
<br />In the Space Corps, an evil man. She knew he must be deleted
<br />And she was not going to rest until he had been defeated
<br /><br />She fired, he ducked, she missed, and cursed beneath her breath
<br />&quot;I'll get you, you bastard!&quot; She cried. &quot;This day is the day of your death.&quot;
<br />&quot;Is that what you think?&quot; He shouted over the ruckus
<br />He pulled his own gun on her, and managed to get a shot off
<br /><br />Taking cover behind an upturned table, she carefully took aim
<br />Her intention was to kill the man, she'd not settle for the maim
<br />She waited 'til he had to reload, and then she stood up tall
<br />A single shot to the forehead...
<br /><br />Job done.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f262d267bb8b11dfc6ab961555ace93f" url=""><![CDATA[Half-Light I - Prologue<br/><br/>Year: 2217
<br /><br />Earth as we know it was dry, not just of water but of anything that could successfully sustain life. Global warming had been and gone, and was widely believed to have been a complete and total hoax. Midway through the 21st century the polar ice caps began to melt at an alarming rate due to the unexplained reversal of the planet's tides.
<br />	Global population had rocketed, and sat comfortably around the 10 billion mark, although no one dared to calculate an accurate figure. Food was scarce and this heralded the introduction of rationing, which of course sparked rioting.
<br />	The year 2058 marked the beginning of the British Civil War. The Scottish and Welsh nations turned on the English and the Irish. Car bombs were an hourly occurrence; it was like the 1970s all over again.
<br />	There were numerous attempts to bomb the English Houses of Parliament, but they always ended in failure. Three years later in the year 2061, the United States of America invaded the British Isles. Due to the Civil War, the invasion lasted only three weeks, and by the end America had control of the whole of Britain.
<br />	By the year 2072 a third of Earth’s lands had been swallowed by the ever hungry oceans. Fossil fuels had long run out and massive recycling plants were dotted all over the planet, producing fuel for equally massive power stations. The Global Council had little under a decade to decide a course of action; else all life would become extinct, that being one of the more conservative estimates.
<br />	Earth had become almost a dictatorship, as this was seen as the only way to maintain order. The President of the United States and Europe, Ms. Jenna Bush Jnr., had seized control of all major parliaments and had formed the Global Council. Crime was at an all time low, but with even a parking ticket landing you a life sentence in the newly opened 'Alcatraz III', a huge prison complex in what used to be Ecuador, this should not have come as a surprise. Everyone was scared but no one did anything about it. People went about their lives in abject misery, locked in an invisible cell to which there was no key.
<br />	Tests funded by the Global Council had proved beyond a shadow of a doubt that there was no way that mankind would survive if it was to remain inhabiting Earth. It quickly became apparent to pretty much everyone that the only viable option was to up sticks and leave but there proved to be a major stumbling block. Test after test had proved inconclusive as to whether or not there was another planet in our solar system that could sustain human life. This of course meant looking further a field.
<br />	Technology was capable of this; however with such a short time-scale, mankind, it seemed, was doomed.
<br />Every story needs a hero, and so up stepped an Englishman named Smith. He claimed to be the last direct descendant of a certain chap named Albert Einstein. No one knew if he was being truthful but at this point no one cared. Smith said that he had developed the technology for a craft to travel at two-thirds the speed of light.
<br />	The Global Council piled funding on him, stating that as far as he was concerned, they had a blank cheque and that no matter what the cost, they would see this project through. In any other circumstances, one could be considered foolish for putting all one's eggs in the one basket, but once in a while it pays off. In this case, it did.
<br />	By the year 2180, every man, woman and child had a boarding pass for one of these 'Super-Ships', known simply as 'Smiths'.
<br />	In true biblical style, a breeding pair of every single animal on Earth was also given passage.
<br />	Airports were turned into docking stations. The largest of these would hold anywhere up to a thousand Smiths, which in turn, would hold anything up to ten thousand passengers, dependent on size.
<br />	For weeks and weeks, Smiths were launched and sat patiently in orbit around Earth, and around its moon, waiting until all ships were off the ground. It took eighteen months but eventually, the last Smith left docking bay 7 at London Spaceport, and joined its sister ships in orbit. Two weeks later, Earth was just a distant memory.
<br />	And mankind survived.
<br />	Each Smith developed its own rules and regulations, its own personality if you will. Pretty soon, Smiths were defined in the same way that one might define a country, the only difference being they were encased in titanium shells.
<br />	Everything on a Smith was propelled by hydrogen, from its engines, to its oxygen regeneration unit, and its lights. This meant in theory that a Smith could travel through space indefinitely. With no friction to damage its exterior, providing there were no unexpected meteor showers, everything should remain intact.
<br />	There were some casualties of course. Not all of the Smiths had been built in the same place so shoddy workmanship was to be expected. However out of the millions of ships that left Earth, only twenty-five thousand or so didn't make it past the fifty year mark.
<br />	There was of course one problem, that is that no one knew where they were headed. The lead ship sent out scouter probes every six months in an attempt to find inhabitable planets but the result was always the same.
<br />	Every ten years, all Smiths would sit in orbit around a suitably sized planet, and Smith Captains would hold council. Captains were always put into office by vote and acted as Judge, Jury and Executioner for their respective Smith. Each Smith Captain would choose his or her own Smith Parliament, and they would aid him or her in making decisions.
<br />	It was however, during the thirteenth Smith Council, that news was received that would once again change everything forever. A suitable planet had been found. As time went on, it was soon realized that it was not just a suitable planet but a suitable system. A binary system with an estimated three hundred inhabitable planets, moons, and other interstellar bodies. This news was obviously received with much joy and celebrations by everyone.
<br />	Five generations of Mankind had called these 'Smiths' their home. Now, at last, that would no longer be the case.
<br />It would take twenty years to reach this new system.
<br />	This is now.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5220610fd6acf9f5be4a03b888d4667a" url=""><![CDATA[Death Becomes You<br/><br/>It is dawn.
<br /><br />You look to the horizon and see that the first sun is rising, straining to escape it's blanket of mist. Moments later the second sun appears and the two battle for superiority in the alien sky, as two Gladiators fighting for their survival.
<br /><br />But this is the last time you will see such a sight for in the middle distance a mushroom cloud erupts and you know that it is time to leave this, the mortal plane.
<br /><br />As the nuclear wind rushes towards you, destroying everything in it's path you realise something. In this moment for the first time in your sorry existence, you are truly happy; at peace.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="25cceb5b65bef0a8639ec1ff1cc8c29b" url=""><![CDATA[Your Clockwork Doll<br/><br/>Her hair pristine she stands atop
<br />A box decorated plainly
<br />Nothing to draw focus
<br />From her absolute beauty
<br /><br />Her dress it flows as she dances
<br />For you, such grace you've never seen
<br />Until the music stops...
<br /><br />Find the key upon her back
<br />Turn it seven times
<br />Hear the music start to play
<br />And let her dance again
<br /><br />You know she'll let you watch all day
<br />Never will she tire
<br />Your beautiful clockwork doll
<br />Dances for her master
<br /><br />&quot;Yeah, that's right baby,&quot;
<br />But she does not hear your words
<br />For she is nothing more than porcelain
<br />Forever beautiful, forever yours
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4fa094a3778878dc80e99059e16bddf0" url=""><![CDATA[My City, She Never Sleeps - A Dystopian SF Poem<br/><br/>My city she never sleeps
<br />Come night she's alive more than ever
<br />Factories fill the air with thick smoke
<br />To allow the priveledged masses to live
<br /><br />My city she never sleeps
<br />I drink alone at the bar
<br />With twenty other men and women
<br />All drinking alone as I
<br /><br />Somewhere in a penthouse suite
<br />Decisions are being made
<br />By those in power with more money than sense
<br />They don't care about us
<br /><br />The scanner atop the bar tells us police brutality is rife
<br />The Force the corporation's personal army
<br />We lonely drinkers share a glance
<br />We know something must be done
<br /><br />My city she never sleeps
<br />I crouch in wait for the sirens
<br />This time they're coming for a man whose only crime
<br />Is to do what he must to feed his family
<br /><br />They arrive, their weapons primed
<br />To take the man away
<br />I drop to the floor, take one then another
<br />Within minutes, five officers lay dead
<br /><br />The man he thanks me, insists he'll do anything
<br />To repay the debt but there's no need
<br />Into the night I vanish, my name but a whisper on the wind
<br />For my city, she never sleeps
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b14c402ecf714a99e200d572ef4a4214" url=""><![CDATA[Brand New Day - A GreenPunk Poem<br/><br/>The sun shines down its light the source
<br />Of power for many a thing
<br />The trains on the rails, the cars on the road
<br />The kareoke machine that enables me to sing
<br /><br />The river it flows, hard and fast
<br />Its current the generator
<br />Bringing life ot the factories that line its banks
<br />For Mother Nature, we love her
<br /><br />No longer do we rape our world
<br />Of here we take great care
<br />The end of mankinds reign of terror
<br />Ended at the Solar flare
<br /><br />The kick up the arse we needed
<br />To make a positive change
<br />To bring new life to the planet we call home
<br />A brand new start, a brand new day
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="adef871fcfd61f83bfa88c41a29cb634" url=""><![CDATA[Kill Him Dead<br/><br/>He sheathed his gun to raucous applause
<br />From those lining the dusty street
<br />He swaggered towards his fallen foe
<br />Spurs tinkled about his feet
<br />He nudged the dead man with the toe of his boot
<br />Not even so much as a whimper
<br />Raised his head to the sky and let out a cry
<br />&quot;F*ck yeah y'bastard, I killed yer.&quot;
<br /><br />The dead man you see had a few nasty traits
<br />Not least his attitude to the ladies
<br />A shuttle came down to ferry the dead he said
<br />&quot;Hope yer f*ckin' rot in Hades.&quot;
<br />The saloon doors swung open and out strode the Sheriff
<br />Pissed as a newt of course
<br />&quot;Good job Son, thanks t'ye for that,&quot;
<br />And then he failed to get on his horse
<br /><br />He took a stool at the bar as people gathered round
<br />Each man offered a whisky
<br />The women were a different matter all together
<br />Most of them wanted to get frisky
<br />&quot;Sorry girls, I'm movin' on,&quot;
<br />he said with a shake of his head
<br />&quot;There's a nasty fella on another planet,
<br />doin' sh*t means I'm gonna' kill him dead.&quot;
<br /><br />A tip of his Stetson, the flash of his smile
<br />He was gone like a whisper on the wind
<br />His ship a silhouette against the moon
<br />In search of those who sinned
<br />Come what may he'll hunt you down
<br />And trust, you don't want that
<br />The Reaper is he, a worthy foe
<br />With his black cowled robes and Stetson hat
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="706692714e6f7dca9906c393a2256581" url=""><![CDATA[The Flash of a Blade<br/><br/>The flash of a blade
<br />Is all you'll see
<br />Such is my skill and cunning
<br /><br />An enemy made
<br />A mistake you'll regret
<br />Looks like you think I'm kidding
<br /><br />Trust me my friend
<br />This is no joke
<br />I reckon you'd best start running
<br /><br />You'll meet your end
<br />At my hand believe
<br />Your corpse will soon be rotting
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>