<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="10">
		<document id="783975b89aa2048160e8dd7751479865" url=""><![CDATA[Help<br/><br/>The was an American Lady who wrote a blog on how a man should please women in their love nest.  It was a good blog and I would like to forward it to a friend does any one know who it was that wrote it so i can pass it on????
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="90cfcc47a9486b8a86c85c9a50c34d00" url=""><![CDATA[Guestbook<br/><br/>Everyone Please come and sign my guestbook, comment on my photo's <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="95491eba86dd1508258096d65de3d69f" url=""><![CDATA[Tips for the ladies in 2008<br/><br/>1. Aspire to be Barbie - the bitch has everything.
<br /><br />2. If the shoe fits - buy one in every colour.
<br /><br />3. Take life with a pinch of salt... a wedge of lime, and a shot of tequila.
<br /><br />4. In need of a support group? - Cocktail hour with the girls!
<br /><br />5. Go on the 30 day diet. (I'm on it and so far I've lost 15 days).
<br /><br />6. When life gets you down - just put on your big girl panties and deal with it.
<br /><br />7. Let your greatest fear be that there is no PMS and this is just my personality.
<br /><br />8. I know I'm in my own little world, but it's ok. They know me here.
<br /><br />9. Lead me not into temptation, I can find it myself.
<br /><br />10. Don't get your knickers in a knot, it solves nothing; and makes you walk funny.
<br /><br />11. When life gives you lemons in 2008 - turn it into lemonade then mix it with vodka.
<br /><br />12. Remember every good looking; sweet, single male is someone else's ex-boyfriend!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ee0450abb0e55fe4e9b7fb1132015a00" url=""><![CDATA[This is for People who would like to know more about ME/CFS<br/><br/>I am a surrefer of ME/CFS and want to spear the word about how ME/CFS afects us all.  So please follow the link below to watch a video on how ME/CFS affects our lives.
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sleepydust.net%2Fme-cfs-chronic-fatigue-syndrome-video.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3BYou"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.sleepydust.net/me-cfs-chronic-fatigue-syndrome-video.html&quot;&gt;You</a> can watch a free video about M.E. / Chronic Fatigue Syndrome here...&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42cbee76175eb61e5b254046a8aa3346" url=""><![CDATA[Hello<br/><br/>Hi Gus, I've never written a blog before so i thought i'd just say hello to every body out there and hope your all having a good day. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8fc94c0f92d6cdbedfc450acc046dc3d" url=""><![CDATA[Car Insurance!!!!<br/><br/>What a day it is today, I didn't realise it was the 1st March today &amp; another year has gone and I need to renew my car insurance what a pain in the ass that is!!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
<br />I hate having to get quote on the internet or phoning all the different companies.
<br /><br />And why is it that even though I've been driving for 15 year with out any accidents, claims etc I end up paying more than the year before?!!!!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a2a17a08e5bd2da13a966773c44eb659" url=""><![CDATA[Car Insurance!!!!<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sick.gif" alt=":)" /> I have just had a phone call from my current insurance company as I didn't realise that I didn't tell them about my dad having a motorway speeding fine &amp; 3 points, SO I HAVE JUST HAD TO PAY AN EXTRA £50 FOR LAST YEARS INSURANCE!!!!!!!!!!!!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="52f987badd14d204898c184096653f7e" url=""><![CDATA[Profound Proverbs<br/><br/>The woman who tells her age is either too young to have anything to lose or too old to have anything to gain.
<br /><br />Don't open a shop unless you like to smile. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Experience is a comb which nature gives to men when they are bald. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Your day goes the way the corners of your mouth turn. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Take time to smell the flowers.  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/flowers.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Friends are the families we make. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Age is an issue of mind over matter, If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8a36e33dfcc2061d99253799b8fa1eae" url=""><![CDATA[Question of the heart<br/><br/>Why is it that you find some one that you like and get on well with and could be Mr wright to find out that they are leaving the country?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="54380a02ff904122b0da72797a4e347f" url=""><![CDATA[Pain's of the heart or am i being stupid??<br/><br/>A close friend of mine went off travelling NZ in January 06.  He told me he loved me and was very upset at leaving me, but I knew that it was something that he had to do, as I couldn't stop him doing what he felt he needed to do as I'd had a similar experience myself (but only move from England to Scotland UK and he is just meant to be travelling).  Plus if you don't let someone do what they want to do it can cause all sorts of problems later in life and regrets.  I haven't heard anything from him since December 06 when we talked on Skype.  I log on to Skype a lot to see if we are ever on at the same time, and I have found out this week that he had deleted me as his friend I've also found out that he has been in touch with all of his mates over here.  It really hurts to find out that after being with him on and off for 6 years that he's just thrown me aside like this.  But I guess in the long run he will be the looser. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>