<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="347c0cbb8be00b25cc80fef92330af97" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair SEO Firm: Writing Blogs and Articles for Promoting<br/><br/>IT Chair SEO Los Angeles is the leading web designing and SEO Agency that is headquartered in Florida, USA. This SEO Firm has been an advocate in doing natural or organic search engine optimization that has matched the desire and exceeded the expectations of their clients worldwide. 
<br /><br />IT Chair SEO Firm strongly believes that the success of their client’s business does not have to require spending thousands of dollars just to get ranked and dominate in the search engines. 
<br /><br />IT Chair SEO Los Angeles is a great partner for promoting businesses whether local or international with a guaranteed increase on sales and return of investment.
<br /><br />From web designing to organic search engine optimization, IT Chair SEO Agency does it all for their client’s website. IT Chair SEO Los Angeles will definitely cater to their SEO needs.
<br /><br />One optimization technique done by IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO Firm</a>   in optimizing a website is by writing articles or blogs. Writing related content or blogs are great sources of information from a search engine point of view. 
<br /><br />The only difference between these two is that blogs are a means to convey messages across in a personal way. Articles on the other hand, are usually considered to be more informative and accurate where details of the businesses ‘products and services are concerned.
<br /><br />Looking into the value each one brings, blogs are timely, personal and have “inside point of view.” Blogs are usually updated on a frequent basis to keep the readers or followers informed on what is presently going on with the website.
<br /><br />To further re-enforce what the clients are selling, IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   uses articles to promote the products and services. Articles are more detailed, informative, and authoritative as well as market driven. Besides, articles get more exposure, since there are more chances of the article being seen by more people. This is because there are many sources on the internet on which articles can be submitted to.
<br /><br />For businesses in need of SEO promotional marketing, contact IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tY29uc3VsdGFudC8_" target="_blank">SEO Consultant</a>   now at (310) 927-2588 or visit &lt;a href=<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F%26gt%3Bhttp%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/&gt;http://www.itchair.com/&lt;/a&gt</a>;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c00768383a59851f6fcad6edd0e7a2de" url=""><![CDATA[Increasing Business Sales with SEO Los Angeles Marketing<br/><br/>Nowadays, internet technology is becoming an essential tool to increase business sales.  Whether it is a small or medium size business, business owners are now establishing its online presence to reach a wider range of potential customers to increase business sales in the fastest way.
<br /><br />Businesses are starting to realize that marketing the business through online SEO marketing and hiring SEO companies and SEO consultant are the best methods to follow the newest developments in search engine optimization and to rapidly increase business sales.
<br /><br />Presently, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO Agency</a>   IT Chair is expanding business markets, gaining new customers, opening communicating with existing customers, and improving business sales or ROI, making all these both possible and attainable for online businesses.
<br /><br />IT Chair has SEO Los Angeles based services that are effectively conducted by certified SEO professionals. These professionals can give your business the most successful strategies to optimize your website presence.
<br /><br />The SEO consultant of IT Chair can give you the most effective keywords to make your business website rank higher in the popular search engines such as Google, Yahoo and Bing.  
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   based services of IT Chair will not just make your website rank higher in search engines but they can also give you more traffic to your website, which ultimately results into more customers. It actually helps you make your website more productive and valuable business tool in the most cost efficient way.
<br /><br />Furthermore, the SEO Los Angeles based service of IT Chair is time efficient. IT Chair                       <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tY29uc3VsdGFudC8_" target="_blank">SEO consultant</a>   is giving you the perfect marketing solution, allowing you to focus on other important business responsibilities.
<br /><br />With IT Chair SEO Los Angeles based services you are guaranteed that you will get higher business sales in the shortest period of time.
<br />So, if you want to raise your business sales become partners with the most reliable SEO Firm, call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="14f72df5283e82ef0add3499b4efae11" url=""><![CDATA[The Growing Importance of SEO<br/><br/>In today’s competitive online environment, it is now becoming difficult to achieve your business goals. However, with the help of search engine optimization from an SEO firm like IT Chair, you can extremely improve your chances of attaining strong business success with a high level of online visibility. 
<br /><br />An SEO firm such as IT Chair is an affordable alternative to high costing traditional marketing methods such as TV Ads and prints. 
<br /><br />With IT Chair SEO Los Angeles based services you no longer have to employ sales representatives or customer representatives just to reach a higher number of customers and business revenue. Thus, it allows you to gain overhead cost savings.
<br /><br />With the expertise of IT Chair experienced and certified SEO consultant of Los Angeles, you can make online users visit your website, inquire, buy your product, avail of your services, so in the process increasing your business visibility. 
<br /><br />This means that IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO Firm</a>   can really increase your business revenue.
<br />The IT Chair SEO consultant experts are well-versed in internet marketing and online businesses so they can guide you through the process of improving your business.
<br /><br />The IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tY29uc3VsdGFudC8_" target="_blank">SEO consultant</a>   will also spend great effort to study your business industry as well as your competitors for them to give you the most effective SEO solution.
<br />Moreover, since SEO Los Angeles services offered by IT Chair are all done by professional SEO experts in the timeliest manner, you can also have efficient time savings, allowing you to do other important business tasks.
<br /><br />Acquiring IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   based services is an essential decision, it will guarantee your lead over the competition during the time you need it the most.
<br />So if you want to have the most dependable method of marketing your business and increasing your profit, call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c83ed0a32835a99fd1e11f62e68ad0ce" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair Offers Free SEO and Web Design Los Angeles Quotes<br/><br/>October 11, 2010 – Los Angeles, California – IT Chair – a leading <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO Firm</a>   and Web Designing Company that provides cost effective, custom services for the online marketing needs of commercial and private websites, has offered free quotes for their SEO and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS93ZWItZGVzaWduLWxvcy1hbmdlbGVzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank">web design Los Angeles</a>   services.
<br /><br />With their highly knowledgeable and experienced team and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   services, businesses can brand their products or services, gain more potential customers, increase profit and get faster return of investment (ROI). Aside from their SEO services, IT Chair also provides web design Los Angeles services to help websites stand out with the right graphics and features provided.
<br /><br />To get a free quote for these services, IT Chair has provided separate online quote request forms for SEO and web design Los Angeles services. 
<br /><br />For the free SEO and web designing quotes, some necessary questions will be asked so that the SEO firm and the web design Los Angeles teams can analyze and determine what details and actions to take. 
<br /><br />By availing IT Chair’s SEO Los Angeles services, businesses can shift from focusing on multiple target markets to a more highly targeted market that their business needs. By keeping updated with the latest web changes and technologies, their SEO Los Angeles specialists can help businesses understand how SEO works and how to they can use their unique selling points to stand out. 
<br /><br />As an online brochure, business website has to be appealing and at the same time, give visitors an idea of what the business is all about and what they are offering. To help businesses with their website designing needs, the web design specialists can provide cost-effective solutions through their free quotes.
<br /><br />Depending on their requirements, IT Chair’s web design specialists can offer the Silver, Gold or Platinum web design Los Angeles service packages. Whether businesses want traffic monitoring software, e-commerce software, custom website design or templates, live chat feature, free monthly updates, and more, their web design Los Angeles specialists can provide it for them.
<br /><br />For more information about IT Chair’s services, please call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eeec98904fd0cd3db9478ba260c1b30e" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair Offers Special Bonuses on the Internet Marketing eB<br/><br/>October 11, 2010 – Los Angeles, California – IT Chair – a professional web design and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO agency</a>  company that also provides quality online marketing, business networking, and blogs creations services, has offered special bonuses for their Internet Marketing eBook.
<br /><br />By getting a copy of this effective guide, business owners can learn about the importance of getting <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   services, and the secrets to Internet marketing. With a regular price of $39.95, the IT Chair Internet Marketing eBook is being offered at the affordable price of $9.95 for the next 50 downloads. 
<br /><br />SEO agency IT Chair, is also offering special bonuses like extra chapters, free consultation, and a free search engine optimization secret. IT Chair can also give ideas about how SEO Los Angeles and internet marketing is done without any cost for business owners. Their SEO firm specialists can give tips on how to market their products and services worldwide through Internet marketing.
<br /><br />Information about Internet Marketing and about the different strategies used by SEO Los Angeles experts is shown and discussed in the eBook. With only 500 copies being sold, the Internet Marketing eBook is composed of 14 chapters with chapters 10 and 13 as the bonus chapters. For Chapter 10, it mainly deals about keyword marketing, one of the SEO techniques used by SEO Los Angeles specialists.
<br /><br />Aside from the two bonus chapters, the SEO firm also provided free Internet marketing consultation as their second bonus. The free consultation can be provided by the president of IT Chair for any concerns about SEO Los Angeles or the other contents of the eBook.
<br /><br />After the reading the book, the business owners availed of the third bonus: free information about a search engine optimization secret. To get the bonus, business owners will need to send their contact information to IT Chair. Their SEO Los Angeles specialists will then send an e-mail about the secret.
<br /><br />For inquiries about the Internet Marketing eBook offered by the SEO firm, IT Chair, please call (310) 927-2588 begin_of_the_skype_highlighting              (310) 927-2588      end_of_the_skype_highlighting or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2Finternet-marketing-ebook-e-book.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/internet-marketing-ebook-e-book.html</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2ba1cc45997a2ac5626b98b53c75f304" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair Offers Three Smart Web Design Los Angeles Service P<br/><br/>October 11, 2010 – Los Angeles, California – IT Chair – a professional web design and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO firm</a>   Company that specializes in providing standard and custom online marketing solutions for commercial or private websites, has offered three <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS93ZWItZGVzaWduLWxvcy1hbmdlbGVzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank">web design Los Angeles</a>  packages with each package having a setup fee of only $199. 
<br /><br />Each of the three packages: Silver, Gold and Platinum web design Los Angeles, contains effective solutions for various needs. Whether businesses need a cost-effective solution for the graphic elements or behind the scenes features involved in website designing, one of their web design Los Angeles packages can provide it for them. 
<br /><br />The first package, which is the Silver web design Los Angeles, is suited for small websites with 5 web pages. In designing the website, their specialists would use CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) and provide 10 photos.
<br /><br />Suited for large websites with at least 15 web pages, the Gold web design Los Angeles package also uses CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) and provides 20 photos. Offering a lot more features, the Gold web design Los Angeles package provides websites with search engine friendly code, sitemap, traffic monitoring software, local listings, blogs, and live chat, and free updates for 1 month.
<br /><br />Providing the same features as the gold package and more, the Platinum web design Los Angeles package is usually recommended for large websites with 25 pages. The new features included in the web design Los Angeles package are search engine submission, e-commerce software for up to 20 products, contact us and other types of forms, flash, and a custom design or template.
<br /><br />Aside from the features or services included in the web design Los Angeles packages, IT Chair can also provide newsletter tools or mailing list, database, content management system, web statistics, guestbook, staff profiles, and online coupons.
<br /><br />For more information about IT Chair’s web design Los Angeles packages, please call (310) 927-2588 begin_of_the_skype_highlighting              (310) 927-2588      end_of_the_skype_highlighting begin_of_the_skype_highlighting              (310) 927-2588      end_of_the_skype_highlighting or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="53b87f9fb56149bd313a6cd37108dce1" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair Offers Smart SEO and Web Design Los Angeles Service<br/><br/>October 11, 2010 – Los Angeles, California – IT Chair – a leading web design and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   company whose staff is highly knowledgeable and experienced in providing a wide array of services, has offered smart SEO and web design Los Angeles services.
<br /><br />To provide even better and exceptional service to business owners managing their websites, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>, IT Chair knows about SEO 2.0 and can provide business owners with the support they need to increase their business’ online presence. With the best <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS93ZWItZGVzaWduLWxvcy1hbmdlbGVzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank">web design Los Angeles</a>   team working on the natural SEO development of their website, businesses can have ten times better looking website and save cost as well.
<br /><br />Technology is continually advancing further so business owners also need to find out how Internet marketing works in the new technology. Here at IT Chair, their SEO Los Angeles specialists know that traditional search engine optimization strategies may not be enough to achieve the type and quality of traffic that the business needs. 
<br /><br />With the new SEO 2.0 technology, IT Chair’s SEO Los Angeles experts can provide a more effective way of increasing their sales and return of investment. Through their SEO agency services, business owners are able to gain more traffic to their website, and have a higher conversion rate with customers finding their website to be more relevant to their needs and wants.
<br /><br />Aside from providing the right traffic that their business needs, the SEO firm IT Chair also provides quality web designing services that are done the smart way. With most businesses aiming to reduce costs on operations and advertisements, getting web design Los Angeles services can help them lessen these expenses.
<br /><br />IT Chair’s web design Los Angeles experts can provide the business website with the right content and design. By using the latest creative technologies available in the market, their web design Los Angeles experts can provide the website with a natural web design and development that may offer better results as compared to banner ads.
<br /><br />For more details about IT Chair’s SEO and web design services, please call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ed397d9f627bf4edf8f8f4f73bb1aede" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair Launches Effective Online Marketing Solution<br/><br/>October 11, 2010 – Los Angeles, California – Web Designing and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO Firm</a>   – IT Chair has launched an effective online marketing solution that will increase business profit.
<br /><br />“The search engine optimization or <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   based services can give you rapid return on investment,” said IT Chair.
<br /><br />SEO Los Angeles based service is the online marketing solution offered by IT Chair that gave businesses wider business market, lots of customers, good business visibility and higher business profits.
<br /><br />With IT Chair professional and expert <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tY29uc3VsdGFudC8_" target="_blank">SEO consultant</a>  , businesses had a larger influx of customers.  
<br /><br />IT Chair SEO consultant made websites rank on search engines first page results and eventually got good traffic. This means that business websites had hundreds of visitors that could be switched to buyers.
<br /><br />The SEO consultant of IT Chair was capable of giving timely SEO services that allowed businesses to have efficient time savings.
<br /><br />The SEO Los Angeles based services of IT Chair is not just an effective online marketing solution, it is also an efficient tool that allows business owners to focus on what they do best.  
<br /><br />So for businesses that needed a guaranteed online or internet marketing tool that can pull many customers and improve business revenue, call (310) 927-2588 begin_of_the_skype_highlighting              (310) 927-2588      end_of_the_skype_highlighting    or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
<br /><br />About IT Chair
<br /><br />IT Chair is a search engine optimization or SEO Firm based in Los Angeles, California that specializes in giving high quality internet and online marketing solutions for businesses. The knowledgeable, energetic certified professional  SEO consultant of IT Chair are capable of using the best proven techniques with the most recent innovative practices in the industry combined with ethical methods to reach the highest search engine optimization solutions which not only make traffic to businesses, but also bring additional sales and revenue.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d32e78c6904c227d2db79d69793782bd" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair SEO Agency Helps Increase Business Revenue<br/><br/>October 11, 2010 – Los Angeles, California – Web Designing and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO agency</a>   – IT Chair has helped businesses increase their revenue.
<br /><br />For those businesses who want to market their product and services online, IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   has the perfect internet marketing solution.
<br /><br />Businesses increased their business revenue by having more customers in the timeliest manner and at the most reasonable rates by the expert IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tY29uc3VsdGFudC8_" target="_blank">SEO consultant</a>  .
<br /><br />IT Chair has offered affordable SEO Los Angeles marketing solutions, unlike expensive traditional marketing medium such as TV Ads and prints. Online marketing of IT Chair can give businesses inexpensive solutions that will last for a longer time.
<br /><br />With IT Chair SEO Los Angeles based services, businesses will have big cost savings. They will no longer have to employ employees to do their online marketing strategies. Thus, businesses will have additional time to do other important business responsibilities.
<br /><br />Moreover, the SEO Consultant of IT Chair can give businesses faultless marketing solution in timely manner. They have enough knowledge and expertise in providing effective online marketing solutions for any type of businesses. 
<br /><br />IT Chair SEO Consultant is also capable of giving businesses more customers by improving business website rankings on popular search engines such as Google, Yahoo and Bing. 
<br />To give businesses the chance of increasing their customers, SEO Los Angeles of IT Chair will also increase the traffic of a business website. This means that businesses will make online users visit their website, buy their product, avail their services and eventually increase their revenue. 
<br />So for business who desire for an effective online marketing solution that will last longer, call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
<br /><br />About IT Chair
<br /><br />IT Chair is a Web Designing and SEO firm, based in Los Angeles, California. They have standard as well as custom made plans to fit businesses commercial or private website necessities.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5bcd8f8d6a359c518b9faf7da6142f5f" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair SEO Los Angeles Encourages Businesses to Use Natura<br/><br/>October 11, 2010 – Los Angeles, California – IT Chair – the leading <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   has encouraged businesses to use natural SEO strategies than Pay Per Click Advertising by presenting the advantages of organic and ethical SEO. 
<br /><br />“You might be spending a fortune in advertising methods for your company or private website. There is no reason to pay for pay-per-click advertising for a high rank. You can achieve top ranks when you use natural methods with the right content,” said Ashkan Sobhe, founder of IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO Agency</a>  .
<br /><br />Based on the popular definition of organic SEO as the process that helps in improving the visibility of a website in search engines &quot;the natural way&quot;, IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tY29uc3VsdGFudC8_" target="_blank">SEO Consultant</a>   has applied and suggested the use of natural SEO methods to their client’s websites.
<br /><br />In order for the website to be fully optimized, their SEO Consultant has conducted thorough website analysis and keyword researching to what keywords or keyword phrases would be used that will work best in the search engines.
<br /><br />Furthermore, IT Chair SEO Los Angeles has done on-page and off-page optimization like: 
<br /><br />Changing the on-page elements or factors such as the title Tag, header tags, page content, alt tag, Meta description tag and Meta keywords tag to improve website's positions in search engines.
<br /><br />For off-page optimization, IT Chair SEO Los Angeles created the right and winning web contents and used those to gain inbound inks.
<br /><br />All these organic SEO tactics from IT Chair SEO Firm have proven to be very effective to increase conversion rates, gain traffic and increase rankings in the major search engines compared to using Pay per Click Advertising.
<br /><br />For inquiries on organic SEO services, contact IT Chair SEO Los Angeles at (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
<br /><br />About IT Chair
<br /><br />IT Chair is an SEO Firm based in Los Angeles. They meet high standards as well as provide custom made plans to fit every commercial or private website requirements. Their SEO Consultant is knowledgeable and energetic and works closely with clients to make sure the work matches their client’s desire and exceeds their expectations.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="26a8742a091ce344a5c14c97248ece43" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair SEO Firm Promotes the Advantages of Using their Sea<br/><br/>October 11, 2010 – Los Angeles, California – IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO Firm</a>   – promoted the advantages of using their search engine optimization services by informing people about their best and proven processes with the latest innovative practices in the SEO industry.
<br /><br />IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   is a Search Engine Optimization and Web Designing Company based in Los Angeles, California.
<br /><br />They have merged the tested methods and procedures of organic SEO techniques to achieve the highest search engine optimization solutions which not only drove traffic to websites, but, also brought sales for their clients.
<br /><br />Furthermore, there are other benefits in using Internet Marketing Services from IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tY29uc3VsdGFudC8_" target="_blank">SEO Consultant</a>  over their competitors. This includes:
<br /><br />Providing one-on-one consultation to every customer inquiry and offering them with customized optimization solutions as well. This is far better than the one-size-fits-all SEO solution that other typical SEO Firm offered.
<br />With IT Chair SEO Los Angeles, they reinforce the website’s off-page elements (e.g. meta description tags, title and alt tags and page content) to enhance the branding of the products and services. 
<br />In applying these, IT Chair SEO Agency has drawn more traffic to websites and converted those visitors to customers and gained consistently high rankings in the major search engines.  
<br />Moreover, IT Chair SEO Los Angeles has committed to provide customers with a customized package that is right for them, from start to finish. 
<br />For inquiries, contact IT Chair SEO Los Angeles at (310) 927-2588 begin_of_the_skype_highlighting              (310) 927-2588      end_of_the_skype_highlighting or log on to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>    
<br />About IT Chair
<br />IT Chair SEO Firm is a professional search engine optimization service company that provides ethical search engine optimization and internet marketing services. They specialize in search engine optimization and other online marketing services through search engine friendly website design and development as well as SEO content development service.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="66fef29ceac4c79a07407ec6379838b" url=""><![CDATA[More Than Flashy Graphics<br/><br/>Looking for a professional <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS93ZWItZGVzaWduLWxvcy1hbmdlbGVzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank">web design Los Angeles</a>  ? 
<br /><br />Then visit IT Chair.
<br /><br />IT Chair is a web design Los Angeles and SEO Company that provides internet marketing services that corresponds and surpasses their client’s wants as well as expectations. They not only offer websites with flashy graphics but also search engine friendly web designs and layouts.
<br /><br />Get a free web design Los Angeles quote today! Call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fitchair.com%2Fquote-free-web-design.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://itchair.com/quote-free-web-design.htm</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="29ee7dd9874e0f502481672e30def248" url=""><![CDATA[Create an Income-Generating Web Business<br/><br/>Your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS93ZWItZGVzaWduLWxvcy1hbmdlbGVzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank">web design Los Angeles</a>   should be more than just fancy images. 
<br /><br />Be sure, your web business is Search Engine friendly and has the competitive advantage to reach your target market. 
<br /><br />So, hire web design Los Angeles professionals who has the knowledge to attract your target market by incorporating basic marketing and SEO principles in your web design and layout.
<br /><br />To discuss how you can transform your website into an income-generating portfolio, visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a634c218dc9cc49ba5e2df92067b3459" url=""><![CDATA[ITChair SEO Los Angeles E-Book<br/><br/>Looking for an internet marketing product that can help give you satisfying results in your SEO campaign? 
<br /><br />IT Chair offers a downloadable online guide to achieve successful internet marketing. It is a cost-effective product at only $9.95. Hurry and grab the opportunity of gaining knowledge in <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>  .
<br /><br />For more information, call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fitchair.com%2Finternet-marketing-ebook-e-book.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://itchair.com/internet-marketing-ebook-e-book.html</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="934a3c316fc3adccb2f407eafa8c2d83" url=""><![CDATA[SEO Los Angeles Internet Marketing<br/><br/>Looking for an <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   company? 
<br /><br />IT chair can cater to all your SEO needs, providing you with some of its newest internet marketing products and services that can aid you in gaining better rankings in the major search engines within a few months. 
<br /><br />To see some of SEO Los Angeles sample works, please click on the link <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2Fseo-los-angeles%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/seo-los-angeles/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d5e8631cd4eb8ff0f53d8ccab3cb7675" url=""><![CDATA[Promoting the Significance of Search Engine Optimization<br/><br/>Search engine optimization (SEO) is just a part of the scope of search engine marketing (SEM) that is dominantly used by the ITChair SEO Firm. Search engine optimization is simply the process of improving the visibility of a website in search engines via natural or unpaid search results.
<br /><br />ITChair is an SEO Firm that provides both SEO Los Angeles and web design Los Angeles services internationally, with expertise in getting their client’s website on top of the search engine page results. 
<br /><br />The SEO Agency applies to their campaign the commonly used wise techniques in search engine optimization such as reciprocal link exchange, directories and articles submission, and social bookmarking. 
<br /><br />SEO, the much preferred search engine marketing strategy used by the ITChair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO Firm</a>   to rank keyword searches, has greater advantages over paid advertisings because:
<br /><br />63% of top natural (organic) listings get click throughs. 
<br />These are achieved by the SEO Agency through optimizing the Meta description to increase clickability, using snippets to describe the content that has been taken from the website, and the use of yahoo search monkey to enhance listing showing reviews, rating and local information.
<br /><br />Natural (organic) search results convert 30% higher than paid advertisings.
<br />One of the strategies applied by the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   Company to increase conversion rate is through the use of long tail search keywords. Long tail keywords are basically an expansion of a core, generic, high volume keyword phrase to include numerous combinations and permutations of the keywords and their associated or relevant phrases.
<br /><br />Compared to paid advertising, search engine optimization is advantageous when it comes to being less expensive, gets better rankings, and it appears more natural and professional. 
<br /><br />So, for your SEO Los Angeles needs, contact (310) 927-2588, email them at <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=info@itchair.com">info@itchair.com</a> or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6f0560de3b48867df31cf098812ae2ba" url=""><![CDATA[What Web Design Los Angeles Outsourcing Can Mean for Busines<br/><br/>How outsourcing web design Los Angeles services can help businesses is a vital question that businesses will ask. If you are the manager of a business and you are currently running an online website to build branding for your business, you may want to consider getting web design Los Angeles services especially if your business has a lot of competitors.
<br /><br />As the manager, you have to come up with ways to market the products or services of your business to gain more sales and profit. With an online website, you can achieve this with the aid of professional web design and SEO agency experts such as IT Chair. If you want your business website to be presentable and at the same time useful for your customers, you also need to optimize the website design and hire the right web design Los Angeles team.
<br /><br />Regardless of the size of your business, investing in web design Los Angeles services can be the key to the success of your website. As a leading web design company in Los Angeles, IT Chair can help you with your web designing needs with their custom web design Los Angeles packages.
<br /><br />When it comes to building a website, getting web design Los Angeles services from IT Chair will help your website:
<br /><strong>
<br />1. Attract the attention of your customers</strong>
<br />When your customers visit your website, it is important that the graphics and content of the website are attractive and interesting enough to make them stay.  
<br /><br />With IT Chair’s web design and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO agency</a>   experts, you can make your website look more attractive, professional and trustworthy.  
<br /><br /><strong>2. Show how your business is special </strong>
<br />To make it easy for your customers to find out how your business is special, the web design Los Angeles experts can implement a website design that can show customers the works.
<br /><br />With a simple yet stylish navigation menu made by web design Los Angeles experts, it will be easier for your customers to find out what your business is all about and what it can offer to them.
<br /><br />To learn more about the web designing and SEO agency, IT Chair, and their services, please visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a61c9007cf89e9ab6379976ad71b8af5" url=""><![CDATA[Traffic versus Conversion: Which Matters Most?<br/><br/><strong>Which is more important, positioning or conversation? </strong>
<br /><br />Web traffic has always been the key factor in determining the popularity of your web business and its position in search engine result pages, but at the end of the day, it all comes down to how many deals you have closed. 
<br /><br />Your target market is now more selective in choosing who to do business with, thus, conversation is more important.
<br /><br /><strong>Conversion happens when people:
<br />•	Request more information
<br />•	Click the buy now button
<br />•	Or pick up the phone and engage with your business directly
<br /></strong>
<br /><strong>Without these actions, you will not earn and without money, your business fails. So how will you secure your website to handle more business? </strong>
<br /><br />This is when SEO Los Angeles services from the best <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">SEO firm</a>   come in. Presently, the leading SEO firm and SEO agency in Los Angeles is ITChair, renowned for providing smart SEO Los Angeles campaigns that will not only drive traffic to your site and boost your branding. Most importantly, their SEO experts will transform your web business into an income-generating online portfolio.
<br /><br /><strong>How can ITChair SEO firm help you make more money?</strong>
<br /><br />Their SEO Los Angeles experts are knowledgeable in search engine optimization. They use the most updated SEO Los Angeles strategies and techniques to drive traffic into your site. They will also integrate online marketing principles into their <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a> campaigns to target your niche market and encourage them to make business with you.
<br /><br />At the end of their SEO Los Angeles campaigns, a reliable SEO agency and SEO firm like ITChair will not only enhance your brand visibility or ensure your ranking in search engines. Most of all, their SEO Los Angeles campaigns will help you achieve your ultimate goal – and that is to make more money online. To know more about ITChair SEO firm and their SEO Los Angeles services, call on (310) 927-2588 or log on to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8ca871cb705aa332c8838cdfe4ed9cfd" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair Combines SEO and Web Design Los Angeles Services in<br/><br/>November 12, 2010 – Los Angeles, California, USA – one of the leading <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   and Web Design Los Angeles Company – IT Chair – has combined their expertise in search engine optimization and web designing to offer their clients a more competitive website.
<br /><br />With the need for businesses to thrive online, “Their online portfolio and presentation must have the basic marketing techniques and strategies embedded on their web design Los Angeles coupled with some SEO Los Angeles strategies to further boost their online presence,” said IT Chair.
<br /><br />Through these embedded principles, businesses will be able to dominate the search engine results, achieve top rankings, bring in more traffic and increase their conversion rates and ROI.
<br /><br />In today’s online marketing landscape, staying ahead of the game is not only a necessity but an opportunity to survive in this forever-evolving and changing environment.
<br /><br />And with the help of IT Chair’s combined strategic web design Los Angeles marketing and SEO Los Angeles solutions, online businesses will have a better chance in taking advantage of the online market, outsmart their competitors and improve their bottom line.
<br /><br />To know more about IT Chair’s experienced team of SEO Los Angeles and Web Design Los Angeles specialists, call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a> 
<br /><br />About IT Chair
<br /><br />IT Chair, Inc. is a Search Engine Optimization (SEO Los Angeles) and Web Designing company, based in Los Angeles, California. The company provides Internet Marketing and Online Marketing for online business needs. 
<br /><br />Their standard as well as custom made plans are designed to fit commercial or private website requirements. IT Chair’s SEO Los Angeles and Web Design Los Angeles teams are knowledgeable, energetic and will work closely to ensure their work matches the desired requirements of the business and exceed expectations.
<br /><br />They do it all, from personal blogs to Online Marketing / Internet Marketing, Search Engine Optimization (SEO Los Angeles), Search Engine Marketing, Web Designing (Web Design Los Angeles), Web Development and E-Commerce (Shopping Cart) websites.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d731b5c8675b1c536e404d664c3f6871" url=""><![CDATA[ITChair Offers the Ultimate Internet Marketing Guide to Onli<br/><br/>November 12, 2010 – Los Angeles, California, USA – leading <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   Company – IT Chair – has offered the ultimate Internet Marketing Guide to Online Success highlighting ideas about how to effectively market products or services online for only $9.95!
<br /><br />The Ultimate Internet Marketing eBook contains SEO Los Angeles secret strategies and methods to help your business:
<br /><br />•	Attracts millions of people to buy your products or avail of your services.
<br />•	Bring in more traffic every month.
<br />•	Increase conversion rates.
<br />•	Boost Sales for up to 1,000%.
<br />•	Dominate the Search Engines Result Pages.
<br /><br />This eBook was written by Ashkan Sobhe, the president and CEO of IT Chair, the leading SEO Los Angeles and Web design Los Angeles Company. This eBook is designed to create awareness and introduce business to the many new, different and innovative ways of marketing anything online.
<br /><br />IT Chair is only selling 500 copies of the Internet Marketing EBook. So Hurry. ACT NOW!
<br /><br />To learn more about the Internet Marketing eBook, call (310) 927-2588 begin_of_the_skype_highlighting              (310) 927-2588      end_of_the_skype_highlighting or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2Finternet-marketing-ebook-e-book.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/internet-marketing-ebook-e-book.html</a>
<br /><br />About IT Chair
<br /><br />IT Chair, Inc. is a Search Engine Optimization (SEO Los Angeles) and Web Designing company, based in Los Angeles, California. The company provides Internet Marketing and Online Marketing for online business needs. 
<br /><br />Their standard as well as custom made plans are designed to fit commercial or private website requirements. IT Chair’s SEO Los Angeles and Web Design Los Angeles teams are knowledgeable, energetic and will work closely to ensure their work matches the desired requirements of the business and exceeds expectations.
<br /><br />They do it all, from personal blogs to Online Marketing / Internet Marketing, Search Engine Optimization (SEO Los Angeles), Search Engine Marketing, Web Designing (Web Design Los Angeles), Web Development and E-Commerce (Shopping Cart) websites.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ee3863dec596860fa68069320a9f2367" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair Offers Free Web Design Los Angeles Analysis Service<br/><br/>November 12, 2010 – Los Angeles, California, USA – IT Chair – a professional IT Company specializing in providing search engine optimization and web design Los Angeles services, offered free website analysis to provide businesses with the best solution for their website designing needs. 
<br /><br />For them to get a free website analysis, businesses only needed to complete the web design Los Angeles quote form provided on their website.
<br /><br />On the form, various options were required to help IT Chair’s web design Los Angeles experts perform a more accurate website analysis. The business was asked to provide information on their website address, their preferred project start date, the number of pages that their website has, comments about the website design or functions that they would like the web design Los Angeles experts to analyze, budget and contact details. 
<br /><br />For businesses who wanted to have IT Chair’s web design Los Angeles experts create or redesign their website, the online form also has provided options for their preferred website address, the current name of their website if they already have a domain name, the number of pages they would like for their new website, and the features that they would like to be added to their website. 
<br /><br />The web design Los Angeles quote form also asked whether the business had already prepared content for their site, whether they would like their website to be optimized for the search engines, and whether they would like to have monthly updates for their website.
<br /><br />With the request submitted and the website analysis completed, IT Chair’s web design Los Angeles experts provided a solution for website designing needs in the form of a quote. Depending on the results of the analysis, IT Chair may recommend either their silver, gold, or platinum web design Los Angeles package. 
<br /><br />To get a free website analysis from the web design Los Angeles experts of IT Chair, please call (310) 927-2588 or fill up the online web design quote form at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2Fquote-free-web-design.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/quote-free-web-design.htm</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4bcdc30f2a849a5edbf1e7ed30e4fb9d" url=""><![CDATA[IT Chair Introduced the New Search Engine Optimization 2.0<br/><br/>November 12, 2010 – Los Angeles, California, USA – IT Chair – one of the leading IT companies in the southern United States dealing in <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>   and web design Los Angeles had introduced their new strategy for SEO Los Angeles called the Search Engine Optimization 2.0. 
<br /><br />It is simply SEO Los Angeles technology that advanced further to a whole new phase of Internet Marketing.Search Engine Optimization 2.0 or SEO 2.0 was different from more traditional SEO Los Angeles and changed Internet marketing in a completely different way.
<br /><br />SEO Los Angeles 2.0 was a much more efficient way to increase the return on Internet marketing investments while it decreased the time required for manual linking and keyword prioritization. It enabled marketers to actually drive traffic to sites and analyze the type and quality of the traffic with regard to sales.
<br /><br />Five ways SEO Los Angeles 2.0 differs from traditional SEO 
<br /><br />1. Natural Links – Unlike traditional SEO, SEO Los Angeles 2.0 allowed for mining of links from blogs, social networks, and other sites that can be used to help drive traffic. This quality traffic leads to sales, is much more effective and required less time to achieve results.
<br /><br />2. No keywords – SEO 2.0 focused on how real people use the Web and read its content, not just its homepage. SEO Los Angeles 2.0 focused more on individual page optimization. This allowed greater flexibility with content development as titles and descriptions may be different and with different targets.  
<br /><br />3. Co-opetition – Instead of competing for position or ranking in search engines, SEO Los Angeles 2.0 created a more hospitable relationship where cross-linking and community between sites was encouraged and yielded better results. 
<br /><br />4. Brand Building – Increased sales with improved brand recognition led to impressive ROI’s (return on investment) on marketing expenditures. Clicks and visits were not important in SEO Los Angeles 2.0 so the focus is more on conversion rather than traffic. 
<br /><br />5. Off-page Optimization – The focus is not just the website. The most successful companies leverage social networks, blogs and other sites to help build their brands and drive traffic and sales. 
<br /><br />SEO Los Angeles 2.0 promised to be a more effective and useful method of marketing so companies will see increased sales. This was due to consumers finding their sites more user-friendly and relevant to their needs and wants. 
<br /><br />Start utilizing SEO 2.0 and be sure to contact <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a> at (310) 927 2588 for any assistance.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13939680aafbda844f7cea3fc2f7ee21" url=""><![CDATA[Generate Higher Sales<br/><br/>Generate higher business sales with IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tbG9zLWFuZ2VsZXMv" target="_blank">SEO Los Angeles</a>  based services.
<br /><br />The SEO services of IT Chair can give you higher sales by:
<br /><br />•	Making your website rank at search engine first page search results
<br />•	Increasing your website number of visitors
<br />•	Giving you cost and time savings
<br /><br />Upon gaining SEO firm services you will surprisingly increase your business profit!
<br />Call (310) 927-2588 or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="840f8fa04ef0d3153f9c2c0f846b1795" url=""><![CDATA[Leave the Competition Behind<br/><br/>Leave the business competition behind when your website is optimized by IT Chair <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pdGNoYWlyLmNvbS9zZW8tY29uc3VsdGFudC8_" target="_blank">SEO Consultant</a>  .
<br /><br />The SEO consultants of IT Chair can help you leave the competition behind by:
<br /><br />•	Giving you more customers
<br />•	Increasing your business sales
<br />•	Reducing your business overhead costs
<br /><br />If you are serious in leading the competition, call (310) 927-2588   or visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itchair.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.itchair.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>