<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="13">
		<document id="e2b94f4f0ad7cd6fa6da9f0aefab8f4d" url=""><![CDATA[i love this guy :P<br/><br/>A guy wrote this in his myspace.
<br />and it should make you think...
<br />- - - - -
<br />I know way too many really beautiful
<br />girls who think they don't look good... It hurts... because it's
<br />our fault, guys I mean. We make girls feel like they have
<br />to be perfect. You know what I mean, flat stomach, big boobs,
<br />round booty, long legs, sexy lips, and on top of all that,
<br />they have to dress like a whore, and be one as well... nobody can
<br />measure up to that... and it's not fair... because nobody should
<br />have to. The little imperfections are what make people special.
<br />If everyone was perfect the world would be so boring, variety is
<br />what makes life interesting. So guys, stop making girls have to
<br />live up to your, I'm sorry, our... deluded fantasy visions of
<br />perfection. Stop acting like boys and start being men... realize
<br />that women don't exist to fulfill our sexual desires. Stop talking
<br />to them solely to get with them, be nice to them because you want
<br />to be their friend, not because you want to hook up with them. Say
<br />nice things about them not to flatter them in hopes that you'll
<br />get some, but because you know they like to hear them. In short...
<br />we need to grow up and stop acting like freaking retarded little
<br />boys.
<br />- - - - - -
<br />girls who agree repost. and to the few guys who have balls
<br />and agree also repost it
<br /><br />th guy who madethisshould bepresident of anywhere
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c0ab787777a2605e7914825227c75cab" url=""><![CDATA[awww i want a boy to say this to me...seriously<br/><br/>Girl: Do i ever cross ur mind
<br /><br />Boy: No
<br /><br />Girl: Do you like me?
<br /><br />Boy: Not really
<br /><br />Girl: Do you want me?
<br /><br />Boy: No
<br /><br />Girl: Would you cry if I left?
<br /><br />Boy: No
<br /><br />Girl: Would you live for me?
<br /><br />Boy: No
<br /><br />Girl: Would you do anything for me?
<br /><br />Boy: No
<br /><br />Girl: Choose--me or ur life
<br /><br />Boy: my life
<br /><br />The girl runs away in shock and pain and the boy runs after her and says...
<br /><br />The reason you never cross my mind is because you're always on my mind.
<br /><br />The reason why I don't like you is because I love you.
<br /><br />The reason I don't want you is because I need you.
<br /><br />The reason I wouldn't cry if you left is because I would die if you left.
<br /><br />The reason I wouldn't live for you is because I would die for you.
<br /><br />The reason why I'm not willing to do anything for you is because I would do everything for you.
<br /><br />The reason I chose my life is because you ARE my life.
<br /><br />REPOST THIS IN 7 MIN. IF YOU CARE FOR SOMEONE A LOT
<br />OR YOU'LL HAVE BAD LUCK IN YOUR UPCOMING RELATIONSHIP AND NOTHING WILL WORK
<br /><br />REPOST IN 7......6......5.....4....3....2....1....0...NOW!!
<br /><br />If your a girl repost this as ''Aww. I want a boy to say this to me.''
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="627b7b35931b294d0f56ccf06075dbf9" url=""><![CDATA[IM COLD,SOMEONE WARM ME<br/><br/>I KNOW I LIVE IN CANADA,BUT I THINK I WAS MEANT TO BE BORN IN LIKE HAWAII OR SOMEWHERE HOTTER,DONT GET ME WRONG I LOVE IT HERE AND WOULD NEVER LEAVE,BUT ITS SO FRICKIN COLD!! LOL I WANT SUMMER BACK,THE SWIMMING,CANOEING,FISHING....ETC SO MANY MORE THINGS TO DO,I FIND ATLEAST,IN SUMMER,SPRING OR EVEN FALL,ANYONE ELSE AGREE????
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dbae5fa67db5a99ef6b3d41c42809373" url=""><![CDATA[being a single mom...<br/><br/>does any other single mom out there find it extreamly difficult to find a man thats ready for a ready made family,or at first its cool,then later on it becomes an issue,you get what im saying? please someone give me some insite,cause im getting sick of feeling red flagged cause i gots me a kid <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4680498926d8af1f9e07ad141dda0257" url=""><![CDATA[hi all!!<br/><br/>you all are wicked <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d4f8a140c9be9a1ad313758e41aa3974" url=""><![CDATA[meanie<br/><br/>now tell me this...whose cruel idea was it to put an &quot;S&quot; in the word &quot;LISP&quot;??? C'mon now <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="30384f7cbe00a0b355bfd89b9ab662e2" url=""><![CDATA[summfin to ponder<br/><br/>if a man is standing in the middle of the forest speaking and there is no woman around to hear him...is he still wrong?!?!?! lol <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="142e85e04c6f46e43e2de72ff0d7b907" url=""><![CDATA[hmmm<br/><br/>if a person told you they were a pathalogical liar...would you believe them?? lol <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="291cb6d4bec952bb0f65989bca81ef75" url=""><![CDATA[im bored<br/><br/>is anyone else bored with this whole facebox,facebook...etc thing going on,maybe its just me,but i just dont find it fun anymore,if someone can change my mind please do thanks
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="959c785f87d4343f5ce35bb4b6d927e5" url=""><![CDATA[?<br/><br/>will i ever find MY mr. right????
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b5dd5cd73eb28baf0ed0b05c6ccd4e4c" url=""><![CDATA[for all you sweethearts out there!<br/><br/>To every guy that regrets hurting or losing her.
<br />To every guy who knows which girl he wants.
<br />To every guy that's said, &quot;You're beautiful.&quot;
<br />To every guy that was never too busy to drive across town(or across the state)( or across the country ) to see her.
<br />To every guy that gives flowers and a card when she is sick.
<br />To every guy who has given her flowers just because.
<br />To every guy that said he would die for her.
<br />To every guy that really would.
<br />To every guy that did what she wanted to do.
<br />To every guy that cried in front of her.
<br />To every guy that she cried in front of.
<br />To every guy that holds hands with her.
<br />To every guy that kisses her with meaning.
<br />To every guy that hugs her when she's sad.
<br />To every guy that hugs her for no reason at all.
<br />To every guy who would give their jacket up for her.
<br />To every guy that calls to make sure she got home safe.
<br />To every guy that would sit and wait for hours to see her, even if they could only spend a few minutes together
<br />To every guy that would give his seat up.
<br />To every guy that just wants to cuddle
<br />To every guy that reassured her that she was beautiful no matter what. And honestly believed what he said.
<br />To every guy who told his secrets to her.
<br />To every guy that tried to show how much he cared through every word and every breath.
<br />To every guy that thought &quot;maybe this could be the one&quot;.
<br />To every guy that believed in her dreams.
<br />To every guy that would have done anything so she could achieve them.
<br />To every guy that never laughed at her when she told him her dreams.
<br />To every guy that walked her to her car.
<br />To every guy that wasn't ...just trying to get laid.
<br />To every guy that gave his heart and still has a piece missing.
<br />To every guy who prays that she is happy even if he is not the one that makes her that way.
<br />To every guy who doesn't care how far away she lives, and will still date her because its her
<br />To every guy who cares the most about how she feels, even when she breaks your heart.
<br /><br />Not many girls appreciate nice guys anymore... And because of this, there are not many left out there... If you are a nice guy repost this with &quot;Nice guys finish last.&quot; If you are a girl that thinks every guy should try to accomplish even a few of these repost this with: &quot;To the nice guys left.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="baf5d7d06768d869174afd56c8dd5ea7" url=""><![CDATA[...<br/><br/>A GUY AND A GIRL CAN BE JUST FRIENDS, BUT AT ONE POINT OR ANOTHER ONE OF THEM WILL FALL FOR THE OTHER, MAYBE TEMPORAIRLY,MAYBE AT THE WRONG TIME,MAYBE TOO LATE,OR MAYBE...JUST MAYBE..FOREVER   <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1c0245e42dcf7132ce7b6b15a32a0f27" url=""><![CDATA["i want this guy"<br/><br/>I'm the guy who will text you every single morning and tell you good morning and every single night to tell you sweet dreams.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who will text you and tell you &quot;i love you and you make me smile&quot; just because.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who will blindfold you and take you to the beach, let you run your toes through the sand and then make you guess where we are.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who will show up at your games (or competitions or meets) without you knowing just to surprise you.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who will hold you when you're crying and wipe away your tears.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who won't pressure you to do things you dont want to.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who still thinks you're beautiful with no makeup on, wearing sweats and a big t-shirt.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who kisses you on the forehead.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who doesn't kiss and tell.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who won't lie to you about where he's going or where he's been or who he's been with.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who'll randomly tickle you just to hear you giggle.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who actually listens to you when you talk.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who's excited all day because i'm looking forward to our date that night.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who is content to just be able to hold you and wants nothing more.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who can't help but smile when you walk into the room.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who'll say i love you first because i'm not afraid to say it.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who's perfectly content with staying in and watching movies and cuddling.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who gets butterflies when he hears your name.
<br /><br />I''m the guy who's not afraid to tell his friends he loves you.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who doesnt mess with other girls when i have you.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who doesn't care about your imperfections and loves you more for them.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who will hold you while we watch the sunset.
<br /><br />I'm the guy that makes you laugh when you're down, makes you happy when you're mad, and makes you smile when you're frowning.
<br /><br />I'm the guy that isn't afraid to eat ice cream with you when you're having a bad day.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who will show up at your house with soup and a movie when you aren't feeling well.
<br /><br />I'm the guy who isn't always trying to act like a hard ass around you.
<br /><br />I'm the guy you call when you have no one else to turn to.
<br /><br />I'm the guy that will come pick your drunk ass up at 3 am when I have to be up at 8.
<br /><br />I'm the guy that tells you the right thing to do or how I really feel, not just what you want to hear.
<br /><br />I'm the guy that loves you for you and not what my friends think of you.
<br /><br />I'm the guy that will love you even when you do something so retarded that I normally wouldn't want to be seen with you.
<br /><br />I'm the guy that is always loyal no matter what.
<br /><br />I'M THE GUY WHO REALLY WANTS TO MAKE YOU THE HAPPIEST GIRL IN THE WORLD &quot;even if I go about it wrong.&quot;
<br /><br />I'M THE GUY WHO WILL WAIT FOR YOU 4 EVER
<br /><br />I AM THIS GUY... one of many... who always ends up losing her to the jerks who'll treat her like crap and are &quot;too good of a friend&quot; to date.
<br /><br />Ladies if this is your perfect guy, repost this with the title &quot;I want this guy&quot;
<br /><br />Fellas if this is you, repost this with the title &quot;I am this guy
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>