<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="18">
		<document id="62a11d59fe2cd16b0287d3d1fdaea4eb" url=""><![CDATA[Teeth Whitening Systems - My Private Knowledge With Teeth<br/><br/>&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstatic.uk.groupon-content.net%2F07%2F76%2F1299671567607.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://static.uk.groupon-content.net/07/76/1299671567607.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;natural  teeth whitening&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot;/&gt;<br />Use salt at regular intervals - plain salt is a great natural teeth whitening agent. Once in a while if you brush your teeth with salt, say once a week, you will not need any more help with your teeth. Use of the salt also improves the strength of the gums. The only thing that one has to watch out is that the salt be powdered extra fine so there is no abrasion action on the enamel of the teeth.<br />&lt;iframe width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2Fembed%2FjYa3dKjDD5M%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://youtube.com/embed/jYa3dKjDD5M&quot</a>; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;<br />Many people rely on at home teeth bleaching kits to bring out the very best in their smiles, but did you know that there are all natural teeth whitening formulas available right now online? You can get the bright white smile you've always wanted while at the same time using safe and gentle products that will take care of your teeth from start to finish. You don't have to rely on harsh chemicals or irritating formulas to get the smile you deserve anymore. Now, you can use the same effective solutions that professional cosmetic dentists use in their offices right in the comfort and privacy of your own home!<br />Brush your teeth as you usually do, and then swish for about a minute. Follow up by spitting it out and washing systematically with water. An additional method to utilize it is by dipping a cotton swap in the solution and softly rubbing it into your teeth, front and back. An old-time favorite, baking soda has many purposes, with tooth whitening. Most dentists agree that it's secure to employ and works fairly quickly. You can utilize it alone on a damp toothbrush or blend it with toothpaste to aid neutralize the salty taste.<br />Strawberries: This delicious fruit has shown tremendous scope with natural teeth whitening. Simply rub it to your teeth and you will see the difference within days.<br />Who doesn't want a bright smile? Stained and yellow teeth always result in an insecure smile and a loss in confidence. This calls for the need to eliminate this disorder. Hundreds of different bleaching formulas have come out in the market: teeth whitening kits and other teeth whitening products are here to claim to give you that perfect white teeth. Dental offices have come up with excellent professional services for whiter and brighter teeth.<br />One of the newest products to hit the market is Dr. Alan Creamer's NutraBrite. Dr. Alan set out to make a natural teeth whitening product that was effective. NutraBrite offers unique benefits compared to other at home teeth whitening products. NutraBrite whitens your teeth up to 5 shades in minutes compared to days or even weeks like other products. This is great if you have a big event coming up or even a special night out that you want results fast. It is also ideal for many of us that time is limited. We live in a society that wants results fast and don't have time to waste. NutraBrtie is a great solution which will get you the results you want in the time you have.<br />This involves crushing up a number of strawberries and coating your teeth with the resulting paste. Then leave it on for several minutes and rinse thoroughly. It is important to rinse it out completely as the acid in strawberries, much like lemons, can damage the enamel and have an effect on the calcium levels.<br />I will start with the professional choice. If your dentist agrees that you should whiten your teeth, they would make trays formed to fit over your teeth. The trays hold a gel solution containing peroxide. The dentist decides how long to keep the whitener on your teeth, and how long you will use it. This method is quite successful, and your dentist is responsible for keeping your mouth healthy and the tooth enamel from deteriorating. The cost could be a huge detriment. Professional whitening is very expensive.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teWxhc2VydGVldGh3aGl0ZW5pbmcub3JnLw__" target="_blank">laser teeth whitening</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teWxhc2VydGVldGh3aGl0ZW5pbmcub3JnL2h5ZHJvZ2VuLXBlcm94aWRlLXRlZXRoLXdoaXRlbmluZy8_" target="_blank">click now</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb6c8a8dd52e77488656e6e3dba96b59" url=""><![CDATA[Swiss Whites Teeth Whitening Kits Will Leave Your Teeth Glea<br/><br/>&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailyrosen.dreamhosters.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2011%2F07%2Fbefore_after_deep_bleaching.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailyrosen.dreamhosters.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/before_after_deep_bleaching.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;teeth whitening&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot;/&gt;<br />After you undergo teeth whitening, there are a few steps you should follow to keep the color of your shiny white teeth. Proper oral hygiene is the number one factor in keeping your teeth white, but you should also avoid any harsh chemicals in your mouth or dark-colored drinks immediately following the procedure. For the long lasting effects, any dark-colored drinks should be consumed with a straw to limit the amount of staining your teeth undergo again.<br />There are innumerable cosmetic dentists in NJ who help their patients realize their dreams of having a gorgeous smile. Before starting the teeth whitening procedure, the cosmetic dentist first determines whether the patient is fit for teeth whitening or not and what type of teeth whitening methods would offer him/her the best results. This is due to the fact that different types of stains require different teeth whitening solutions and procedures.<br />&lt;iframe width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2Fembed%2F2hKfYzLXp-E%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://youtube.com/embed/2hKfYzLXp-E&quot</a>; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;<br />People looking to have the most dramatic results without a trip to the dentist should use the whitening strips; brush on gels or whitening tray systems. These products provide the best tooth whitening results for people who choose to whiten their teeth on their own at home. Each of these products is used for a period of weeks. They are either used twice a day or for an extended time once a day. These types of whiteners start to show their results after 14 days and the results improve with extended use and are easily maintainable.<br />BriteSmile is considered one of the gentlest teeth whitening procedures around, and many people with sensitive teeth chose it. It utilizes a hydrogen peroxide gel that has a very carefully mixed chemical balance for the best whitening results. It takes three twenty minute applications of the gel, making it the perfect procedure for those people who are in a hurry.<br />Laser Whitening. This is also called the &quot;power whitening&quot;. Though very expensive, a lot of people, especially recording artists and film stars, consider it the most effective teeth whitening technique.<br />In this article you will learn how to use food grade hydrogen peroxide as an all natural alternative to whiten your teeth at home. But first let's look at what else is available.<br />Undergoing the process to have your teeth whitened by a cosmetic dentist is virtually painless and can be done in a short amount of time. Your professional dentist will attempt to help you achieve the shade of white you desire, even if it takes more than one visit to get to that shade. The professional whitening your dentist can provide will also last much longer than any products you can use at home.<br />If you are tired of wasting money on countless whitening toothpastes, maybe it is time that you went to the dentist to get your teeth whitened. Even though there are many different tooth pastes, whitening strips and gums that claim to brighten the shade of your smile, you will never find a product that gives you the same results in as little time as you can at your dentist's office.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYWlseXN0cmVuZ3RoLm9yZy9wZW9wbGUvMTk1NTQ5Mi9qb3VybmFs" target="_blank">Knowing Your Options For Natural Teeth Whitening</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy8yMzI4ODU0" target="_blank">Whiter Teeth, Teeth Whitening, Natural Teeth Whitening</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FsZnJlZGRjb3VsdGVyMTQucG9kb21hdGljLmNvbS9lbnRyeS8yMDEyLTA5LTE1VDAzXzI1XzAzLTA3XzAw" target="_blank">Phony Teeth Whitening Exposed</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="21b1decd7ddd5e01eefb0f54d0417420" url=""><![CDATA[Teeth Whitening Results In Cleaner Teeth<br/><br/>Products that work to give you a stunning smile<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8169%2F7990179129_779fa086af.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8169/7990179129_779fa086af.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;205&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;<br /><br />There are plenty of options open to you to whiten your smile. Cut back on drinks that can stain your teeth, like coffee or tea. Have your teeth professionally cleaned on a regular basis by your dentist. You can have your teeth whitened professionally. Of course, getting your teeth whitened professionally can be expensive, but there are other options. There are all sorts of teeth whitening products out there. Of course, figuring out which products work the best and the most effectively can be a challenge. In this article we will take a look at the highest rated teeth whitening products on the market.<br /><br />In relation to nature and healing products, strawberries are generally popular. There are two ways you can go if you want to use strawberries to whiten your teeth. To begin, you can dice the strawberries, put them on your teeth and let them sit for a few minutes, brush your teeth and then rinse your mouth out completely. You can also smash the strawberries up into a pulp, add some salt to make a paste and then brush that paste on to your teeth. Let the paste linger for a few minutes and then rinse out your mouth thoroughly. A majority of people have a preference for the pulp method because it gives them greater results. <br /><br />The Philips Sonicare HealthyWhite Power Toothbrush has grown rapidly in popularity over the last year or so. These are little known secrets of teeth whitening that are quickly becoming more popular. Users who swear by them don't hesitate to pay the 90 bucks for one toothbrush. This product does not require bleach or chemicals to whiten your teeth. It works by removing the stains that have set in by giving you a vigorous brushing. Most people recognize the sonicare brand as the best toothbrush around. This toothbrush helps get you the extra time you need when brushing visible teeth. A few weeks from now you will see a visible difference in the overall color of your teeth.<br /><br />Have you tried one of the dozens of whitening toothpastes that are on the market today? It's hard to find toothpaste that doesn't contain at least a miniscule amount of teeth whitener. All of the major toothpaste brands make whitening toothpastes that you can use to counteract minor stains and discoloration. Your dentist will be able to tell you which one will work the best for you. Just remember that whitening toothpastes have a reputation for being harsh on the enamel.<br /><br />Cavities can increase when the enamel is weak, so don't use too much toothpaste whitener. <br /><br />You don't have to have expesive treatments to get a brighter smile. You will find whitening pastes, gels, trays, powders available. How do you know which product is best? Your best option is to ask your dentist. This will help you figure out the best course of action for your teeth. Before you know it your smile will blow them away.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL0NhbWVyb25FQ29uZTIxLm5ld3N2aW5lLmNvbS9fbmV3cy8yMDEyLzA5LzE2LzEzODkxODAxLWhhdmUtdGhlLXRlZXRoLXlvdXZlLWFsd2F5cy13YW50ZWQtd2l0aC10aGVzZS10ZWV0aC13aGl0ZW5pbmctaWRlYXM_" target="_blank">Teeth Whitening Advice That Can Really Work</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYWlseXN0cmVuZ3RoLm9yZy9wZW9wbGUvMTk1NDI0Mi9qb3VybmFs" target="_blank">Make Your Smile Your Best Fashion Accessory With These Tips</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/forrestfrankie/blog/blogid=12049109" target="_blank">Having A Brighter Smile Through Teeth Whitening</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="17e62e2f8f39e937530b01500db6b05b" url=""><![CDATA[Print White Teeth Always Keeps Smile<br/><br/>Natural Solutions For Many Teeth and Gum Problems<br /><br />Whether you're trying to cure a toothache, make your teeth whiter or prevent gum disease, there are many natural remedies that can be helpful in between visits to the dentist. Brushing and flossing your teeth is certainly important, but there are numerous other methods available that can give these a boost, like herbs, oils, etc. We will offer you some hints on different ways you can optimize and maintain a healthy mouth.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8169%2F7992620981_47e7928ee7.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8169/7992620981_47e7928ee7.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;217&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;<br /><br />Even though we are going to focus upon natural remedies for proper gum and tooth care, if you have an urgent need to go to the dentist, always do that first. Some people will have, for instance, an abscess tooth which needs to be taken care of right away. Sometimes your tooth can become so infected that it can spread throughout your body causing you to be ill. Along with the bitter taste and a swollen jaw, a tooth infection that is spreading can produce the symptoms in your body. If you are feeling pain, get some prescription pain medication from your dentist, along with antibiotics to clear up the infection. If you can't get to a dentist, or you can't afford it, it's best to go to an emergency room where you'll at least be given medicine to bring the abscessed tooth under control. You've probably heard of the many health benefits of green tea, and this is something that's also very good for your teeth. Green tea packs a punch with the antioxidants supplying a huge variety of positive aspects like inhibiting some diseases, adding a little pizzazz to your metabolism, keeping your weight in check and helping achieve healthy gums too. There are alternate solutions you can use if you opt to use green tea. If you do not like taking supplements, you can find green tea as an additive in mouthwash and toothpaste. The quality in tea that delivers a healing trait is called a catechin; it is advisable to drink tea in order to get the best exposure to your teeth.<br /><br />Common sense is probably your best bet in regard to taking care of your teeth. There are just a few simple things we need to do everyday. You need to floss at least once a day. You should also brush your teeth twice a day. To make sure that our teeth are healthy, we need to avoid the common everyday sugary foods that we have access to which can be detrimental to our teeth and gums. This includes beverages such as soda, which are highly acidic, and wear away the enamel on your teeth. By ignoring these problems, or at least not applying common sense principles, dental problems may be in the pipeline if you don't do something soon. Our overall health is greatly affected by our mouth because it is the first place where infections and toxins will likely be present. If you can maintain clean teeth and gums; you will be less likely to have as many cavities and tooth decay. Of course your dentist will have the ultimate say on your dental needs, but you can increase the positivity of your dental hygiene by following some of the remedies we have suggested above.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9EaWVnb0RBYnVybjE4L3Bvc3RzLzIzOTA0NDcvU29tZStGcmVxdWVudGx5K0Fza2VkK1F1ZXN0aW9ucytXaXRoK1RlZXRoK1doaXRlbmluZw__" target="_blank">Effective At - Home Teeth Whitening Remedies</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvdG54Y2Zla3VzcnV5bXhxc21nZWgvY29udGVudC8xMC1tb3N0LWVmZmVjdGl2ZS1uYXR1cmFsLXRlZXRoLXdoaXRlbmluZy1pZGVhcy1udXJzZS1zLXR1dG9yaWFsLTY0Mzc0MDU_" target="_blank">3 Things Teeth Whitening Brilliance Can Give You</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGl2ZW5vdGRlYWQuY29tL0FkZW5FQWxsZXJkaWNlMTIvV2hhdC1BcmUtWW91ci1PcHRpb25zLVdpdGgtVGVldGgtV2hpdGVuaW5nLVRyZWF0bWVudHMtLXByb2ZpbGUtMjg2MTY4Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">Your Teeth Whitening Options</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="40803434bfb4f86769240dfbf4b440e5" url=""><![CDATA[Are Mint Cosmetics The Next Step Forward For Teeth Whitening<br/><br/>Whitened teeth are something many people like the look of particularly when it comes to celebrities and movie stars. It matters much more, though, that you keep your teeth and gums free of harmful substances such as bacteria, etc. Keep reading to learn a few things that you can do to clean your teeth and ensure that your dental checkups go as quickly and as painlessly as possible.<br /><br />As someone who wants whiter teeth it is important to practice caution in the methods you choose to reach this goal. It is important to not just jump on a friend's advice or on something you read on the web--talk to your dentist and do your homework first. For instance, one of the most common pieces of advice you will be given for whiter teeth is to use baking soda. A professional or a dentist, however, will warn against making regular use of this specific product. Baking soda is abrasive and can be quite damaging to the enamel on your teeth if you use it a lot. Other substances that can damage your mouth if you use them too much are lemon juice and vinegar. While great for temporarily whitening, prolonged use is damaging because these substances are highly acidic. This is one area where some commonly suggested home remedies aren't always good to follow. <br /><br />Traditionally in India, the neem tree is used for keeping the teeth clean and healthy. The bark, twigs, and leaves from the neem tree have antiseptic properties. Still being used in many parts of the world, neem twigs can be purchased online and in health food stores. There's one other way you can benefit from the neem tree if using a twig to brush your teeth is just too weird for you. Many natural toothpastes now contain neem.<br /><br />This will help you clean your teeth naturally and safely, as well as prevent gum diseases from developing. You'll find natural toothpastes that have neem and healing herbs as well.<br /><br />People who like to chew gum are unknowingly damaging their teeth because of the sugar in the gum. However, plaque formation can be prevented by chewing gum that has xylitol, which is a natural sweetener. Chewing is generally good for you because it promotes the flow of saliva in your mouth. As a result, it prevents food particles from getting stuck and plaque from forming in your teeth. But most chewing gums contain either sugar or sugar substitutes that can actually harm the teeth.<br /><br />You can chew gum that's all-natural instead. You'll find chewing gums promoting whiter teeth as well. If you have dentures or have had a lot of dental work done already, chewing gum might not be recommended as it can stick to dental work. <br /><br />There may be days when you feel it's just a hassle to go through all the trouble to keep your teeth clean, but know that it's all worth it. It won't take you long to floss, brush, and rinse your mouth every day. Regularly visiting your dentist is also something you need to do to make sure your teeth are in good health. If you make it a point to practice good dental habits, you lower your chances of developing more serious dental problems.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Rldm9ueGJlZ2JpZTE5LnBvc3Rlcm91cy5jb20vaGF2ZS10aGUtdGVldGgteW91dmUtYWx3YXlzLXdhbnRlZC13aXRoLXRoZXNl" target="_blank">Simple Advice For Brighter, Whiter Teeth</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYWR2aWxsZS5jb20vYmxvZ3MvNTU4MDI2X3NpbXBsZV9hZHZpY2VfZm9yX2JyaWdodGVyX3doaXRlcl90ZWV0aA__" target="_blank">What You Should Do To Whiten Your Teeth</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy8yMzU0NzYz" target="_blank">Have The Teeth You've Always Wanted With These Teeth Whitening Ideas</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="56718369b650f861c324bec99d4b229b" url=""><![CDATA[Best Teeth Whitening Products For Your Perfect Smile<br/><br/>The preference of bleaching agent for any in-office teeth whitening treatment is the powerful hydrogen peroxide. It is a fast-acting ingredient contained in teeth whitening gel. When used for whitening, hydrogen peroxide concentrations range from 9% to 40%.<br />Teeth Whitening Techniques and ProductsToday there are a variety of techniques and products available to whiten your teeth. There are many at home whitening products available that use carbamide peroxide gel and also professional whitening options at your dentist. Both of these techniques are very effective at enhancing your smile, but at home whitening takes a bit longer to notice results.<br />&lt;iframe width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2Fembed%2FUwqnwFZoPZU%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://youtube.com/embed/UwqnwFZoPZU&quot</a>; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;<br />Everyone I know wants a bright beautiful smile. It is very important for us to take great care of one's teeth in order to achieve a great smile. An attractive smile can also help your appearance and to get a bright and attractive smile; you will need teeth whitening. Teeth bleaching will ensures that you have a more enthusiastic and confident smile to improve to your personality.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmycityteethwhitening.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2012%2F01%2Fphoto-teeth-whitening.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://mycityteethwhitening.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/01/photo-teeth-whitening.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;best teeth whitening&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot;/&gt;<br />Tooth whitening home kits certainly are worth checking out. At-home whitening kits usually employ a method of teeth bleaching (though they vary greatly). It is not perfect and has its own set of temporary disadvantages such as sore gums, slow results if at all, inconvenience of wearing gooey-saliva filled plastic trays and other contraptions etc.<br />Ask for referrals: Is any of your friends been using teeth whitening product which is effective? Then that is probably the right place to begin your search. It can prove to be an easy way to shop for the best teeth whitening kit. You can also ask your dentist to recommend a teeth whitening product.<br />Whiter teeth can lead to more confidence, a better first impression and a healthier smile. With many methods available to accomplish the goal of whiter teeth, many are using these methods to brighten their smile. While, there are many cosmetic dentists who offer amazing results with in-office whitening, this can be costly and time consuming.<br />There are many of these products that you can use and you can even ask your doctor for product samples. Another alternative could be the natural ingredients that you find at the grocer that you can use for teeth cleaning. Another important thing that you should consider is practicing a healthy lifestyle as well as changing your eating habits. You also need to avoid all the factors that trigger discoloration like cigarettes, coffee, alcohol and any other food that is too sugary. Teeth whitening London is a very safe and hygienic procedure that will leave you with an admirable confident sparkling smile.<br />Now that you know more about how to find the best teeth whitener strips to use at home, you should definitely begin researching a few different types so that you can go out and buy some to try as soon as possible. Do not suffer with stained teeth, there is another way! Even if you cannot afford to enlist the help of a dentist, you can have whiter teeth. Try out some teeth whitening strips and you'll be well on your way to a sparkling white smile in no time at all!<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYWR2aWxsZS5jb20vYmxvZ3MvNTUwMjM1X25hdHVyYWxfdGVldGhfd2hpdGVuaW5nX3RpcHM_" target="_blank">Teeth Whitening Is Not As Hard As You Think</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXJlY3RvcmlzZS5jb20vbGlzdGluZy81MTI1MjMtQWR2aWNlLU9uLUhvdy1Uby1XaGl0ZW4tWW91ci1UZWV0aC5odG1s" target="_blank">Whiter Teeth Can Be Yours With These Handy Tips.</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdXBlcm5vdmEuY29tL0FzYUtDb2xxdWhvdW4xL2Jsb2cvODMyNTkz" target="_blank">Advice On How To Whiten Your Teeth</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="78200d02906c999b6d90496fe6986ddd" url=""><![CDATA[Is Natural Teeth Whitening Effective?<br/><br/>Tooth Whitening Products that Will Give You the Most Beautiful Smile in the World<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8445%2F7998499948_cb8614eb03.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8445/7998499948_cb8614eb03.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;241&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;<br /><br />Wanting to have a whiter smile is nothing to be embarrassed about. We all want our smiles to be as bright and shiny as possible. After all, a healthy white smile is a lot more fun to look at than a discolored and stained smile. Back in the day, the dentist was the only one that could give you a professionally done teeth whitening treatment. Currently, there are a lot of teeth whitening products that can be bought OTC and do a great job. There are also things from nature that can be used as a tooth whitener. Keep reading until you discover the most popular teeth whiteners available.<br /><br />You probably already know that baking soda works great as a cleaner in your house. Were you familiar with baking soda's ability to clean your mouth too? You have probably noticed the baking soda toothpastes that are on the market. Even though you can use these to whiten your teeth, baking soda can do the same job. If you choose to use this method, try mixing baking soda and salt together and use it to brush your teeth in a forceful manner.<br /><br />Let it stay on your teeth for a couple of minutes and then rinse out your mouth entirely. However, be aware that this methods does not taste good at all. <br /><br />The white insides of orange peels can also be wonderful teeth whitening products. You can decide to put the orange peel in your mouth on your teeth or you can use it in a mashed up mixture of orange peel and bay leaves, which produce a organic tooth whitener. Both methods work well, but you may not like the taste that comes from the addition of the bay leaves.<br /><br />Have you tested any of the many whitening toothpastes that are on the shelves right not? It is difficult to find a toothpaste without some type of whitener in it. All of the major toothpaste brands make whitening toothpastes that you can use to counteract minor stains and discoloration. You dentist can determine which one is the best for you. Be careful because a majority of whitening toothpastes are very bad on your tooth enamel.<br /><br />Cavities will develop if you have a weak enamel, so do not use too much whitening toothpaste. <br /><br />There are all sorts of popular teeth whitening products to choose from. Ask your dentist about a method that would work the best for you. If you are having problems with cavities, you might want to talk to your dentist concerning a whitening session. However, if you have a healthy smile, you should be able to use any tooth whitening product available.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pYW1zcG9ydC5vcmcvcGcvYmxvZy9Eb21lbmljVUJhcnRvbjE5L3JlYWQvMTAyNDE1MTcvdGVldGgtd2hpdGVuaW5nLXRpcHMteW91LWNhbnQtcGFzcy11cC1vbg__" target="_blank">Get Whiter Teeth! Follow These Tips And Trickwww./a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL01lbmRvZWx6amVhQ2FybXlxZWxpdGEubmV3c3ZpbmUuY29tL19uZXdzLzIwMTIvMDkvMTgvMTM5MzIzOTQtZ2V0LXdoaXRlci10ZWV0aC1mb2xsb3ctdGhlc2UtdGlwcy1hbmQtdHJpY2tzMQ__" target="_blank">How To Have Whiter Teeth With Natural Methods</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYWR2aWxsZS5jb20vYmxvZ3MvNTUwMjM1X25hdHVyYWxfdGVldGhfd2hpdGVuaW5nX3RpcHM_" target="_blank">Tricks To Getting Whiter Teeth Quickly And Effectively</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d5b8a61cd6cd28a237bdb6a7c4fca255" url=""><![CDATA[Tips On Natural Teeth Whitening Methods<br/><br/>Brighten Your Smile with Teeth Whitening Products<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8443%2F8004434754_51885f58dd.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8443/8004434754_51885f58dd.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;293&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;<br /><br />Wanting to have a whiter smile is nothing to be embarrassed about. We all wish to have the whitest and prettiest smile there is. After all, it is better to look at a smile that is white and beautiful than one that is discolored and stained. It used to be that the only you could get your teeth professionally whitened was to book an appt with your dentist. Today there are a lot of tooth whitening products that you can buy over the counter that will also get the job done. There are also things from nature that can be used as a tooth whitener. Read on and find out which are the most popular teeth whitening products.<br /><br />In relation to nature and healing products, strawberries are generally popular. There are two approaches you can take if you want to use strawberries to whiten your teeth. You can slice up the berries and put the slices directly on to your teeth and leave them there for a few minutes and then thoroughly brush your teeth and rinse your mouth. You can also smash the strawberries up into a pulp, add some salt to make a paste and then brush that paste on to your teeth. Let the paste linger for a few minutes and then rinse out your mouth thoroughly. A lot of people like the pulp method because it gives a better outcome. <br /><br />Did you know that hydrogen peroxide could be utilized as a mouthwash that heals? This is found in the brown bottles and not in the white or clear bottles. You can find it in the same location as your toothpastes and other oral products. Blend equal parts of hydrogen peroxide and water together and then gargle with it in your mouth. It will kill bacteria and fight cavities. You can also put your toothbrush into this healing mixture and utilize it to brush your teeth. Quick whitening. Be careful and do not swallow the mixture.<br /><br />Rinse your mouth thoroughly after each application. Even though hydrogen peroxide is wonderful when it is used to get your teeth whiter and clean your mouth, it is very harmful if swallowed.<br /><br />BriteSmile To Go Whitening Pens are very popular. Teeth whitening pens have become quite popular in the last few years. Because they are easy to use for spot treating, more and more people are choosing pens for whitening. A common complaint is that it takes longer for the pens to work than it does for trays or strips. Many users suggest using the pens as a spot treatment after having your teeth whitened professionally to keep your teeth bright and shiny. <br /><br />They are many kinds of well known tooth whiteners that you can opt for. Ask your dentist to recommend the best method for you. If you have issues with cavities, you probably want your dentist to do a whitening. However, if your teeth are healthy, you should be capable of using any of the teeth whitening products on the market.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9BbWFyaW9uS0JhY2hvcnNrL3Bvc3RzLzI0MjIwMDYvSGF2ZStUaGUrVGVldGgrWW91JTI3dmUrQWx3YXlzK1dhbnRlZCtXaXRoK1RoZXNlK1RlZXRoK1doaXRlbmluZytJZGVhcw__" target="_blank">How To Get Whiter Teeth Quickly And Easily</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL0p1YW1hbnVsQmFuY2Vrcy5uZXdzdmluZS5jb20vX25ld3MvMjAxMi8wOS8yMC8xMzk3OTI3Ni1zaW1wbGUtYWR2aWNlLWZvci1icmlnaHRlci13aGl0ZXItdGVldGg_" target="_blank">Have The Teeth You've Always Wanted With These Teeth Whitening Ideas</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvdGtwZWNwcHFqeWVrYWhweXl2ZGgvY29udGVudC9jaGVjay1vdXQtdGhlc2UtZ3JlYXQtdGVldGgtd2hpdGVuaW5nLXRpcHMtNjQ3NTk2Nw__" target="_blank">Check Out These Great Teeth Whitening Tips</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4a3492f8f7fec0e9f1099e4f9e3f2146" url=""><![CDATA[Teeth Whitening Advice Everyone Should Know About<br/><br/>There are many people who yearn for a bright, white smile. Luckily, there are many actions you can take in order to prevent new stains forming on your teeth. If this doesn't go far enough for you, some products can actually restore whiteness as well. The below article provides some suggestions for whitening your teeth and maintaining it that way.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8456%2F8049924110_6a5d8659a8.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8456/8049924110_6a5d8659a8.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;289&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;<br />It's easy to get teeth whitening strips, and they are quite inexpensive. You place the strip on your teeth and let it remain for a set amount of time. Whitening strips enjoyed a brief surge in popularity, but their lack of results mean that less and less people are buying them.<br /><br />Thoroughly read the instructions on the teeth whitening products, and follow them very carefully. Don't leave them on too long, or it can cause gum inflammation and increase your teeth sensitivity. To make the most of your whitening procedure, you should also consider avoiding any drinks that are very acidic, such as soda.<br /><br />If you are uncomfortable about your teeth color, your dentist can give you information about teeth whitening options. Although some people may think this is just wasting money, anything that can help you regain self-esteem and increase the quality of your life is a worthwhile investment.<br /><br />If you use whitening strips that are supposed to stay on your teeth for two hours and the experience is making your gums sore, switch to the sort of strips that only stay on for a half-hour. Although the half hour whitening strips have to be applied for a longer time period, two weeks or so, gums won't be as sensitive.<br /><br />Drinking water is a great thing for the health of your mouth since it helps whiten your teeth. Drinking water regularly will help rinse your teeth, and prevent stains from appearing on your teeth. You should drink water while you are eating and after you eat.<br /><br />Eating cheese and other dairies is good for the enamel. Studies show that the calcium inherent in cheese can aid in building up your tooth enamel. Restoring the health of your enamel leads to a brighter, whiter smile. More cheese, please!<br /><br />Ask your dentist if he offers an at home gel that will whiten teeth. Your dentist will create a mouth piece that is full of gel, and you will be instructed to wear this piece for several nights per night for two to three weeks. This method is reported to whiten your teeth by up to eight shades.<br /><br />If you whiten your teeth to the point of overdoing it, you can run into more problems and actually do more damage to your teeth. In fact, if the whitening product you're using is extremely strong, you could end up permanently harming your teeth. You will ruin your goal of whiter teeth and they may not be fixable. Your dentist may be able to help you find a whitening product that is safe and effective.<br /><br />Most of these products claim to be better than your average toothpaste, but this is not the case at all. It is wise to consult your dentist before using any teeth whitening toothpaste, for he or she will be able to guide you towards the best choice, to get the maximum results you desire.<br /><br />Whitening your teeth is a great way to make the quality of your life better. Whiter teeth will make you more physically attractive and increase your level of confidence. Your smile will be wider and more natural as you proudly show off your pearly whites. Follow these teeth whitening tips to get quick but sustainable results.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RhbmdlbG9sY29ua2xlMjIucG9zdGVyb3VzLmNvbS9uYXR1cmFsLXRlZXRoLXdoaXRlbmluZy1tZXRob2Rz" target="_blank">3 Things Teeth Whitening Brilliance Can Give You</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/denzelbraulio/blog/blogid=12120860" target="_blank">Knowing Your Options For Natural Teeth Whitening</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9EYWtvdGFOQWRraW5zNy9wb3N0cy8yNTU4MDgxL1RlZXRoK1doaXRlbmluZytIb21lK1RpcHM_" target="_blank">Print Teeth Whitening At Home Gets Positive Reviews Up!</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e8b2601e3656032cd3c7dc31aeee4277" url=""><![CDATA[Teeth Whitening Prices<br/><br/>Oral Care Myths and Proper Care for Your Teeth<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8037%2F8051587567_5d3dc194a2.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8037/8051587567_5d3dc194a2.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;right&quot; width=&quot;206&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;<br />You know, it really is not necessary to be high tech with caring for your teeth and gums. For some reason, a lot of people either ignore them or simply do not bother to learn.<br /><br />So take a good look at all you do for your teeth, and then if needed make important changes. There is lots you can do beyond reducing sugar consumption and regular brushing. If your oral hygiene habits are lacking, then you should make the effort if you want to have nice looking teeth later in life.<br /><br />Every time you eat some, especially a full meal, rinse out with water to reduce food particles around your teeth. You know what needs to be done, you really have to use the water in an effort to keep food from building up around and between teeth. It is best to rinse immediately after you eat so you get the food particles out before they become lodged and settled.<br /><br />There is nothing wrong with going ahead and just drinking that water you rinse with. So this will work great if you are not in a position to brush after lunch while at work. Improving your gum circulation is one of the reasons that you need to brush your mouth. Bleeding gums and other problems can be prevented by flossing correctly. Another great approach is buying one of those devices with soft rubber tips on the ends. Toothbrushes had those on them very many years ago but not anymore. Use that rubber tip to give a gentle massage to your gums in the areas that are around your teeth. The tool is meant for massage, not for food removal. You do not have to do this every single day, but it can be very useful to do it several times throughout the week.<br /><br />It is critically important that you prevent your gum lines from receding as long as possible. If you have been using a hard-bristle brush, then take a look at your gums and check them for signs of receding. So remember that when you brush, you always want to just be firm or a little less so and not hard. Ask your dentist about this if you are not sure and want a professional opinion.<br /><br />Trust us, this is not something you want to happen to you when you are in your twenties, and that is not unusual either. <br /><br />Proper care of your teeth means a lot of things, and the conditions you can prevent are not hard to do. This gum condition happens to young people and adults with increasing regularity. Once your gums have fallen down, then you will need to be extra diligent about oral hygiene.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teWxhc2VydGVldGh3aGl0ZW5pbmcub3JnLw__" target="_blank">laser teeth whitening</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teWxhc2VydGVldGh3aGl0ZW5pbmcub3JnL2h5ZHJvZ2VuLXBlcm94aWRlLXRlZXRoLXdoaXRlbmluZy8_" target="_blank">learn this here now</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="78e550b564f1216e7228af9fcb57690c" url=""><![CDATA[10 Best Natural Teeth Whitening Tips - Dentist Guide<br/><br/>How To Keep Your Teeth Healthy - Simple Techniques<br /><br />Your teeth are often used as an indicator of sorts to determine whether or not your body is healthy in general. Your mouth is useful for many reasons, one of which is a place to stop infection and disease from spreading to the rest of your body. If you follow some basic precautions, such as we'll be covering in this article, it's not that hard to maintain healthy teeth and gums.<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdXBlcm5vdmEuY29tL0dodXJheWNlV2VhdGhlYm9yc3BvL2Jsb2cvMTExNDcyNQ__" target="_blank">Teeth Whitening Home Tips</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvamd0cGFnemh4Ym1tbWNqZnR6aG8vY29udGVudC9yZXN1bHRzLW9mLXRlZXRoLXdoaXRlbmluZy1hZ2VudHMtdmFyeS02NzA1OTE0" target="_blank">Truths And Myths About Natural Teeth Whitening</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9FbWVyc29uWkNvcmUxNC9wb3N0cy8yNTgyNDI4L1RlZXRoK1doaXRlbmluZyUzQStIb3crSXMrSXQrSW1wb3J0YW50JTNG" target="_blank">All - Natural And Economical Teeth Whitening Suggestions</a><br /><br />It is very important to floss your teeth, a habit that most people do not have. Flossing cleans areas of the teeth that a brush can't reach. This is something you should do once a day to get the maximum benefits. Forming the habit of flossing on a daily basis is what everyone needs to do - it really is that quick! Anyone that has flossed before understands how little time is involved and how many benefits you receive because of your due diligence. A water flosser is also an alternative, something that is much easier to do than using actual string. Flossing is a way that you can avoid pain later at the dentist with just a few minutes of extra work. A healthy diet is very important for everyone, and it is also good for your mouth and your body. People that have weight problems, or that are sick very often, we'll eat healthier - this is also how you make your gums and teeth wholesome as well. Eating anything from Swiss chard to kale is a good choice to make because of the vitamin B component built into the vegetables themselves. You also feel better and your teeth will look great! The other side of the coin is to avoid junk foods as much as possible, as these contribute to tooth decay and other dental problems. It is definitely worthwhile to eat the right foods - a healthy body and teeth will definitely be yours.<br /><br />You should also stay away from highly acidic foods, and drinks, as this can have a detrimental effect on your teeth. This can actually cause damage to the enamel on your teeth so you should stay away from acidic products. To be specific, carbonated sodas are probably the worst thing in this regard. If you only drink water, but it is sparkling, you should revert back to regular water immediately. The enamel of your teeth can actually be eroded by drinking too much grapefruit juice or orange juice which are very acidic. Although fruit is healthy, fruit juices contain higher concentrations of sugar than fresh fruit, which is also potentially harmful for your teeth. To really protect your teeth, drink beverages like water and tea which will not harm your teeth. Green tea has proven benefits to your teeth, and even coffee may contain elements that fight tooth decay if you don't add a lot of sugar to it. <br /><br />Proper hygiene is easy! As long as you start doing it and stay with the program, your mouth and teeth will stay healthy for years to come. As we have said, smoking can be detrimental to your physical and oral health so quit the habit when you can. Basically, all you have to do is visit your dentist regularly, practice good oral hygiene, and your teeth and gums will be healthy for years.<br /><br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8182%2F8055677121_3d21668d8c.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8182/8055677121_3d21668d8c.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;223&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c4f04c3bbac913041295c6777f6d3e11" url=""><![CDATA[Tricks To Whiten Teeth And Keep Them White<br/><br/>How white your teeth are can have effects on other areas of your life because stained or yellow teeth can hold you back. A large number of people have used different solutions to make their teeth whiter. Take the time to consider which option is the best for your teeth before spending too much on any one choice. This article describes the different whitening processes available, and gives you plenty of tips for whitening your teeth.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8321%2F8055677857_bdb58fa8a4.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8321/8055677857_bdb58fa8a4.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;right&quot; width=&quot;232&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;<br /><br />Make sure the toothbrush you use is the right one. Ask your dentist about what brand or type of toothbrush is best.<br /><br />Stop smoking immediately. Smoking has been shown to discolor your teeth due to the nicotine and smoke.<br /><br />One simple thing you can do to get sparkling white teeth is to use a whitening toothpaste. These toothpastes use friction to wipe away plaque and stains. The effects of the paste are gradual, but over time, your teeth will brighten up as it removes stains.<br /><br />Bleach whitening is not recommended if you gum disease of any sort or untreated cavities. You don't want to cause pain to yourself or increase damage to your gums or teeth. If you want to whiten your teeth, but suffer from these conditions, sit down with your dentist to discuss alternative methods.<br /><br />To keep your teeth white, avoid drinking beverages that can stain the teeth. Drinks that stain teeth include soft drinks, tea and coffee. If you were to drink these kinds of beverages, it is a good practice to alternately sip water as you drink them.<br /><br />Talk to your dentist if you're thinking about starting a teeth whitening treatment. There are a large number of items on the market. They can be costly, and also it is hard to deal with finding the ones that will work for you. Check with your dentist to get advice. They should have the best advice for you in this area.<br /><br />Teeth whitening strips can be found easily, as they are readily available at an affordable price. You simply put on the strip for a short period of time to help lighten your teeth. Teeth whitening strips did not work as well as anticipated, and their popularity has lessened.<br /><br />For a quick clean up and whitening of teeth, try eating a delicious apple. Crunchy foods like apples tend to be very abrasive, which quickly brushes away any visible staining without hurting your teeth.<br /><br />In summary, achieving the look of white teeth is very desirable for everyone. Most people think it is impossible to have whiter teeth, so they just let it go. Use these tips and your teeth will become visibly whiter in a few weeks.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pYW1zcG9ydC5vcmcvcGcvYmxvZy9EZXZvblNCYWludGVyMjIvcmVhZC8xMDk3NDAyMi9hbi1hbHRlcm5hdGl2ZS1vZi1uYXR1cmFsLXRlZXRoLXdoaXRlbmluZw__" target="_blank">How Can You Spot The Best Teeth Whitening Kits Online</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dlb2ZmcmV5dWFsZXhhbmQucG9zdGVyb3VzLmNvbS9uYXR1cmFsLXRvb3RoLXdoaXRlbmluZw__" target="_blank">Using A Natural Teeth Whitening Product</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9CcmFuZG9uU0FsYmF1Z2gxL3Bvc3RzLzI1ODI1MTQvTmF0dXJhbCtUZWV0aCtXaGl0ZW5pbmcrLStIb3crVG8rR2V0K1Byb2Zlc3Npb25hbCtSZXN1bHRzK0F0K0hvbWU_" target="_blank">Teeth Whitening Naturally – Home Remedies</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d8fcc3d79a826889abfb29d1a9fb3c93" url=""><![CDATA[New Teeth Whitening Treatment<br/><br/>However, it is important to bear in mind that too much use of the teeth whitening pen can yield uneven effects. As such, to obtain better result and uniform bleaching it is advisable to employ a special brush tip. This particular special brush tip is handy and doubly dependable.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.downersgrovedental.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2010%2F10%2FDowners_Grove_Dentist_Teeth_Whitening.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.downersgrovedental.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/10/Downers_Grove_Dentist_Teeth_Whitening.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;teeth whitening&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot;/&gt;<br />Teeth Cleaning: The dental technician or the dentist will start the process by cleansing your teeth. This is important because the plaque, that is there on your teeth, may have a major adverse impact on the teeth whitening process.<br />Dentist will tell you if it’s appropriate for you to undergo a teeth whitening treatment and will recommend it if you are. First the dentist will apply a gel or rubber shield on gums so that the soft tissue will not be damaged. Then they will apply the bleaching product to the teeth by means of a tray which will fit the shape of your mouth. After this the dentist would just give you some instructions and you’ll continue the treatment at home.<br />How Should Hydrogen Peroxide Whitening Gels Be Used?Carefully follow the directions as written by the manufacturer and do not use more gel than specified to avoid side effects like gum irritation and pain. Specifics will vary from brand to brand, but generally you will use a tray to hold the gel in contact with your teeth for a short period of time per session, with one or two sessions per day as needed.<br />&lt;iframe width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2Fembed%2F_d_ovQjk5ag%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://youtube.com/embed/_d_ovQjk5ag&quot</a>; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;<br />Teeth tend to get stained and discolored over time due to various reasons. Some of the common factors responsible for this are excessive consumption of tea, coffee, soft drinks, to tobacco, or red wine. The teeth whitening process is also helpful in lightening the naturally dark colored teeth with tetracycline, and those with deeper stains and discolorations.<br />Different whitening products will get you different results depending on the amount and concentration of the active whitening ingredient, called peroxide, that is found in the product. One of the most commonly used over the counter at home whitening products are teeth whitening strips. Whitening strips are made by a number of different manufacturers and vary greatly in the concentrations of peroxide used and in their whitening effectiveness.<br />People with stained or dull teeth usually benefit from whitening, which is a safe and effective way to brighten stained, discolored or dull teeth. Even a stubborn single tooth that is noticeably duller or less white than your other teeth can be individually brightened.<br />The shade of white you choose to go with your teeth is a matter of personal preference. You might be limited to a shade that is a little less than you desire, depending on the initial damage that was done to your teeth. Extensive damage from smoking, coffee or other harmful substances might be harder to get as white as you would like, but any improvement can be better than your original stains.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pYW1zcG9ydC5vcmcvcGcvYmxvZy9BbmRlcnNvblJCYWlsbGllL3JlYWQvMTEwNDY2MzUvdGVldGgtd2hpdGVuaW5nLWdlbHMtZG8tdGhleS13b3Jr" target="_blank">Selected Teeth Whitening Methods That Work</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvemVrcWtrbmFnZmtxeHZxcnBtYnkvY29udGVudC90YWtlLWNhcmUtb2YtdG9vdGhhY2hlcy10aGUtbmF0dXJhbC13YXktd2l0aC1uby1kZW50aXN0LTY3ODA5MDc_" target="_blank">Natural Teeth Whitening Options And Other Cheap Alternatives</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy8yNTk2NTUw" target="_blank">Teeth Whitening By Natural Means</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ac8130fbc9de4643779c79155599afae" url=""><![CDATA[Print Teeth Whitening At Home Gets Positive Reviews Up!<br/><br/>Teeth whiteners are no longer only reserved for Hollywood starlets with your cosmetic dentist to whiten your teeth. teeth whitening is a phone call away for West Haven and Milford, CT residents by calling the trusted cosmetic dentists.<br />On the other hand, teeth bleaching are the method of making the teeth whiter than its natural color. It makes use of oxidizing agents like carbamide peroxide. Nowadays, there are now whitening products that contain this agent but it is still safer to consult your dentist or have the solution applied by a dental expert to avoid hassles or side effects.<br />To avoid the side effects associated with peroxide teeth bleaching you should only use one high concentration peroxide whitening product at a time. Choose a quality brand of whitening gel, whitening strips or a whitening pen and use it according to the directions. Continue to brush regularly with a high quality toothpaste, either a restorative toothpaste if you are suffering from sensitive teeth, or a whitening toothpaste to maintain the new smile you'll receive from a peroxide whitening product.<br />Almost every product on the market has side effects. I've not seen much side effects coming from a White Ice teeth lightening solution, but it's better to be safe than sorry. If the teeth is more sensitive, ensure you check with your vet or dentist before picking any whitening products. But if your teeth is really yellow-colored, I suggest you twenty-four hours a day test out this product to observe it for yourself.<br />Cosmetic teeth whitening is one of the safest and the most effective teeth whitening procedures. The cosmetic dentists in NJ use state-of-the-art methods and procedures to offer bright, sparkling teeth to their patients. Teeth cleaning, filling of cavities, and treating unhealthy gums, are usually part of the cosmetic teeth whitening. However, complete dental makeovers involve correcting irregular and chipped teeth, reducing gaps between the teeth, re-structuring of lips and chin, and other cosmetic dental procedures in addition to teeth whitening.<br />&lt;iframe width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2Fembed%2FpQbY6UpAlI0%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://youtube.com/embed/pQbY6UpAlI0&quot</a>; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdentalimplantsjalandhar.com%2Fyahoo_site_admin%2Fassets%2Fimages%2Fwhitening.39124922_std.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dentalimplantsjalandhar.com/yahoo_site_admin/assets/images/whitening.39124922_std.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;teeth whitening&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot;/&gt;<br />Another more traditional method of whitening is by applying a bleaching paste to the teeth and using a special toothbrush to scrub them clean. This method is often used on younger patients and generally can be completed in less than 45 minutes.<br />Also involved are 3 adjustable mouth trays to guarantee you get a perfect fitting mouth guard. This indicates that your whitening result really should be maximised without having any leakage of the whitening gel.<br />How Long Will Whitening With Hydrogen Peroxide Take?Just as with the whitening results it's difficult to estimate the length of time you'll need to whiten to reach your goal, but you can expect to see results within one to two weeks of daily treatment. This is far faster than whitening with toothpaste alone.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYWR2aWxsZS5jb20vYmxvZ3MvNjMxOTM0X3RoZV9kYW5nZXJzX29mX3RlZXRoX3doaXRlbmluZ19hdF9ob21l" target="_blank">10 Best Natural Teeth Whitening Tips - Nurse's Guide</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/antoinegrady/blog/blogid=12050632" target="_blank">Natural Teeth Whitening Alternatives</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdXBlcm5vdmEuY29tL2x5SnVmb2RpdHZpaFNoZWEvYmxvZy8xMTc4NDAx" target="_blank">What Are The Safe Natural Teeth Whitening Options At Hand ?</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f16020b68355d90c50c4c42ea334dfef" url=""><![CDATA[Best Teeth Whitening Home Remedies<br/><br/>&lt;iframe width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2Fembed%2FveQy8gDNgfg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://youtube.com/embed/veQy8gDNgfg&quot</a>; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;<br />Strawberry teeth whitening: The secret to this inexpensive home whitening method is acid, which acts as an astringent to remove surface discoloration. However, as in the case of lemon juice, Strawberry also have acid which may be unsafe for the teeth.<br />I think the best strategy if you are looking for the whitest smile when having teeth whitening is just to keep your expectations in check. Not everyone is going to look as white as celebrities teeth featured in fashion magazines or on the TV. The likes of P Diddy, J-Lo and Simon Cowell all have veneers and these are much whiter than the natural tooth's colour so do not expect this outcome unless you have a very white coloured dentin.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fimages01.olx.in%2Fui%2F11%2F95%2F36%2F1340613453_404668936_4-Best-Teeth-Whitening-Kochi-Health-Beauty-Fitness.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://images01.olx.in/ui/11/95/36/1340613453_404668936_4-Best-Teeth-Whitening-Kochi-Health-Beauty-Fitness.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;best teeth whitening&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot;/&gt;<br />One of the first tips to understand is that different kits have different ingredients in different amounts. Most people feel that the best kits contain a high concentrate of carbamide peroxide or hydrogen peroxide, and come in a fairly thick gel. You can do a little research and read technical reviews on the ingredients in different home kits to see what the concentrations are and also read customer reviews that describe real experiences with the products. This can help you decide which ones you may wish to try.<br />With teeth whitening in Dallas, you need never constrain your smile. Laugh out loud and hearty, revealing your wide array of beautiful and sparkling white teeth. Get proactive and buy yourself the best teeth whitening products available. Laser teeth whitening under the supervision of a licensed dentist ensures bright and clean teeth, but it is also the most expensive option. Mouthwashes and pastes without fluoride are a bad idea as they make the teeth brittle. Teeth whitening kits are recommended by the dentists in Dallas.<br />Teeth Whitening Techniques and ProductsToday there are a variety of techniques and products available to whiten your teeth. There are many at home whitening products available that use carbamide peroxide gel and also professional whitening options at your dentist. Both of these techniques are very effective at enhancing your smile, but at home whitening takes a bit longer to notice results.<br />This is simply because they yield the largest concentration levels of both carbamide peroxide (highest quality whitener to date), and potassium nitrate (provides sensitivity protection). These are fabulous alternative products that reside online as opposed to achieving the same 'bright white' effect via your local dentist.<br />Trays: You can get custom-fitted trays, and fill these with the formulations in home teeth whitening kits. You then wear these for a certain period of time, usually for a couple of hours.<br />Sensitive teeth and Allergic The person who have sensitive teeth, receding gums should get a prior permission from their dentists for whitening of the teeth. The persons who are prone to allergies also should not whiten their teeth as the bleaching powder contains peroxide.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvaXZ2dWN0am5kZGJremltZHdxcmcvY29udGVudC90ZWV0aC13aGl0ZW5pbmctdGlwcy10aGF0LXdpbGwtZW5oYW5jZS15b3VyLXNtaWxlLTY4MzMyMjQ_" target="_blank">How To Have Whiter Teeth With Natural Methods</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy8yNjIxMTQy" target="_blank">Successfully Whiten Your Teeth With These Proven Tips</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pYW1zcG9ydC5vcmcvcGcvYmxvZy9BbGZyZWRUQ29tcHRvbjE2L3JlYWQvMTEwNDY3MzYvc3VjY2Vzc2Z1bGx5LXdoaXRlbi15b3VyLXRlZXRoLXdpdGgtdGhlc2UtcHJvdmVuLXRpcHM_" target="_blank">Advice On How To Whiten Your Teeth</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e48dd29ac247072e3be4684fe3eac927" url=""><![CDATA[Natural Teeth Whitening Alternatives & Other Cheap Optio<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy8yNjQzNzc0" target="_blank">Teeth Whitening Naturally</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL1dlcm95ZHJsZXlQYXRrdXJpY2EubmV3c3ZpbmUuY29tL19uZXdzLzIwMTIvMTAvMTEvMTQzNjY3NjctbmF0dXJhbC10ZWV0aC13aGl0ZW5pbmctYXQtaG9tZS10aXBz" target="_blank">Selected Teeth Whitening Methods That Work</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvbWZ2b25teHJoY3FlZm94bGJnZnQvY29udGVudC9hcmUteW91LWluLXNlYXJjaC1vZi10ZWV0aC13aGl0ZW5pbmctdGVjaG5pcXVlcy02ODg5MDg5" target="_blank">Natural Teeth Whitening Alternatives</a><br /><br />Top Recommended Products For Dental Health<br /><br />Healthy teeth might be your goal, but this can be a difficult thing, because many things you do cause problems. One thing that contributes to tooth decay is your diet. When you have a habit, such as chewing gum or smoking, that can cause a problem. This article will give you some recommendations to help you choose good products for preventing cavities, gum disease and other dental woes.<br /><br />White teeth is a goal that many people have, and there are several products that can assist you. Anyone that goes to their local dentist will be able to have their teeth whitened. The problem is that it is the most expensive route to go. Teeth whitening toothpaste is at the other end of the spectrum, something that is affordable for most people. If you have stains on your teeth, this type of toothpaste will work better than regular brands. If you want something stronger than toothpaste, strips and gels can also help you. It is recommended that you use these products for at least two weeks, maybe more. You can maintain the brightness of your teeth by repeating the teeth whitening gel or strips every 60 days. The only drawback is that you can remove the enamel from your teeth if you do it too much. <br /><br />It is even possible to find chewable toothbrushes if you travel a lot or simply don't have access to your normal toothbrush. The market has several products available built on this concept--a combination of toothbrush, toothpaste and, from time to time, even mouthwash. While these can be convenient, it's not good to use them on a regular basis. For one thing, this is very wasteful and will cost a lot more money; furthermore, even though you might be able to use them for a few brushings, they are only designed to be used once. It's also not really recommended for young kids or anybody who may swallow it accidentally. Still, the chewable toothbrush can be useful if you're traveling and don't want to bother with carrying around a toothbrush and toothpaste.<br /><br />No matter what kind of dental products you're using, it's a good idea to visit your dentist at least twice per year. Some people only go to the dentist when they have a toothache, but this isn't a good policy. If you visit your dentist regularly you'll be able to catch any number of problems (like gum disease) while the problem is in its early stages and keep it from getting worse. Your dentist will also be able to help you figure out which products are the best and the best ways to use them. For example, most people do not brush or floss properly--this is something on which your dentist can advise you. How you brush is at least as important as how often and with what kind of toothbrush. <br /><br />Tooth care products are a wise investment if you want to keep your teeth and gums healthy at any age. Gum disease has been shown to lead to heart disease later on. This is yet another reason why having a healthy mouth is essential for your overall health. To make sure that your dental health is always 100%, use some of the dental products we have recommended above.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8056%2F8076215352_40dab88c93.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8056/8076215352_40dab88c93.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;240&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a0cf7df480c86acbf38e24b1fa8eb04" url=""><![CDATA[Teeth Whitening Tips That Can Change Your Life!<br/><br/>More and more individuals are placing a priority on obtaining white teeth. A large number of people have used different solutions to make their teeth whiter. There are a lot of things out there that whiten teeth so you need to think about what the best options are before you use one. This article can help by providing various whitening tips and advice to assist you with your own whitening endeavors.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm9.static.flickr.com%2F8049%2F8082275491_a462b462df.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://farm9.static.flickr.com/8049/8082275491_a462b462df.jpg&quot</a>; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;290&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;<br /><br />Avoid smoking cigarettes and cigars. It is a widely known fact that they can discolor your teeth. To prevent yellow teeth, give up your smoking habit. Speak to your doctor about medications that can help you quit smoking if you're having difficulty. However, the right advice and a strong support system are essential.<br /><br />Don't use mouthwashes. If you are having problems with keeping your teeth looking white, you might want to consider not using it. Mouthwash plays host to a whole series of chemical compounds. Some of these substances may actually discolor or stain your teeth.<br /><br />A thin layer of petroleum jelly can protect your brilliant smile. While it won't taste fantastic, it can create a stain barrier on your teeth for a couple hours.<br /><br />Once you have taken the time to whiten your teeth, you should always keep them clean by brushing regularly throughout the day. Food can encourage the growth of bacteria in your mouth and on your teeth. Whitening your teeth softens them and causes them to be more susceptible to bacteria growth and damage. You can prevent that damage by brushing after each meal.<br /><br />One of the things that you can do in order to get whiter teeth is to drink through a straw. The liquid will not set on the teeth as long, and this reduced the opportunity to stain them. The liquid is naturally guided toward your throat and does not generally contact your teeth.<br /><br />A good toothbrush is essential for keeping your teeth their whitest. Talk to your dentist to determine what sort of brush is best suited for you.<br /><br />A good whitening mouthwash can be helpful. It may take months to see results using this method, but it does help. Hydrogen peroxide is the active ingredient in these mouthwashes, and is known to be effective in teeth whitening. You are going to want to rinse your mouth for thirty seconds twice a day before you brush.<br /><br />After going through any teeth whitening procedures, you should stick to drinking clear liquids at least for the next three days. Right after a whitening treatment, your teeth will be more sensitive and absorb dark pigments from coffee or tea for instance.<br /><br />This could be the best option if your teeth have substantial discoloration or if you are looking for quicker results. A professional cleaning is more expensive but can provide excellent results that can be seen faster than many other treatments.<br /><br />The introduction let you know that opinions differ with regard to teeth whitening. Hopefully this article will have helped you to learn some safe, dependable ways to whiten your teeth. Now you've got what it takes to begin safely working on a dazzling smile.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teWxhc2VydGVldGh3aGl0ZW5pbmcub3JnLw__" target="_blank">laser teeth whitening</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teWxhc2VydGVldGh3aGl0ZW5pbmcub3JnL2h5ZHJvZ2VuLXBlcm94aWRlLXRlZXRoLXdoaXRlbmluZy8_" target="_blank">hydrogen peroxide for whitening teeth</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="15c6fddbbf3468d021ad53f953cb585e" url=""><![CDATA[Teeth Whitening Products In Dallas<br/><br/>The teeth whitening gel is perfect way to make your teeth look snow and cost effective part of the teeth bleaching products. White teeth with dazzling smile help in making the personality of the person look stylish and elegant. To make the smile appealing and attractive some of the interesting tooth whitening techniques available in the market helps in improving the over all appearance of person and leaves a good affects the other.<br />Lost of teeth whitening methods are available, such as whitening toothpastes, over-the-counter gels, rinses, strips, and trays, as well as whitening agents that will get from the dentist.<br />&lt;iframe width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fyoutube.com%2Fembed%2F_JdX4HjaRG8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://youtube.com/embed/_JdX4HjaRG8&quot</a>; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;<br />If you are considering whitening your teeth, then you will need to find all of your options. Believe or not, there is more than one way to get your teeth whitened. Basically there are two ways to get your teeth whitened. You can get it done by a dentist, who is quite expensive, but you can get the results instantly, or you could try some home remedies which take more time and patience but only cost the fraction of the price of a dentist visit. The choice is yours, but you should consider the pros and cons of both before proceeding.<br />&lt;img src=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ragingrouge.com%2F01-beauty-blog-product-reviews-makeup%2Fproduct-reviews%2Fluster-tooth-whitening-whiter-teeth.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.ragingrouge.com/01-beauty-blog-product-reviews-makeup/product-reviews/luster-tooth-whitening-whiter-teeth.jpg&quot</a>; alt=&quot;best teeth whitening&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;300&quot;/&gt;<br />With so much similarity between the various home whitening kits on the market, it can be a tough call to determine which is the best home teeth whitening kit out there. Actually, which is the best wholly depends on how much you want to spend, as all of the products out there are essentially going to give you the same experience.<br />Check reviews: The benefit of shopping online is that you can check for online reviews for best teeth whitening products. There are many third party sites which would publish consumer reviews on various such products for the benefit of customers. Also, if you are directly buying from the suppliers don't forget to check their customer testimonial page before placing your order.<br />For getting long lasting results, it is quite obvious to follow healthy dental hygiene. This includes brushing daily after each meal. Flossing is another good practice that helps in eliminating the debris accumulated in the roots of the teeth. Taking food enriched with calcium is good enough to be taken like milk and cheese. This will strengthen teeth and thus this will lead to teeth whitening as well.  Scaling twice in a year is also recommended as this way the health of the teeth can be maintained. Do visit dentist for regular consultation as this would keep your teeth in good health. You will regain your smiles after getting the treatment and will feel more confident.<br />Whilst home teeth whitening works, and is of course effective it will take more perseverance and time than at the dentist clinic. So, here you have a simple trade off between the cost and speed.<br />Jessie Johanson is a dentist specializing in cosmetic services. Additional information to learn about the best teeth whiteing products.along with her recommendations can be found here.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9EYWtvdGFOQWRraW5zNy9wb3N0cy8yNjY1MjQzL0hvbmVzdCtBZHZpY2UrT24rV2hpdGVuaW5nK1lvdXIrVGVldGgrVG9kYXk_" target="_blank">Maintain Those Pearly Whites With These Tips</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvb3NpdG54YmJxZHR5c25la3d0ZmYvY29udGVudC9nZXQtd2hpdGVyLXRlZXRoLWZvbGxvdy10aGVzZS10aXBzLWFuZC10cmlja3MxLTY5MzM0NDI_" target="_blank">Successfully Whiten Your Teeth With These Proven Tips</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL0NoYW50eWRyYVNidXRvd2Vhc3JzLm5ld3N2aW5lLmNvbS9fbmV3cy8yMDEyLzEwLzEzLzE0NDE1MDY4LW1haW50YWluLXRob3NlLXBlYXJseS13aGl0ZXMtd2l0aC10aGVzZS10aXBz" target="_blank">Teeth Whitening Is Not As Hard As You Think</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>