<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="14">
		<document id="be0a85aae34815e8ec19e62cd68ed643" url=""><![CDATA[girls and boys listen up<br/><br/>girls /boys is u like each other then tell each other before it's to late tell ur ture feelings bout them 
<br /><br />thank you
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="afc40e71e312815a66321c0f0b72f7da" url=""><![CDATA[hi<br/><br/>hi every1
<br />wanna here a joke :
<br />Coming into the bar and ordering a double, the man leaned over and confided to the bartender, &quot;I'm so pissed off !&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Oh yeah? What happened?&quot; asked the bartender politely.
<br /><br />&quot;See, I met this beautiful woman who invited me back to her home. We stripped off our clothes and jumped into bed and we were just about to make love when her god damned husband came in the front door. So I had to jump out of the bedroom window and
<br />hang from the ledge by my fingernails!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Gee, that's tough!&quot; commiserated the bartender.
<br /><br />&quot;Right, but that's not what really got me aggravated,&quot; the customer went on.
<br /><br />&quot;When her husband came into the room he said 'Hey great! You're
<br />naked already! Let me just take a leak.' And damned if the lazy
<br />son of a bitch didn't piss out the window right onto my head?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Yeech!&quot; the bartender shook his head. &quot;No wonder you're in a lousy mood.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Yeah, but I haven't told you what really, really got to me.
<br /><br />Next, I had to listen to them grunting and groaning and when they finished, the husband tossed his condom out of the window.
<br />And where does it land? My damned forehead!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Damn, that really is a drag!&quot; says the bartender.
<br /><br />&quot;Oh, I'm not finished. See what really pissed me off was when
<br />the husband had to take a dump. It turns out that their toilet is broken, so he stuck his ass out of the window and let loose right on my head !&quot;
<br /><br />The bartender paled. &quot;That would sure mess up my day.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Yeah, yeah, yeah,&quot; the fellow rattled on, &quot;but do you know what
<br />REALLY, REALLY, REALLY pissed me off? When I looked down and saw
<br />that my feet were only SIX inches off the ground!!&quot; 
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6441491d15960747fe21d5e9d153d1aa" url=""><![CDATA[read this<br/><br/>Colin meets a girl on the street. He says, &quot;Come on, babe, let's go in the alleyway and get it on. I've got fifteen bucks.&quot;
<br /><br />She says, &quot;FIFTEEN bucks? You're crazy. For fifteen bucks, I'll let you LOOK at it.&quot;
<br /><br />They go into the alleyway, she pulls down her pants, and he gets down on his knees. But he can't see anything, because it's too dark, so he gets out his lighter. He lights his lighter, and he says, &quot;My God, your pubic hair... it's so curly and thick... it's BEAUTIFUL.&quot;
<br /><br />She says, &quot;Thank you.&quot;
<br /><br />He says, &quot;You mind if I ask you a personal question?&quot;
<br /><br />She says, &quot;Go ahead.&quot;
<br /><br />He says, &quot;Can you pee through all that hair?&quot;
<br /><br />She says, &quot;Of course.&quot;
<br /><br />He says, &quot;Well, you better start. You're on fire.&quot; 
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e8e506d437b4e8cec92e6a5f54a6f2ec" url=""><![CDATA[read this<br/><br/>guy can't obtain an erection so he goes to the doctor.
<br />The doctor tells him the muscles at the base of his penis are broken down and there's nothing he can do unless he's willing to try an experimental surgery. 
<br />The guy asks what the surgery is. 
<br />The doctor tells him they take the muscles from the base of a baby elephants trunk, insert them in the base of his penis, and hope for the best. 
<br />The guy says that sounds pretty scary but the thought of never having sex again is even scarier so go ahead. The doctor goes ahead and performs the surgery and about 6 weeks later gives him the go ahead to &quot;try out his new equipment&quot;. 
<br />The guy takes his girlfriend out to dinner. 
<br />While at dinner he starts feeling an incredible pressure in his pants. It gets incredibly unbearable and he figures no one can see him so he undoes his pants.
<br />No sooner does he do this than his penis pops out of his pants, rolls across the table, grabs a dinner roll, and disappears back into his pants. 
<br />His girlfriend sits in shock for a few moments, then gets a sly look on her face. 
<br />She says &quot;That was pretty cool! Can you do that again?&quot; 
<br />With his eyes watering and a painful expression on his face, he says &quot;Probably, but I don't know if I can fit another dinner roll up my ass!&quot;.
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c1ab0ef5e123efc9d756833b8591fe76" url=""><![CDATA[read this<br/><br/>A guy can't obtain an erection so he goes to the doctor.
<br />The doctor tells him the muscles at the base of his penis are broken down and there's nothing he can do unless he's willing to try an experimental surgery. 
<br />The guy asks what the surgery is. 
<br />The doctor tells him they take the muscles from the base of a baby elephants trunk, insert them in the base of his penis, and hope for the best. 
<br />The guy says that sounds pretty scary but the thought of never having sex again is even scarier so go ahead. The doctor goes ahead and performs the surgery and about 6 weeks later gives him the go ahead to &quot;try out his new equipment&quot;. 
<br />The guy takes his girlfriend out to dinner. 
<br />While at dinner he starts feeling an incredible pressure in his pants. It gets incredibly unbearable and he figures no one can see him so he undoes his pants.
<br />No sooner does he do this than his penis pops out of his pants, rolls across the table, grabs a dinner roll, and disappears back into his pants. 
<br />His girlfriend sits in shock for a few moments, then gets a sly look on her face. 
<br />She says &quot;That was pretty cool! Can you do that again?&quot; 
<br />With his eyes watering and a painful expression on his face, he says &quot;Probably, but I don't know if I can fit another dinner roll up my ass!&quot;.
<br />wb x
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ecac5a154551dfa7d5907e9df2b293e5" url=""><![CDATA[read this<br/><br/>There was a couple going at it for the first time, and after a while, the guy asks the woman to open her legs a little wider. 
<br /><br />She does and they continue.
<br /><br />A few minutes go by and he tells her again, &quot;Open your legs a little wider.&quot;
<br /><br />She does, then he says again, &quot;A little wider, hon.&quot;
<br /><br />The woman starts getting pissed off but she does it. 
<br /><br />This continues until he asks again, &quot;Can you open them just a little wider?&quot;
<br /><br />So she finally yells, &quot;What are you trying to do; get your balls in too?&quot;
<br /><br />He says &quot;No, I'm trying to get them out.&quot;
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7af792fbede542ba11f9d721c0607bdc" url=""><![CDATA[read this<br/><br/>It was my 30th birthday and I wasn't feeling too great when I woke up that morning. 
<br /><br />I went down to breakfast knowing my wife would be pleasant and say &quot;Happy Birthday&quot; and probably have a present for me. 
<br /><br />She didn't even say &quot;Good Morning,&quot; let alone &quot;Happy Birthday.&quot; 
<br /><br />I figured, &quot;Well, that's wives for you. The children will remember.&quot; The children came down to breakfast and didn't say a word.
<br /><br />When I started to the office I was feeling pretty low and despondent. As I walked into my office, my secretary Janet said, &quot;Good Morning, Boss, Happy Birthday.&quot;
<br /><br />I felt a little better - at least someone had remembered. 
<br /><br />I worked until noon, then Janet knocked on my door and said, &quot;You know, it is such a beautiful day outside and it's your birthday, let's go to lunch, just you and me.&quot; 
<br /><br />I said, &quot;That's the greatest thing I've heard all day. Let's go.
<br /><br />We went to lunch. We didn't go where we normally go. We went out into the country to a little private place. We had two martinis and enjoyed lunch tremendously. 
<br /><br />On the way back to the office, she said, &quot;You know, it is such a beautiful day, we don't need to go back to the office, do we?&quot; I said, &quot;No, I guess not.&quot; She said, &quot;Let's go to my apartment.&quot;
<br /><br />After arriving at her apartment, she smiled at me and said, &quot;If you don't mind, I think I'll go into the bedroom and slip into something more comfortable.&quot;
<br /><br />Mad at my wife for forgetting about my birthday, not to mention that Janet was quite beautiful, I felt justified in staying. &quot;Sure,&quot; I excitedly replied.
<br /><br />She went into the bedroom and, after a few minutes, she came out carrying a big birthday cake, followed by my wife, children and dozens of our friends. 
<br /><br />They were all singing Happy Birthday... and there I sat on the couch... naked.
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3576e0de3419482d70a2a22959d0d0c1" url=""><![CDATA[read this<br/><br/>An Irishman walks into a bar in Dublin, orders three pints of Guinness and sits in the back of the room, drinking a sip out of each one in turn. 
<br /><br />When he finishes them, he comes back to the bar and orders three more. 
<br /><br />The bartender asks him, &quot;You know, a pint goes flat after I draw it, it would taste better if you bought one at a time.&quot; 
<br /><br />The Irishman replies, &quot;Well, you see, I have two brothers. One is in America, the other in Australia, and I'm here in Dublin. When we all left home, we promised that we'd drink this way to remember the days when we drank together.&quot; 
<br /><br />The bartender admits that this is a nice custom, and leaves it there. 
<br /><br />The Irishman becomes a regular in the bar, and always drinks the same way. He orders three pints and drinks them in turn. 
<br /><br />One day, he comes in and orders two pints. All the other regulars notice and fall silent. 
<br /><br />When he comes back to the bar for the second round, the bartender says, &quot;I don't want to intrude on your grief, but I wanted to offer my condolences on your great loss.&quot;
<br /><br />The Irishman looks confused for a moment, then a light dawns in his eye and he laughs. &quot;Oh, no,&quot; he, says, &quot;everyone's fine. I've just quit drinking
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c35422c24f6dcdd66cfe0f8c98507f6f" url=""><![CDATA[read this<br/><br/>Little Mary was not the best student in Sunday School. Usually she slept through the class. One day the teacher called on her while she was napping, ''Tell me, Mary, who created the universe?'' When Mary didn't stir, little Johnny, an altruistic boy seated in the chair behind her, took a pin and jabbed her in the rear. ''God Almighty !'' shouted Mary and the teacher said, ''Very good'' and Mary fell back to sleep. 
<br /><br />A while later the teacher asked Mary, ''Who is our Lord and Savior?'' But Mary didn't even stir from her slumber. Once again, Johnny came to the rescue and stuck her again. ''Jesus Christ!'' shouted Mary and the teacher said, ''Very good,'' and Mary fell back to sleep. Then the teacher asked Mary a third question, ''What did Eve say to Adam after she had her twenty-third child?'' And again, Johnny jabbed her with the pin. This time Mary jumped up and shouted, ''If you stick that damn thing in me one more time, I'll break it in half!'' The Teacher fainted. 
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a1ef21bd7051453199a2f10d5241c80d" url=""><![CDATA[read this<br/><br/>Two guys are in a strip joint, one is sitting in front of the other. A woman comes on stage and starts stripping.
<br />The guy in back, Paul, says, &quot;Oh yeah, Oh yeah!&quot;
<br /><br />Then the first guy turns around and says, &quot; Hey Paul, shut up!&quot;
<br /><br />Then two women come out and start stripping. Paul, once again, starts, &quot;Yeah baby..mmmm....yeah!&quot;
<br /><br />Once again the guy in front turns around and tells Paul to be quiet. So three women come out and start stripping. Paul is silent.
<br /><br />The guy in front says, &quot;Hey Paul, where's all your excitement now?&quot;
<br /><br />Paul says, &quot;All over your back!&quot; 
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a605dda89d8e63976bd9179e9617814" url=""><![CDATA[read this joke<br/><br/>Coming into the bar and ordering a double, the man leaned over and confided to the bartender, &quot;I'm so pissed off !&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Oh yeah? What happened?&quot; asked the bartender politely.
<br /><br />&quot;See, I met this beautiful woman who invited me back to her home. We stripped off our clothes and jumped into bed and we were just about to make love when her god damned husband came in the front door. So I had to jump out of the bedroom window and
<br />hang from the ledge by my fingernails!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Gee, that's tough!&quot; commiserated the bartender.
<br /><br />&quot;Right, but that's not what really got me aggravated,&quot; the customer went on.
<br /><br />&quot;When her husband came into the room he said 'Hey great! You're
<br />naked already! Let me just take a leak.' And damned if the lazy
<br />son of a bitch didn't piss out the window right onto my head?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Yeech!&quot; the bartender shook his head. &quot;No wonder you're in a lousy mood.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Yeah, but I haven't told you what really, really got to me.
<br /><br />Next, I had to listen to them grunting and groaning and when they finished, the husband tossed his condom out of the window.
<br />And where does it land? My damned forehead!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Damn, that really is a drag!&quot; says the bartender.
<br /><br />&quot;Oh, I'm not finished. See what really pissed me off was when
<br />the husband had to take a dump. It turns out that their toilet is broken, so he stuck his ass out of the window and let loose right on my head !&quot;
<br /><br />The bartender paled. &quot;That would sure mess up my day.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Yeah, yeah, yeah,&quot; the fellow rattled on, &quot;but do you know what
<br />REALLY, REALLY, REALLY pissed me off? When I looked down and saw
<br />that my feet were only SIX inches off the ground!!&quot; 
<br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88f70ab5ca57217ef4fddc175282c36a" url=""><![CDATA[text<br/><br/>Your Name: 
<br />Your Number: 
<br />Best time to text: 
<br /><br />I dare you to copy and paste this and see how many numbers you get.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c4d314dae719c640221a55a273d56f39" url=""><![CDATA[read this joke<br/><br/>A blind carpenter walks into a lumber mill and shouts out, &quot;I am a blind carpenter and I need a job.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman walks over to the blind carpenter and says, &quot;If you're blind, how can you work in a lumber yard?&quot;
<br /><br />The blind carpenter says, &quot;I can tell any piece of lumber by it's smell.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman says &quot;O.K. I'll give you a test and if you pass the test, you've got a job.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman takes the carpenter over to a table and says, &quot;I will put some lumber on a table in front of you and you tell me what it is.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman then puts a piece of lumber on the table and says, &quot;Ready!&quot;
<br /><br />The carpenter bends over and takes a deep sniff moving his head from one side to the other. He says &quot;That's a number two pine, two by four, eight foot long.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman says, &quot;Duh! That's right, but pine is easy to tell by the smell and I think you guessed the rest. Here's another piece of lumber for you to identify.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman puts a piece of lumber on the table and says, &quot;Ready!&quot;
<br /><br />The blind carpenter bends over and takes a deep sniff moving his head from one side to the other and says, &quot;This is a tough one, please turn it over so I can smell the other side.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman does this and says &quot;Ready!&quot;
<br /><br />The carpenter takes another deep sniff moving his head from side to side. He then says, &quot;That's a clear heart red wood, four by four, six foot long.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman is amazed and says &quot;That's right, but I still think you're just lucky and still guessing. Let me try one more time and if you get it right you got a job.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman then goes into the office and asks his secretary to help him stump the blind carpenter by taking off all of her clothes and laying down on the table. She takes off her clothes walks out of the office and lays face down on the table. The foreman says, &quot;Ready!&quot;
<br /><br />The blind carpenter takes a deep sniff moving his head from side to side. He looks puzzled and takes another sniff and says, &quot;This also is a tough one, please turn it over so I can smell the other side.&quot;
<br /><br />The foreman gestures with his hand to the secretary, she rolls over, and the foreman says, &quot;Ready!&quot;
<br /><br />The blind carpenter moves his head from side to side again looking puzzled. He sniffs one more time, looks surprised, and says, &quot;I got it. That's a shit house door off a tuna boat.&quot;
<br /><br />He got the job. 
<br /><br />wb
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="23ca03be2c14822c522e6f0e58741659" url=""><![CDATA[joke husbands<br/><br/>Three women were sitting around throwing back a few drinks and talking about their love lives.
<br />One woman said, &quot;I call my husband the dentist. Nobody can drill like he does.&quot;
<br />The second woman giggled and confessed, &quot;I call my husband the miner because of his incredible shaft.&quot;
<br />The third woman quietly sipped her whiskey until her friend asked, &quot;Say, what do you call your husband?&quot;
<br />She frowned and said, &quot;The postman.&quot;
<br />&quot;Why the postman?&quot;
<br />&quot;Because he always delivers late, and half the time it's in the wrong box.&quot;
<br />write back thank you
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>