<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="adfc889619f86f05af7e52d992a319db" url=""><![CDATA[o ffs<br/><br/>god it all craked of agen on saturday nyt!! but even worse!! way worse! bloody hell shes a ryt blubberin baby! onli wantin sort fings out wif er tbh, but she neva been a tru m8 2 me, yu kno wat der say keep ur enemies close, n dats wat i did, n she played ryt in 2 my hands
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e46e1d85ea831c7a1e5f14dbba25a99f" url=""><![CDATA[<br/><br/>wel 2day found out e dunt lyk me<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> but its oki i spose, y is it weneva i reli lyk sum1 dey dnt lyk me but wen sum1 reli lyks me i dnt lyk dem <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/book.gif" alt=":)" />  i reli lyk &lt;3 dat special boi &lt;3 but sum fings jus rnt ment 2 b r dey <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />ma quote of da day is........
<br />&lt;3 love can be like heaven but can also hurt like hell &lt;3
<br />it's all up 2 ur path in lyf i believe, y has lyf gota b so cruel?
<br />people lv takin piss outa hu i lyk but tbh! dey dnt kno its reli hurtin me inside, i kno e dnt lyk me so y u gota rub it in ma face!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />y is it hes my prince charmin n i jus cnt b his fukin cinderella!!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />how is it that im finkin of im dis moment,im missin im, n relisin ow much e dusnt even care
<br /><br />i jus want dat &lt;3 dat special boi &lt;3 2 read dis n 2 understand ow much i acutally lyk im!!n wish e cud change his mind<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="61ae52b900489bc5198c5659f1a77c52" url=""><![CDATA[wat happens in my lyf?<br/><br/>dat boy stil dnt lyk me<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> wat a surprise hey^o) 
<br /><br />i need dis answerin *¢?? ????? ????? ???????? ???? ?f ??? ???? 2 ? ??f ???1 ??? ??? ? ?????? ????*
<br /><br />plz people comment on dat cuz i believe dat if u reli lv sum1 u can pull urself thru enyfin<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> help
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9f55c6fd1b87141b7dddccf8b823b458" url=""><![CDATA[.*. 14 signs you've found your soulmate .*.<br/><br/>14. When you argue and fight with them, but still cant get them out 
<br />of your mind... 
<br /><br />13. When your on the phone with them late at night and they hang up 
<br />but you miss them already when it was just five minutes ago... 
<br /><br />12. You read their texts over and over again... 
<br /><br />11. You walk really slow when you're with them... 
<br /><br />10. You feel shy whenever you're with them... 
<br /><br />9. When you think about them, your heart beats faster and 
<br />faster... 
<br /><br />8. You smile when you hear their voice... 
<br /><br />7. When you look at them, you can't see the other people around 
<br />you... all you see is him/her... 
<br /><br />6. You start listening to slow songs, while thinking of them... 
<br /><br />5. They become all you think about... 
<br /><br />4. You get high just from their scent and there kiss... 
<br /><br />3. You realize that you're always smiling to yourself when you think 
<br />about them... 
<br /><br />2. You would do anything for them... 
<br /><br />1. While reading this, there was one person on your mind the whole 
<br />time..... 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5c95c450d0d8c3311a9dbfd54fc6f3f" url=""><![CDATA[wen da boy yoo lyk is seeing sum1 else:(<br/><br/>so wat am i ment 2 do ? wen all i do is see him lukin @ her, kissed er, huggin er <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> y cnt it b me? i wonder!
<br />es not been goin out wif er long but hes lyk i fink shes da 1 n always will b n all dis bullshit!! n y is e rubbin it in ma face!
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bce1cabcfba21dbaddf48a9aa7803cbd" url=""><![CDATA[-x- da lyf of a teenager -x-<br/><br/>hiya tis me! jess! its 11th of october 2006, wel 2days been ratha weird had dat bitch of a teacher miss tayler givin me bitch eyes! 1 day sum1 shud knok er out it b wel worth it! lol den she as da nerve 2 smile at me dat wa jus takin it 2 far! 2 damn far! fukin h8 da bitch nywayz dats enuf from me lv yaz xxx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2a83e2483b2b6a3f5e3d7ca8f41e608" url=""><![CDATA[~x~ da lyf of a teenager~x~<br/><br/>wat am i spose 2 do? jus wallow in self pitty? or go 4 it? its so confusin cnt believe im lyk dis ive neva been lyk dis b4! mum n dad dnt help eitha always on bout wat dey wa lyk wen dey was my age tbh hu givs a fuk it was lyk a century ago!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42fc1f405b3691bd5c312102d94db2a5" url=""><![CDATA[2day 16th of october<br/><br/>2day is da day i found out ive lost my bakup plan, he's  gon now all i av left is my self n my self onli, which is quite upsettin got no1 2 turn 2, dno wats da mata wif me 2day, it feels lyk its da worst day eva, i h8 bein fuked round i jus wana boy i can turn 2 hu wil treat me ryt n b der 4 me n not jus want me 4 money or wateva! :'( <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="18214c73cf8b8c0fa2065a4d218fce77" url=""><![CDATA[sooooooo.......<br/><br/>so dis is wat boredom feels lyk,,<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> getin sik of skwel!!! 2 much fukin work!! grrr <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />  wat yu all fink,,? y dus it all happen now??  im getin so stressed out,,!! makin tym 4 revision, cw, makin tym 4 friends, makin tym 4 family n makin tym 4 ryan, its all getin 2 me reli bad!! now i c y people top dem selves at my age
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4866ea1d4a3e8970dbeaf180193b0a75" url=""><![CDATA[hmmmmm......<br/><br/>hmmmm.... cant fink of ote 2 du,,?
<br />people msg me plz<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> or write 2 me,,?
<br />cuz i am a fun person<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> n jus wana a chat<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
<br />Lv yaz,,x
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ddcfea6a0fc764b87fd588bbce0466a4" url=""><![CDATA[sooooooooo......<br/><br/>bored eny1 wana chat,,?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="df3f25bc630dc505dc73b7b90cd9d6e3" url=""><![CDATA[omg!!<br/><br/>omg i cnt believe all dis shit datz goin about,, hu da fuk dus emily fink she is!!
<br />i dint wana make er cry last nyt, dnt even kno y she did//? 
<br />its usually er dat makes every1 else cry, every1 keeps goin 2 me least uve put er in er place now! but i dnt lyk feelin lyk dis, all i did was tlk 2 er den mayb of raised ma voice a lil bit, but hey, she was rasin it at me! god imagin if i shouted at her!! bloody hell, lmao n now shes lyk makin me sound lyk da bad guy 2 every/!! how pathetic hey!
<br />o wel see wat happens 2nyt lol
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>