<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="10">
		<document id="e0a7e2c7e22d1a6ed1e9d9b855ae4bc4" url=""><![CDATA[Finally an explanation......<br/><br/>Why women take so long in public toilets....... 
<br /><br />When you have to visit a public loo there is invariably a line of women,
<br />you smile politely and take your place, 
<br />it finally gets to your turn, you check for feet under the 
<br />cubicle doors. Every one is occupied. but....eventually a door opens and you 
<br />dash in, nearly knocking the woman down.
<br />Leaving the cubicle, you get in 
<br />to find the door won't latch. It doesn't matter, 
<br />the wait has been so long 
<br />you are about to wet your pants!
<br />The dispenser for the modern &quot;seat covers&quot; 
<br />is handy, but empty. You would hang your handbag on a door hook,
<br />if there was one, but there isn't - so.....
<br />you carefully, but quickly drape it around 
<br />your neck, yank down your pants, and assume &quot;The Position.&quot; 
<br /><br />In this position your aging, toneless thigh muscles begin to shake. 
<br />You'd love to sit down, but you certainly hadn't taken time to wipe the seat or lay 
<br />toilet paper on it, so you hold &quot;The Position&quot;. 
<br />To take your mind off your 
<br />trembling thighs for a moment,
<br />you reach for horror or horrors an empty 
<br />toilet paper dispenser. Your thighs start to shake more. 
<br />You remember the tiny tissue that you blew your nose on yesterday 
<br />- the one that's still in your handbag 
<br />which is now burning your neck &amp; shoulders with the weight.
<br /><br />So you contort your arm into a very unnatural position and start to fumble 
<br />around in the deep dark depths of your handbag for that small crumpled 
<br />'used' tissue no bigger than your thumbnail. 
<br />Someone pushes your door and because the latch
<br />doesn't work it hits your head which is bent over from 
<br />holding the hanging handbag, and you start to topple backward. 
<br />&quot;Occupied!&quot; you scream, as you reach for the door and drop the precious,
<br />tiny, crumpled tissue you had only just retrieved with your index finger into an unknown 
<br />puddle on the floor.......if that isn't enough you lose your balance 
<br />altogether and gravity pulls you down.......
<br /><br />down directly onto the TOILET SEAT.It is wet, of course, 
<br />you bolt up knowing all too well that it's too late. Your bare bottom
<br />has made contact with every imaginable germ &amp; life form that lives
<br />on the uncovered seat. By this time, the 
<br />automatic sensor on the back of the toilet 
<br />is so confused that it flushes, propelling a stream of water 
<br />like a fire hose into the bowl which sprays a fine mist of water 
<br />that covers your bum and runs down your legs 
<br />along with the various life forms, and down into your dishevelled pants 
<br />which have now dropped down to your ankles. The flush somehow sucks 
<br />everything down with such force that you grab onto the empty toilet paper 
<br />dispenser for fear of being dragged in too. At this point, you give up. 
<br /><br />You're soaked by the spewing water and the wet toilet seat. You're 
<br />exhausted. You try to wipe yourself with a piece of gum wrapper you found 
<br />in your pocket and then slink out inconspicuously to the sinks. You can't 
<br />figure out how to operate the sensor taps. You run your hands underneath it 
<br />grateful for the 2 drops there, then around the basin itself.
<br /><br />You go to the towel dispenser past the line of women still waiting, where of course there 
<br />are no paper towels so you move over to the hand blower, which, yes you've 
<br />guessed it, also doesn't work. You are no longer able to smile politely to 
<br />the women, but there is an unspoken understanding between you all. A kind 
<br />soul at the very end of the line points out that you have a piece of toilet 
<br />paper trailing from your shoe. (Where was that when you NEEDED it?<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> You 
<br />yank the paper from your shoe, plonk it in the woman's hand and tell her 
<br />warmly, &quot;Here, you just might need this.&quot;
<br /><br />As you exit, you spot your hubby, who has long since entered,
<br />used, and left the Men's. Annoyed, he asks, 
<br />&quot;What took you so long, and why is your handbag hanging around your 
<br />neck?&quot;
<br /><br />This is dedicated to women everywhere who deal with public loo's. 
<br /><br />It also finally explains to the men what really does take us so long 
<br />and also answers their other commonly asked question about why women go 
<br />to the loo in pairs. It's so the other one can hold the door, hang 
<br />onto your purse and hand you, Kleenex under the door!
<br /><br />Have fun xxx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9b0862f1a829e45676535ee521a2363f" url=""><![CDATA[Friends.....<br/><br/>?.·:*¨¨*:·.??.·:*¨¨*:·.?
<br />(¸.•´
<br />?(¸.•´)
<br />?.·:*¨Once in a while you find a friend¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*¨Who loves you right from the start,¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*¨And the friendship is so true and right¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*¨It warms your deepest heart.¨*:·.?
<br />(¸.•´?(¸.•´)?.·:*¨¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*
<br />¨¨*:·.?(¸.•´?(¸.•´)
<br />?.·:*¨Once in a while that friendship lasts¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*¨A whole long lifetime through.¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*¨Once in a while it happens like that,¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*¨Like it happened with me and you!¨*:·.?
<br />(¸.•´?(¸.•´)?.·:*¨¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*
<br />¨¨*:·.?(¸.•´?(¸.•´)
<br />?.·:*¨¨*:·.?Thanks for being my Friend!?.·:*¨¨*:·.?
<br />(¸.•´?(¸.•´)?.·:*¨¨*:·.?
<br />?.·:*
<br />¨¨*:·.?(¸.•´?(¸.•´) 
<br /><br />Thanks to all youz hwho have added me as a friend and here is to many more who will......xx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f338fe9ce6e54cb85fb0de015103c67" url=""><![CDATA[Naughty nursery rhymes......xx<br/><br/>Mary had a little skirt
<br />with splits right up the sides
<br />and every time that Mary walked
<br />the boys could see her Thighs
<br />Mary had another skirt
<br />twas split right up the front
<br />...but she didn't wear that one very often
<br /><br />Simple Simon met a Pieman, going to the fair.
<br />Said Simple Simon to the Pieman,
<br />What have you got there?
<br />Said the Pieman unto Simon,
<br />Pies, you dickhead.
<br /><br />Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall
<br />Humpty Dumpty had a great fall.
<br />All the kings horses and all the kings men,
<br />said &quot;F*** him, He's only an egg.
<br /><br />Mary had a little lamb
<br />It ran into a pylon.
<br />10,000 volts went up it's arse
<br />and turned it's wool to nylon
<br /><br />Georgie Porgy pudding and pie.
<br />kissed the girls and made them cry.
<br />When the boys came out to play,
<br />He kissed them too, cause he was gay.
<br /><br />Jack and Jill
<br />Went up the hill
<br />to have some hanky panky.
<br />Silly Jill forgot her pill
<br />And now there's little Franky.
<br /><br />Old Mother Hubbard
<br />Went to the cupboard
<br />to fetch her poor dog a bone.
<br />When she bent over
<br />Rover took over,
<br />And gave her a bone of his own.
<br /><br />Have fun guys!!! xx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7062179c6a5ca4a684bb0fe42bc6d8b1" url=""><![CDATA[What it means.....<br/><br/>*Kiss on the belly----&quot;lets have sex&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Forehead ----&quot;Forever you will be mine&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Ear ---&quot;I'm horny&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Cheek ---&quot;I adore you&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Hand ---&quot;We're Friends&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Neck ---&quot;I want you so bad it's not even funny&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Shoulder ---&quot;We belong together&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Lips ---&quot;I love you&quot; OR &quot;I want you&quot;
<br />*Holding Hands ---&quot;We can learn to love each other&quot;
<br />*A wink ---&quot;Let's get it on&quot;
<br />*Slap on the Butt ---&quot;That's mine&quot;
<br />*Playing with the Ear ---&quot;I can't live without you&quot;
<br />*Holding on tight ---&quot;Won't let go&quot;
<br />*Looking into each other's Eyes ---&quot;Don't let go&quot;
<br />*Playing with Hair on Head ---&quot;I'm crazy about you&quot;
<br />*Arms around the Waist ---&quot;I love you too much to let go&quot;
<br />*Laughing while Kissing ---&quot;I am completley Comfortable with you&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="57de0facb42aa4d7d3bb5de9bf5bacbf" url=""><![CDATA[Vaseline Biker.....<br/><br/>A young man has always dreamed on owning a Harley Davidson. One day he has finally saved up enough money so he goes down to the dealer. After picking out the perfect bike the dealer warns him that if he leaves his Harley in the rain the chrome has a tendency to rust. He tells the young man an old biker's trick is to keep a jar of Vaseline handy and smear it on the chrome if the bike must be left out in the rain.
<br /><br />A few months later the young man meets a woman and falls in love. She asks him to come home and meet her parents over dinner. He readily agrees and the date is set. At the appointed time he picks her up on his Harley and they ride to her parents house. Before they go in she tells him that they have a family tradition that whoever speaks first after dinner must do the dishes.
<br /><br />After a delicious dinner everyone sits in silence waiting for the first person to break and get stuck doing the dishes. After a long fifteen minutes the young man decides to speed things up so he reaches over and kisses the woman in front of her family.
<br /><br />And no one says a word...! Next he decides to take a more direct approach so he throws her on the table and has sex with her in front of everyone. And still no one says a word!
<br /><br />Now he is getting desperate, so he grabs her mother and throws her on the table. They have even wilder sex. But no one says a word!!!
<br /><br />By now he is getting very worried and is wondering what to do next when he hears thunder in the distance. His first thought is to protect the chrome on his Harley, so he reaches in his pocket and pulls out the Vaseline.
<br /><br />And the father says, &quot;Okay dammit, I'll do the dishes.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24fedc55206ffb1bef4d9973be4e5a39" url=""><![CDATA[Dont get caught sleeping at your desk.....<br/><br/>If you do say.....
<br /><br />10. &quot;They told me at the blood bank this might happen.&quot; 
<br /><br />9. &quot;This is just a 15 minute power-nap like they raved about in that time management course you sent me to.&quot; 
<br /><br />8. &quot;Whew! Guess I left the top off the tippex. You probably got here just in time!&quot; 
<br /><br />7. &quot;I wasn't sleeping! I was meditating on the mission statement and envisioning a new paradigm.&quot; 
<br /><br />6. &quot;I was testing my keyboard for drool resistance.&quot; 
<br /><br />5. &quot;I was doing a highly specific Yoga exercise to relieve work-related stress. Are you discriminatory toward people who practice Yoga?&quot; 
<br /><br />4. &quot;Why did you interrupt me? I had almost figured out a solution to our biggest problem.&quot; 
<br /><br />3. &quot;The coffee machine is broken...&quot; 
<br /><br />2. &quot;Someone must've put decaf in the wrong pot...&quot; 
<br /><br />And the #1 excuse to say if you get caught sleeping at your desk. 
<br />1. &quot; ...... AMEN!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="27201ce60a2cedd158b7b02537ce8fee" url=""><![CDATA[A message for husbands, perhaps....<br/><br/>A woman was walking down the street when she was confronted by a
<br />particularly dirty and shabby-looking homeless woman who asked her
<br />for a couple of dollars for dinner. The woman took out her bill fold,
<br />extracted ten dollars and asked, &quot;If I give you this money, will you
<br />buy some chocolate with it instead of dinner?&quot;
<br />&quot;No,&quot; I had to stop chocolate years ago, the homeless woman replied.
<br /><br />&quot;Will you use it to go shopping instead of buying food?&quot; the woman asked.
<br />&quot;No,&quot; I don't waste time shopping, the homeless woman said. &quot;I need to
<br />spend all my time trying to stay alive.&quot;
<br />&quot;Will you spend this on a beauty salon instead of food?&quot; the woman asked.
<br />Are you NUTS!&quot; replied the homeless woman. &quot;I haven't had my hair
<br />done in 20 years!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Well,&quot; said the woman, &quot;I'm not going to give you the money. Instead,
<br />I'm going to take you out for dinner with my hubby and myself tonight.&quot;
<br />The homeless Woman was astounded. &quot;Won't your hubby be furious with
<br />you for doing that? I know I'm
<br />dirty, and I probably smell pretty disgusting.&quot;
<br /><br />The woman replied, &quot;That's okay. It's important for him to see what a
<br />woman looks like after she has given up shopping, hair appointments, and
<br />chocolate.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2b4b1966465513e680ae57f0b2e1dac1" url=""><![CDATA[Divorce letter.......funny<br/><br/>Letter of Regret / Divorce In Writing
<br /><br />Dear Wife:
<br /><br />I'm writing you this letter to tell you that I'm leaving you forever. I've been a
<br />good man to you for seven years and I have nothing to show for it. These last 
<br />two weeks have been hell. Your boss called to tell me that you quit your job
<br />today and that was the last straw. 
<br /><br />Last week, you came home and didn't even notice that I had a new haircut, had
<br />cooked your favorite meal and even wore a brand new pair of silk boxers. You ate 
<br />in two minutes, and went straight to sleep after watching all of your soaps. You
<br />don't tell me you love me anymore; you don't want sex or anything that connects
<br />us as husband and wife. Either you're cheating on me or you don't love me 
<br />anymore; whatever the case, I'm gone. 
<br /><br />Your EX-Husband 
<br /><br />P.S. Don't try to find me. Your SISTER and I are moving away together! Have a great life!
<br /><br />******************************* 
<br />Dear Ex-Husband -
<br /><br />Nothing has made my day 
<br />more than receiving your letter. It's true that you and
<br />I have been married for seven years, although a good man is a far cry from what
<br />you've been. I watch my soaps so much because they drown out your constant 
<br />whining and griping. Too bad that doesn't work. I DID notice when you got a
<br />hair cut last week, but the first thing that came to mind was &quot;You look just like
<br />a girl!&quot; Since my mother raised me not to say anything if you can't say something 
<br />nice, I didn't comment. And when you cooked my favorite meal, you must have
<br />gotten me confused with MY SISTER, because I stopped eating pork seven years ago. 
<br /><br />About those new silk boxers: I turned away from you because the £49.99 price tag 
<br />was still on them, and I prayed that it was a coincidence that my sister had just
<br />borrowed fifty quid from me that morning. After all of this, I still loved
<br />you and felt that we could work it out. So when I hit the lotto for ten million 
<br />pounds, I 
<br />quit my job and bought us two tickets to Jamaica. But when I got home
<br />you were gone. Everything happens for a reason, I guess.
<br /><br />I hope you have the fulfilling life you always wanted. My lawyer said that the 
<br />letter you wrote ensures you won't get a penny from me. So take care. 
<br /><br />Signed,
<br /><br />Your Ex-Wife, Rich As Hell and Free!
<br /><br />P.S. I don't know if I ever told you this, but my sister Carla was born Carl. 
<br /><br />I hope that's not a problem.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="21b60d08a588dfc62fece6aec8be001e" url=""><![CDATA[Wife from hell<br/><br/>A police officer pulls over a speeding car. The officer says, I clocked you
<br />at 80 miles per hour, sir.' The driver says, 'Gee, officer I had it on 
<br />cruise control at 60, perhaps your radar gun needs calibrating, Not looking
<br />up from her knitting the wife says: 'Now don't be silly dear, you know that
<br />this car doesn't have cruise control.' As the officer writes out the ticket, 
<br />the driver looks over at his wife and growls, 'Can't you please keep your
<br />mouth shut for once?'
<br />The wife smiles demurely and says, 'You should be thankful your radar
<br />detector went off when it did.' 
<br />As the officer makes out the second ticket for the illegal radar detector
<br />unit, the man glowers at his wife and says through clenched teeth, 'Darn it,
<br />woman, can't you keep your mouth shut?' The officer frowns and says, 'And I 
<br />notice that you're not wearing your seat belt, sir. That's an automatic £75
<br />fine.' The driver says,
<br />Yeah, well, you see officer, I had it on, but took it off when you pulled me
<br />over so that I could get my license out of my back pocket.' The wife 
<br />says, Now, dear, you know very well that you didn't have your seat belt on.
<br />You never wear your seat belt when you're driving.' And as the police
<br />Officer is writing out the third ticket the driver turns to his wife and barks, 'WHY DON'T YOU PLEASE SHUT UP??'
<br />The officer looks over at the woman and asks, 'Does your husband always talk
<br />to you this way, Mam?
<br /><br />'Only when he's been drinking.'
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5c1f21e2f6e58d2daa386117cfd14a5e" url=""><![CDATA[Test for Dementia<br/><br/>&quot;It's that time of year to take our annual senior citizen test.&quot;Exercise
<br /><br />of the brain is as important as exercise of the muscles.
<br /><br />As we grow older, it's important that we keep mentally alert.
<br /><br />The saying; &quot;If you  don't use it, you will lose it&quot; also applies to the
<br /><br />brain, so ..
<br /><br />Below is a very private way to gauge your loss or non-loss of
<br /><br />Intelligence.So, take the following test presented here and determine if
<br /><br />You are losing it or are still &quot;with it,&quot;
<br /><br />The spaces below are so you don't see the answers until you have made
<br /><br />your answer.OK, relax, clear your mind and begin.
<br /><br />WELL MAYBE NOT THAT CLEAR!
<br /><br />1. What do you put in a toaster?
<br /><br />Answer: &quot;bread.&quot;  If you said &quot;toast,&quot; then give up now and go do
<br /><br />something else.  Try not to hurt yourself.  If you said, &quot;bread,&quot; go to
<br /><br />Question 2.
<br /><br />2. Say &quot;silk&quot; five times.  Now spell &quot;silk.&quot;  What do cows drink?
<br /><br />Answer: Cows drink water.  If you said &quot;milk,&quot; please do notattempt the
<br /><br />next question.  Your brain is obviously over stressed and may even
<br /><br />overheat.  It may be that you need to content yourself with reading
<br /><br />something more appropriate such as Children's World.  If you said
<br /><br />&quot;water&quot; then proceed to question 3.
<br /><br />3. If a red house is made from red bricks and a blue house is made from
<br /><br />blue bricks and a pink house is made from pink bricks and a black house
<br /><br />is made from black bricks, what is a green house made from?
<br /><br />Answer: Greenhouses are made from glass.  If you said &quot;greenbricks,&quot;
<br /><br />what the devil are you still doing here reading these questions?????  If
<br /><br />you said &quot;glass,&quot; then go on to Question 4.
<br /><br />4. It's twenty years ago, and a plane is flying at 20,000 feet
<br /><br />overGermany (If you will recall, Germany at the time was
<br /><br />politicallydivided into West Germany and East Germany.)  Anyway, during
<br /><br />the flight, TWO of the engines fail.  The pilot, realizing that the last
<br /><br />remaining engine is also failing, decides on a crash landing procedure.
<br /><br />Unfortunately the engine fails before he has time and the plane fatally
<br /><br />crashes smack in the middle of &quot;no man's land&quot; between East Germany and
<br /><br />West Germany.  Where would you bury the survivors?  East Germany or West 
<br /><br />Germany or in &quot;no man's land&quot;?!
<br /><br />Answer: You don't, of course, bury survivors.
<br /><br />If you said ANYTHING else, you are a real dunce and you must NEVER try
<br /><br />to rescue anyone from a plane crash.  Your efforts would not be
<br /><br />appreciated.  If you said, &quot;Don't bury the survivors&quot;, then proceed to
<br /><br />the next question. 5.
<br /><br />5. Without using a calculator - You are driving a bus from London to
<br /><br />Milford Haven in Wales.   In London, 17 people get on the bus.  In 
<br /><br />Reading, six people get off the bus and nine people get on.  In Swindon, 
<br /><br />two people get off and four get on. In Cardiff, 11 people get off and 16
<br /><br />people get on. In Swansea, three people get off and five people get on
<br /><br />in Carmathen, six people get off and three get on. You then arrive at
<br /><br />Milford Haven. What was the name of the bus driver?
<br /><br />Answer: Oh, for crying out loud!
<br /><br />Don't you remember your own name?  It  was YOU!!
<br /><br />Now pass this along to all your &quot;smart friends&quot; and hope they do better
<br /><br />than you did
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>