<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="4de61a434b398ab648527c07123dfbe8" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning system doesn’t actually “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is to transport heat from one station to another.  It doesn’t actually cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your system uses to carry the heat is called a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor in your unit changes the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows through the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating in the duct work.  The cool air is redistributed through your house.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can cause your system to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient system means higher bills.  It forces your compressor to work harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your system is efficient.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating through your ducts passes over the evaporator coil, it is cooled and can no longer hold as much moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, similar to what happens when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fars.com%2Flocations%2Fft-myers-fl-hvac.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://ars.com/locations/ft-myers-fl-hvac.aspx</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines become clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks in your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection should include an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Consider having a cut-off float switch installed, this will shut off your unit before water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate same day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="82d9473f0b7358eb19bedc08fecb8c64" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning system doesn’t actually “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is to transport heat from one station to another.  It doesn’t actually cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your system uses to carry the heat is called a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor in your unit changes the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows through the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating in the duct work.  The cool air is redistributed through your house.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can cause your system to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient system means higher bills.  It forces your compressor to work harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your system is efficient.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating through your ducts passes over the evaporator coil, it is cooled and can no longer hold as much moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, similar to what happens when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fars.com%2Flocations%2Fft-myers-fl-hvac.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://ars.com/locations/ft-myers-fl-hvac.aspx</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines become clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks in your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection should include an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Consider having a cut-off float switch installed, this will shut off your unit before water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate same day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7bdbb2e213fcbb243643990f5009c1de" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning system doesn’t actually “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is to transport heat from one station to another.  It doesn’t actually cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your system uses to carry the heat is called a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor in your unit changes the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows through the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating in the duct work.  The cool air is redistributed through your house.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can cause your system to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient system means higher bills.  It forces your compressor to work harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your system is efficient.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating through your ducts passes over the evaporator coil, it is cooled and can no longer hold as much moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, similar to what happens when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fars.com%2Flocations%2Fft-myers-fl-hvac.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://ars.com/locations/ft-myers-fl-hvac.aspx</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines become clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks in your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection should include an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Consider having a cut-off float switch installed, this will shut off your unit before water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate same day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5ac6eff74390c3eee3d6c1b4473617c4" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning program doesn’t truly “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner would be to transport heat from one station to yet another.  It doesn’t actually cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your system makes use of to carry the heat is called a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor in your unit modifications the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows via the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating within the duct work.  The cool air is redistributed by way of your house.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can trigger your program to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient technique indicates higher bills.  It forces your compressor to work harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection consists of an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your method is efficient.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating via your ducts passes over the evaporator coil, it is actually cooled and can no longer hold as a lot moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, comparable to what takes place when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fars.com%2Flocations%2Fft-myers-fl-hvac.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://ars.com/locations/ft-myers-fl-hvac.aspx</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines turn out to be clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks in your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection really should include an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Look at having a cut-off float switch installed, this may shut off your unit prior to water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate very same day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d01c31f8be28179c16476fdf5be7b91d" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning method does not really “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is always to transport heat from 1 station to yet another.  It does not really cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your system uses to carry the heat is named a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor in your unit changes the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows via the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating within the duct function.  The cool air is redistributed via your residence.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can cause your system to cool much less efficiently.  An inefficient technique means greater bills.  It forces your compressor to work harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your program is effective.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating via your ducts passes more than the evaporator coil, it's cooled and can no longer hold as much moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, comparable to what happens when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F775887%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailystrength.org/people/775887/journal</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/KeelinpvgsxKrystal/blog/blogid=4655242" target="_blank">http://en.pan.netcom/KeelinpvgsxKrystal/blog/bl...</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmariomoran1127.insanejournal.com%2F501.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://mariomoran1127.insanejournal.com/501.html</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines turn into clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks inside your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection ought to contain an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Think about getting a cut-off float switch installed, this will shut off your unit just before water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate identical day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="524b3a11d6136332e8101860136e80ed" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning method doesn’t really “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is usually to transport heat from 1 station to yet another.  It does not essentially cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your system makes use of to carry the heat is referred to as a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor within your unit adjustments the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows by means of the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating inside the duct work.  The cool air is redistributed via your home.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can cause your technique to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient program indicates greater bills.  It forces your compressor to function harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your technique is efficient.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating by way of your ducts passes more than the evaporator coil, it truly is cooled and can no longer hold as considerably moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, comparable to what occurs when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ziki.com%2Fen%2Fspt-8212%2B273782%2Fpost%2FAir-Conditioning-Fort-Myers-Florida%2B12832105"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.ziki.com/en/spt-8212+273782/post/Air-Conditioning-Fort-Myers-Florida+12832105</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fairconditioningreplacementfortmyers68.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F09%2F02%2Fair-conditioning-fort-myers-florida%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://airconditioningreplacementfortmyers68.wordpress.com/2011/09/02/air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida/</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F21134543%2Fair-conditioning-fort-myers-florida"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/21134543/air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines turn into clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks within your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection need to incorporate an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Think about getting a cut-off float switch installed, this can shut off your unit before water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate very same day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a7aa39bcca8a31e6f86a78c692e5520a" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning method does not actually “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is to transport heat from 1 station to a further.  It doesn’t in fact cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your technique utilizes to carry the heat is referred to as a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor in your unit modifications the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows via the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating within the duct function.  The cool air is redistributed by means of your house.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can trigger your method to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient program indicates higher bills.  It forces your compressor to function harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your system is efficient.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating through your ducts passes more than the evaporator coil, it can be cooled and can no longer hold as considerably moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, comparable to what takes place when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogabond.com%2FTripView.aspx%3FTripID%3D138936"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.blogabond.com/TripView.aspx?TripID=138936</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fac-replacement-fort-myerwww..tumblr.com%2Frss"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://ac-replacement-fort-myerwww..tumblr.com/rss</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogster.com%2Fosvaldorutle36%2Fair-conditioning-fort-myers-florida-2"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.blogster.com/osvaldorutle36/air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida-2</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines turn into clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks in your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection should include an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Take into account getting a cut-off float switch installed, this can shut off your unit prior to water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate same day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f214ff7b1ea0021b571fb03e7392c73" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning technique does not in fact “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is to transport heat from one station to a further.  It does not in fact cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your program makes use of to carry the heat is known as a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor within your unit modifications the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows by way of the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating in the duct function.  The cool air is redistributed through your home.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can cause your program to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient method means greater bills.  It forces your compressor to function harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection consists of an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your method is efficient.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating by means of your ducts passes more than the evaporator coil, it can be cooled and can no longer hold as considerably moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, similar to what happens when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Facreplacementfortmyerwww..wetpaint.com%2Fpage%2FAir%2BConditioning%2BFort%2BMyers%2BFlorida%2B%252889%2529"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://acreplacementfortmyerwww..wetpaint.com/page/Air+Conditioning+Fort+Myers+Florida+%2889%29</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fosvaldorutle36409.webs.com%2Fapps%2Fblog%2Fshow%2F8334056-air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://osvaldorutle36409.webs.com/apps/blog/show/8334056-air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.squidoo.com%2Facreplacementfortmyers87"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.squidoo.com/acreplacementfortmyers87</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines turn into clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks within your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection need to contain an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Consider getting a cut-off float switch installed, this may shut off your unit prior to water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate identical day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a476077ab3683a145fcd9bf73a639a80" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning system doesn’t truly “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner would be to transport heat from 1 station to an additional.  It does not basically cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your system utilizes to carry the heat is referred to as a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor in your unit adjustments the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows through the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating within the duct function.  The cool air is redistributed via your residence.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can cause your system to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient system indicates higher bills.  It forces your compressor to work harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection consists of an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your technique is effective.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating through your ducts passes over the evaporator coil, it really is cooled and can no longer hold as a lot moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, comparable to what happens when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/wrightsonny/blog/blogid=4655164" target="_blank">http://en.pan.netcom/wrightsonny/blog/blogid=46...</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F21134613%2Fair-conditioning-fort-myers-florida"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/21134613/air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myindospace.com%2Fblog%2Fview_blog.php%3FBlogId%3D124146%23viewdetails"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.myindospace.com/blog/view_blog.php?BlogId=124146#viewdetails</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines become clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks inside your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection need to include an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Look at getting a cut-off float switch installed, this can shut off your unit prior to water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate exact same day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="90f971a76335cc4b4b8f0ab8a1e96df0" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning method doesn’t basically “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is usually to transport heat from 1 station to a different.  It does not essentially cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your method uses to carry the heat is called a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor in your unit modifications the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows through the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating within the duct function.  The cool air is redistributed by way of your house.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can cause your technique to cool much less efficiently.  An inefficient program means higher bills.  It forces your compressor to work harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your program is effective.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating via your ducts passes over the evaporator coil, it is actually cooled and can no longer hold as considerably moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, comparable to what happens when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Facservicefortmyers90.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F09%2F02%2Fair-conditioning-fort-myers-florida%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://acservicefortmyers90.wordpress.com/2011/09/02/air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida/</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/KeelinpvgsxKrystal/blog/blogid=4655242" target="_blank">http://en.pan.netcom/KeelinpvgsxKrystal/blog/bl...</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogabond.com%2FTripView.aspx%3FTripID%3D138936"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.blogabond.com/TripView.aspx?TripID=138936</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines turn into clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks inside your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection must consist of an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide therapy.  Take into account getting a cut-off float switch installed, this can shut off your unit before water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate similar day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="93fa602fcd69e37b65c4c56898e90da7" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning system does not basically “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is to transport heat from one station to a further.  It does not basically cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your program uses to carry the heat is known as a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor inside your unit changes the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows by means of the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating in the duct function.  The cool air is redistributed by way of your house.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can trigger your method to cool much less efficiently.  An inefficient system means greater bills.  It forces your compressor to work harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your program is efficient.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating by means of your ducts passes more than the evaporator coil, it is cooled and can no longer hold as a lot moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, similar to what occurs when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/KeelinpvgsxKrystal/blog/blogid=4655242" target="_blank">http://en.pan.netcom/KeelinpvgsxKrystal/blog/bl...</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmariomoran1127.insanejournal.com%2F870.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://mariomoran1127.insanejournal.com/870.html</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.journalhome.com%2Felmomccormicksac%2F234148%2Fair-conditioning-fort-myers-florida.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.journalhome.com/elmomccormicksac/234148/air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida.html</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines become clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks within your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection ought to contain an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Contemplate getting a cut-off float switch installed, this can shut off your unit just before water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate exact same day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f1cc8cd7940467e7019452b05cb69dd" url=""><![CDATA[Air Conditioning Fort Myers Florida<br/><br/>How Your A/C Works Fort Myers Florida<br /><br />A central air conditioning method doesn’t really “cool” the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air …<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner “Cool” The Air?<br />Central air conditioning systems are split systems:  an outdoor and an indoor unit.  The function of an air conditioner is usually to transport heat from 1 station to a different.  It does not basically cool the air, but rather creates cool air by removing heat from the air.  The vehicle your method uses to carry the heat is known as a refrigerant.<br /><br />The compressor inside your unit changes the refrigerant into a gas.  As the gas flows via the outdoor coil, it loses heat and condenses into a liquid.  This liquid travels into the evaporator coil.  There the refrigerant expands into a gas.  It then absorbs heat circulating within the duct function.  The cool air is redistributed by means of your residence.  Meanwhile, the heat absorbed by the refrigerant is carried back outside.<br /><br />Dirty coils and improper refrigerant levels can trigger your system to cool less efficiently.  An inefficient technique indicates greater bills.  It forces your compressor to function harder and shortens the life span of your unit.  An annual inspection includes an assessment of the coils and refrigerant charge, to insure that your program is effective.<br /><br />How Does Your Air Conditioner Dehumidify The Air?<br /><br />As the warm air circulating by way of your ducts passes more than the evaporator coil, it truly is cooled and can no longer hold as considerably moisture.  The excess moisture condenses, similar to what happens when moisture condenses on the outside of a glass. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsonnywright1128.insanejournal.com%2F668.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://sonnywright1128.insanejournal.com/668.html</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F775857%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailystrength.org/people/775857/journal</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Facservicefortmyers71.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F09%2F02%2Fair-conditioning-fort-myers-florida%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://acservicefortmyers71.wordpress.com/2011/09/02/air-conditioning-fort-myers-florida/</a><br /><br />Occasionally, the drain lines turn into clogged.  This can result in an overflow, leading to water leaks in your ceilings or calls.  An annual inspection ought to incorporate an assessment of your drain lines and an algaecide treatment.  Look at having a cut-off float switch installed, this may shut off your unit before water overflows. ARS/Rescue Rooter of Fort Myers Plumbing, Heating and air conditioning is open 24 hours per day 7 days per week. For immediate identical day service call us now!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>