<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="18">
		<document id="d2bff29f9d04b8737bd2a6960cf9ddc5" url=""><![CDATA[Micron Associates: HeadLINES<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmicronassociates.org%2Fnews%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://micronassociates.org/news/</a>
<br /><br />Micron Associates: HeadLINES
<br /><br />Manufacturing numbers from the US, China and Germany expected the renewing optimism for the global economic outlook and encouraging investors to take on risk. Early in the afternoon trading in New York, the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 1.16 percent, the Standard &amp; Poor’s 500 Index gained 1.24 percent and the Nasdaq Composite Index climbed 1.32 percent.
<br /><br />In Europe, the Stoxx 600 Index wrecked the session with a 2 percent increase. The euro also gained, strengthening 0.8 percent to US$1.3194 and 0.7 percent to 100.52 yen. An index of the US manufacturing sector rose in January to its maximum level since June, while China’s factory sector unexpectedly stretched out. In Europe, Germany posted its first increase in<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmicronassociates.org%2Fnews%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://micronassociates.org/news/</a> manufacturing output in four months while a UK manufacturing gauge climbed to an eight-month high.
<br /><br />John Manley, chief quity strategist at Wells Fargo Funds Management in New York told Reuters told that “Manufacturing numbers are what the market is jumping on”. Some strategists are updating their bearish forecasts to mirror a better-than-expected start to 2012. Just two weeks after saying that investors should “remain cautious,” Larry Hatheway, the chief economist at UBS, raised his recommendations on global shares and high-yield bonds in a January 23 note to customers entitled, “Wrong, but not too late,” Bloomberg News reported. Royal Bank of Scotland Group, and Benoit Anne, the global head of emerging-markets strategy at Societe Generale said their estimates for developing nations were proven wrong.
<br /><br />Financial shares were among the leading<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmicronassociates.org%2Fnews%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://micronassociates.org/news/</a> gainers including Morgan Stanley which rose nearly 7 percent amid talk that Facebook will choose the firm to take the lead on its planned initial public offering. More details are expected later today. The latest round of US earnings included solid numbers for Whirlpool as its upbeat outlook for the full year lifted its stock more than 15 percent.
<br /><br />It wasn’t all good news, however. Shares of Amazon tanked, dropping more than 9 percent a day after the online retailer warned of a possible first-quarter loss. And the latest data on the jobs front in the US fell short of expectations, as the private sector added 170,000 jobs in January, according to the ADP National Employment Report. Economists’ had called for a gain of 185,000 jobs, according to Reuters.
<br /><br />Investors will eye the US government labour market report due on Friday for further clues. It’s expected to show the economy created 150,000 jobs, and a gain in private payrolls of 170,000, according to Reuters data.”The overall economy lacks oomph and is having trouble creating jobs. Manufacturing is one of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmicronassociates.org%2Fnews%2Ffew"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://micronassociates.org/news/few</a> bright spots in an otherwise disappointing story,” Cary Leahey, managing director at Decision Economics, told Reuters.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9c9dcafcd4057af321df3591607cdd2" url=""><![CDATA[Micron Associates: Hi! TECH<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmicronassociates.net%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://micronassociates.net/</a>
<br /><br />Micron Associates: Hi! TECH
<br /><br />WELCOME! MICRON ASSOCIATES BLOG GIVES YOU AN UPDATE IN A DAY TO DAY UPGRADE OF INVENTIONS THAT IS CURRENTLY AVAILABLE IN THE MARKET.
<br />HOPE YOU ENJOY!  AND BE ON THE LINE OF THIS INNOVATIVE WORLD.
<br /><br />WHAT’S NEW LATEST TECHNOLOGY
<br /><br />Micron Associates is one among the sites that provides Fashion and Technology which both commonly focus on innovation.  Innovative Products but with design aesthetics. In what is called a blend of the ‘commercial and fantastical’, collaboration between top electronic firms and high fashion connoisseurs have proven to be an upside in both industry.
<br /><br />PRIVACY POLICY
<br /><br />Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in focusing on how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making well informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.
<br /><br />INFORMATION WE COLLECT
<br />Micron Associates Blog may collect and store such personal information you have given to us. In addition, we may also collect information through the use of Cookies or such data files that may be downloaded to your computer when you visit the Micron Associates Blog site.
<br /><br />Micron Associates Blog may collect personal information when you
<br /><br />Register with Micron Associates Blog to become a Publisher or Advertiser,
<br />Provide comments or submit a problem to our website
<br />Request information from Micron Associates Blog and provide your name or return contact information, or
<br />Respond to special offers, contests or surveys. As part of the registration process, you may be asked to provide contact information and other personally identifying information. Providing some of the requested information is optional and Micron will indicate what information is required and what information is optional.
<br /><br />LINKS TO OTHER SITES
<br />This website provides links to web sites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party sites.
<br /><br />CONSENT AND CHANGES
<br />Micron Associates Blog may find it necessary or be legally compelled to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date so that you are always aware about the information we collect, how we make use of it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Except as otherwise necessary for law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by this website prior to the effective date of the policy change.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="84662ca2c48110db18b917e44a640851" url=""><![CDATA[Brightbridge Wealth Management Headlines Facebook executive<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feverythingfacebook.net%2Fbrightbridge-wealth-management-headlines-facebook-executive-takes-heat-in-hearing-on-privacy%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://everythingfacebook.net/brightbridge-wealth-management-headlines-facebook-executive-takes-heat-in-hearing-on-privacy/</a>
<br /><br />Reporting from Washington-
<br /><br />A top senator, angry that Facebook Inc. failed to quit millions of preteens from making use of its social networking internet site, accused co-founder Mark Zuckerberg of lacking “social values” and becoming far more concerned with creating the firm than with children’s privacy.
<br /><br />“It really is my common feeling that folks who are 20, 21, 22 years old actually don’t have any social values at this point,” Senate Commerce Committee Chairman John D. Rockefeller IV (D-W.Va.) told one more top Facebook executive at a hearing Thursday.
<br /><br />“I feel he was focused on how the organization model would function,” Rockefeller stated about Zuckerberg, who was a 19-year-old Harvard student when he designed Facebook in 2004. “He wanted to make it bigger and faster and greater than anybody else ever had.”
<br /><br />The company’s policy calls for users to be at least 13, a move developed to steer clear of federal regulations for sites employed by young children. But a current Consumer Reports survey identified that about 7.5 million active Facebook users were younger than 13.
<br /><br />Rockefeller’s comments came as a Facebook executive for the initial time came below congressional quizzing in a current round of hearings about concerns that technologies businesses are not protecting individual privacy. Executives from Apple Inc. and Google Inc., which sent witnesses to a hearing last week, also appeared at Thursday’s hearing before a Commerce subcommittee.
<br /><br />Rockefeller, a crucial player on technology concerns, and other lawmakers are thinking about new regulations to defend on-line privacy, particularly for children. The problem has gained momentum with the current revelation that an obscure file on iPhones and iPads could shop thousands of detailed records of a user’s whereabouts.
<br /><br />Rockefeller mentioned he was lately told by Facebook Chief Operating Officer Sheryl Sandberg that the firm has only 100 people monitoring the posts and other activities of about 600 million users.
<br /><br />“My reaction to that is that is just definitely indefensible,” Rockefeller told Facebook Chief Technology Officer Bret Taylor, saying he was worried about kids getting targeted by sexual predators and on-line bullies. “I want you to defend your business here since I do not know how you can.”
<br /><br />Taylor stated Facebook shuts down the accounts of people found to be lying about their age to stay away from the company’s restriction.
<br /><br />“We do not allow people to misrepresent their age,” Taylor said.
<br /><br />But he admitted Facebook depended on other users to report such violations to enforce the policy.
<br /><br />The under-age dilemma at Facebook showed that massive technology organizations have not made privacy a top priority, stated Amy Guggenheim Shenkan, president of Common Sense Media, a nonprofit kids and family advocacy group.
<br /><br />Such hugely effective innovators should be in a position to generate approaches to better shield children’s privacy, Shenkan said. She then took a swipe at Facebook for hiring a high-powered public-relations firm to push news organizations to write unfavorable stories about privacy concerns at Google.
<br /><br />“Instead of spending funds to – employ PR firms to try and take down the other organization, let’s take that money and devote it on figuring out technological techniques that will shield our youngsters,” she told the subcommittee. “It cannot be 100 individuals sitting in a Facebook office trying to monitor 600 million conversations.”
<br /><br />Sen. John F. Kerry (D-Mass.), who has introduced bipartisan legislation to avoid the misuse of sensitive consumer details, mentioned that privacy protection is not “the enemy of innovation.”
<br /><br />“Firms collecting people’s data, whether you’re a tech titan or not, ought to comply with a simple code of conduct,” Kerry said.
<br /><br />But Taylor warned that new privacy restrictions could squelch Facebook and other social networks.
<br /><br />Facebook tries to safeguard privacy by letting users choose which info they share, he mentioned. But Taylor cautioned that several men and women want to share their photographs and other particulars of their lives to get the most out of social networks, and Facebook doesn’t want to assume that all its users want to put a vault around their information.
<br /><br />“We realize that trust is a foundation of the social Web. Men and women will quit employing Facebook if they lose trust in our services,” he stated. “At the very same time, overly restrictive policies can interfere with the public’s demand for new and innovative methods to interact.”
<br /><br />But lawmakers stated numerous folks are clamoring for a lot more protection of their individual data, particularly now as much more mobile devices can give detailed information about a person’s whereabouts.
<br /><br />David Vladeck, director of the Federal Trade Commission-s Bureau of Consumer Protection, mentioned such place data deserved “specific protection,” although the agency has stopped brief of calling for legislation.
<br /><br />Google also has said it collects place data from mobile devices making use of its Android computer software. But Google and Apple executives stated they collected the data anonymously and shared it with third-party applications only if the user agreed.
<br /><br />“Does Apple track the location of my iPhone?” Sen. Roy Blunt (R-Mo.) asked, holding up his device.
<br /><br />“We do not, sir,” stated Catherine A. Novelli, Apple’s vice president for worldwide government affairs.
<br /><br />The company never tracked a user’s actual location from the data collected on iPhones and iPads, only the place of nearby cellphone towers and Wi-Fi hot spots, she stated.
<br /><br />Apple mentioned a computer software glitch caused the location information to be updated even when the user had selected not to use location-based services. The bug was fixed in the most recent computer software release, and the information will be encrypted in the subsequent update, Novelli stated.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4fcf43829a09d0afa37f9727467d3c22" url=""><![CDATA[Brightbridge Wealth Management Headlines Airbnb offers $50,0<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.1888pressrelease.com%2Fbrightbridge-wealth-management-headlines-airbnb-offers-50-0-pr-328511.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.1888pressrelease.com/brightbridge-wealth-management-headlines-airbnb-offers-50-0-pr-328511.html</a>
<br /><br />(1888PressRelease) August 21, 2011 - Airbnb announced a $50,000 insurance policy and the formation of a 24/7 customer support hotline Monday after two users recently said their use of the company’s travel services had left them the victims of vandalism and theft.
<br /><br />Up to this point, Airbnb - a website that connects travelers with people who are willing to host travelers - had been on a hot streak: It had landed high-profile celebrity and tech investor Ashton Kutcher as an advisor, as well as a funding round of $112 million, which valued the company at $1.3 billion.
<br /><br />In June, an San Francisco Airbnb user identifying herself as E.J. said on her personal blog that a person who rented her apartment on the website had trashed her home and stolen her jewelry, some cash and electronics, among other things. E.J. followed up that post with one Thursday accusing Airbnb of trying to get her to remove her original blog post as well as neglecting to help her recover from the “nightmare” of a situation.
<br /><br />Another Airbnb user, Troy Dayton, told the website TechCrunch that he too had his home vandalized by someone who had rented his apartment through the service and that he’d come home to find “meth pipes everywhere.”
<br /><br />After a back-and-forth between TechCrunch and investors in Airbnb, Chief Executive Brian Chesky wrote a blog post Monday saying his San Francisco start-up hadn’t handled its users’ situations correctly and was looking to make things right.
<br /><br />“Last month, the home of a San Francisco host named EJ was tragically vandalized by a guest,” Chesky said. “The damage was so bad that her life was turned upside down. When we learned of this our hearts sank. We felt paralyzed, and over the last four weeks, we have really screwed things up.”
<br /><br />The CEO apologized for Airbnb’s mistakes and said the last few days have given the company a “crash course in crisis management.”
<br /><br />Chesky said that Airbnb is working with the San Francisco Police Department to set things straight for E.J. and that a suspect is in custody.
<br /><br />“I hope this can be a valuable lesson to other businesses about what not to do in a time of crisis,” he said. “With regards to EJ, we let her down, and for that we are very sorry. We should have responded faster, communicated more sensitively, and taken more decisive action to make sure she felt safe and secure. But we weren’t prepared for the crisis and we dropped the ball. Now we’re dealing with the consequences.”
<br /><br />In an attempt to “make it right,” Chesky said Airbnb would launch its $50,000 Airbnb Guarantee on Aug. 15, which it says will provide up to $50,000 in insurance for any loss or damages at the property of an Airbnb “host” by someone who made their reservations through the company’s website.
<br /><br />Next week, the site will launch a 24/7 hotline for its users to report any problems with its service or to complain about other users, he said. If an Airbnb user can’t reach anyone when they need to, Chesky said he’d be reachable by email at brian.chesky ( @ ) airbnb dot com dot 
<br /><br />“We will extend this program to E.J. and any other hosts who may have reported such property damage while renting on Airbnb in the past,” he said.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f9b49043916053deeb45349a67cd5b0b" url=""><![CDATA[Micron Associates Features The Micron FZ-16<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsmall-business.ezinemark.com%2Fmicron-associates-features-the-micron-fz-16-7d35995085ad.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://small-business.ezinemark.com/micron-associates-features-the-micron-fz-16-7d35995085ad.html</a>
<br /><br />Revenue details
<br />Micron Technology chalked up revenue of $2.07 billion. The 24 analysts polled by S&amp;P Capital IQ expected to see a top line of $2.01 billion on the same basis. GAAP reported sales were 8.4% lower than the prior-year quarter’s $2.26 billion.
<br />Source: S&amp;P Capital IQ. Quarterly periods. Dollar amounts in millions. Non-GAAP figures may vary to maintain comparability with estimates.
<br /><br />EPS details
<br />EPS came in at -$0.23. The 26 earnings estimates compiled by S&amp;P Capital IQ anticipated -$0.20 per share. GAAP EPS were -$0.23 for Q2 compared to $0.07 per share for the prior-year quarter.
<br />Advertise | AdChoices
<br /><br />Source: S&amp;P Capital IQ. Quarterly periods. Non-GAAP figures may vary to maintain comparability with estimates.
<br /><br />Margin details
<br />For the quarter, gross margin was 13.0%, 630 basis points worse than the prior-year quarter. Operating margin was -7.2%, 1,370 basis points worse than the prior-year quarter. Net margin was -10.8%, 1,400 basis points worse than the prior-year quarter.
<br /><br />Looking ahead
<br />Next quarter’s average estimate for revenue is $2.13 billion. On the bottom line, the average EPS estimate is -$0.13.
<br /><br />Next year’s average estimate for revenue is $8.57 billion. The average EPS estimate is -$0.38.
<br /><br />Investor sentiment
<br />The stock has a three-star rating (out of five) at Motley Fool CAPS, with 1,161 members rating the stock outperform and 129 members rating it underperform. Among 230 CAPS All-Star picks (recommendations by the highest-ranked CAPS members), 205 give Micron Technology a green thumbs-up, and 25 give it a red thumbs-down.
<br />Of Wall Street recommendations tracked by S&amp;P Capital IQ, the average opinion on Micron Technology is outperform, with an average price target of $9.98.
<br />Is Micron Technology the best semiconductor stock for you? You may be missing something obvious. Check out the semiconductor company that Motley Fool analysts expect to lead “The Next Trillion-Dollar Revolution.” Click here for instant access to this free report.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f5828d0aa0675296ffd3ab648efe5590" url=""><![CDATA[Micron Associates Technology Goes Red<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.squidoo.com%2Fmicron-associates-barcelona-spain9"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.squidoo.com/micron-associates-barcelona-spain9</a>
<br /><br />Revenue details
<br />Micron Technology chalked up revenue of $2.07 billion. The 24 analysts polled by S&amp;P Capital IQ expected to see a top line of $2.01 billion on the same basis. GAAP reported sales were 8.4% lower than the prior-year quarter’s $2.26 billion.
<br />Source: S&amp;P Capital IQ. Quarterly periods. Dollar amounts in millions. Non-GAAP figures may vary to maintain comparability with estimates.
<br /><br />EPS details
<br />EPS came in at -$0.23. The 26 earnings estimates compiled by S&amp;P Capital IQ anticipated -$0.20 per share. GAAP EPS were -$0.23 for Q2 compared to $0.07 per share for the prior-year quarter.
<br />Advertise | AdChoices
<br /><br />Source: S&amp;P Capital IQ. Quarterly periods. Non-GAAP figures may vary to maintain comparability with estimates.
<br /><br />Margin details
<br />For the quarter, gross margin was 13.0%, 630 basis points worse than the prior-year quarter. Operating margin was -7.2%, 1,370 basis points worse than the prior-year quarter. Net margin was -10.8%, 1,400 basis points worse than the prior-year quarter.
<br /><br />Looking ahead
<br />Next quarter’s average estimate for revenue is $2.13 billion. On the bottom line, the average EPS estimate is -$0.13.
<br /><br />Next year’s average estimate for revenue is $8.57 billion. The average EPS estimate is -$0.38.
<br /><br />Investor sentiment
<br />The stock has a three-star rating (out of five) at Motley Fool CAPS, with 1,161 members rating the stock outperform and 129 members rating it underperform. Among 230 CAPS All-Star picks (recommendations by the highest-ranked CAPS members), 205 give Micron Technology a green thumbs-up, and 25 give it a red thumbs-down.
<br />Of Wall Street recommendations tracked by S&amp;P Capital IQ, the average opinion on Micron Technology is outperform, with an average price target of $9.98.
<br />Is Micron Technology the best semiconductor stock for you? You may be missing something obvious. Check out the semiconductor company that Motley Fool analysts expect to lead “The Next Trillion-Dollar Revolution.” Click here for instant access to this free report.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8dd6e71e2e55818720d26f40f3b0e77c" url=""><![CDATA[Micron Associates Features The Micron FZ-16<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsmall-business.ezinemark.com%2Fmicron-associates-features-the-micron-fz-16-7d35995085ad.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://small-business.ezinemark.com/micron-associates-features-the-micron-fz-16-7d35995085ad.html</a>
<br /><br />Micron offers full systems and slip-ons for a vast array of the high performance sport bike and cruiser motorcycles, Most of their product features not seen on any competitor’s products. Extensive color options and use of standard and “high” mount exhausts for the sport bikes allows for many different looks and styles for customers, making its machine as unique as the individual who rides on it.
<br /><br />Micron engineers fabricate not only the highest quality products available in the exhaust world, but also some of the most unique and beautiful products available anywhere. In today’s market, Micron features the Yamaha FZ16.  Inspired by the naked bike concept, the FZ-16 is modeled after its more popular counterpart the FZ1 with scaled down engine. The FZ-16 uses 140/60 size rear radial tubeless tire. Micron introduces their new design of a high performance and high quality experience, Yamaha FZ16.
<br /><br />These are far and away the finest addition ever offered for the 1000, because with one simple bolt on the machine takes on an entirely new look, losing completely the “boat anchor” stock muffler that is so distracting to the looks of the machine. Clean and neat from the exhaust back, the Micron GP really smoothes out the look of the bike as no other exhaust can.
<br /><br />The Micron Canister: Quality is what Micron Associates do and offer to their clients. The best feature of micron products that contribute to its ability to meet it’s given requirements as well as their customers wants and satisfaction.
<br /><br />This is just a number one approach that they are in capable of to be the reliable leading manufacturer around the world. So in view of this fact, Micron pronounces their new product in the market. A new product in which you’re earned money will be going to the real world of use.
<br /><br />The Micron canisters are well constructed using polished stainless steel end caps (or CNC machined billet aluminum for flange mounts), a stainless steel interior tube and a clean sleeve with no sleeve rivets to rattle loose or wreck the carbon fiber (as many of our competitors set-ups do). Then the Micron canisters use our unique 3&amp;4-bolt end cap designs, which means that unlike companies which are stuck in the 1970’s and use rivets to hold their cans together with the sleeve as a stressed member, our canisters have NO rivets holding the sleeves to the end caps.  Most companies will say that they use “this or that” to secure the rivets, but the bottom line is that these are just layers of fixes to a less expensive and old design. Micron quality means the canister sleeve should not be used as a structural member of the canister, as the continual heating and cooling cycles, combined with the shaking and pounding that a muffler takes, makes rivets a very weak and poor choice for assembly. Six months or a year down the road a poor finish forces both ill will and an unnecessary second purchase on your part. Better to buy quality once, and leave the problems to others.
<br /><br />To know more about micron canister just visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.micronexhaust.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.micronexhaust.com</a> in which will add colors and can make your machine as unique as your passion for your motorcycling with the wide range of colors of micron canister.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="de34f5ca8a99a3778eab0e3cb8c93738" url=""><![CDATA[Micron Associates<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmicronassociatesredsmith87.blogspot.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://micronassociatesredsmith87.blogspot.com/</a>
<br /><br />Sprint Nextel Corporation S +0.36% : Sprint Nextel Corporation S +0.36% and its no-contract brand Boost Mobile have recently been rated highest among full-service and non-contract providers in J.D. Power and Associates’ Wireless Purchase Experience Study, Volume 1. Sprint share prices reached US$2.52 on Thursday, with 13% up. There were 100.51 million stock shares traded, which was 2.3 times more than average volume. Do you want to know when company insiders will buy their shares? Want to add and monitor this company on an on-going basis? It can be done for free by registering below.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c3d6b0b7cfdb1e803186ef25996799" url=""><![CDATA[eldridge financial switzerland<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feldridgefinancialswitzerlandwicapi.blogspot.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://eldridgefinancialswitzerlandwicapi.blogspot.com/</a>
<br /><br />February 15, 2012 – LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA – (Kazor.com) – Britain is once again suffering a recession and unemployment risks coming close into three million this year as forecasted by the leading economic forecaster. The UK’s economic recovery is ‘paralyzed’ by Europe’s debt crisis, the Ernst &amp; Young Item club will warn, as it cut its GDP growth forecast from 1.5 per cent to 0.2 per cent. According to Eldridge Financial Blog, the dire prediction comes after nine European countries including France, have had their credit ratings downgraded on Friday, dropping world stock markets into turmoil.
<br /><br />Economists had hoped that exports and business investment would strengthen the economy this year, with public and consumerspending still in the doldrums. Nevertheless, Europe accounts for more than 40 percent of British trade and business confidence has been roughly hit by insecurity about the future of the Continent and the single currency. On Eldridge Financial Blog in the Sunday Telegraph quoted Professor Peter Spencer, chief economist at the Item Club, as saying: ‘Figures for the last quarter of 2011 and the first quarter of this year are likely to show that we are back in recession, and we are going to have to wait until summer before there are signs of improvement. Although he said the double dip was unlikely to be prolonged, he warned that unemployment was nevertheless likely to hit three million by early next year. Figures set for release on Wednesday are expected to show the jobless figures continued to rise in the three months up until the end of November. Professor Spencer admitted that the Item Club’s predictions were based on positive assumptions about European policymakers’ ability to keep the euro zone from falling apart. The longer the uncertainty continues, the more debilitating the impact will be on the UK’s economic prospects, he added. The European Commission vice-president for economic affairs, Olli Rehn, yesterday attacked the decision by Standard &amp; Poor’s to cut down the credit ratings of so many European countries.
<br /><br />The downgrades were ‘inconsistent’, claiming that the euro zone was taking ‘decisive action’ over the economic crisis.
<br /><br /><strong>About Eldridge Financial Blog</strong>
<br /><br />Find investment ideas, stock quotes, charts, business news, market research and learning a lot of things financially!!! Geared towards the young professional seeking investment ideas and personal financial advice. Never invest into a stock discussed on this web site unless you can afford to lose your entire investment.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9e8a030c4aefdbcdf39dd3fb09fcdc46" url=""><![CDATA[Eldridge Financial Blog: Key aims to piggyback on China’s<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmcdanielfal.wordpress.com%2F2012%2F02%2F22%2Feldridge-financial-blog-key-aims-to-piggyback-on-chinas-success%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://mcdanielfal.wordpress.com/2012/02/22/eldridge-financial-blog-key-aims-to-piggyback-on-chinas-success/</a>
<br /><br />More Chinese investment in New Zealand farms and infrastructure will be targeted by the Government.
<br /><br />Prime Minister John Key today released a strategy to double trade with the Asian super power by 2015, saying it is critical for the country’s financial wellbeing.
<br /><br />Opening Our Doors to China has taken over a year to develop and comes as public anger grows over farm land sales to foreigners, particularly the Crafar farms bought by a Chinese company.
<br /><br />The idea of Chinese investors taking over the Crafar farms has not sat well with many and the Green Party says the farms were sacrificed for the sake of a stronger relationship with China.
<br /><br />But Key is eager to develop the relationship with Beijing, believing New Zealand can be prosperous on the back of “probably the fastest growing economy in the world”.
<br /><br />“They’re our second largest market…by 2020 they’re likely to be the largest economy in the world,” said Key.
<br /><br /><strong>Remarkable benefits</strong>
<br /><br />The New Zealand – China strategy is designed to double two-way trade with the People’s Republic to $20 billions by 2015. It aims to increase the number of Chinese students in NZ, assist NZ food, beverage and agribusiness exporters and target Chinese investment in infrastructure and farmland.
<br /><br />The strategy would mean more sales like the Crafar farms which the Greens say was approved to facilitate the broader strategy of the China/New Zealand trade and other arrangements.
<br /><br />Co-leader Russel Norman accepts the relationship is important but is quick to point out New Zealanders can’t buy land in China.
<br /><br />Key says the long term benefits are remarkable and he believes the Government has got the balance around ownership “about right”.
<br /><br />Key said the strategy sets out “ambitious” medium term goals and provides a clear direction for a co-ordinated Government effort over a five year period. 
<br /><br />It has a strong trade focus but also looks at building political and diplomatic ties through a set of five goals that specify action such as developing more high-quality science and technology collaborations.
<br /><br />Two-way trade with China was up 22% last year.
<br /><br /><strong>Investment encouraged</strong>
<br /><br />The Government also says in the strategy that Chinese investment in New Zealand is tiny compared to Australia and needs to grow “to levels that reflect the growing commercial relationship with China,” for continued engagement with the world’s fastest-growing superpower.
<br /><br />Investment into China by New Zealand firms is also minuscule, at $541 million, compared with $36 billion of Australian investments in China, partly because of New Zealand’s wider track record of exporting commodities for others to process rather than investing in its own high-value production.
<br /><br />Part of the problem, the strategy says, is that “Chinese investors are unaware of New Zealand opportunities”, with resources to improve two-way understanding of commercial opportunities to be beefed up by, among other moves, establishment of a high-level New Zealand China Council.
<br /><br />The relatively small size of investment opportunities in New Zealand was also a factor in limited Chinese inward investment, as well as the strict controls that apply to Chinese companies seeking to invest outside the Chinese mainland.
<br /><br />New Zealand firms’ inexperience of Chinese markets was a major reason there was not more investment flowing from this country into China.
<br /><br />While China invested approximately US$60 billion globally in 2010/11, Chinese-owned assets in New Zealand amount to only NZ$1.87 billion in total, compared with $100 billion invested by China in Australia.
<br /><br /><strong>What China wants</strong>
<br /><br />Before Key’s speech, PwC Partner Colum Rice told TV ONE’s Breakfast that the business community will be looking for a “positive statement” from the Government.
<br /><br />“Bill English has made statements about encouraging trade but this will be where the rubber hits the road and we’ll see what they have come up with,” he said.
<br /><br />Rice says the release of an official strategy will be the proof that the Government is strongly committed to a bigger relationship with China, despite the worries of some Kiwis.
<br /><br />China is already New Zealand’s number two trading partner but Rice says there has been much less work done on the investment side.
<br /><br />Rice, who deals with Chinese business people looking to invest, says assuming Chinese only want dairy farms is wrong because they are looking for good opportunities across a broad range of sectors.
<br /><br />He encourages New Zealand businesses to embrace the opportunities of dealing with China and says the current relationships established are only scratching the surface of what the FTA can offer.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e0ffbb3cb4c6ae71a7cc3dfb39ae7e7f" url=""><![CDATA[Micron Associates - Blogspot: GRAVITO-MAGNETIC ORBITS FOR MI<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.valueinvestingnews.com%2Fmicron-associates-blogspot-gravitomagnetic-orbits-micron-siz"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.valueinvestingnews.com/micron-associates-blogspot-gravitomagnetic-orbits-micron-siz</a>
<br /><br />The two body dynamics of an orbiting particle is usually governed by Newton’s laws of gravity and mechanics. Here the Kepler problem has been studied with the addition of the Lorentz force of magnetism. For micrometeoroids and small man made debris particles electromagnetic interactions may become important. The space environment is filled with charged particles, electrons and ions, that may be deposited on a 1 - 100 microns sized particle. The orbits of such charged particles have been modeled in earth orbit, with the dipole magnetic field superposed on the gravity field. An initial study of this problem has been conducted. Figures 1 illustrates a 600 second time frame of particles in a 300 kilometer altitude Earth orbit with a 5.7’ inclination. The solid line is the pure Kepler problem. The dashed lines are the paths taken by various sized particles with a single positive charge of 1.6x10-‘~ coulombs. The additional energy required to deflect these particles from a Kepler orbit
<br />comes from the deposition of charge at the initial stage in the calculation. From there the energy of the particle is conserved since both the gravitational and magnetic forces are conservative, i.e. $F d r = 0. The orbit of 1 micron sized particles has been computed and the results are shown in figures 2 through 5. The results of this numerical exercise in magneto-orbital dynamics a r e rather unexpected, but appear physically correct when studied. The particle was set in a 2000km orbit with a 5.7’ inclination. Figure 2 displays how the magnetic field torques the orbital plane. Figure 3 then shows how the orbit is flipped over and shoved toward the north pole. This is analogous to the spin orbit interaction in the quantum atom. He r e the magnetic moments of the Earth’s magnetic field and the
<br />orbit a r e parallel. The flip in the orbit is a result of the system’s requirement to reach a lower magnetic energy by antiorienting the magnetic moments. The energy lost by reorienting the magnetic moment goes into gravitational potential energy by shoving the orbit above the north pole. Since this model is classical, and the electromagnetic radiation emitted by the accelerating charge is negligible, events depart from the Bohr quantum analog above. The charged particle finds itself in a magnetic bottle near the north pole, figure 4. The spiralling charged particle is deflected upward by the converging magnetic field. The spiral then climbs upward only to be drawn back down by gravity. The spiral bounces up
<br />and down gradually reaching on average a lower altitude with each bounce. This ephemeris run went for 84000 iterations, with three seconds per iteration, before the particle crashed into the Earth. Figure 5 is a close up of the oscillating orbital spiral shortly before it crashes into the earth. This problem explores a hole in the current understanding of orbital mechanics of particles. Ions and electrons in the Earth environment are treated as obeying the laws of electromagnetism, and collectively according to plasma physics.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="91e3b99accf2fb9bd1653df2690b3447" url=""><![CDATA[Micron Associates<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopingtech.com%2Ftag%2Fmicron-associates%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.shopingtech.com/tag/micron-associates/</a>
<br /><br />Three partners formed the company in 2002, then it was a small consultancy for SEC qualified private investors. Over the years, resulting from the success of the company it has grown and expanded into one of the finest venture capital firms today. Micron Associates’ success has been honed over the years. They have refined their research methods and have an excellent understanding of the financial markets. MA is a client base and their fruitful portfolios illustrate the achievements of the advice we give to our clientele. Micron Associates Spain put their success down to passion, persistence, and hard work. Finding the right investments at the right time doesn’t come down to luck it comes down to understanding the economics of the deal. Their proven formula is the foundation of all advice we give their clients; this is their guide to ensure the success of financial growth. Micron Associates mission is to fulfill the financial goals of MA’s clients’. The ambitions of MA’s clients are what drives the firm to become a first-class brokerage firm, MA’s clients’ are their heartbeat. Each client will get the personal touch; each client deserves MA’s professional attention to their financial growth objectives. Throughout a client’s relationship, Micron Associates endeavour to maintain the highest level of professionalism possible when giving advice about any financial planning. 
<br /><br />At Micron Associates, Madrid, Spain we hire financial experts across all aspects of financial planning, this ensures that we offer the right advice to each of our clients depending on their needs. It is important for this company to establish that each client has professional advice that fits in with their current and future goals. We ensure that all advice we give is unbiased and based on thorough research using the very latests financial tools and methodologies.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d4da63e97668679cc8baa93001be9f8b" url=""><![CDATA[Fed Apprehension Job Gains Could Fade By Eldridge Financial<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.articlesnatch.com%2FArticle%2FFed-Apprehension-Job-Gains-Could-Fade-By-Eldrige-Financial-Blog%2F3814513"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.articlesnatch.com/Article/Fed-Apprehension-Job-Gains-Could-Fade-By-Eldrige-Financial-Blog/3814513</a>
<br /><br />WASHINGTON “” The current strong gains in hiring makes the Federal Reserve policymakers worried that it could buzz if the economic growth of the US doesn”t go up.
<br /><br />According to the Fed”s minutes on Tuesday, members were first stated their concerns before they make a plan to keep interest rates at record lows until at least late year 2014. However, some of the members want to take further procedures to improve the economy current status if a condition gets worse or inflation remains reclaimed.
<br /><br />After the meeting, Fed presented the somewhat current view of the economy mainly because of the three consecutive months of hiring in two years. It was concluded that there have been similar raptures of hiring in the previous two years which ended up fading.
<br /><br />On the speech echoed by the Fed Chairman Ben Bernanke last week in the economists gathering, the decline of the economy recovery was the main concern of Fed as it did last year.
<br /><br />Americans aren”t receiving meaningful pay augmentation. Gas prices are high. Additionally, Europe”s debt crisis could reflect on the U.S economy. Provided that the inflation will remain on its current position, analysts think that the Fed will likely give interest rates down in order for them to give the economy an additional support. Most of the economists don”t think that Fed officials will alter their interest-rate policy at their following meeting on April 24-25 and will only relieve credits if the economy gradually moves from its current status.
<br /><br />The economy outlook is going up. Employers added an average of 245,000 jobs a month from December through February. On the other side, the rate of unemployed dropped nearly to 8.3%. The government will report Friday on the job market in March. Most of the economists supposed that the report will give a better month of job creation with a net gain of 210,000 jobs. They also expect that the unemployment rate will remain at 8.3%.
<br /><br />About Eldridge Financial Blog
<br /><br />Find investment ideas, stock quotes, charts, business news, market research and learning a lot of things financially!!! Geared towards the young professional seeking investment ideas and personal financial advice. Never invest into a stock discussed on this web site unless you can afford to lose your entire investment
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6e1ec5d3d526e011719fd195d7eabf5b" url=""><![CDATA[Eldridge Financial Blog: Uk In Recession Again As Recovery<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.articlesnatch.com%2FArticle%2FEldridge-Financial-Blog--Uk-In-Recession-Again-As-Recovery-Is----paralyzed----By-The-European-Debt%2F3649252"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.articlesnatch.com/Article/Eldridge-Financial-Blog--Uk-In-Recession-Again-As-Recovery-Is----paralyzed----By-The-European-Debt/3649252</a>
<br /><br />Britain is once again suffering a recession and unemployment risks coming close into three million this year as forecasted by the leading economic forecaster. The UKs economic recovery is paralyzed by Europes debt crisis, the Ernst &amp; Young Item club will warn, as it cut its GDP growth forecast from 1.5 per cent to 0.2 per cent.According to Eldridge Financial Blog,the dire prediction comes after nine European countries including France, have had their credit ratings downgraded on Friday, dropping world stock markets into turmoil.
<br /><br />Economistshadhopedthatexportsandbusinessinvestmentwouldstrengthen theeconomythis year,withpublicandconsumerspendingstillin thedoldrums.Nevertheless, Europe accounts for more than 40 percent of British trade and business confidence has been roughly hit by insecurity about the future of the Continent and the single currency.On Eldridge Financial Blogin the Sunday Telegraph quoted Professor Peter Spencer, chief economist at the Item Club, as saying: Figures for the last quarter of 2011 and the first quarter of this year are likely to show that we are back in recession, and we are going to have to wait until summer before there are signs of improvement. Although he said the double dip was unlikely to be prolonged, he warned that unemployment was nevertheless likely to hit three million by early next year. Figures set for release on Wednesday are expected to show the jobless figures continued to rise in the three months up until the end of November. Professor Spencer admitted that the Item Clubs predictions were based on positive assumptions about European policymakers ability to keep the euro zone from falling apart. The longer the uncertainty continues, the more debilitating the impact will be on the UKs economic prospects, he added. The European Commission vice-president for economic affairs, Olli Rehn, yesterday attacked the decision by Standard &amp; Poors to cut down the credit ratings of so many European countries.
<br /><br />The downgrades were inconsistent, claiming that the euro zone was taking decisive action over the economic crisis.
<br /><br />About Eldridge Financial Blog
<br /><br />Find investment ideas, stock quotes, charts, business news, market research and learning a lot of things financially!!! Geared towards the young professional seeking investment ideas and personal financial advice. Never invest into a stock discussed on this web site unless you can afford to lose your entire investment
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="789704c2e4ba3ce631e847926ac77314" url=""><![CDATA[Cruse & Associates | Utilize the federal grants to help<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcruseandassociates.info%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://cruseandassociates.info/</a>
<br /><br />With the soaring debt obligations in the United States of America, an increasingly large number of people are looking for options to meet their obligations without having to repay the money. As the lenders charge outrageously high interest rates on the loans, most of the debtors look for options to take out money that they don’t have to repay so that they don’t incur further debt. When it comes to money that need not repay, the only thing that comes to mind is the grants that are backed by the Federal government. The personal debt level can reach such a height that you may not be able to tackle it on your own and this is when you may need to get help from the Federal grants.
<br /><br />What does the government do for you? As the government sees that the consumer credit card debt level is spiraling out of control, it tries to take certain steps that can ease off your financial worries. The federal government offers grant cash for all those people who demonstrate pressing financial needs and therefore if you can show that your monthly income is not letting you pay off all your debts, you can easily be able to get grants that can be used to repay debts.
<br /><br />If you’re a student who is eager to complete a college education but doesn’t have enough funds, you can get Federal Pell grant, TEACH grant, SMART grant and use the proceeds to pay the college costs and the tuition fees. However, it is not that anyone can take out such grants as this is free money given by the government. Each type of grant will have its own qualification criteria and hence you have to make sure that you meet this criterion in order to get grants that can fulfill your pressing financial needs. A few grants are identical and if you can find out a grant option that can meet your financial needs, you should take the required steps to get them.
<br /><br />The government has its own website through which you can easily take out the grant money. You may have to fill out an application form, through which you will be able to divulge your personal details to the government, your name, address, total monthly income of your family and the total expenses that you may incur in college. Only after they see that you’re earnestly in need of the federal grant money, they will take the step of granting the money and realizing your financial dream. Don’t waste the money in other unnecessary expenses. Utilize the funds in repaying your debt obligations as soon as possible and secure a debt free life.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="95faa2940d50118530a2c446acf1a018" url=""><![CDATA[About Us | Cruse & Associates<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcruseandassociates.info%2Fhome%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://cruseandassociates.info/home/</a>
<br /><br />If you have been planning to buy your dream home for very long and you are unable to do that because of the rising prices everywhere, Cruse and Associates are here to help you.
<br /><br />Cruse and Associates can take a loan that will help you to buy your dream home. We provide qualified individuals or companies for the purpose of financing acquisition of lot, house and lot, condominium unit or townhouse, construction of houses, renovation or expansion of an existing house, refinancing of an existing mortgage, or multi-purpose loan.
<br /><br />Cruse and Associates steadfast efforts in accomplishing company’s goals have assisted us in having an enormous client base in this competitive industry. Some of the factors that distinguish us from others are:
<br /><br />? Timely execution of our services
<br /><br />? Reliable customer service
<br /><br />? Rich expertise
<br /><br />? Efficient team of employees
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="95386bb6bbb5c9c9802f0af51476738c" url=""><![CDATA[Money laundering - Bark & Co Solicitors - Specialist Fra<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.barkco.com%2FExpertise%2FMoney%2Blaundering"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.barkco.com/Expertise/Money+laundering</a>
<br /><br />As one of the leading serious fraud firms in UK, Bark &amp; Co regularly have to advise their clients on the implications of money laundering charges which often accompany investigations and prosecutions of fraud. UK legislation is wide ranging and recent changes to the law have increased the likelihood of money laundering charges being pursued vigorously by the authorities. The team at Bark &amp; Co are experts in the interpretation of the law and in particular the parameters open to the prosecuting authorities in respect of money laundering charges.
<br /><br />In the UK, primary legislation on money laundering includes the Terrorism Act 2000, the Anti-Terrorism Crime &amp; Security Act 2001, the Proceeds of Crime Act 2005 and the Serious Crime and Police Act 2005. Secondary legislation comprises Money laundering Regulations 2003 and 2007. These increasingly stringent regulations put the onus on businesses to ensure that certain controls are in place to prevent them being used for money laundering purposes including customer due diligence measures and internal controls and monitoring systems.
<br /><br />Under UK law, it is a money laundering offence when a person enters into, or becomes concerned in, an arrangement which facilitates by whatever means the requisition, retention, use or control of criminal property (assets or money) by another person. In many cases, the authorities seek to block suspected money laundering activities at an early stage by applying severe constraints even where there is scant evidence of wrong doing. Actions include forfeiture of assets etc.
<br /><br />Bark &amp; Co frequently has cases under way where our clients are facing both fraud and money laundering charges. In one such recent example the FSA and City of London Police had mounted a combined operation into a large boiler room fraud based overseas. This case has been singled out as a good example of the increasing scale and prevalence of this type of fraud and demonstrates how international operations are being used to bypass the UK financial regulations and authorities to launder money abroad. In another fully contended, cut-throat trial, our client was implicated in a conspiracy to defraud a bank of more than £200M, setting up several offshore accounts to money launder the proceeds of the fraud. In all cases, Bark &amp; Co set out to ensure that our experience and expertise is carefully matched to client requirements, utilising the best legal counsel where necessary to achieve the best outcome.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a24aefc0453133ed36d809d1e18f2161" url=""><![CDATA[Indirect Tax - Bark & Co Solicitors - Specialist Fraud F<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.barkco.com%2FExpertise%2FIndirect%2BTax"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.barkco.com/Expertise/Indirect+Tax</a>
<br /><br />Indirect Tax
<br />Indirect taxes, predominantly Value Added Tax and excise duties, are now a common subject of civil litigation. Litigation of this kind often involves a department of Government such as Her Majesty’s Revenue and Customs making allegations of fraud or dishonesty against legitimate businesses and their directors.
<br /><br />The Commercial and Indirect Tax Fraud team at Bark &amp; Co has an excellent reputation for successfully negotiating and litigating a wide range of disputes. We have a large team of specialist
<br /><br />Areas of Expertise:
<br /><br />The specialisations of the Commercial and Indirect Tax Fraud Team include:
<br /><br />• VAT Fraud
<br />• MTIC Fraud
<br />• Carousel Fraud
<br />• Knowledge/Means of Knowledge Input Tax Denial
<br />• Invalid Invoice disputes
<br />• Assessments of VAT and/or Excise
<br />• Excise Diversion Fraud
<br />• Seizure of goods upon importation
<br />• Repayment Supplement Appeals (delayed authorisation of VAT returns)
<br />• Default Surcharge Appeals
<br />• Extended Verification of VAT returns
<br />• Freezing and Restraint Orders
<br /><br />Our team retains litigation expertise in all the relevant forums, particularly in the VAT and Duties Tribunals and the High Court.
<br /><br />Current cases include high profile MTIC and Carousel fraud allegations amounting to hundreds of millions of pounds that are set to test both UK and European legislation.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>