<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="16b19f1330ac8991fcc1d48efbefcd6a" url=""><![CDATA[Lewis is still in the adjust the heat admitted that playin<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 18 morning, Miami media published an article, reported the rashard lewis is still trying to think of a way to adapt to and blend in Miami, lewis said in an interview, oneself need to change before the shooting, passing the second habit, only in this way can we better in Miami.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">nike air max womens</a> Below is part of the paper:Since rashard lewis in July this year to veteran minimum salary and Miami after signing, he still hasn't found in Miami feeling. &amp;quot;I now goal is to continue to training every day in training, hope oneself can improve not appear degenerative signs.&amp;quot; Lewis in today accept media interviews that said, &amp;quot;I feel to come here, all in an effort to keep their own state<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90</a>, I feel once I miss a day of training, I afraid I will fell behind. We now distance new season opening only two weeks' time, so I have to take the time to training and for the training of gradually find the feeling of a team.&amp;quot;The 33-year-old lewis in the offseason this year had undergone knee surgery, he had previously missed the previous two seasons of most of the game
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 mens</a>. Lewis now state also had not fully recovered. Lewis, and this is ray Allen and arrived in Miami to participate in training camp, Miami fans to the two pitchers on the arrival of the high expectations. But, after three preseason games after the game,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 womens</a> lewis obviously haven't found for Miami play game feeling.&amp;quot;Rashard can play very good.&amp;quot; Miami coach spor Stella said, &amp;quot;after all he missed the previous two seasons, so he will find state and feeling is need some time, we will keep on this issue patience.&amp;quot; Spor Stella had said these words do not ban people think of last season Eddie - the Treasury situation,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 90</a> garage there has been no way to Miami for competition, and handsome, have been foreign is such a statement. Finally, there is no garage for Miami battle circumstances also get a championship ring, lewis is not to repeat mistakes of the garage.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a15d51e75626d54f2d15b484f645f079" url=""><![CDATA[NBA China "behind the scene more: the SAN Antonio spur<br/><br/>The sixth NBA China &quot;has both in Beijing and Shanghai are two games contest, the NBA China&quot; is sent players in the history of the most luxurious team, the Miami heat and the clippers two teams were 11 NBA all-star, three NBA finals MVP and six Olympic gold medal winner,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a> and this is also the first time a NBA championship teams participating in China. In addition to high level of dual meet outside, the NBA China &quot;another big attraction is the Mongolian cow in the game for the supporters of the build special field event creates&quot; the small high tide.At the break, the large screen in the audience to all search for targets,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a> finally lens frames to a row of fan body, happy smiling face instantly appear in the field on the big screen, let them feel the idol star with the same special courtesy, in addition,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1jLTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2011</a> the whole row fans have been provided by the rich prize, one of the lucky fans got a polaroid-type camera, the interactive link is first appeared in the NBA China &quot;. In addition, hoodwinks the cow is still in the museum made a fan paradise. A lot of fans in the big screen and polaroid-type stop before were big show happiness, some fans from the sidelines waiting for NBA face coloured drawing or pattern, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1tZW4tYy00XzUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2011 men</a>and fans immersed in a pitched battle the NBA's interactive game a long time unwilling to leave... As the NBA China's official market cooperation partners, hoodwinks the cow game in micro bo in &quot;the fans happy season&quot; as the theme opened two exclusive rob ticket channel, for the majority of fans provides close feeling NBA charm precious opportunity.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS13b21lbi1jLTRfNi5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2011 women</a>
<br /> Beijing station activities involved in number four days to reach 20000, some fans come all the way from hebei, shaanxi provinces to watch the game.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3fd9e0a10f14755c8d010c43384dbc1" url=""><![CDATA[Many teams pre-season nap green unlined upper garment army<br/><br/>With the league one of history's most dream team all the way the lakers losing streak, the heat, and thunder and tyrannical cannot avoid loss. Yesterday the celtics to a 75-107 loss to 76 people 32 points, but also in the United States basketball created quite a stir.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a> From NBA season with only half a month, but the former tyrannical seems to have still not ready.Just go a ray Allen, the celtics in the preseason performance as lost as soul. In Europe's two games are played very failure, defeat yesterday to 76 people, rivers simply in the second half substitute for all to take, wheel convey to 15 people. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a>In this summer, green army in order to fill the position of the ray Allen, signed John terry and courtney lee two shooting guard, the squad will be changed. But rivers still says it needs further investigation team, especially inside. New signing wade is expected to become the team's starting center, but jerry buss condition is also good, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi1jLTEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2012</a>rookie gaza ling more let him see the substitute of hope.And the celtics are similar and thunder and the SAN Antonio spurs, two squad change is not large, but in the face of the other team strength gradually to ascend, they must also internal tapping latent potentialities. The spurs in pre-season rotary as many as 18 people, GDP trio although all appear<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi1tZW5zLWMtMV8yLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 2012 mens</a>, but never more than 20 minutes, more time to substitute.The lakers, heat and the clippers is as far as possible, let them take charge of star of rest, to restore the old injury, catch up with the real season.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi13b21lbnMtYy0xXzMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2012 womens</a> The lakers playing squad is still unable to see Howard figure, even the coach mike brown also some embarrassed to say: &quot;I really don't know when he can return.&quot; Kobe Bryant have holidays by turns a field, 38 years old Nash also the rest, zijin corps in pre-season is don't want to hurt their any one superstar.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ac50daa97044b3f99f21f0c0f560b765" url=""><![CDATA[The lakers insider meet bullish hill recovery training is ex<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 19, according to the Los Angeles times news, the lakers reserve power forward Jordan - hill has returned to training, and if all goes well,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a> he could catch up with the new season's opener.In today's training, Jordan - hill and not involved in against the link, but in addition he still show the good state. &quot;In addition to the body fight training beyond, he finished each other a training course,&quot;
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDEyLWMtMS5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2012</a> coach mike brown said, &quot;for the team's tactical and specific movement route, he is also in constant familiar. Of course want to catch up with the progress, he still has a lot of things to do.&quot;&quot;He has the actual combat drills, and in tomorrow he will 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDEyLWMtMS5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2012 mens</a>still be without confrontation training, they (the team trainers) to assess his injury. Now they also did not give specific (recovery) schedule.&quot;&quot;According to requirements, he is currently training will also to run by warm-up. Although don't have to give priority to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDEyLWMtMS5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2012 womens</a>with 100% of the speed to run, but appropriate activities or necessary, and see his present recovery, I feel very surprised.&quot;Jordan - hill is in the pre-season game against golden state, was diagnosed with a back of intervertebral disc herniation.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDEyLWMtMS5odG1s" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 2012</a> From the rockets last season for the lakers turn after he was regarded as the team inside the most reliable bench. This summer, the lakers and hill signed a two year, $7.1 million contract.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="452a147b1fc35d825849a41e8b7a7efa" url=""><![CDATA[NBA rockets 109-102 the grizzlies LinShuHao state recovery<br/><br/>Star to a great extent determine the team performance is good or bad, in the gold content general NBA have obvious reflect. Yesterday, the rockets is at home with LinShuHao get 7 points,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">nike air max shoes</a> 5 rebounds, 12 assists performance, with a 109-102 the grizzlies, stopped straight flagging.This, the state of recovery LinShuHao saved the losing streak in the mire of the rockets. The game LinShuHao shooting is not outstanding, 9 throw in 3 to 7 points is the performance of the general, but it is by his 12 assists, and activate the rockets team offensive. 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDExLWMtNC5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2011</a>In LinShuHao lead bottom, the rockets changes the normal, from the first quarter will hold the lead, and in the third quarter and small time more than half a two-digit advantage. Although grizzlies run at the end of a wave of big 6-0 triumph score high tide, but still can't stop the rockets win.Having Martin, patterson, delfino, Douglas and parsons five players in double, 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDExLWMtNC5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2011 mens</a>these outside threats player's outstanding performance, let the rockets on the offensive end comprehensive flowering. 50% shooting from the field and 40.9% from 3-point, let the rockets in the face of the same five players in double grizzlies without falling when wind.&quot;Today we have put into the ball. This is not only I a person's credit, but everybody together diligently the results.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDExLWMtNC5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2011 womens</a>&quot; LinShuHao game appear very modest, &quot;in forcing opponents expanding defence after, I can easy selection will ball in inside or outside, it must want to thank you all outstanding feel.&quot;Teammates have won LinShuHao as the biggest hero. Parsons evaluation way: &quot;his organization is very good, the vision is, for all of us to create a lot of scoring opportunities.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDExLWMtNC5odG1s" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 2011</a>
<br /> To YuLinShu hao shooting data, parsons think: &quot;he's with strong deduoshaofen it doesn't matter, he to show they can use what kind of method on the offensive end of the leading this team, how to help the team to win. Tonight, he way to play the game to help us win over rivals.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="16c50d77b9bb215e43989c942ed69248" url=""><![CDATA[Delfino: rocket gradually establish a confident young help b<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 19 morning, according to American media, the rockets players delfino today accept media interviews, talk about the rockets in training camp and preseason performance of attack.When talking about the rockets play has made progress, delfino think,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a> through the pre-season and monopoly of the contest, the rockets are gradually find confidence. &quot;Yes, we have been talking about this, in the front of the pre-season games in the middle, we met a few teams have playoff team strength. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a>Everyone in the team competition with the process of gradually running in game, are also searching for your confidence.&quot; Delfino said, &quot;although in previous games against the spurs in our team was disrupted lead, but we soon through the training before corrected committed some mistakes. In the game against the grizzlies in the middle, our team will play very hard, play obviously than the previous games more organized,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1jLTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2011</a> more discipline. These are all proof of progress.&quot;When it comes to concrete against the grizzlies this game the rockets performance, delfino pointed out: &quot;we work hard to try to be sure good shoot, and strive to do to keep shooting,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1tZW4tYy00XzUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2011 men</a> I feel that we do, it is no longer like the previous game there shoot is quite hasty. In the third quarter after the match started, we have threw some gambling type shot, because in the second half after the match started, we started a bit slow, a little be opponent repression, but we work well done. I think, from the overall point of view, now the team played well, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS13b21lbi1jLTRfNi5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2011 women</a>all of us during the game pass well done, every play the players made a contribution in the defensive end, especially we played very good.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e58736311763416df6192922d5bf2f15" url=""><![CDATA[The rockets next week morris can return Martin courage to<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 19 morning, according to American media, the rockets play in the first five pre-season games after the game, and then they will enter into nearly a week of continuous training and adjust time,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a> but marcus - morris but because the injured thierry to dedicate themselves to the next training in. The rockets trainer Keith Jones sports, said morris sprain ankle better, but now is not comprehensive training.Keith Jones said, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a>marcus - the rockets in morris on Saturday before training should have no way to participate in the team for training, but in the rockets next week to play the next pre-season, morris should be able to return. &quot;In morris appearance, he really did good,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi1jLTEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2012</a> he in September training effect is very good, and made some progress.&quot; The rockets coach McHale said, &quot;he returned to the team in September when training very hard, the state keep fairly well. Morris recently the injury let me feel very sad, but I think he will be able to get a chance. A lot of players in our team construction process are all have a chance,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi1tZW5zLWMtMV8yLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 2012 mens</a> I hope he can well behind, and then play game, because he played really well.&quot;McHale said, behind Maurice upon his return also need a gradually due to injury recovery process. &quot;I never deliberately to limit which a player, but for example a player missed the whole camp training, or maybe there is injury and anxious to return, in his back, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMi13b21lbnMtYy0xXzMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2012 womens</a>
<br />he may not be in one hundred percent of the state. McHale said, &quot;morris return back after the situation should also is such, but he don't have too many irons in the fire, we want to bring him back to health again after a good play, the opportunity have. We don't want to see our players in training team behind three weeks time, or his state only 85% was anxious to play game.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="19cfb56534c49e745b12df336c7659e5" url=""><![CDATA[20 morning post: carter comment may when the sixth man Ant<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 20,, the NBA fighting in full swing, the following is today NBA each big news summary.
<br />Carter said may when the sixth manJohn terry's run away to the mavericks bench offensive firepower a problem,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">nike air max black</a> but veteran air carter immediately stand up statement said they are willing to make sacrifices for the team's sixth man, playing the role of John terry as before, carter said: &quot;I would like to the bench, to help the team to win. When the reserve team play,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05NS1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 95</a> they need to keep the team moving forward, I would like to a victory for his team to do anything.&quot; Carter skill omnipotent, he can not only long shot three points, also can break through the basket score, and carter averaging seven rebounds
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05NS1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 95 mens</a>. The mavericks coach Carlisle praise carter is a first team player, apparently for carter's comment very satisfied.Anthony refused to the benchThe yankees' rodriguez recent poor state, from the star players into the team's backup, and kobe Bryant before make a phone call to encourage rodriguez cheer up. The knicks small forward Anthony also expressed as rodriguez feel sad
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05NS1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 95 womens</a>, at the same time declare yourself absolutely do not want to be a substitute, Anthony said: &quot;I can't imagine it all, I can't accept.&quot;Jordan - hill hard won the contract extensionLake National People's Congress striker, rocket old will Jordan - hill has begun to return to training, but until now he still didn't get the team's contract extension.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05NS1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 95</a> In the previous against warriors pre-season, hill contributed 10 points, he is the lakers bench powerful supplement. The lakers coach brown said: &quot;in no contract extension security situation, hill's performance is very good. The team will continue to consider his performance, and then decided to give him a contract. But at least now, hill also can't get the contract.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5416d7da749a1b6a7f44eb085360a194" url=""><![CDATA[The wizards executive woll six candidate item facial butt<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 20, 2012, according to American media, wizards carried out including the team core John - woll, six rookie in the 2013-14 season's contract option, will they stay in the team. The six rookie including 4 a level 2010 and 2 2011 level.Four 2010 rookie theo led to, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">nike air max womens</a>he is this year of the no. 1 pick, and first 17, Kevin - sierra Finn, the first round of the 23 trevor booker, and the first round number 27 of Jordan crawford. Two level 2011 rookie were first 6 show Jane - dimensional plug the first round and no. 18 rookie Chris singer's meal.The 2013-14 season is four level 2010 rookie of the fourth year, 2 level 2011 rookie of the third year.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90</a>&quot;In the past several seasons, we will these talent outstanding young people brought to the team, and development have become the core of the team line-up, we are very happy in their later period of time also to the wizards effect.&quot; The team general manager glen feld said, &quot;these people add those who experienced veterans, give us a very solid foundation,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 mens</a> we can compete with other teams, in the future on the road will also continue to successful go on.&quot;In accordance with the provisions of the alliance, the local time is on October 31st, rookie contract option execution date, now distance this time left about 12 days or so, the wizards have made the decision to advance.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 womens</a>In 2005 to labor clause revised later, first rookie standard contract from the original 3 + 1 into 2 + 1 + 1, which means it is in the first three years of security, the last years is the team option, and now has become the first two years of security, two years after each have a team option. The so-called the team option, is the team have the right to extend or terminate the contract. Now the wizards execution is walter your four people behind of the 1, dimensional plug interest etc. 2 people in front that 1.Are rebuilding of wizards is veteran and new combination of team, 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 90</a>theo is their core. 2011-12 season woll 66 regular-season games all starting, averaging 16.3 points and 4.5 rebounds and 8.0 assists, the top is gradually become mature. College have facial button James Jordan crawford is averaging 14.7 points and 3.0 assists, and assists in the world after the second team, scoring if do not calculate be traded go Nick Yang, is also the team the second.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2382857d8346b5de21b04abf25ddd4a5" url=""><![CDATA[Si handsome: James can compete with the best defensive play<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 20, morning, from the Miami guard the sun newspaper news say, lebron James came into the league for 9 years, he has won numerous honors, including best rookie, the MVP of the season award, the all-star game MVP and finals MVP, the season first team, the season's first defensive rotations... It must be admitted that, 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a>James very comprehensive, but there is one award chim emperor has never sold one, that's defensive player of the year.Over the past four years, and only 2 players won the defensive player of the year, and it is center, are &quot;warcraft&quot; Dwight - Howard, and last season's tyson chandler. James in the award in the second highest ranking selection, the last season with 112 points in the fourth row.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a> The local time Friday when accepting a reporter to interview, Miami coach spor Stella said he hoped the James can receive this year defensive player of the year. &quot;If lebron (James) to compete defensive player of the year, in my opinion this is a good thing,&quot; handsome, said, &quot;I think last season he in the defensive end effect and influence not loss to the alliance any one person.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTUtYy0xNi5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 95</a>&quot;In fact from China after returned to Miami, Miami in many players still in upside down time. As James, local time Thursday in Miami victory over Detroit preseason, James performance is very general. &quot;Still had not fully recovered,&quot; James said. &quot;but this is only a matter of time, we need a process.&quot; On the other hand, Miami there are still some injury problems,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTUtbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LTk1LW1lbnMtYy0xNl8xNy5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 95 mens</a> such as check moss, Joel - Anthony and HaSiLeM etc because of injury did not participate in the with the pistons in pre-season, and according to reveal, handsome, HaSiLeM is expected to wait for the player to local time on Saturday Miami and the spurs on the pre-season tour return.Wade in and pistons on the pre-season tour performance good, 23 minutes against attack down 21 points and five assists. This wade said: &quot;I now is still in the adjust my rhythm,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTUtbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LTk1LXdvbWVucy1jLTE2XzE4Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 95 womens</a>
<br /> I found myself there are still some aspects need to strengthen, but I with his present overall performance will be satisfied.&quot; The handsome, said: &quot;I'm very happy wade the present situation, he returned to the old speed and agility. Wade had knee surgery this summer, before Miami's dwyane wade is likely only in this year's pre-season dozen 1 game; Now China is the 2 games, wade has three consecutive games debut, and performance becomes more and more outstanding, the Miami absolutely is a good news.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="722117ac065e80071a966d504515b6a4" url=""><![CDATA[Rider two will contract option Owen Thompson left-behind<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 20, early morning, Cleveland cavaliers general manager Chris - grant in the local time Friday team's facility in formally announced that the cavaliers have carried out the defender Carey - Michael Owen and striker Tristan da cunha Thompson contract for the third year in options<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a>.Young Michael Owen and Thompson is known as the cavaliers future, &quot;Carey (Owen) and Tristan (Thompson) as a player and as a man, is the team to build team representatives of thoughts. They focus, diligence, have a talent, we are looking forward to them as a part of the cavaliers,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a>
<br /> in Cleveland, continuous improvement and eventually succeed.&quot; The 20-year-old Owen is 2011 NBA first overall pick, and 21 year old Thompson was in 2011 the first round of the sequence 4 rookie.As a rookie of the year, Owen in the 2011-04 season on behalf of the cavaliers played a total of 51 of the regular season and all starting,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtYy0yMC5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 90</a> averaging 30.5 minutes for 18.5 points 3.7 rebounds and 5.4 assists 1.1 steals enter an item in an account, field goal percentage is 46.9%. The offseason, Michael Owen in training the right hand fracture, but now has healed. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LTkwLW1lbi1jLTIwXzIxLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 men</a>Since lebron James left Cleveland and join Miami, Owen became the cavaliers new leader.Thompson regular season on behalf of the cavaliers played a total of 60 games, among them 25 starts, averaging 23.7 minutes for contribution 8.2 points and 6.5 rebounds 1.0 blocked shots, he was named in the second team last season rookie.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LTkwLXdvbWVuLWMtMjBfMjIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 90 women</a> The cavaliers believe that the upcoming 12-13 season, Mr Thompson will be playing more points, and his rebounds number is likely to reach double digits. It is not difficult to see that the cavaliers to Michael Owen and Thompson has high expectations.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="687c576f58de4e3111a9113b155a4543" url=""><![CDATA[Warriors two core exit pre-season small Treasury bench wi<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 22, 2012, the NBA regular season continue. As in previous games and the Portland trail blazers an ankle injury, the warriors defender<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">nike air max black</a> Steven garage will and another injured didier general Andrew bogut absent together the next pre-season. But doctors say two personal status is good.Local time Saturday garage accepted fokker the doctor's examination, the result is don't need to worry too much about. Fokker<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05NS1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 95</a> doctor is garage and Andrew bogut ankle surgery the surgeon, both in the April this year the surgery.Warriors coach mark - Jackson also said he does not too worried about the Treasury ankle, but in the final two preseason games, the database will not appear in court. &quot;Now let him play is not have what meaning, let him play no harvest, I wouldn't worry too much, but we for this
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05NS1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 95 mens</a> things to change some clever.&quot; Jackson said.Another has been injured players Andrew bogut also accepted fokker doctor's inspection, the team general manager myers said, fokker &quot;for yourself to see like&quot;, and gives the conclusion is the big man is formulated 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05NS1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 95 womens</a>in accordance with the schedule after rehabilitation.Fokker has not ruled out Andrew bogut local time in October 31 warriors back in the opener of the opportunity, but myers said no one dare to guarantee Andrew bogut will be able to play.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05NS1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 95</a>
<br />Previously fokker given rehabilitation schedule is 6 months, accurate calculation, it is in this year's October 27,.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b4b4c26559cdadd84cba2c726272ef09" url=""><![CDATA[Allen's defected green army reason unearned respect nature<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 22, ray Allen gave up the celtics on higher contract, choose at lower wages and in the Miami lineup plays the same role, about Allen defected green unlined upper garment of the cause of the army opinions vary, of which the most way of god and the contradiction between the rajon rondo. 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">nike air max womens</a>But in accept the Miami herald &quot;interview, Allen revealed himself to leave the celtics reason, because in Boston he didn't get the team to a striker when the some respect.
<br />If Allen have no choice to join the heat of words, so his shirt most likely in after they retired hanging in over the arena, and &quot;big bird&quot; Byrd, Russell and library west the legend of the shirt hanging together together. 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90</a>Allen help green unlined upper garment army in 22 years won the first championship, but also it is in wear green shirt, he broke the NBA history's 3-point streak. However Allen eventually chose to give up these should have some glory, is also a substitute role,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 mens</a> but this name old striker finally chose to join green army base salary of old rivals the heat, and have no choice to stay in Boston.
<br />It is also for Allen to Celtic not loyalty, he was Boston fans' abuse, because in the United States, loyalty is the pronoun of Boston, as money is refers to New York, Chicago is political symbol, rocky mountain represents the Denver, 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 womens</a>and Hollywood is Los Angeles general portraiture. Allen natural understand green unlined upper garment armed soldiers loyal trust, but he chose to leave - even if he can there and get higher contract, get few players can enjoy jersey retirement honor.
<br />However, when the celtics requirements Allen to Bradley substitute, to help the team rebuilding, Allan refused the team's this location. He finally chose to Miami, although also is playing the role of the bench, but in Miami he won the higher respect. &quot;In Boston, they told me to let me make the bench, to reduce the appearance of time.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 90</a> I said:&quot; in the past two years in the field you see me as a trap (refers to is not score point) to use, then you and how to use me? '&quot; Allen said, &quot;is it in all the tactics of you all movement the ball, and my task is to pass the ball to other place, never for I create opportunities to score, and I are in the game most of the time a person stood alone in the corner of.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f8a8230250435de2b77872b46e70bcc4" url=""><![CDATA[The rockets coach to young players talk: they often train<br/><br/>According to &quot;Houston chronicle&quot; news, for young for the rockets, training is also full of difficulties, boss McHale feel quite a headache. Thursday ZhanBa grizzlies,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a> the rockets have 6 days of training time, until next week to four rockets against the sixth preseason opponent - the hornets. Today's training, the rockets offense and main practice with a zone defense. But MaiShuai feel progress is slow, the players often would want a long time to master, and will be in a very short period of time back to origin.MaiShuai disappointedly said:
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a> &quot;in our study, to focus more some. We are instill more tactics, like the players to grasp as soon as possible. But young players don't know that we need to learn so many things that we can't spend three hours explain a problem. For these young players, you must be patient. Sometimes, they thought often interrupt. You just finished things<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTUtYy0xNi5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 95</a>, don't have much time, they all forgotten, today this kind of thing happened many times.&quot;
<br />For today's training and after teaching &quot;, MaiShuai are discontented, after the game he put the young players together, the criticism education, &quot;we must treasure the training time, and constantly progress. I've never seen any NBA teams, especially young team can in training under the condition of bad play the perfect game.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTUtbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LTk1LW1lbnMtYy0xNl8xNy5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 95 mens</a> Normally, you in training do perfect, in the game will also encounter setbacks. If we in training appear worse, I can't imagine what it's like to after game.&quot;Rookie terence - Jones in training step on to livingston and injury, and then out of the training, since October 7 days after the beginning of training camp, he has been suffered an ankle injury problems.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTUtbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LTk1LXdvbWVucy1jLTE2XzE4Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 95 womens</a> Patterson today something off, jia Juan - Johnson and Royce - white in training to play power forward. Marcus - morris has returned to the personal training, he is on October 11 sprained his left ankle, the next three days he is expected to recover with the team.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="662bddfe123d9552caa69ad5caf2290f" url=""><![CDATA[Charles barkley see failure bynum prospect small sharks s<br/><br/>Pre-season has come to an end, the new season is imminent, but Andrew bynum a move into the 76 ers, still did not give his first show in Philadelphia.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a> For &amp;quot;small shark&amp;quot; future, Charles barkley said do not look good.Bynum still beset by a knee injury, as for injury what, who can't also a decision. &amp;quot;Bynum came to 76 people, let me very happy,&amp;quot; Charles barkley said, &amp;quot;76 people are want him as never before has done things, 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a>this is a difficult challenge. This takes bynum in each night become the team's core character. He must stay healthy, then the game play dominant, attract lane-packing, for the perimeter players create vacancy opportunity, but as you know, he is with him.&amp;quot;Bynum in the lakers got two championship rings, 24 years old he was last season best team the second team, or all star western starting center
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtYy0yMC5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 90</a>, averaging 18.7 points and 11.8 rebounds 1.93 shots. But in Charles barkley view, the &amp;quot;small shark&amp;quot; excellent play, depends entirely on kobe Bryant and pau gasol, and even pau gasol in the game tough degree, also more than Andrew bynum.&amp;quot;Joe Johnson in the sun is a great player, but in the eagle he hard to keep the same level, small amare stoudemire can also feel the same situation in New York
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LTkwLW1lbi1jLTIwXzIxLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 men</a>, left a players, they will be different.&amp;quot; Charles barkley said.Before this, bynum has never become a team on the pitch and the leader, he is in kobe Bryant and pau gasol on the wings of a dove in the battle. This let bynum although 24 years old, but the mind is still not mature, often have some childish behavior, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtbmlrZS1haXItbWF4LTkwLXdvbWVuLWMtMjBfMjIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 90 women</a>such as the playoffs last season to the mavericks he and the extremely dangerous foul, and unaccountable three points selection. In April this year, the lakers general manager mitch kupchak admitted, bynum is a &amp;quot;sometimes is very good, sometimes very bad&amp;quot; players, the problem is - you do not know which one day he is good or bad.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="453f9a9ed7828f3e2e1bcc2da46a2244" url=""><![CDATA[The rockets rookie praise book hao to be modest lamb effor<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 23, morning, the United States media published an article in the rockets rookie player jeremie lamb write new diary, lamb in the diary of the talked about in Houston's life and the rockets some of the relevant situation. The following is the lamb latest diary part of translation<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">nike air max womens</a>:This is the first time I've been really one personal life, it was really cool! For me, have their own space is a good thing. So far, I am very like Houston, this is a makes me feel excited city. In 2011 I was with the Connecticut school team here too NCAA national championship, so I to the city has a very good memory. I to the present travel will use satellite locator<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90</a>, but in general I have been able to find the place where I want to go to.My parents and sister also come along with me together from Atlanta moved to Houston to live, but they are not and I live in the same street, they live from me about 5 minutes by car. My sister this year, 17 years old, so she was in Houston for a new middle school to continue to study,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 mens</a> she came to Houston for life and study is also felt very excited. Let my family live from me so nearly place is a wonderful thing. In the end of the training, when I feel tired, I'll call my mother, let them for me a delicious meal. I myself will cook rice, I like his breakfast do some Fried eggs, Fried steak and so on. I usually at half past seven every morning or get up at 8 o 'clock,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 90 womens</a> and then make breakfast, eat breakfast at half past eight after go out to go to the team's training. However, in addition to breakfast, but other food I wouldn't do. During the period of university, I have your own hamburger, behind I'll try.We talk about the rockets! Our team is a great team, we players get along very well, I really like the rockets now coaching staff.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC1jLTIwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 90</a>
<br /> We had a few field difficult pre-season games, but we have been working to training, to allow the team to become more outstanding. As for my personal performance of in the preseason, I feel is ok. There are some things that I can do better, but this is a learning process. I now are trying to training their control of the ball, as well as the ball of his ability, I still trying to improve their rebound congested ability.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="23a656c3f4d84e69151eb804b7cc0b4d" url=""><![CDATA[Arenas close to joining CBA zero, agent or with yi teammate<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 23 morning, according to the English website yahoo sports reporter mark - J - spears exposure material, a sources say, NBA free agent, said &quot;zero, agent&quot; gilbert arenas is approaching and guangdong hongyuan vaulted sign a one-year contract<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLWMtMzIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 1</a>. If arenas will eventually be able to sign with the guangdong hongyuan vaulted smoothly, he will be in the new season and yi jianlian in the CBA league together. And in marbury and t-mac later, and there will be former NBA all-star companion CBA league, this will further increase the CBA league people, help CBA develop sports market.Arenas a former all-star player, he was in the league for 11 years,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLWMtMzIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">cheap nike air max 1</a> arenas career altogether has played in 552 regular-season games, averaging 35.1 minutes against contribute 20.7 points and 5.3 assists 3.9 rebounds 1.6 steals. - 06 season is arenas, the most outstanding performance of 1 year, he was on behalf of the wizards has played in 80 regular-season games, and averaged 29.3 points and 6.0 assists 3.5 rebounds 2.0 steals. In the summer of 2008
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDEwLWMtNy5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2010</a>, arenas and wizards renewed a six-year contract worth $111 million. But after that, because of injury, arenas frequent absence game; And in the end of 2009, arenas in the door &quot;the event. 10 to 11 in the middle of the season, the Washington wizards will arenas traded to the Orlando magic.Last season was finished, just to be traded to the Orlando magic in the near arenas team he had layoffs, 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0yMDA5LWMtMTAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2009</a>although at that time arenas contract with 3 year, $63 million and be cut soon, arenas and joined the Memphis grizzlies, however, this is just a temporary employment. After the end of last season, arenas is out of work. In grizzly bear period, arenas played in only 16 games, averaging only played 12 minutes, averaging is only poor 4.4 points 1 assists,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDExc2hvZXNvbnNhbGUuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLWdyaWZmZXktbWF4LTEtYy0zNC5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air griffey max 1</a> is in the lowest career.As early as the end of September has been sources said arenas the former NBA all-star player is seriously considering China played the new season. This offseason, arenas most of the time and its trust Joe o bond training with gaza, occasionally appear in the lakers or the clippers play the game in the gym, and state looks good.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3d948c6613aa1bbd00057fb577ae1a66" url=""><![CDATA[The rockets training camp packed low efficiency MaiShuai<br/><br/>According to &quot;Houston chronicle&quot; news, in yesterday, McHale is dissatisfied with the players training attitude, with the rockets rotation of the basic sure, layoffs have also been put on the agenda, and those who take a non-guaranteed contract players are likely to be cut. Because the rockets training camp &quot;crowded&quot; (a total of 17 players), training efficiency is low, today carried on marathon training after that<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAwOS1jLTEwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 2009</a>, MaiShuai still were not satisfied effect, think the players thought is not centralized, training intensity is not enough.MaiShuai says, it will take some time reiterated some things, and give young people the chance to as much as possible. He thinks that, when lean squad after, this situation will change, on the other hand, it is preparing for the future, those players can be decentralized to the membership of league NBDL team viper team continues to exercise.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAwOS1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAwOS1tZW4tYy0xMF8xMS5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2009 men</a> He said: &quot;when we make layoffs later, things will get better. Some players and viper team signup. Our training number decreases after, training efficiency will be improved, strength also will follow up. Now, we have to cost a lot of time to repeat.&quot;MaiShuai revealed, the rockets will be the lower 2 to 3 players in the league NBDL play, continue to exercise and investigation. Cloth LuKeMan, jia Juan - Johnson, Forbes, horse check, Greg Smith five players get laid off most probability. For training today overall effect, MaiShuai also ineffable satisfaction, &quot;I dare not say training today how much better than yesterday.&quot; Yesterday, MaiShuai in training after criticism players don't concern, easy to desert.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAwOS1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAwOS13b21lbi1jLTEwXzEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nike air max 2009 women</a>
<br />Rookie terence - Jones return to training today, before an ankle injury has plagued him. He said: &quot;I can control this situation. I feel good, I want to play. I'll continue to treat ankle, although it is not 100%, but also have no serious, I can insist on down.&quot; Jones, hope he don't be affected by an ankle injury, from on the pre-season, Jones is very close to the backup power forward position, if the main power forward patterson top to center position, Jones may be able to get more playing time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="788d019f1190db440df9a5b9a09c813c" url=""><![CDATA[Parker's has not yet returned to normal state manu eager to<br/><br/>Beijing time on October 22,, according to the SAN Antonio media reports, Tony - parker in SAN Antonio against magic game play 31 minutes 42 seconds. &quot;The French sports car&quot; the play so long time, because he felt his own state not enough to play regular season, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max</a>so need more play pre-season to get back into the rhythm.This summer, parker first eye injuries, then with the French national team in the Olympic Games, lead to the already 30 years old veteran competitive state can't and than in former years. Before playing magic, parker has only taken part in a pre-season friendly. This field, parker to consult with head coach gregg popovich,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1jLTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2011</a> hope I can play for a period of time.Popovich answer, but parker's condition is not good, rely on to become famous speed and breakthrough is always slow a beat -- 13 only three, scored 10 points. &quot;I think I'm still looking for state and rhythm,&quot; parker said, &quot;my shot is always a little short. Of course, this is only my second pre-season games, so this is normal
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1tZW4tYy00XzUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nike air max 2011 men</a>.&quot;The problem is, the distance from the regular season opener, parker only 10 days the period of adjustment. He is very worried, the fourth quarter request once played, but be gregg popovich press the on the bench.&quot;His shot was struggle, but he want to play game,&quot; popovich said,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS13b21lbi1jLTRfNi5odG1s" target="_blank">nike air max 2011 women</a> &quot;I gave him a lot of time. He wants to return to the regular season as soon as possible to fit the requirements&quot;.Not only parker, ginobili also hope that more than a dozen recently, in order to prepare for the regular season. At present, the GDP trio, in pre-season games are played most, unexpectedly is 36 years old Tim Duncan, but is averaging also didn't to 20 minutes.&quot;We before training really long, very hard,&quot; ginobili said,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5haXJtYXgyMDEyc2hvZXMyeW91LmNvbS8_" target="_blank">nike air max cheap</a> &quot;but you guys need some 30 minutes or more game, to test their state. I don't know bobo how think, anyway, I think I need a field and the regular season similar games.&quot; Manu's still in the offseason, he follow Argentina a club a practice on Wednesday, their physical no problem.But popovich obviously don't want to let his three core in pre-season overexert - after all, soon have 82 games waiting for them.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f71c524da7c71146f7e7f9caf561b25" url=""><![CDATA[Individually only two points in 8 1 when six Ums PageSever f<br/><br/>Beijing Time 25th 13th October 2012 NBA season continue playing Houston Rockets 97-90 victory over the Hornets in New Orleans, performance LinShuHao some disappointed Uschung, 31 minutes just eight shots get two points 5 rebounds, 2 assists and steals, and BL-cke for up to 6 times .<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Cheap Kobe 7</a> Error Rockets before leaving five preseason games, 3 wins 2 negative LinShuHao attended the four meetings, the first three games and averaged only 5.3 points and 4.7 assists, and the fourth field although scored 7 points Rebounds 5, 12 assists and steals. But four preseason games outside causes without field by double or marked many questions. ESPN even reported missile wettbewerbsf not on considerations LinShuHao compatibility available as Boss Alexander, when Yao Ming, earn a great interest in it, Conna Is the Chinese star in the entire area of effect. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLTd2aWktYy0xOC5odG1s" target="_blank">Kobe VII</a>Only a small number of fields pre-season games and a lot of value, but LinShuHao feel some pressure. Today, against the New Orleans Hornets, LinShuHao is as exciting. The opponent is LinShuHao Thurs Schwartz Coase, last season, he finished his outstanding performance knicks a wave of seven victories from a plaster as a defense against LinShuHao created many problems mentioned. Two people meet again, Schwartz Coase SOON open T its doors after the breakthrough of the middle LinShuHao, draping Game 2 + 1 LinShuHao then the end will prevent some defensive big s,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLTd2aWktYy0xOC5odG1s" target="_blank">Kobe 7 Cheetah</a> intelligent protection step Zhuangyuanlou injury caused Anthony Davis go on n Next day seven points 20 seconds to a face behind Schwartz Coase started burst the balloon, against the attack Martin's teammate scoring easy dunks. LinShuHao help his teammate and defense took a good condition, the first quarter gave the Hornets center robin - a ceiling lopez record.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLTd2aWktYy0xOC5odG1s" target="_blank">Kobe 7 USA</a> But in scoring pers Nlichen LinShuHao not yet found a way in the first quarter three shots, a short break after a steal breakthrough for hand lay-up and a three-point attempt and Longshot the iron hot is. LinShuHao and quick breakthrough screen role and after the break are subject to the key defense opponents, often break the line of defense, after the car had two or three people to help you. The support of the first half of H Until LinShuHao points 1 and 10 seconds in a fast break break layups left scored two straight points Halfcourt five one and two. In the second H Half find scoring LinShuHao individual, but still defensive teammates after winning witness two other foreign aid Martin made 3-pointers, the Rockets in the third quarter set with a wave of flood pre two figures, it was his best performance section. But small game, like LinShuHao points,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLTd2aWktYy0xOC5odG1s" target="_blank">Kobe 7 Big Bang</a> but the error still results from their opponents the ball close, fortunately, after the green guide Eren missiles Lich is worried signals victory. LinShuHao 31 minutes only 8 shots, get two points 5 rebounds, 2 assists and steals, and BL-cke for up to 6 times error. Although the defense also pursue Schwartz Coase eight Ums Appear courts, but opponents have hit 13 points, 11 assists excellence LinShuHao pers Nlichen attack large e obstacles which makes also have committed many errors. Few days ago in the U.S. journal SBN time when collecting the search LinShuHao season, LinShuHao last season really everybody, embroidered with his ball, his shocked layup difficult, and accelerate the breakthrough, etc., but these opponents have extensive research, it may also choose to z, it needs new ways to cloud ltigen develop. Must &quot;Preseason LinShuHao five below his personal gek Nlichen attack really Fights, it means no longer existing conventional attack. Now looking LinShuHao and rockets Ma Took LinShuHao must adapt myself to find new methods of attack and missile new environment to build their offensive tactics, so they appear to prevent the leaders of the team players Ao t 1, the only two points embarrassing.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8f518739e67877ba9a6bd419c2f6c584" url=""><![CDATA[Performance LinShuHao dark to hide a window, he and a partne<br/><br/>Beijing time on 25 October 2012-13 NBA season continues, leaving Houston Rockets 97-90 victory over the Hornets in New Orleans, LinShuHao poor performance, only eight of 1 Win 2 points and five assists and six rebounds error behavior but the last two games and the form that Martin backcourt combination found tacit consent. Fox Sports on missiles and performance LinShuHao talk new season,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2UtbGVicm9uLTlpeC1jLTEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Cheap Lebron 9 Shoes</a> especially when it comes to the point that it LinShuHao three years in the face of the third type of offense for this growth is very young player unfavorable. This means that weight LinShuHao to the new system and new teammates Hnen, he and his teammates as soon as m Resembled a chemical reaction takes LinShuHao rockets and new season may have outstanding performance of the key. LinShuHao in the first three preseason games, the first three games against the Thunder, New Orleans and San Antonio to participate, an average of only 5.3 points and 4.7 <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2UtbGVicm9uLTlpeC1jLTEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Cheap Lebron 9 Shoes Low</a>assists LinShuHao power in the new system if pers Nliche performance or be bottom drawer is far from ideal, but the fourth game of 7 points 5 rebounds, 12 assists and steals, so that everyone can see some positive factors. Especially Kevin Martin backcourt combination LinShuHao and allm disappear Cheerful Be sparks, Martin apart from three points 5 4 saves the game with 22 points. Many experts believe LinShuHao and Kevin Martin will be very good strike partner will be a powerful breakthrough left LinShuHao Martin turned much space as the Knicks last season, novak, fildes, Martin properties LinShuHao k Can benefit.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2UtbGVicm9uLTlpeC1jLTEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Lebron 9 Shoes Cheap</a> Evidence Hornets passing lanes LinShuHao study in the first half LinShuHao Martin and mounting stands between rival defense. LinShuHao h hangs only by the F Ability of a person steals rail S with Schnellverschlu Martin breakthroughs. But in the second H half, and LinShuHao Martin backcourt combination allm cheerful on the enemy defenses SOON adapted T begin the third quarter LinShuHao win defensively against the pass au s after Martin hit three points: The third quarter with 5 minutes Lin Hao help book about the new Martin, met longshot. Rockets backcourt combination allm Find cheerful feel,
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Cheap Lebron 9</a> help each other k Nnte disappear in fact thrive, and also met a barrage of attacks by three rockets to win 12 points hornets. But in the fourth quarter, a group LinShuHao substitute for clear amplification Ndnis tacit team is not enough, and it is several times flying opponents mistakes fortunately after a big lead en, and then to win the missile. LinShuHao the game is not perfect, just two points in 8 1 3 rebounds, five assists and six times the mistakes if pers Nlich or state is run with his teammates inadequate. But to see both games between him and Kevin Martin has a lot of tacit Gain Ndnis, more time and meet the intruder, believe that two people attacking a good partner.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4211fe7dea99e2131d844deba360a37d" url=""><![CDATA[For 18 + 7 expansion haddon 16 points home win thunder maver<br/><br/>Yesterday to pr Sentieren heart tee K His body yi, Qinhuangdao finished checking the ABC balanced fitness. Although yi did Every action Qualification, but the rules ben CONFIRMS be, each player must have scores, then yi are no exception. In Test reverse layup, yi ran two sets of 63 seconds, achieved the following results defenders standard. Yi resistance test first, then came to the field test for the differences found in three test groups china Arab League first group threw 26 missed 17, unable to meet the standards,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Cheap Kobe 7</a> by the second group to the line to go for illegal fishing, a lockable border row its 23rd 20, only 100 seconds convicted reverse layup for testing yi. is not difficult, it was news that defender yi speed near default. Day and the two arms of the study yi, the first group of 61 seconds 12 missed reaching the second group of 58 h speed 62 seconds Ago than 63 seconds defenders Qualifizierungsma Exception. &amp;quot;Yi said frankly:&amp;quot; After the test Never experienced heart tee body K is an innovation, the target heart tee K body probably is dr any lengths in order to st strengths training, but also her own needs met.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Cheap Lebron 9</a> at heart tee K body at the same time is not only through and through, which is most of the game, to gather useful items and details think for a lot of young players and a very good memory, usually pay more attention to training. &amp;quot;United test end o Qinhuangdao allowed to return to Beijing, then it will stay in Beijing for training, Beijing time on October 25 News, NBA, playing at home against Mavericks, Kevin Durant and Russell -.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1oeXBlcmZ1c2UtMjAxMS1qZXJlbXktbGluLXBlLXNob2VzLXAtMTE3Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Cheap Jeremy Lin Shoes</a> Inaccurate forecasts are speckled form and the Thunder to a 88-76 victory over the Dallas Mavericks four certain score (sniper in the first) .. 16-23, 24 30, 18:12:17 Thunder: Durant red line of 18 points, seven rebounds and five assists , 15 points and seven rebounds barca, Haddon 16 points and five assists, Forecasts brooke contribution of 8 points, nine rebounds and six assists calf 21 points. Claude and nine rebounds, 11 points and five rebounds shaun. After starting the to help competition, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1oeXBlcmZ1c2UtMjAxMS1jLTE1Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Cheap Nike Hyperfuse 2011</a>and Claude KeLiSen start, the Mavericks 8-4 to play the game right away w while r Chen a 2 beautiful ne return + 1, then the predictions and Brooke organized air relay, thunder with 21-14 victory. Although the end of the snipers have power, but at the end of the first quarter 16-23 behind. period Haddon took the team tackled the norm, and even a man seven points and help score Rewriting in Thunder 32-19. Wright led to a counter-attack, this time by 8-4 small flood wave start. Subsequently end, the two sides launched fierce battle to grab the barca au ergew hnlicher eye that tron help ons Simple ramp down 11 points, thunder halftime lead 53 -. second H half<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1oeXBlcmZ1c2UtMjAxMS1jLTE1Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Rajon Rondo Shoes</a>, the Mavericks are 11-5 in a wave of small flood, reduced the difference in points to 7 points, but l is a flash in the pan, on this day last seven minutes nger only three goals, the thunder again gr he the difference in points scored three ZhanBa, Thunder ahead 71-57. trifles, a Claude 6 points, helping the Mavericks to the score corresponding to 63-73.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1oeXBlcmZ1c2UtMjAxMS1qZXJlbXktbGluLXBlLXNob2VzLXAtMTE3Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Jeremy Lin Shoes</a> thunder sw show surface, inside and au s reprisals points seven. Between the two teams more intense when the sniper would point difference is a single digit, and Haddon Meinuo 3 State aid constant thunder. W While Dallas and then the performance but useless And finally to the Thunder 88-76 victory over the Dallas Mavericks.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="487425bdb384e8040e32e112c024ce73" url=""><![CDATA[Martin LinShuHao second encounter error Waldquelle single f<br/><br/>Beijing time on 25 October, the famous American sports media sports fox Perspective the Houston Rockets, when mentioned the new season Hnt, performance LinShuHao will have with him the rocket, think Fabolous has to show his magic, direct rocket experienced circulating lzungen 12-13 in the season a little bit. YuLinShu hao from the rocket, Fox Sports, &amp;quot;as l ridiculously it was said that the rockets in the hunt for a loss Dwight Howard will get a consolation prize.&amp;quot; LinShuHao fact the last season, the Knicks created the famous &amp;quot;Lin crazy<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL2RlcnJpY2stcm9zZS1zaG9lcy1jLTUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Derrick Rose Shoes</a>, Tales But this M Tales end of each M, Lin Hao book in April due to an injury. LinShuHao now receive $ 25 million in torches large s contract is also on the back of a huge burden, he must show them magic help rockets change squad make a difference. fox sports &amp;quot;think LinShuHao arrival rocket probably benefit most players Kevin Martin. Martin disappointed Uschenden season, he was an average of 17.1 points in the last seven seasons there, but LinShuHao revolution Re match will benefit very t Dliche Martin, many open shots as last season, novak fildes obtained at heart tee LinShuHao the beginning . LinShuHao individual needs large one It is to overcome its debt problems last season, it is 3.6-fold error in each game,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL2RlcnJpY2stcm9zZS1zaG9lcy1jLTUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">AdiZero Crazy Light</a> which means that the data is high and the fifth division of the error concerning Gt only 1.7 assists, which need to be improved. Second confronted LinShuHao large e difficulties can k in the last three years with three different offenses that hinder progress since the Golden State Warriors for the Knicks, Rockets, dam game Ftigen team was ge changed. However LinShuHao is the first time the key market leaders hosted a full season, it can help k Can fabolous 24 years after his potential. Reported according to the official website of the NBA yesterday, the NBA vice president Stu Jackson, NBA All-Star Game was decided, the voting rules to change, Decided the NBA to cancel the central position of the voice, to three attacking such a decision means that the its new season NBA All-Star Voting attacking three defensive players + 2 &amp;quot;combination. These change is very reasonable.&amp;quot; Jackson explained Rte, why go the NBA All-Star voting rules Change, we found that the central star is allowed only seems to have become the starting point and the center of this approach exceeded a little. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL2RlcnJpY2stcm9zZS1zaG9lcy1jLTUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Derrick Rose Shoes 2012</a>&amp;quot;K According to a statement from Jackson to the rule Change when a few years, some two very good center Can the fans decide, set all, and they can also be in the last All-Star his start&amp;quot; in the rules of origin is unm possible. &amp;quot;After <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Cheap Lebron 9</a>Jackson, showed that this decision is the union held the last meeting of the month to compete, Changes the Ver, We feel a long time ago can k, But let's not make a decision without Change real, so I went to the tournament this idea advanced by the discussion they also think that such a ... change is significant has fans vote if. the choice of the most flexible and the balance of the contest &amp;quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f05789540f989f54c2684cdc87791c4" url=""><![CDATA[For the season 9 new medium LinShuHao jin beauty Sch The age<br/><br/>Beijing time on 25 October after ABC reported in that Forest crazy &quot;surge to ten months later Ter blow on this day, bringing rockets LinShuHao a new departure and arrival times are also soup ONED in his The History of the&quot; New Age &quot;. 
<br />Now I can not wait, LinShuHao said, &quot;because in the season, there were many speculations and sight, and then I do a lot of things to au outside. Now can the basketball court I'm very excited back, began to realize that I am in need of the stain of basketball. &quot;Although most rockets LinShuHao cut in December,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Cheap Kobe 7</a> but this year the season is very positive, and eventually around 25 million dollars for three years and sign the name of Asian leaders. &quot; If the rockets reach this problem is not I contr l, LinShuHao said, &quot;but I'd spent playing in general, no matter if I had a purpose. LinShuHao last season in the first 25 games you can get 18.2 points and 7.6 assists data, but at the end of the season due to injury and the absence LinShuHao in low season said after recovering, and now it has reduced weight and jins,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1oeXBlcmZ1c2UtMjAxMi1jLTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Cheap Nike Hyperfuse 2012</a> she has now distinctly ago than in the past. &quot;look for me now is just the beginning, I was still in the stages of learning , every day I make a lot of training hard, so I have to try to reduce this type of error, and hope to be able to make progress as a player, I'm still room for improvement. &quot;More LinShuHao Au Addition, rockets and many young players as pastors takes 2011 seconds round of last season has averaged 9.5 points and 4.8 rebounds per game performance. Although Parsons is a young player, but compared to . another rookie, it is in fact a veteran I know that if I need to happen is, after making his debut with a professional attitude to the fight &quot;pastor said I have a very good feeling, and I think these new young players in the middle, I can easily performed. &quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rZC00aXYtYy0xNy5odG1s" target="_blank">Kevin Durant Shoes</a>
<br />Rockets began in the cup after Luis Scola team to rejuvenate, but the coach at McHale still think the West is still angry rocket m waves Possible. Hao book are competitors on the registered stock Ment at the beginning of words , now a Chinese leaders seem still very optimistic. &quot;Maybe we were still young, maybe we are not about the game experience,&quot; LinShuHao said, &quot;but because we have a lot in common and have their own advantages, nimble, quick , F outstanding athletic abilities. Now we strive Ons rely on their advantage of playing. &quot;Five preseason games rockets 3-2 and the home game 12th October, 95 -, - 75 victory over New Orleans Hornets, but since 17109-102 victory over the Memphis Grizzlies, but the rocket is not playing a game, hold trainings for the season was a period of adjustment to prepare,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb2JlN2ZvcnNlbGwuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rZC00aXYtYy0xNy5odG1s" target="_blank">Cheap KD 4</a> but also in of training to learn new content. After tonight's game, the rocket Orlando, travel 26, are on the road against the Orlando Magic, which can also be their last pre-season. 28 rockets afternoon at Toyota Center he Ffnete one Ffentliches Training Fans, 31, will be on the road this season in Detroit, he opened Winning the opener against the piston. Before the start of the game at half past one, the player rocket into practice on the ground, practicing priest, and is the o in the bore of the Binnenm Markets and find tha Country Jonas Kazlauskas and lamb, etc.. In the physical trainer under the direction of salmon, band tension
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>