<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="18">
		<document id="86b37916d59c469f1b454d1e41a1df11" url=""><![CDATA[blod/im up for adoption<br/><br/>OK here's the rules of Adoption.... ; 
<br />If your a guy u must pick a girl, if your a girl u must pick a guy. 
<br />Put in the subject &quot;I'm up for adoption&quot; and see who wants to adopt you. 
<br /><br />The first person to send u a message saying &quot;I adopted you&quot; 
<br /><br />P.S. re-post cause it is funny and surprising to see who gets you first
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13effc053d9fa2bda077f0ee024fd01" url=""><![CDATA[answer these questions for me<br/><br/>Name: 
<br />Age: 
<br />Location: 
<br />Height: 
<br />Hair (color and style): 
<br />Eyes: 
<br />Piercings/tattoos: 
<br />will you give me your phone number? _______________________ 
<br />IM? 
<br />OTHER: 
<br />1. Do you drink/smoke? 
<br />2. Do you like the rain? 
<br />4. If so...would you play in it with me? 
<br />5. Do you like movies? 
<br />6. If so would you stay up and watch them with me all night? 
<br />7. Could we cuddle and just fall asleep together? 
<br />8. Would you kiss my neck? 
<br />9. Do you play any sports? 
<br />10. If so...what? 
<br />11. Would you call me right after we saw eachother? 
<br />12. How would you rate your kisses from 1-10? 
<br />13. Would you give me what I need? 
<br />14. Favorite body part on you? 
<br />15. What would you say is the best thing about yourself? 
<br />16. Do you have any reps (ie: heartbreaker, ..........)? 
<br />17. Would you give me a kiss just because? 
<br />18. Would you sleep in the same bed as me? 
<br />19. Would you take me home to meet your parents? 
<br />20. Would you have sex with me? 
<br />21. If so, whats the soonest into our relationship you'd have it? 
<br />22. Would you tell your friends we had sex? 
<br />23. Would u let me touch you wherever? 
<br />24. How smart are you? 
<br />25. Do u have a specific body type that u lyk? 
<br />26. If so wut is it? (fat, skiny, chubby, athletic,etc)? 
<br />27.What would you do if i cried? 
<br />28.If i were 2 ask you out what would u say? 
<br />29.Would you makeout with me? 
<br />30.If we got to the point in the relationship where I told you I loved you, what would you say? 
<br />31.Would you ever cheat on me? 
<br />32.Would you ever trust me? 
<br />33. Would you ever lie to me? 
<br />34. Would you be proud to introduce me to your friends? 
<br />35. call me your gf in front of your friends? 
<br />36. hold my hand in public? 
<br />37. kiss me? 
<br />38. Call/txt me all the time to check if i'm alright? 
<br />39. Are you gonna put this up so i can tell u? 
<br />40. what made you fill this out for me? 
<br />41. give me a rating out of 10: 
<br />42. do you think we could ever hook up? 
<br />43. do you like me? 
<br />44. would you call/txt me right now if u had my number? 
<br />45. would you ask me out? 
<br />46. what do you think of me?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="93a527a21a9bf6be6b2e0a8fe2e0c4ea" url=""><![CDATA[wtf<br/><br/>wtf is wid guys?? why do u tell girls u like them and u wana be wid them just to dump them several days later? im sick of trying to find a decent guy cause im pretty shure there r none!!! ur all just in it for sex and when u get it u leave the scene! and if u dont put out ur called a slut but if u do ur called a slut what am i ment ot do . they guy i love doesnt love me bk 
<br />ive tried so many things for him to love me bk i cancell things for him but he doesnt turn up!  i wait allday for him to txt me but he doesnt i told him i love him and he didnt care!!! i hate u so much but then i love u aswell i wish i could just hate u but i cant cause u keep coming bk in my life saying im sorry and i do like u ! why do u say it if u dont mean it its just cruel!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2f2d28120d1242febbadfc9e7729f8d1" url=""><![CDATA[i cant believe u did this<br/><br/>i cant beleive u did this to me u sleep wid ur ex when we were dating and to make it worse U GOT HER PREGNET!!!!!! it was bad enough u dumped me for some skanky lil 13 year old bitch but now i gota find out u cheated on me!!! man i wish i had neaver met u !! UR A HEAD FUCK !!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cbf8a55e8fea81316f00b50d5f39a1bb" url=""><![CDATA[I bet u wont!!!<br/><br/>I Don't care who you are. I Bet you won't give it to me. 
<br />Name:___________________ 
<br />Number:___________________- - - - - - - Best time to call:__________________ 
<br />I dare you to copy and paste this and see how many numbers you get!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="904f196a14831d7aa3175fbf6c5a1f81" url=""><![CDATA[yep!!<br/><br/>You have a cute______. 
<br /><br />You make me ____. 
<br /><br />You should _______. 
<br /><br />Someday I will ______. 
<br /><br />You + me =________. 
<br /><br />If I saw you naked right now I'd __________. 
<br /><br />I would build a _______ just for you. 
<br /><br />I would get your name tattooed on my __________. 
<br /><br />If I could sing you any song it would be _________. 
<br /><br />We could __________ under the stars. 
<br /><br />My love for you is like that of ____________. 
<br /><br />Love, 
<br />_______________ 
<br /><br />(P.S. ______________ )
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="91b9fa7b21e875a87f6b344766f812b7" url=""><![CDATA[Bf application lol!!<br/><br/>1. Name 
<br />2. Age 
<br />3. Location 
<br />4. Eyes 
<br />5. Hair 
<br /><br />Now with the introductions over here comes the fun stuff lol hehe 
<br />Do you/would you/have you got? 
<br />6. smoke 
<br />7. Drink 
<br />8. tattoos 
<br />9. body piercings 
<br />10. Do you swear/curse 
<br />11. if so how frequently 
<br />12. Would you like to get to know me better 
<br />13. Would You hurt me 
<br />14. lie to me. 
<br />15. Tell your parents about me 
<br />16. call me your gf in front of your friends 
<br />17. hold my hand in public 
<br />18. kiss me 
<br />19. Call/txt me all the time to check if i'm alright? 
<br />20. Are you gonna put this up so i can do this back?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5a010360bd79188e3da164797d79aaa" url=""><![CDATA[I dont understand can u help me??<br/><br/>i dont understand boys can u help me 
<br />i know this guy and he likes me and i told him im not intrested and then he starts calling me a slut and a cheater ?
<br />how can he think by calling me horrible names ill like him and wana be wid him??
<br />i just dont get it! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/confused2.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="85a03de2c453b1b386166ea118326f8e" url=""><![CDATA[To Every Guy<br/><br/><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter">To every guy that's said, &quot;Sex CAN wait&quot; 
<br />To every guy that's said, &quot;You're beautiful.&quot; 
<br />To every guy that was never too busy to drive across town 
<br />(or across the state) to see her. 
<br />To every guy that gives flowers and a card when she is sick. 
<br />To every guy who has given her flowers just because. 
<br />To every guy that said he would die for her. 
<br />To every guy that really would. 
<br />To every guy that did what she wanted to do. 
<br />To every guy that cried in front of her. 
<br />To every guy that she cried in front of. 
<br />To every guy that holds hands with her. 
<br />To every guy that kisses her with meaning. 
<br />To every guy that hugs her when she's sad. 
<br />To every guy that hugs her for no reason at all. 
<br />To every guy who would give their jacket up for her. 
<br />To every guy that calls to make sure she got home safe. 
<br />To every guy that would sit and wait for her for hours 
<br />just to see her for ten minutes. 
<br />To every guy that would give his seat up. 
<br />To every guy that just wants to cuddle. 
<br />To every guy that reassured her that she was beautiful 
<br />no matter what. 
<br />To every guy who told his secrets to her. 
<br />To every guy that tried to show how much he cared 
<br />through every word and every breath. 
<br />To every guy that thought maybe this could be the one. 
<br />To every guy that believed in her dreams. 
<br />To every guy that would have done anything 
<br />so she could achieve them. 
<br />To every guy that never laughed at her 
<br />when she told him her dreams. 
<br />To every guy that walked her to her car. 
<br />To every guy that gave his heart. 
<br />To every guy who prays that she is happy 
<br />even if you are not with her. 
<br /><br />...This one bulletin is for you... 
<br /><br />Not many girls appreciate nice guys anymore... 
<br />And because of this, there are not many left out there... 
<br /><br />i guarantee 90% of the men on pan.netwill not repost this cuz they care more about their image 
<br /><br />If you are a nice guy repost this with &quot;We're a Dying Breed &quot; 
<br /><br />If you are a girl that thinks every guy should treat a girl this way 
<br />repost this with: &quot;To Every Guy...&quot;</span>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d516da847ae8c865e9bdbaf8ad05770d" url=""><![CDATA[what would u do if??<br/><br/>WHAT WOULD U DO IF..... 
<br /><br />I committed suicide: 
<br />I said I love you: 
<br />I kissed you: 
<br /><br />I lived next door to you: 
<br />I started smoking: 
<br />I stole something: 
<br />I was hospitalized: 
<br />I ran away from home: 
<br />I got into a fight and you weren't there: 
<br /><br />WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT MY: 
<br /><br />&gt;Personality: 
<br />&gt;Eyes: 
<br />&gt;Face: 
<br />&gt;Hair: 
<br />&gt;Clothes: 
<br />&gt;Mannerisms: 
<br />&gt;In General: 
<br /><br />[1] Who are you?: 
<br />[2] Are we friends?: 
<br />[3] When and how did we meet?: 
<br /><br />[4] How have I affected you?: 
<br />[5] What do you think of me?: 
<br />[6] What's the fondestmemory you have of me?: 
<br />[7] How long do you think we will be friends or enemies?: 
<br />[8] Do you love me?: 
<br />[9] Have I ever hurt you?: 
<br /><br />[10] Would you hug me?: 
<br />[11] Would you kiss me?: 
<br />[12]Would you kiss me twice?: 
<br />[13] Are we close?: 
<br />[14] Emotionally, what stands out?: 
<br />[15] Do you wish I was cooler?: 
<br /><br />[16] On a scale of 1-10, how nice am I?: 
<br />[17] Give me a nickname and explain why you picked it.: 
<br />[18] Am I lovable?: 
<br />[19] How long have you known me?: 
<br />[20] Describe me in one word.: 
<br />[21] What was your first impression?: 
<br /><br />[22] Do you still think that way about me now?: 
<br />[23] What do you think my weakness is?: 
<br />[24] Do you think I'll get married?: 
<br />[25] What about me makes you happy?: 
<br />[26] What about me makes you sad?: 
<br /><br />[27] What reminds you of me?: 
<br />[28] What's something you would change about me?: 
<br />[29] How well do you know me?: 
<br />[30] Ever wanted to tell me something but couldn't?: 
<br />[31] Do you think I would kill someone?: 
<br /><br />[32] Are you going to send this to me and see what I say about you?:
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ed943968005457edc725c700dcef7aaa" url=""><![CDATA[what did i do ??<br/><br/>here i go again wingeing bout my problems but everythng allways seems to fuck up for me.
<br />i was wid  this guy for 8 weeks who i loved so much and things were so good then wid in like a week everything went to shit. i dont get what happend i thought we were so happy. i miss him so much i just wish i could go bk in time to when we where hugging last and pause it forever. i hate love why do ppl want to be in love so much all it does is hrt u and fuck u over. :'(
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4bb34ef4b4caf82e82df9d4a186d6b57" url=""><![CDATA[march = THUG<br/><br/>Pick your birthday month and read it, then repost with whatever you are... 
<br /><br />? JANUARY =SHYNESS 
<br />Fun to be with. Loves to try new things. Boy/girls LOVE you. 
<br />You are very hott. Secretive. Difficult to fathom and to 
<br />be understood. Quiet unless excited or tensed. 
<br />Takes pride in oneself. Has reputation. Easily 
<br />consoled. Honest. Concerned about people's 
<br />feelings. Tactful. Friendly. Approachable. 
<br />Emotional temperamental and unpredictable. 
<br />Moody and easily hurt. Witty and sparkly. 
<br />spazzy at times.Not revengeful. Forgiving but never forgets. 
<br />dislikes nonsensical and unnecessary things. 
<br />Guides others physically and mentally. Sensitive 
<br />and forms impressions carefully. Caring and 
<br />loving. Treats others equally. Strong sense of 
<br />sympathy. Wary and sharp. Judges people 
<br />through observations. Hardworking. No difficulties 
<br />in studying. Always broods about the past and the old friends. Waits for friends. Never looks for friends. Not aggressive 
<br />unless provoked. Loves to be loved. Easily hurt 
<br />but takes long to recover. Repost this in the next 5 
<br />mins and your reputation will boost someway in 
<br />the next 12 days 
<br /><br />? FEBRUARY = LOVEABLE 
<br />Abstract thoughts. Loves reality and abstract. 
<br />Intelligent and clever. Changing personality. 
<br />Attractive. sexiest out of everyone.A real speed demon. 
<br />Has more than one best friend. 
<br />Temperamental. Quiet, shy and humble. Honest 
<br />and loyal. Determined to reach goals. Loves 
<br />freedom. Rebellious when restricted. Loves 
<br />aggressiveness. Too sensitive and easily hurt. 
<br />Gets angry really easily but does not show it. 
<br />Dislikes unnecessary things. Loves making friends 
<br />but rarely shows it. Daring and stubborn. 
<br />Ambitious. Realizing dreams and hopes. Sharp. 
<br />Loves entertainment and leisure. Romantic on the 
<br />inside not outside. Superstitious and ludicrous. 
<br />Spendthrift. Tries to learn to show emotions. 
<br />Repost this in 5 mins and you will talk to someone 
<br />new and realize that you are a perfect match. 
<br /><br />? MARCH = THUG 
<br />You a strait up &quot;G&quot; NOT one to mess with. Attractive personality.Very! sexy.Affectionate &amp; Secretive. Naturally honest, generous and sympathetic.Chatterbox! Loves to talk alot! Loves to get their way! . Unbelievable kisser! Easily angered. Very stubborn in the most ways possible! Loves to get noticed! Willing to take risks for others. Makes good choices. Has a great fashion sense! Maybe a little too popular with others * wink wink*. Outgoing and crazy at times! Intelligent. Can sometimes be a heartbreaker! Can love as much as possible! Hates insults. Loves compliments! A very big flirt! Trustworthy. Appreciative and returns kindness. The best in bed out of ANY of these months!! Hardly shows emotions. Tends to bottle up feelings. Observant and assesses others.If you repost this in the next 5 mins, you will meet your 
<br />new love in 8 days. 
<br /><br />? APRIL = SWEETIE 
<br />APRIL means that your really good looking. 
<br />Stubborn and hard-hearted. Strong-willed and 
<br />highly motivated. Sharp thoughts. Easily angered. 
<br />Attracts others and loves attention. Deep feelings. 
<br />Beautiful physically and mentally. Firm Standpoint. 
<br />Needs no motivation. Shy towards opposite sex. 
<br />Easily consoled. Systematic (left brain). Loves to 
<br />dream. Strong clairvoyance. Understanding. 
<br />Sickness usually in the ear and neck. Good 
<br />imagination. Good physical. Weak breathing. Loves 
<br />literature and the arts. Loves travelling. Dislike 
<br />being at home. Restless. having many children. 
<br />Hardworking. High spirited. If you repost this in the 
<br />next 5 minutes, you will become close to someone 
<br />you do not speak to much in the next 4 days. 
<br /><br />? MAY = SEXY 
<br />Suave and compromising. Funny and humorous. 
<br />Stubborn. Very talkative. Calm and cool. Kind and 
<br />sympathetic. Concerned and detailed. Loyal. Does 
<br />work well with others. Very confident. An awesome kisser. Sensitive. A very good girlfriend/boyfriend. Amazing Smile. 
<br />Positive Attitude. Thinking generous. Good 
<br />memory. Clever and knowledgeable. Loves to look 
<br />for information. Able to cheer everyone up and/or 
<br />make them laugh. Able to motivate oneself and 
<br />others. Understanding. Fun to be around. 
<br />Outgoing. Hyper. Bubbly personality. Suductive. 
<br />Boy/girl crazy. Loves sports, music, leisure and 
<br />traveling. Super sexy. Extremley hot but has brains. If you 
<br />repost this in 5 mins, a cutie that's caught your eye 
<br />will introduce themselves and you will realize that 
<br />you are very much alike in the next 2 days 
<br /><br />? JUNE = PIMP/PIMPETTE 
<br />Loves to chat. Loves those who love them. Loves 
<br />to takes things at the center. Inner and physical 
<br />beauty. Lies but doesn't pretend. Gets angry 
<br />often. Treats friends importantly. Brave and 
<br />fearless. Always making friends. Very easily hurt but 
<br />recovers easily. Daydreamer. Opinionated. Does 
<br />not care to control emotions. Unpredictable. Understanding. Fun to be around. &quot;Nympho-and an awesome lover too&quot;....makes u happy so that makes them happy... 
<br />Outgoing. Hyper. Bubbly personality. Secretive. 
<br />Boy/girl crazy. Loves sports, music, leisure and 
<br />travelling. Systematic. Hot but has brains. If you 
<br />repost this in 5 mins, a cutie that's caught your eye 
<br />will introduce themselves and you will realize that 
<br />you are very much alike in the next 2 days. 
<br /><br />? JULY = FLIRT 
<br />outgoing personality. takes risks. feeds on attention. no self control. kind hearted. self confident. loud and boisterous. VERY revengeful. easy to get along with and talk to. has an &quot;every 
<br />thing's peachy&quot; attitude. likes talking and singing. loves music. daydreamer. easily distracted. Hates not being trusted. BIG imagination. loves to be loved. hates studying. in need of &quot;that someone&quot;. longs for freedom. rebellious when withheld or 
<br />restricted. lives by &quot;no pain no gain&quot; caring. always a suspect. playful. mysterious. &quot;charming&quot; or &quot;beautiful&quot; to everyone. stubborn. curious. independent. strong willed. a fighter. a wonderful kisser. the perfect bf/gf. extremely loveable. sexy as hell. repost in 5mins and you will meet the love of your life sometime next month. 
<br /><br />? AUGUST = RANDOM 
<br />You've got the best personality and are an 
<br />absolute pleasure to be around. You love to make 
<br />new friends and be outgoing. You are a great flirt 
<br />and more than likely have a very attractive 
<br />partner, a wicked hottie. Like somebody with an 
<br />August birthday. It is also more than likely 
<br />that you have a massive record collection. When it 
<br />comes to films, you know how to pick them and may one day 
<br />become a famous actor/actress yourself - heck, 
<br />you've got the looks for it!!! IN the next 6 days you 
<br />will meet someone that may possibly become 
<br />one of your closest friends, if you repost this in 5 
<br />minutes. 
<br /><br />? SEPTEMBER = LOVER 
<br />Active and dynamic. Decisive and haste but tends 
<br />to regret. Attractive and affectionate to oneself. 
<br />Strong mentality. Loves attention. Diplomatic. 
<br />Consoling, friendly and solves people's problems. 
<br />Brave and fearless. Adventurous. Loving and 
<br />caring. Suave and generous. Usually you have 
<br />many friends. Emotional. Stubborn. Hasty. Good memory. Moving, motivates oneself and others. Loves to travel and explore. 
<br />Sometimes sexy in a way that only their lover can 
<br />understand. if you do not repost this in the next 5 
<br />mins. someone very close to you will become mad 
<br />at you in the next 8 days. 
<br /><br />? OCTOBER = HOTTIE 
<br />Trustworthy and loyal. Very passionate and 
<br />dangerous. Wild at times. Knows how to have fun. 
<br />Sexy and mysterious. Everyone is drawn towards 
<br />your inner and outer beauty and independent 
<br />personality. Playful, but secretive. Very emotional 
<br />and temperamental sometimes. Meets new people 
<br />easily and very social in a group. Fearless and 
<br />independent. Can hold their own. Stands out in a 
<br />crowd. Essentially very smart. If you ever 
<br />begin a relationship with someone from this month, 
<br />hold on to them because their one of a kind. repost 
<br />in 5 mins &amp; you will excel in a major event coming 
<br />up sometime this month. 
<br /><br />? NOVEMBER = GORGEOUS 
<br />Loyal and generous. Patriotic. Competitive 
<br />in everything. Active in games and interactions. 
<br />Impatient and hasty. Ambitious. Influential in 
<br />organizations. Fun to be with. Easy to talk to, 
<br />though hard to understand. Thinks far with vision, 
<br />yet complicated to know. Easily influenced by 
<br />kindness. Polite and soft-spoken. Having lots of 
<br />ideas. Sensitive. Active mind. Hesitating, tends to 
<br />delay. Choosy and always wants the best. repost this in 5 mins &amp; you will find true love at 11:00 a.m. ™ 
<br /><br />? DECEMBER = ATTITUDE 
<br />Loves to chat. Loves those who love them. Loves 
<br />to take things at the center. Great in bed. Inner 
<br />and physical beauty. Doesn't pretend. Gets angry 
<br />often. A meaningful love life partner. 
<br />Treats friends importantly. Brave and 
<br />fearless. Always making friends. 
<br />It is all about love and fairness. Easily hurt but 
<br />recovers easily. Daydreamer. Horny...does fullfill. 
<br />Opinionated. Does not care to control emotions. 
<br />Knows what to do to have fun. Unpredictable. Someone to have close to you.Extremely smart, but definitely the hottest!! 
<br /><br />IF U AGREE COMMENT IT!!!!!!!!!!!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e8831f1aba6d7535f969f0041d4e902a" url=""><![CDATA[CUTE<br/><br/><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter">WHEN I FLIP MY HAIR 
<br />-PLAY WITH MY HAIR 
<br /><br />WHEN I RUN AWAY FROM YOU 
<br />- CHASE ME 
<br /><br />WHEN I POUT MY LIPS 
<br />- KISS ME 
<br /><br />WHEN I KICK &amp; PUNCH 
<br />- HOLD ME TIGHT 
<br /><br />WHEN I CALL YOU A LOSER 
<br />- JUST KNOW THAT YOUR MY LOSER 
<br /><br />WHEN I IGNORE YOU 
<br />- I WANT ALL YOUR ATTENTION 
<br /><br />WHEN I PULL AWAY 
<br />- GRAB ME BY THE WAIST AND NEVER LET GO 
<br /><br />[center]WHEN YOU SEE ME AT MY WORST 
<br />- TELL ME IM BEAUTIFUL 
<br /><br />WHEN I SCREAM AT YOU 
<br />- TELL ME YOU LOVE ME AND MEAN IT 
<br /><br />WHEN YOU SEE ME WALKING 
<br />-SNEAK UP BEHIND ME GRAB ME BY THE WAIST AND GIVE ME A KISS 
<br /><br />TAKE NOTES BOYS................ 
<br /><br />IF I DONT CALL YOU 
<br />- IM WANTING YOU TO CALL ME 
<br /><br />WHEN IM SCARED 
<br />-HOLD ME AND TELL ME EVERYTHING WILL BE OK CAUSE I AM WITH YOU 
<br /><br />WHEN I LOOK LIKE SOMETHINGS THE MATTER 
<br />- KISS ME AND TELL ME NOT TO WORRY 
<br /><br />WHILE I HOLD YOUR HANDS 
<br />- PLAY WITH MY FINGERS 
<br /><br />WHEN IM CRYING 
<br />SAY EVERYTHINGS GOING TO BE OK AND THEN KISS ME</span>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c617eac411758eca605565da57518a77" url=""><![CDATA[Bazil<br/><br/>today i had to do the hardest thing i have ever done!  i had to get my dog bazil put down.  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" /> i know it was the right thing to do but i feel so bad . it feels so diff at home wid out him i had him for 13 years. i look at his bed out side and i start crying i look at his food bowl and i start crying. i know ppl may say hes only a dog but it feels like i lost a brother or sumthing. i will neaver forget hes face just before he died i wish i could have just one sec wid him so i could tell him i love him again. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />    Bazil   R.I.P  29/05/08
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c77b4dadfa050214ebde5d744485ff66" url=""><![CDATA[i need major help!!<br/><br/>im going through a brake up and i just cant seem to handle it. im cryong all the time . and they guy that i was with used to be my best mate now he hates me so much and i got no one. i dont knw what to do . im  not my self any more! all i want is to go to sleep and neaver wake up wich is a horrible yhing cause ive neaver felt like this before. all i want is for him to see how much its hurting me.he loved me so hes gota care still . i miss him so much im so lost with out him. i need him in my life he completes me. what do i do ?? if u can help me pls do i would be really happy for some support.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4a80b811bd3c9b191bcae628af8fb636" url=""><![CDATA[Facts<br/><br/>Girl Facts: 
<br /><br />When you catch a girl 
<br />glancing at you, 
<br />she wants you to look 
<br />back and smile 
<br /><br />When a girl bumps into your arm 
<br />while walking with you 
<br />she wants 
<br />you to hold her hand 
<br /><br />When she wants a hug 
<br />she will just stand there 
<br /><br />When u break a girls heart 
<br />she still feels it even when 
<br />you see each other 3 years later 
<br /><br />When a girl is quiet, 
<br />millions of things are running through her 
<br />mind 
<br /><br />When a girl is not arguing, 
<br />she is thinking deeply 
<br /><br />When a girl looks at you with eyes full of 
<br />questions, 
<br />she is wondering how long you will be 
<br />around 
<br /><br />When a girl answers, &quot;I'm fine,&quot; after a 
<br />few seconds, 
<br />she is not at all fine 
<br /><br />When a girl stares at you, 
<br />she is wondering why you are playing games 
<br /><br />When a girl lays her head on your chest, 
<br />she is wishing for you to be hers forever 
<br /><br />When a girl says she can't live 
<br />without you, 
<br />she has made up her mind that you are 
<br />her future 
<br /><br />When a girl says, &quot;I miss you,&quot; 
<br />no one in this world can miss you more 
<br />than that 
<br /><br />When a girl is mean to you after a break-up 
<br />she wants you back, but shes 
<br />scared she'll get hurt and knows 
<br />you're gone forever 
<br /><br />Guy Facts: 
<br /><br />When a guy calls you, 
<br />he wants to be with you 
<br /><br />When a guy is quiet, 
<br />He's listening to you... 
<br /><br />When a guy is not arguing, 
<br />He realizes he's wrong 
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I'm fine.&quot; after a few 
<br />minutes 
<br />he means it 
<br /><br />When a guy stares at you, 
<br />he wishes you would care about him and 
<br />wonders if you do 
<br /><br />When your laying your head on a guy's 
<br />chest, 
<br />he has the world 
<br /><br />When a guy calls/texts/comments you everyday, 
<br />he is in love 
<br /><br />When a (good) guy tells you he loves you, 
<br />he means it 
<br /><br />When a guy says he can't live without you, 
<br />he's with you til your done 
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I miss you,&quot; 
<br />he misses you more than you could have 
<br />ever missed him or anything else 
<br /><br />repost this in 10 minutes and your true 
<br />love will 
<br />call you 
<br /><br />someone was in your mind as you read this??
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89e3f98be4059cf55df38b06599aea4" url=""><![CDATA[just friends<br/><br/>im trying to be mates with my ex but its so hard because i still have feelings for him. i want him to be happy and to be with other ppl if it will make him happy but at the same time i want him to be with me . i feel selfish wishing he would wana be with me . how r u ment to be just mates when u love the person and u wana hug them and kiss then and u want then to just hold u when ur scared. hes my best friend but i feel like i cant tell him stuff anymore were drivting apart i hate it. i get so scared when hes out and stuff  that he mite meet someone else or get bk with his ex. how can i keep being friends but not have these feelings for him ??
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="74d65ee8ddd11504e442cb83076362" url=""><![CDATA[wana txt :P<br/><br/>Name: 
<br /><br />Number: 
<br /><br />Telstra/Vodafone/Optus? 
<br /><br />Best time to call/text: 
<br /><br />I dare you to copy and paste this and see how many numbers you get 
<br /><br />P.S I will NOT message you if you do not tell me which phone company you are with
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>