<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="22">
		<document id="ada8a5e31cea28ed2ca7ea643e15dd7e" url=""><![CDATA[*r u in love*<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" /> 15 Signs Of Falling In Love
<br />FIFTEEN:
<br />U LOOK AT THEIR PROFILE/PICTURE CONSTANTLY
<br /><br />FOURTEEN:
<br />WHEN U R ON THE PHNE WITH THEM LATE AT NIGHT AND THEY HANG UP, U
<br />STIL MISS THEM EVEN WHEN IT WAS JUST 2 MINs AGO.
<br /><br />THIRTEEN:
<br />U READ THEIR TXTS OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
<br /><br />ELEVEN:
<br />U WALK REALLY SLOW WHEN U R WITH THEM
<br /><br />TEN:
<br />U FEEL SHY WHENEVER U R /THEY R AROUND.
<br /><br />NINE:
<br />WHEN U THINK ABOUT THEM, UR HEART BEATS FASTER AND SLOWER AT THE
<br />SAME TIME
<br /><br />EIGHT:
<br />U SMILE WHEN U HEAR THEIR VOICE.
<br /><br />SEVEN:
<br />U START LISTENING TO SLOW SONGS, WHILE THINKING OF THEM
<br /><br />SIX:
<br />THEY R ALL U THINK ABOUT.
<br /><br />FIVE:
<br />U REALlIZE THAT U R AlWAYS SMILING TO URSELF WHEN U THINK
<br />ABOUT THEM.
<br /><br />FOUR:
<br />U WOULD DO ANYTHING 4 THEM, OR ANYTHING TO C THEM.
<br /><br />THREE:
<br />WHILE READING THIS, THERE WAS ONE PERSON ON UR MIND THE WHOLE TIME
<br /><br />TWO:
<br />U WERE SO BUSY THINKING ABOUT THAT PERSON, YOU DIDN'T NOTICE NUM.
<br />TWELVE.
<br /><br />ONE:
<br />U JUST SCROLLED UP TO CHECK &amp; ARE NOW SILENTLY LAUGHING AT YOURSELF <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angel.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1f7cd00506ff2844d8473fac1f9f26c" url=""><![CDATA[dreams do come true<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> Dreams do come true, but only when
<br />They make it through despair,
<br />Limping into everyday
<br />Transformed beyond repair. 
<br /><br />No dream would be a dream if it
<br />Could pass for something real,
<br />Nor would we sail for paradise
<br />Would it its shoals conceal. 
<br /><br />So it is with love: the dream
<br />Long longed for, now possessed,
<br />Must be a dream no longer, but
<br />An emperor undressed. 
<br /><br />Stark naked it must come to us
<br />In unaccustomed shame,
<br />And we must take it in our arms
<br />And love it all the same. 
<br /><br />And we must love love as it is
<br />That dreams might still come true,
<br />Mangled into miracles
<br />To make our lives anew.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca9b8d8fda30169dd58b56674fad7078" url=""><![CDATA[when r we goin act upon wht we think?<br/><br/>when r we goin act upon wht we think?
<br /> are you unsure what are you going to do in the near future?be sure my friend,being a book worm  won't help you in any case!all you want to do is sit at home which u will regret in the later stages of your life,only beacause you have not seen the real world which no 1 can imagine.trust me people,if you want to be one of the person who are intelligent according to their marksheets and not according to the real world statistics,you got no where to survive here.deciding that you want to do a certain things in your life is alright,but implement on it,start doing things that r related to that,dnot just make fool around yourself around people whom you said about 10min ago that you want to do this thing,when he ask you how?you simply don't ans  confused?
<br />be a smart guy .when you do things that is your dream even if you get little out of what you did  your heart will say i love it,the satisfaction is unmatched with the work you did before your heart said you lets go for it......
<br />so my friends when you think try to act upon it,dnt sit like a lame duck.because happiness lies when you try somthing and u succeed in it.also when you fail in it,you will know better who r on your side and who are not!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a78991c3ba6543344397e09dd913c09" url=""><![CDATA[ur my heart<br/><br/>I love you, but I'm not in love with you.
<br />I want your friendship minus your desire.
<br />I would not lead you falsely or betray you.
<br />I feel the tenderness, but not the fire.
<br />I have no reason for my lack of yearning,
<br />No explanation for what I don't feel,
<br />No other love to whom I might be turning,
<br />No anguish to suggest this isn't real.
<br />Passion is a horse that knows no master,
<br />And I cannot with fences make it stay.
<br />It must run free towards daylight or disaster,
<br />Awake to glory in no other way.
<br />So I must say what you don't want to hear,
<br />But it's a truth that both of us must bear
<br />That even if time goes by ahead with me,
<br />You are always in my heart to Live with me
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d0c8d3fd32d2664d447dde92b7d464ca" url=""><![CDATA[Let's be together<br/><br/>Let's go out and have some fun.
<br />It doesn't matter where or when,
<br />Or what we say or what we do,
<br />As long as it's just me and you.
<br /><br />Let's be together for a while
<br />And get to know each other well,
<br />Exchanging jokes and tales and chatter
<br />Before we get to things that matter.
<br /><br />Let's see what happens when we dance
<br />Across an evening sky, and glimpse
<br />Below the stirrings of a sea
<br />That might-or not-wind-haunted be
<br /><br />Let these moments be persistent,
<br />As I always dreamed to be with you till the end,
<br />Whatever may happened with us my dear,
<br />You are my life to always cheer
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2b208c562c7080ea841331c90ccd9c25" url=""><![CDATA[pearls of a dew<br/><br/>After I see the pearls of Dew,
<br />I wish I could be around that dew,
<br />Just like the morning greens,
<br />I find it always pure and clean,
<br />I dont know what did you find in me,
<br />That you say that I have changed from Thee,
<br />Never will I ever change,
<br />As its a bond to never change,
<br />As I Love to be the same at heart,
<br />As I want to be small as that,
<br />For now I must have caught in you,
<br />Many faults that are new,
<br />Because I felt that you are new,
<br />Not like that friend which I knew,
<br />But infact I wont ever comprehend on that,
<br />As you are always intact,
<br />I would be always near your heart,
<br />Just like the blood of your heart,
<br />Treat me as you wish to do,
<br />I wont utter a word against you,
<br />As I cant see a single drop of your tears,
<br />Which scatters my mind along with your tears,
<br />As you are my heart to hold me ever,
<br />You are my Love forever
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9de82851641126876513a9f06b590afa" url=""><![CDATA[my precious stone<br/><br/>Jewels are cut from more than precious stone.
<br />A life, too, is cut to catch the light.
<br />No beauty is refracted when a lone, 
<br />Isolated stranger rides the night.
<br /><br />Can you be jewels to each other's sun?
<br />Each needs a light to shine upon the heart, 
<br />Awakening the loveliness that one
<br />Never could reveal if still apart.
<br /><br />Do, then, both shine and give refraction,
<br />So you may be both source of light and jewel.
<br />Have each the strength to translate into action
<br />A love that is both sparkling fire and fuel.
<br /><br />When two are one the sun and jewel can play:
<br />Now each heart will the other's light display
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="de5706be24f04e4702d2153e62190139" url=""><![CDATA[for u always<br/><br/>My dear friend who I never ever seen…..
<br />But I can see your love towards me!!!
<br /><br />In the valley of your dreams I want to be a meadow
<br />I will always there in the fence of your loneliness
<br /><br />I can’t to go away from you and why you stay there away from me?????
<br /><br />I will be there in the darkness of your sad as a fire fly
<br />I will be there in the brightness of your happiness as a little star
<br /><br />You are the one who teach me love
<br />You are the one who show me friendship
<br />You are the one who feels me care
<br />You are the one I want to be always with me!!!!!
<br /><br />Come close to me... I’m here for you always
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ab3491e22df2ddf89f7eda0abdebb3d7" url=""><![CDATA[my night queen<br/><br/>How can I fall in love with only words?
<br />Words and pictures, grainy and compressed?
<br />A jaypeg love is truly for the birds.
<br />You'd have to wonder whether I'm repressed.
<br />But love it is, through all the bits and bytes,
<br />For someone who's like no one else I've met:
<br />Tender, charming, bright, queen of my nights,
<br />All I've ever dreamed of, on the Net.
<br />And though she's living in a distant place,
<br />I love her as I've loved no one before.
<br />Will I ever get to touch her face,
<br />Hold her in my arms and, perhaps, more?
<br />Ay, me! No matter what, I'm still in love
<br />For just to converse with her more and More
<br />To know about her a bit than that new day
<br />As I find her special everyday
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d05c7378fe72f8699da7ec3762f4d7b7" url=""><![CDATA[true love<br/><br/>How can I fall in love with only words?
<br />Words and pictures, grainy and compressed?
<br />A jaypeg love is truly for the birds.
<br />You'd have to wonder whether I'm repressed.
<br />But love it is, through all the bits and bytes,
<br />For someone who's like no one else I've met:
<br />Tender, charming, bright, queen of my nights,
<br />All I've ever dreamed of, on the Net.
<br />And though she's living in a distant place,
<br />I love her as I've loved no one before.
<br />Will I ever get to touch her face,
<br />Hold her in my arms and, perhaps, more?
<br />Ay, me! No matter what, I'm still in love
<br />For just to converse with her more and More
<br />To know about her a bit than that new day
<br />As I find her special everyday
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8a51766a15647966ae1447dd4c412e90" url=""><![CDATA[LOVE<br/><br/>Love comes through the eyes that see
<br />And through the ears that hear,
<br />For people are quite beautiful,
<br />And words make feelings clear. 
<br /><br />Love comes through the hands that touch
<br />With unabashed affection,
<br />For only skin-to-skin can love
<br />Maintain its true direction. 
<br /><br />Love comes through the tastes and smells
<br />Of fresh and well-cooked food,
<br />For in the gift of nourishment
<br />Is much else that is good. 
<br /><br />But though love comes through senses five,
<br />Love comes from the heart,
<br />For there resides the greater love
<br />Of which ours is a part
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="633f1f666fb5d857f0489125d16d01a1" url=""><![CDATA[MY LOVE<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> Love means more when life is hard
<br />And choices lead to sacrifice,
<br />And every passion has its price
<br />In duties paid and windows barred. 
<br /><br />Though I have loved for many years,
<br />Love is still for me a spring
<br />That will from stone sweet fragrance bring,
<br />And make a garden of our tears. 
<br /><br />The love of children, children's children,
<br />Flowing to the distant verge,
<br />Flowing from the ancient urge
<br />To make a home of wilderness, 
<br /><br />Has been my joy, my inner dance
<br />Of ecstasy, as day by day
<br />I move the mountains in my way
<br />And claim through love the gifts of chance
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="20903d790928fb2901a92bc35086dad7" url=""><![CDATA[GO AHEAD WITH YOUR HEART<br/><br/>Go ahead with your heart
<br />In love you let the heart do all the thinking
<br />And say with courage simply what seems true.
<br />Time will in good time do all the linking,
<br />But you must know you've done what you can do. 
<br /><br />Passion understands far more than reason,
<br />Seeing in the dark with more than sight.
<br />Truth, in truth, can vary with the season,
<br />Nor can you ever know you've got it right. 
<br /><br />So throw yourself into the stream of being
<br />And let the moment take you where it will.
<br />Fear does nothing for the bitter keening
<br />That only love's sweet sacrifice can still.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d894593e1e9ade9f58326aaabe947e6e" url=""><![CDATA[my thought<br/><br/> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> ? Take up one idea. Make that one idea your life. Think of it. Dream of it. Live on that. Let the brain, muscle, nerves, every part of your body be full of that idea and just leave every other idea alone. This is the way of success. 
<br /><br />? Waste of time is most extra vagant, and costly of all expenses.
<br /><br />? Arise! Awake! and stop not till the goal is reached.
<br /><br />? Whatever you think, you can do it.
<br /><br />? Don’t be afraid to take a big step. You can not cross a charm in two small jumps.
<br /><br />? A lift off for great new benefits. 
<br /><br />? Be persistent, be hopeful and work hard to make your dreams come true.
<br /><br />? Your success and happiness starts with you.
<br /><br />? Do not let anybody or anything cloud the vision of your future. 
<br /><br />? Look part the obstacles to your goal and become an achiever.
<br /><br />? Winning is not everything, but the effort to win is.
<br /><br />? Look with love and compassion at the good qualities in everything.
<br /><br />? You cannot climb the ladder of success with your hands in your pocket.
<br /><br />? Doing and showing are more powerful than telling.
<br /><br />? When you know where you are going you are halfway there.
<br /><br />? An intelligent plan is the first step to success.
<br /><br />? You get the best out of others when you give the best of yourself.
<br /><br />? Exercise is to body what prayer is to the soul.
<br /><br />? Just because something is difficult does not mean you should not try. It means you should just try harder.
<br /><br />? Life is either a daring adventure or nothing.
<br /><br />? A challenge is an invitation to try something new and to expand your horizon.
<br /><br />? No defeat is final until you stop trying.
<br /><br />? You win only if you aren't afraid to lose.
<br /><br />? One thing you can’t recycle is a wasted time.
<br /><br />? The best way to escape a problem is to solve it.
<br /><br />? They can’t take away our self respect if we do not give it to them.
<br /><br />? Don’t say you don’t have enough time, You have exactly the same number of hours per day that were given to Mother Teresa, Albert Einstein, M.K. Gandhi and Pasteur.
<br /><br />? What matters most is how we respond to what we experience in life.
<br /><br />? Winners don’t do different things, They do things differently.
<br /><br />? Always believe in yourself, this is the only way to succeed.
<br /><br />? There is nothing impossible in this world as impossible itself says I am Possible.
<br /><br />? Do not dwell in the past, do not dream of the future, concentrate the mind on the present moment.
<br /><br />? Success is a journey not a destination.
<br /><br />? You cannot escape the responsibility of tomorrow by evading it today.
<br /><br />? There is always something to do.
<br /><br />? A pessimist see the difficulty in every opportunity and an optimist see the opportunity in every difficulty.
<br /><br />? Good things come to those who wait.
<br /><br />? The more risk you take, The more rewards you get.
<br /><br />? When all else is lost, the future still remains.
<br /><br />? Change your dreams into thoughts and thoughts into action.
<br /><br />? Failing to plan is equal to planning to fail.
<br /><br />? You may be disappointed if you fail, but you are doomed if you don't try.
<br /><br />? Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will.
<br /><br />? Be the change that you want to see in the world.
<br /><br />? There is no glory without sacrifice. If you have the will, you will find a way.
<br /><br />? Failure is just an obstacle on the road. Not the end of the journey.
<br /><br />? Possibilities are endless. 
<br /><br />? Keep your head and your heart in the right direction and you will never have to worry about your feet.
<br /><br />? Happiness is like a butterfly. The more you chase it, the more it will elude you. But if you turn your attention to other things. it comes softly and sits on your shoulder.
<br /><br />? In the middle of difficulty, there will always lies opportunity. 
<br /><br />? You cannot discover new oceans unless you have the courage to loss sight of the shore. 
<br /><br />? In the confrontation between the stream and the rock, the stream always wins. Not through strength, but through persistence.
<br /><br />? Happiness is not dependent on your circumstances or your bank balance. Happiness is a daily decision.
<br /><br />? The key to happiness is not that you never get upset, frustrated or irritated. It is how quickly you decide to snap out of it.
<br /><br />? Law of Progress : Everything has ups and downs - nothing travels in straight lines. This applies to your own progress in any project. Keep your eye on your target, keep putting in the effort and you reach your target despite the ups and downs. Successful people realize that they reach their goals by continuously correcting. We get off course, correct, and get back on course. Ships do it. Rockets and missiles do it. Correct. Correct. Correct.
<br /><br />? Shortcuts to Success : PLAN while others are playing. DECIDE while others are delaying. PREPARE while others are daydreaming. BEGIN while others are procrastinating. WORK while others are wishing. SAVE while others are wasting. SMILE while others are frowning. COMMEND while others are criticizing. PERSIST while others are quitting.
<br /><br />? Anyone who has never made a mistake has never tried anything new.
<br /><br />? Whatever you think or you want in your mind, you will get it.
<br /><br />? You can be what you want to be as long as you carry out your true self. Just be confident with what you have and must have a good attitude towards everything.
<br /><br />? Be grateful that you do not have everything you want. That means you have the opportunity of being happier tomorrow than you are today.
<br /><br />? All Ways Think Positive, What You Think, Is What Happens.
<br /><br />? Keep my words positive, because my words become behaviours. Keep my behaviours positive, because my behaviours become habits. Keep my habits positive, because my habits become my values. And keep my values positive, because they become my destiny.
<br /><br />? Doubt sees the obstacles, faith sees the way. Doubt sees the darkest night, Faith sees the day. Doubt dreads to take a step, Faith soars on high. Doubt questions &quot;who believes?&quot; Faith answers, &quot;I.&quot;
<br /><br />? The only real limitation on your abilities is the level of your desires. If you want it badly enough, there are no limits on what you can achieve.
<br /><br />? The happiest of people don't necessarily have the best of everything they just make the most of everything that comes along their way.
<br /><br />? The more precisely you plan, the harder destiny will hit you.
<br /><br />? He who would like to have something he never had, will have to do something well, that he hasn’t done yet. 
<br /><br />? Good things may come to those who wait, but all the really excellent stuff will be gone by then.
<br /><br />? Nothing is miserable unless you think it is so.
<br /><br />? You cannot wait for inspiration. You have to go after it with club.
<br /><br />? All men who have achieved great things have been great dreamers.
<br /><br />? Success does not mean the absence of failures, it means the attainment of ultimate objectives. It means winning the war, not every battle.
<br /><br />? As long as you are trying your very best, there can be no question of failure.
<br /><br />? The real voyage of discovery consists not in seeking new lands, but in seeing with new eyes.
<br /><br />? If you think you can, you can. And if you think you can't, you're right.
<br /><br />? It's a funny thing about life. If you refuse to accept nothing but the best, you very often get it.
<br /><br />? In the long run, men hit only what they aim at. Therefore, they had better aim at something high.
<br /><br />? Success, remember, is the reward of toil.
<br /><br />? Life is a grindstone. Whether it grinds us down or polishes us up depends on us.
<br /><br />? By the work one knows the workman.
<br /><br />? It is the nature of man to err, but only the fool perseveres in error.
<br /><br />? Men were born to succeed, not to fail.
<br /><br />? Life is like riding a bicycle. You don't fall off unless you stop peddling.
<br /><br />? Your life is what your thoughts make it.
<br /><br />? The obscure we eventually see. The completely obvious takes longer.
<br /><br />? A chip on the shoulder indicates that there is wood higher up.
<br /><br />? Things turn out the best for the people who make the best of the way things turn out.
<br /><br />? It is what you learn after you know it all that counts. 
<br /><br />? The difference between a successful person and others is not a lack of strength, not a lack of knowledge, but rather a lack of will.
<br /><br />? Any fool can criticize, condemn, and complain, and most do.
<br /><br />? You may be disappointed if you fail. You are doomed if you don't try.
<br /><br />? Intelligence is like a river, the deeper it flows, the less noise it makes.
<br /><br />? You can't have an island of excellence in a sea of indifference.
<br /><br />? One who takes small steps goes fast.
<br /><br />? I am not ashamed to confess that I am ignorant of what I do not know.
<br /><br />? You will become as small as your controlling desire; as great as your dominant aspiration.
<br /><br />? You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it.
<br /><br />? I always view problems as opportunities in work clothes.
<br /><br />? If you don't invest very much, then defeat doesn't hurt very much and winning is not very exciting.
<br /><br />? Good is not good where better is expected.
<br /><br />? The way I see it, if you want a rainbow, you have to put up with the rain.
<br /><br />? The difference between failure and success is doing a thing nearly right and doing a thing exactly right.
<br /><br />? The harder you work, the luckier you get.
<br /><br />? People seldom improve when they have no other model but themselves to copy.
<br /><br />? Don't be afraid to take a big step is one is indicated. You can't cross a chasm in two small jumps.
<br /><br />? Unless you try to do something beyond what you have already mastered, you will never grow.
<br /><br />? Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do.
<br /><br />? Paralyze resistance with persistence.
<br /><br />? The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we are, but in what direction we are moving.
<br /><br />? When one door is shut, another one opened.
<br /><br />? The only limit to ourrealization of tomorrow will be our doubts of today.
<br /><br />? I don't believe in pessimism. If something doesn't come up the way you want, forge ahead. If you think it is going to rain, it will.
<br /><br />? The only time you can't afford to fail is the last time you try.
<br /><br />? Two men look through the same bars; one sees mud and one the stars.
<br /><br />? Anything the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve.
<br /><br />? A great pleasure in life is doing what people say you cannot do.
<br /><br />? The time to repair the roof is when the sun is shining.
<br /><br />? There is a better way for everything. Find it.
<br /><br />? There are times when the greatest change needed is a change of my viewpoint.
<br /><br />? There is no substitute for hard work.
<br /><br />? Do not wish to be anything but what you are and try to be that perfectly.
<br /><br />? Well done is better than well said.
<br /><br />? One of life's most painful moments comes when we must admit that we didn't do our homework, that we are not prepared.
<br /><br />? Talk less think more.
<br /><br />? I am always running late but at least I am always running.
<br /><br />? Sometimes you're ahead, sometimes you're behind. The race is long, and it ends only with you. 
<br /><br />? Nothing is impossible to a willing's heart.
<br /><br />? Where there is a will there is a way. 
<br /><br />? If you can start exploring possibilities, you will start surpassing all known boundaries. 
<br /><br />? Success does not come in a day.
<br /><br />? We can never predict what will happen next moment. 
<br /><br />? Strive to learn something new today. 
<br /><br />? Birth was not our choice. Death will not be our choice. But the way we live our life is our choice. 
<br /><br />? Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is mystery. Today is a gift. That is why it is called &quot;the present&quot;. Live in &quot;the present&quot; and make your life beautiful today.
<br /><br />? Ability can take you to the top, but it takes character to keep you there.
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7075c9093ec14be52dc3f417a228ee85" url=""><![CDATA[guess who<br/><br/>Somebody Bigger Than You And I
<br />Who made the mountain, who made the tree
<br />Who made the river flow out to the sea
<br />Who hung the moon up in the starry sky
<br />Somebody bigger than you and I
<br /><br />Who made the flowers to bloom in the spring
<br />Who writes the song for the robin to sing
<br />Who sends the rain to the earth when it's dry
<br />Somebody bigger than you and I
<br /><br />He lights the way when the road is so long
<br />He keeps you company His love is so strong
<br />With his love their to guide you
<br />He walks there beside you
<br />Just like He walks with me
<br /><br />When I get weary and filled with despair
<br />Who gives me the strength to go on
<br />You know, It's because he does care
<br />And Who gives me the faith which humbles me to cry
<br />There's Somebody bigger, much Bigger than you and I
<br /><br />Bigger than you and I
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="740d455748d9ff847d5a5c34eaf572ab" url=""><![CDATA[GODsends rainbow<br/><br/>Whatever your cross, 
<br />Whatever your pain, 
<br />There will always be sunshine, 
<br />After the rain... 
<br />Perhaps you may stumble, 
<br />Perhaps even fall, 
<br />But God's always ready, 
<br />To answer your call... 
<br />He knows every heartache, 
<br />Sees every tear, 
<br />A word from His lips, 
<br />Can calm every fear... 
<br />Your sorrows may linger, 
<br />Throughout the night, 
<br />But suddenly vanish, 
<br />In dawn's early light... 
<br />The Savior is waiting, 
<br />Somewhere above, 
<br />To give you His grace, 
<br />And send you His love... 
<br />Whatever your cross, 
<br />Whatever your pain, 
<br />&quot;God always sends rainbows... 
<br />After the rain...&quot; 
<br />To get out of difficulty, one must usually go through it! Seeking your favor.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="47660b8132b5d0b6446491fcb2ba3206" url=""><![CDATA[The true way to live the life<br/><br/>Life has it own way to teach us lessons, in each and ever stage of life. It may be through our parents, teacher, friends or anyone whom we don't even know. And lives the rest on us have take it. 
<br />I will give u a very nice example about it, and the way we must take it. 
<br />Everybody in this world have seen the plants growing, they grow on good soil, on rocks, near river side, even on buildings and many other places you will have seen it. But what we have to not it and observe about it that, though it grows in any place its root will absorb only that nutrient which are good for the plant. And its leaves will absorb only the fresh part of the air, which is good for the health and growth of plant. 
<br />The thing I want to say through this msg is that we must absorb the good part of the lesson which the life teaches us,and let the bad part left out of our life. 
<br />This is the true way to live the life.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="151eef8e5bbdb5a35bb658ddcb150d54" url=""><![CDATA[life<br/><br/>The best kind of friend is the kind you can sit on a porch and swing with, 
<br />never say a word, 
<br />and then walk away feeling like it was the best conversation you've ever had . 
<br /><br />It's true that we don't know what we've got until we lose it, 
<br />but it's also true that we don't know what we've been missing until it arrives. 
<br /><br />Giving someone all your love is never an assurance that they'll love you back! 
<br />Don't expect love in return; 
<br />just wait for it to grow in their heart but if it doesn't, 
<br />be content it grew in yours. 
<br />It takes only a minute to get a crush on someone, 
<br />an hour to like someone, 
<br />and a day to love someone, 
<br />but it takes a lifetime to forget someone. 
<br /><br />Don't go for looks; they can deceive. 
<br />Don't go for wealth; even that fades away. 
<br />Go for someone who makes you smile because it takes only a smile to make a dark day seem bright. 
<br />Find the one that makes your heart smile. 
<br /><br />May you have enough happiness to make you sweet, 
<br />enough trials to make you strong, 
<br />enough sorrow to keep you human, enough hope to make you happy. 
<br /><br />Always put yourself in others' shoes. 
<br />If you feel that it hurts you, 
<br />it probably hurts the other person, too 
<br /><br />The happiest of people don't necessarily have the best of everything; 
<br />they just make the most of everything that comes along their way. 
<br /><br />Happiness lies for those who cry, 
<br />those who hurt, those who have searched, 
<br />and those who have tried, 
<br />for only they can appreciate the importance of people who have touched their lives. 
<br /><br />When you were born, 
<br />you were crying and everyone around you was smiling. 
<br />Live your life so that when you die, 
<br />you're the one who is smiling and everyone around you is crying.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="33ede5f462a7ef9200696428c450fe7f" url=""><![CDATA[funda of success full romance<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/hug.gif" alt=":)" />hi,every one !!! 
<br />most of d ppls fall in love bt very few get success in keeping a good relationship with their life partner.i personally do not belive in dominating/interference on my partners personal life. 
<br />what matters is trust,&amp; honestly understanding ur partner bt can u imagine a life without rOmAnCE n specially wen ur engaged so go on rOmAncE.....RoManCE it takes it all see it with new way i bet u it will change u r life !!!! 
<br /><br />1. Watch the sunset together. 
<br />2. Whisper to each other. 
<br />3. Cook for each other. 
<br />4. Walk in the rain. 
<br />5. Hold hands. 
<br />6. Buy gifts for each other. 
<br />7. Roses. 
<br />8. Find out their favorite cologne/perfume and wear it every time you're together. 
<br />9. Go for a long walk down the beach at midnight. 
<br />10. Write poetry for each other 
<br />11. Hugs are the universal medicine. 
<br />12. Say I love you, only when you mean it and make sure they know you mean it. 
<br />13. Give random gifts of flowers/candy/poetry etc. 
<br />14. Tell her that she's the only girl you ever want. Don't lie. 
<br />15. Spend every second possible together. 
<br />16. Look into each other's eyes. 
<br />17. Very lightly push up her chin, look into her eyes, tell her you love her, and kiss her lightly. 
<br />18. When in public, only flirt w/ each other. 
<br />19. Put love notes in their pockets when they aren't looking. 
<br />20. Buy her a ring. 
<br />21. Sing to each other. 
<br />22. Always hold her around her sides. 
<br />23. Take her to dinner and do the dinner for two deal. 
<br />24. Spaghetti? (Ever see Lady and the Tramp 
<br />25. Hold her hand, stare into her eyes, kiss her hand and then put it over our heart. 
<br />26. Dance together. 
<br />27. Let your girl fall asleep with her head in your lap. (It looks real cute) 
<br />28. Do things like write I love you in a note so that they have to look in a mirror to read it. 
<br />29. Make excuses to call them every 5 minutes 
<br />30. Even if you are really busy doing something, go out of your way to call and say I love you. 
<br />31. Call from your vacation spot to tell them you were thinking about them. 
<br />32. Remember your dreams and tell her about them. 
<br />33. Always tell her how pretty she looks. 
<br />34. Tell each other your most sacred secrets/fears. 
<br />35. Be Prince Charming to her parents.(Brownie Points) 
<br />36. Brush her hair out of her face for her. 
<br />37. Hang out with ! his/her friends. (more brownie points) 
<br />38. Go to church/pray/worship together. 
<br />39. Take her to see a romantic movie and remember the parts she liked. 
<br />40. Learn from each other and don't make the same mistake twice. 
<br />41. Describe the joy you feel just to be with him/her. 
<br />42. Make sacrifices for each other. 
<br />43. Really love each other, or don't stay together. 
<br />44. Let there never be a second during any given day that you aren't; thinking about them, and make sure they know it. 
<br />45. Love yourself before you love anyone else. 
<br />46. Learn to say sweet things in foreign languages. 
<br />47. Dedicate songs to them on the radio. 
<br />48. Fall asleep on the phone with each other. 
<br />49. Stand up for them when someone talks trash. 
<br />50. Never forget the kiss goodnight. And always remember to say, &quot;Sweet dreams.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="abb57d16d4a5e87d1fbfb9098c8f17af" url=""><![CDATA[misterious life<br/><br/>[pLife is such a big mystery 
<br />No one knows how to solve it 
<br />If someone gets one clue 
<br />It doesn't mean u r the winner. 
<br /><br />Just a single clue can just make u confused 
<br />And sometimes even more tensed 
<br />Coz' if that clue is negative 
<br />It can make u feel like a sinner. 
<br /><br />The feeling of a winner 
<br />Just vanishes with that of a sinner. 
<br /><br />Don't think about the solution 
<br />Just enjoy the life 
<br />If u doesn't get any clue 
<br />It doesn't mean it's the end of ur life. 
<br /><br />Life will go on and on 
<br />Just in the end 
<br />You will come to know 
<br />If u were a WINNER 
<br />Or if u were a SINNER.... 
<br /><br />DO COMMENT IF U LIKE THE POEM OR NOT.. 
<br />ITS ONE OF MY ORIGINAL POEMS..
<br />uzzled]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ae4f59c85703190ade8b5d6679898efc" url=""><![CDATA[really sad<br/><br/>We said we would be friends till the end 
<br />You said you would always be my friend 
<br />You stabbed be in the back 
<br />now what we had we can't get back 
<br />I see you everyday 
<br />but I still feel the need to pray 
<br />I miss you more and more 
<br />but it can never be like before 
<br />I will love you forever 
<br />But you will never 
<br />I guess you're not the same any more 
<br />but what happened to before 
<br />Did you ever really care 
<br />Did you ever really dare 
<br />you thought it was a game 
<br />so with you lays the blame <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9087a73577d9c37efe41067a07eab1f7" url=""><![CDATA[we should try to reach upto our dreams<br/><br/>An arrow is useless without a target, a journey is pointless without a destination and life is worthless without goals. 
<br /><br />Just like everything in this world is built for a purpose, our own life should be guided by goals. What is the point of putting efforts into anything, if you donâ€™t know what you want or where you want to go? 
<br /><br />Today, before you go to sleep, take time out to think. Think about your dreams. Think about what you really want to do in life. Think about how you can make a difference in this world. And once you get the answers, set goals for yourself. 
<br /><br />Goals can be anything â€“ making X amount of money, reaching Y position in an organization, being a successful entrepreneur, getting famous, doing community service, etc.. Set goals for the long-term and then, formulate short-term goals which will help you reach the long-term ones. And then, all you would need to do to reach these goals is be smart and work hard. 
<br /><br />Setting goals help us in two ways: 
<br /><br />Direction: Goals give direction to our life. Make us work for a reason. And help us achieve what we want. Short-term goals are a road-map to accomplish long-term goals. 
<br /><br />Focus: Goals help us remain focused and prioritize. Often, we tend to forget what we should be doing and fritter away time in doing things that are fruitless and in some cases, detrimental and harmful. Whenever we feel lost, we should just read our goals to get back on track. If circumstances are not as desired, we can modify our short-term goals and work towards them. 
<br /><br />Goals give us a reason to wake up every morning. We should make it a point to write down our goals and read them every day to remind and motivate ourselves. Then, we should have faith and confidence in our ability to accomplish them. And of course, have the determination to continue in spite of challenges. 
<br /><br />If our mind can think of it, we certainly have the ability to do it! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>