<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="32e79705b89c03e84330dcb0f6ab64c" url=""><![CDATA[put this up if ya knw sum 1 who died frm cancer<br/><br/>------00------Please
<br />----00-00----Put This
<br />---00---00---On Your
<br />---00---00---Blog If
<br />---00---00---You Know
<br />----00-00----Someone
<br />-----000-----Who Died
<br />----00-00----Of
<br />---00---00---Cancer
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb3235077137a6ba8ebc927b94e500d6" url=""><![CDATA[plzzzz do this :)<br/><br/>1. Would you be in control?
<br /><br />2. Would you talk dirty to me?
<br /><br />3. Would you kiss me with a little tongue or a lot of tongue?
<br /><br />4. Would you go down on me?
<br /><br />5. Would you giv me a hickie?
<br /><br />6.How many rounds would we go?
<br /><br />7 What would you wanna do afterwards?
<br /><br />8.Would you take off all ur clothes then take mine off slowly?
<br /><br />9 Would you lick and bite me all over?
<br /><br />10. would you like 2 play or get straight to the point?
<br /><br />11 Would you take your time?
<br /><br />12. would you fall asleep with me afta were done?
<br /><br />13. wud u go fast or slow?
<br /><br />14. where wud u wana &quot;do it&quot;?
<br /><br />15. wud u do it2day?
<br /><br />16. wud u do it 2morrow?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="af6a22fabddc51c2dda706d625edf1a0" url=""><![CDATA[GOT UR NUMBA<br/><br/>want your number 
<br /><br />I Don't care who you are but no-one under the age of 16 please. I Bet you won't give it to me.
<br />Name:___________________Number:___________________- - - - Best time to call:__________________I dare you to copy and paste this and see how many numbers you get.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="98405caa57d35212c3836d4da27230dc" url=""><![CDATA[love<br/><br/>If this doesn't touch
<br />u.....you're
<br />heartless...for sure
<br /><br />One night a guy &amp; a girl were driving
<br />home from the movies. The boy sensed
<br />there was something wrong because of
<br />the painful silence they shared
<br />between them that night. The girl then
<br />asked the boy to pull over because she
<br />wanted to talk. She told him that her
<br />feelings had changed &amp; that it was
<br />time to move on. A silent tear slid
<br />down his cheek as he slowly reached
<br />into his pocket &amp; passed her a folded
<br />note. At that moment, a drunk driver
<br />was speeding down that very same
<br />street. He swerved right into the
<br />drivers seat, killing the boy.
<br />Miraculously, the girl survived.
<br />Remembering the note, she pulled it
<br />out &amp; read it.
<br />&quot;Without your love, I would die.&quot;
<br /><br />1st: If u post this on a bulletin in 5
<br />minutes someone special will message
<br />or call you.
<br /><br />2nd: REPOST IF YOU CARE ABOUT SOMEONE
<br />SO MUCH THAT YOU CANT LIVE WITHOUT
<br />THEM!!! &quot;(EVEN YOUR BEST FRIENDS!)&quot;
<br /><br />3rd: REPOST AS &quot; 6 word love letter&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ff2341afbb7cd296efb2cf29e2a52a85" url=""><![CDATA[on a scale of 0-12 wat am i<br/><br/>On a scale from 0-12 what am i? Respond and then post to see what people think about u
<br /><br />12- FUCKABLE
<br />11-GORGEOUS
<br />10-ON FIRE!!!
<br />9-HOT HOT HOT
<br />8-Kinda hot
<br />7-Real pretty
<br />6-Pretty
<br />5-Cute
<br />4-Okay
<br />3-Kinda ugly
<br />2-Ugly
<br />1-Hideous
<br />0-Dont ever talk to me again
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="319e523824dc034bec2a10f299bf02fa" url=""><![CDATA[sad love story<br/><br/>Boy: I missed you at school today, why weren't you there?
<br /><br />Girl- Yeah, I had to go to the doctor.
<br /><br />Boy- Oh really? Why?
<br /><br />Girl- Oh nothing, annual shots, thats all.
<br /><br />Boy- Oh.
<br /><br />Girl- So what did we do in math today?
<br /><br />Boy- You didn't miss anything that great.......just lots of notes.
<br /><br />Girl- Ok, good.
<br /><br />Boy- Yeah
<br /><br />Girl- Hey, I have a question......
<br /><br />Boy- Ok, ask away.
<br /><br />Girl-........How much do you love me?
<br /><br />Boy- You know I love you more than anything.
<br /><br />Girl- Yeah.....
<br /><br />Boy- Why do you ask?
<br /><br />Girl-................&gt;silence&lt;..........
<br /><br />Boy- Is something wrong?
<br /><br />Girl- No, nothing at all.
<br /><br />Goy- Ok, good.
<br /><br />Girl- ..............How much do u care about me?
<br /><br />Boy- I would give you the world in a heartbeat if I could.
<br /><br />Girl- You would?
<br /><br />Boy- Yeah.........of course I would &gt;sounding worried&lt; is there something wrong?
<br /><br />Girl- No, everything is fine......
<br /><br />Boy- Are you sure?
<br /><br />Girl- Yeah.
<br /><br />Boy- Ok.......I hope so.
<br /><br />Girl- ..............Would you die for me?
<br /><br />Boy- I would take a bullet for you anyday, hunny.
<br /><br />Girl- Really?
<br /><br />Boy- Anyday. Now seriously, is there something wrong?
<br /><br />Girl- No, I'm fine, your fine, we're fine, everyones fine.
<br /><br />Boy- ............Ok. If your sure.
<br /><br />Girl-......................Well, I have to go. I'll see you tomorrow at school.
<br /><br />Boy- Alright, bye. I LOVE YOU.
<br /><br />Girl- Yeah, I love you to, bye.
<br /><br />THE NEXT DAY AT SCHOOL:
<br /><br />Boy- Hey, have you seen my girlfriend today?
<br /><br />Friend- No
<br /><br />Boy- Oh. Ok.
<br /><br />Friend- She wasn't here yesterday either.
<br /><br />Boy- I know, she was acting all wierd on the phone last night.
<br /><br />Friend- Well dude, you know how girls are sometimes.
<br /><br />Boy- Yeah........but not her.
<br /><br />Friend- I don't know what else to say, man.
<br /><br />Boy- Ok, well I gotta get to english, I'll see you after school.
<br /><br />Friend- Yeah, I gotta get to science, talk to you later.
<br /><br />THAT NIGHT:
<br /><br />-ring-
<br />-ring-
<br />-ring-
<br />-ring-
<br />Girl- Hello?
<br /><br />Boy- Hey.
<br /><br />Girl- Oh, hi.
<br /><br />Boy- Why weren't you at school today?
<br /><br />Girl- Uh.......I had another doctor appointment.
<br /><br />Boy- Are you sick?
<br /><br />Girl- ..................Um I have to go, my mom's calling on my other line.
<br /><br />Boy- I'll wait.
<br /><br />Girl- It may take a while, I'll call you later.
<br /><br />Boy-........Alright, I love you hunny.
<br /><br />very long pause&lt;
<br /><br />Girl- (with tear in her eye) Look, I think we should break up.
<br /><br />Boy- What?
<br /><br />Girl- Its the best thing for us right now.
<br /><br />Boy- Why?
<br /><br />Girl- I love you.
<br />click&lt;
<br /><br />THE GIRL DOESNT COME TO SCHOOL FOR 3 MORE WEEKS, AND DOESNT ANSWER HER PHONE.
<br /><br />Boy- Hey dude.
<br /><br />Friend- Hey.
<br /><br />Boy- Whats up?
<br /><br />Friend- Nothing much. Hey have you talked to your ex lately?
<br /><br />Boy- No.
<br /><br />Friend- So you didn't hear?
<br /><br />Boy- Hear what?
<br /><br />Friend- Um, well, I don't know if I should be the one to tell you......
<br /><br />Boy- Dude, tell me!
<br /><br />Friend- Uh....call this number....433-555-3468
<br /><br />Boy- Ok............
<br /><br />BOY CALLS NUMBER AFTER SCHOOL
<br /><br />-ring-
<br />-ring-
<br />-ring-
<br />Voice- Hello, Suppam County Hospital, this is nurse Beckam.
<br /><br />Boy- Uh.......I must have the wrong number, I'm looking for my friend.
<br /><br />Voice- What is her name, sir?
<br />(boy gives info)
<br /><br />Voice- Yes, this is the right number, she is one of our patients here.
<br /><br />Boy- really? Why? What happened? How is she?
<br /><br />Voice- Her room number is ..646, in building A, suite 3.
<br /><br />Boy- WHAT HAPPENED?!
<br /><br />Voice- Please come by sir and you can see her, goodbye.
<br /><br />Boy- WAIT! NO!
<br />*dial tone*
<br /><br />BOY GOES TO HOSPITAL, AND TO ROOM ..646, BUILDING A, SUITE 3. GIRL IS LYING IN THE HOSPITAL BED.
<br /><br />Boy- Oh my God! Are you ok?
<br /><br />Girl- ..................
<br /><br />Boy- Sweetie! Talk to me!
<br /><br />Girl- I..........
<br /><br />Boy- You what? YOU WHAT?
<br /><br />Girl- I have cancer and I'm on life support.
<br /><br />Boy- .....................&gt;breaks into tears&lt;......................
<br /><br />Girl- They're taking me off tonight.
<br /><br />Boy- Why?
<br /><br />Girl- I wanted to tell you but I couldn't.
<br /><br />Boy- Why not?
<br /><br />Girl- I didn't want to hurt you.
<br /><br />Boy- You could never hurt me sweetheart.
<br /><br />Girl- I just wanted to see if you felt about me as the same I felt about you.
<br /><br />Boy- ?
<br /><br />Girl- I love you more than anything, I would give you the world in a heartbeat. I would die for you and take a bullet for you.
<br /><br />Boy- ...........
<br /><br />Girl- Don't be sad, I love you, and I'll always be here with you.
<br /><br />Boy- Then why'd you break up with me?
<br /><br />Nurse- Young man, visiting hours are over.
<br /><br />BOY LEAVES, GIRL IS TAKEN OFF LIFE SUPPORT, AND DIES.
<br /><br />But what the boy didn't know is that the girl only asked him those questions so she could hear him say it one last time, and she only broke up with him because she knew she only had 3 more weeks to live, and thought it would cause him less pain and give him time to get over her before she died.
<br /><br />NEXT DAY
<br /><br />The boy is found dead with a gun in his hand..with a note in the other...
<br />THE NOTE SAID:I told her I would take a bullet for her....just like she said she would die for me... 
<br /><br />Copy and paste this if you cryed at this story..If you didn't cry, copy and paste it anyway. Why? Because the girl and the boy would have wanted that. And, because I said so
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cdc9a8ea5d4f1705a73af89bb0fe3047" url=""><![CDATA[girl and boy facts<br/><br/>Girl facts...x:
<br /><br />When you catch a girl
<br />glancing at you,
<br />she wants you to look
<br />back and smile...x
<br /><br />When a girl bumps into your arm
<br />while walking with you
<br />she wants
<br />you to hold her hand...x
<br /><br />When she wants a hug
<br />she will just stand there...x
<br /><br />When u break a girls heart
<br />she still feels it when
<br />you run into each other 3 years later...x
<br /><br />When a girl is quiet,
<br />millions of things are running through her
<br />mind...x
<br /><br />When a girl is not arguing,
<br />she is thinking deeply...x
<br /><br />When a girl looks at you with eyes full of
<br />questions,
<br />she is wondering how long you will be
<br />around...x
<br /><br />When a girl answers, &quot;I'm fine,&quot; after a
<br />few seconds,
<br />she is not at all fine...x
<br /><br />When a girl stares at you,
<br />she is wondering why you are playing games...x
<br /><br />When a girl lays her head on your chest,
<br />she is wishing for you to be hers forever...x
<br /><br />When a girl says she can't live
<br />without you,
<br />she has made up her mind that you are
<br />her future...x
<br /><br />When a girl says, &quot;I miss you,&quot;
<br />no one in this world can miss you more
<br />than that...x
<br /><br />When a girl is mean to you after a break-up
<br />she wants you back, but shes
<br />scared she'll get hurt and knows
<br />you're gone forever...x
<br /><br />Guy Facts...x:
<br /><br />When a guy calls you,
<br />he wants to be with you...x
<br /><br />When a guy is quiet,
<br />He's listening to you...x
<br /><br />When a guy is not arguing,
<br />He realizes he's wrong...x
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I'm fine.&quot; after a few
<br />minutes
<br />he means it...x
<br /><br />When a guy stares at you,
<br />he wishes you would care about him and
<br />wonders if you do...x
<br /><br />When your laying your head on a guy's
<br />chest,
<br />he has the world...x
<br /><br />When a guy calls/texts/comments you everyday,
<br />he is in love...x
<br /><br />When a (good) guy tells you he loves you,
<br />he means it...x
<br /><br />When a guy says he can't live without you,
<br />he's with you til your done...x
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I miss you,&quot;
<br />he misses you more than you could have
<br />ever missed him or anything else...x
<br /><br />repost this in 10 minutes and your true
<br />love will
<br />call you
<br /><br />someone was in your mind as you read this??
<br /><br />Post this as
<br /><br />IF YOUR A GUY &quot; When a guy misses you...&quot;
<br /><br />AND
<br /><br />IF YOUR A GIRL POST IT AS &quot;When a girl misses you...&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="22ba60dcbd3ddeef370b79ebfac5f636" url=""><![CDATA[what a kiss really means...<br/><br/>What a kiss really means...
<br /><br />*Kiss on the stomach-----&quot;lets have sex&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Forehead ----&quot;Forever you will be mine&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Ear ---&quot;I'm horny&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Cheek ---&quot;We're friends&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Hand ---&quot;I adore you&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Neck ---&quot;We belong together&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Shoulder ---&quot;I want you&quot;
<br />*Kiss on the Lips ---&quot;I love you&quot; OR &quot;I want you&quot;
<br /><br />**Kiss on each finger---- &quot;I love every part of you&quot;
<br />**Kiss on the chest-----&quot;Stay tonight&quot;
<br />**Kiss on the nose----- &quot;You're silly, and I love that&quot;
<br />**Smile Kisses (when you smile while you kiss)---&quot;Wow, you're amazing. I love this feeling&quot;
<br />**Kissing with your eyes closed--- &quot;I am yours&quot;
<br />** Kissing with your eyes open----&quot;How am I doing? -OR- I want to see you smile as we kiss&quot;
<br /><br />What the gesture means...
<br />*Holding Hands ---&quot;We can learn to love each other&quot;
<br /><br />-Edit: There are different kinds of hand holding.
<br />* Holding hands loose: I'm not in the mood
<br />* Holding hands tight, fingers together: You're my partner and the one I want by my side
<br />* Holding hands tight, fingers interlocked: We have something amazing and wonderful, and I'm happy to just stay in this moment forever
<br /><br />*Slap on the Butt ---&quot;That's mine&quot;
<br />*Playing with the Ear ---&quot;I can't live without you&quot;
<br />*Holding on tight ---&quot;Don't let go&quot;
<br />*Looking into each other's Eyes ---&quot;Don't leave me&quot;
<br />*Playing with Hair on Head ---&quot;Tell me you love me&quot;
<br />*Arms around the Waist ---&quot;I love you too much to let go&quot;
<br />*Laughing while Kissing ---&quot;I am completely Comfortable with you&quot;
<br /><br />**Kissing then Wrestling--- &quot;Ah, ha! You want me? Come and get me!&quot;
<br />**Laying your head on his/her chest and holding hands--&quot;This is a perfect moment. Let's pretend time can stop and we can just be together&quot;
<br /><br />--Advice--
<br />*Don't ask for a kiss, take one.
<br />*If you were thinking about someone while reading this, you're definitely in Love.
<br /><br />--Requirements--
<br />*Post this again after reading!! Or you will have a bad year of Relationships.
<br /><br />If you LIKE, LOVE, OR MISS someone right now and can't get them out of your head then Re-post this within One Minute and Whoever you are missing will surprise you. Repost this as &quot;What a kiss means&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="53d5499c1fd10d4c6e4fdceddf47f178" url=""><![CDATA[ill kill any guy who does this to my girl or any girl<br/><br/>If any guy has done this they need shooting!
<br />your views please?
<br /><br />Guy: &quot;Can we have sex right now?
<br /><br />Girl: &quot;Can we do what?&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: &quot;You know, can I be your first, finally?&quot;
<br /><br />Girl: &quot;Um.....no.&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: &quot;Why?&quot;
<br /><br />Girl: &quot;Because, you have a girlfriend, who happens to be my friend.......&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: &quot;So, if you don't tell, I won't tell.&quot;
<br /><br />Girl: &quot;Besides that, I'm waiting for someone special. Someone that I want to be with for the rest of my life to be my first.&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: &quot;I'm not special to you?&quot;
<br /><br />Girl: &quot;You're my friend. That's all.&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: looks forward and keeps driving.
<br /><br />5 minutes pass.......
<br /><br />Guy: starts to run his hand up the girl's thigh.
<br /><br />Girl: moves his hand, &quot;Don't touch me.&quot;.
<br /><br />Guy: tries to kiss her.
<br /><br />Girl: screams, &quot;Would you stop.&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: continues trying.
<br /><br />Girl: moves to the back seat
<br /><br />Guy: parks on an abandoned street and gets in the backseat with the girl.he starts to kiss her.
<br /><br />Girl: pushes him off and scoots over, &quot;Please, don't do this.&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: &quot;Don't do what, I know you want it, I can see it in your eyes.&quot; Moves over to her and starts to unbutton her pants.
<br /><br />Girl: pushes him harder and says, &quot;No, don't.&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: getting aggravated, punches her and tells her to stop &quot;playing hard to get&quot;.
<br /><br />Girl: crying, continues to fight.
<br /><br />Guy: punches her harder, pulls her pants off, and holds her down.
<br /><br />Girl: screams as he penetrates her, &quot;NO, please don't do this to me!&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: puts his hand over her mouth.
<br /><br />An hour passes.........
<br /><br />TinkAnika (8:00:35 PM): Guy: pulls back and wipes himself off.
<br /><br />Girl: sits on the corner of the seat, crying.
<br /><br />Guy: looks at her and says, &quot;You better not tell anybody about this. If you're really my friend, you won't tell anybody about this. You know I love you.&quot; He reaches out his hand to touch her cheek.
<br /><br />Girl: pulls back, &quot;Just take me home, now.&quot;
<br /><br />Guy: says, &quot;Alright.&quot; Gets in the front seat and drives her home.
<br /><br />2 months later.........
<br /><br />Girl: &quot;Doctor, what's wrong with me. I haven't had my time of the month in 2 months.&quot;
<br /><br />Doctor: looks at her, &quot;You haven't been having your &quot;time&quot; for a reason.&quot;
<br /><br />Girl: looks at him and says, &quot;Why?&quot; dreading the answer that she was sure to receive.
<br /><br />Doctor: &quot;You are pregnant.&quot;
<br /><br />Girl: faints.
<br /><br />The story gets out that she is pregnant, and people start looking to the Guy. He claims that it isn't his because she was sleeping with every guy in the school(which was a lie). He goes to her and tells her, &quot;I'm telling you, if you lie to people and say that I raped you, I'll kill you.&quot;
<br /><br />The Girl is completely devastated. First, he took her virginity and got her pregnant....then he lied about it. So completely depressed......the girl commits suicide by drug overdose.......
<br /><br />Girls, if this story touched you, repost it as &quot;No means no&quot;
<br /><br />Guys, if this story pisses you off, repost it as &quot;I'll kill any fucker who does this to my girl or any girl
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f4235e85bb0632f088b31a15f078a66e" url=""><![CDATA[my fine is £490 ooops lol<br/><br/>This is fun to do. Just read the 'offence' and if you've done it, you owe that fine. Keep going until you've read each 'offence' and added up your total fine. When you are done post this as: &quot;My fine is £...&quot; 
<br />You don't have to confess your answers, just the amount of your fine 
<br /><br />Smoked pot -- £10 
<br />Did acid -- £5 
<br />Ever had sex at church -- £25 
<br />Woke up in the morning and did not know the person who was next to you -- £40 
<br />Had sex with someone on MySpace -- £25 
<br />Had sex for money -- £100 
<br />Ever had sex with a Puerto Rican -- £20 
<br />Vandalized something -- £20 
<br />Had sex on your parents' bed -- £10 
<br />Beat up someone -- £20 
<br />Been jumped -- £10 
<br />Cross dressed -- £10 
<br />Given money to stripper -- £25 
<br />Been in love with a stripper -- £20 
<br />Kissed someone who's name you didn't know -- £10 
<br />Hit on some one of the same sex while at work -- £15 
<br />Ever drive and drank -- £20 
<br />Ever got drunk at work, or went to work while still drunk -- £50 
<br />Used toys while having sex -- £30 
<br />Got drunk, passed out and don't remember the night before -- £20 
<br />Went skinny dipping -- £5 
<br />Had sex in a pool -- £20 
<br />Kissed someone of the same sex -- £10 
<br />Had sex with someone of the same sex -- £20 
<br />Cheated on your significant other -- £10 
<br />Masturbated -- £10 
<br />Cheated on your significant other with their relative or close friend -- £20 
<br />Done oral -- £5 
<br />Got oral -- £5 
<br />Done / got oral in a car while it was moving -- £25 
<br />Stole something -- £10 
<br />Had sex with someone in jail -- £25 
<br />Made a nasty home video -- £15 
<br />Had a threesome -- £50 
<br />Had sex in the wild -- £20 
<br />Been in the same room while someone was having sex --£25 
<br />Stole something worth over more than a hundred dollars-- £20 
<br />Had sex with someone 10 years older -- £20 
<br />Had sex with someone under 21 and you are over 27 -- £25 
<br />Been in love with two people or more at the same time-- £50 
<br />Said you love someone but didn't mean it -- £25 
<br />Went streaking -- £5 
<br />Went streaking in broad daylight -- £15 
<br />Been arrested -- £5 
<br />Spent time in jail -- £15 
<br />Peed in the pool -- £5 
<br />Played spin the bottle -- £5 
<br />Done something you regret -- £20 
<br />Had sex with your best friend -- £20 
<br />Had sex with someone you work with at work -- £25 
<br />Had anal sex -- £80 
<br />Lied to your mate -- £5 
<br />Lied to your mate about the sex being good -- £25 
<br /><br />Tally it up and title it: &quot;My Fine Is...&quot; copy and paste, then repost as a new bulletin
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4eb28ccbbe799e6a065ec75582bce4a4" url=""><![CDATA[to all da playa's out there<br/><br/>Boyz Read 
<br />Galz Read 
<br /><br />I See All These Blogs Day In And Day Owt On The Spotlite And Most Them Happen To Be About Boyz And The Way They Treat Galz Etc And All The Galz Writing On Them Saying Boyz This Boyz That And That There All The Same Liar's Cheats Etc. 
<br /><br />But At The End Of The Day Yeh Galz Are Just As Bad Fair Enough There Not As Bad But Yhu See Galz With The Nice Guys (And Yes There Are Some Owt There Just Gotta Look Hard) But Yhu See All These Galz With The Nice One's And All They Wanna Do Is Play Cheat And Lie To Them. 
<br /><br />No Boy Or Girl Shuld Be Treated Like That. Both Us Boyz And Yhu Galz Shuld Be Treated Right Wiv The Same Amount Of Respect And Love That Yhu Shuld Get. 
<br /><br />To All The Playa'z Owt There Boyz And Galz Stop All This Playin Shizzle Thinkin Yhur All Hard And Kool Coz Yhu Get A Few Different People Each Nite Its Makes Me Sick Tbh.Love Isnt Bowt Havin 'Sex' Wiv Half The Teenage Population Everynyt Or 2. Its About Showin Yhur Boyfriend/Girlfriend The True Meanin Of Love Wiv Respect, Trust And Yhur Heart. 
<br /><br />If Yhu Ent Got Them 3 Things Yhur Gunna Get Nowere In A Relationship Buh That's Down To Yhu.But To All Them Good People Just Keep To What Yhur Doin And Yhull Find The Rite Guy/Gal That's Nice Caring And Lovin If Yhu Havent Already. 
<br /><br />If Yhu Show Yhur Ovahalf's How Much Yhu Love Them With These 3 Things Then They Will Realize It And They Then Will Give It Back To Yhu, Myt Take A Wile For Them To Give It Back But Just Be Patient And Yhu Will Have It Returned. But Most Important Thing In A Relationship Is Trust If Yhu Ent Got It Yhur Gunna Fail (N) 
<br /><br />But To All The Good Boyz And Galz Owt There I Wish Yhu Luck In Findin The Right Person =] If Yhur A Playa Read Diz Learn It And Sort It Owt And Join Us Good People Coz Its Just Sick And Wrong To Do Wa Yhur Doin. 
<br /><br />And I Ent Rote This Coz Im A Nasty Person Or Nowt I Just Rote It Coz I Want Playa'z To Realize That Its Not Rite To Be A Playa And Thats There's More To A Relationship Then Just 'Sex'.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cd4cc43f37643a9d997864531215795f" url=""><![CDATA[do this please :D<br/><br/>How old do I look? 
<br />[ ] 11 
<br />[ ] 12 
<br />[ ] 13 
<br />[ ] 14 
<br />[ ] 15 
<br />[ ] 16 
<br />[ ] 17 
<br />[ ] 18 
<br />[ ] 19 
<br />[ ] 20 
<br />[ ] 21 
<br /><br />How good do i look from 1-10 (1-ugly / 10-HoTT) 
<br />[ ] 1 
<br />[ ] 2 
<br />[ ] 3 
<br />[ ] 4 
<br />[ ] 5 
<br />[ ] 6 
<br />[ ] 7 
<br />[ ] 8 
<br />[ ] 9 
<br />[ ] 10 
<br /><br />Would you rather.. 
<br />[ ] Do me 
<br />Or 
<br />[ ] Date me 
<br /><br />Would you rather be on top or bottom? 
<br />[ ] Top 
<br />[ ] Bottom 
<br /><br />Do I have pretty eyes? 
<br />[ ] Yes 
<br />[ ] No 
<br /><br />Do you like my body? 
<br />[ ] Yes 
<br />[ ] No 
<br /><br />Would you be sad if I moved? 
<br />[ ] Yes 
<br />[ ] No 
<br /><br />Would you come visit me? 
<br />[ ] Yes 
<br />[ ] No 
<br /><br />Am I.. 
<br />[ ] Hott 
<br />[ ] Beautiful 
<br />[ ] Sexy 
<br />[ ] Cute 
<br />[ ] beastly mongrel 
<br /><br />Would you rather.. 
<br />[ ] Makeout 
<br />[ ] Cuddle 
<br />[ ] Fuck 
<br />[ ] Go out 
<br /><br />Do you want to go out with me? 
<br />[ ] Yes 
<br />[ ] No 
<br /><br />Would you give me your number? 
<br />[ ] Yes &lt;-- Dropp Yah Numba =P 
<br />[ ] No 
<br /><br />Are you going to repost this so I can answer for YOU? 
<br />[ ] Yes 
<br />[ ] No
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>