<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="13">
		<document id="463bb3aca8517460933463e6a4e3c64b" url=""><![CDATA[Bothered By Hemorrhoids? Read This Helpful Piece<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQvZ3JlYXQtdGlwcy1mb3ItdHJlYXRpbmctYW5kLXByZXZlbnRpbmctaGVtb3JyaG9pZHMtMy8_" target="_blank">Check out this site over here now.</a><br /><br />Are you looking for hemorrhoid tips? You want to find the most helpful information for this uncomfortable condition. The below article will provide you with this needed information.<br /><br />Add lemon to your water if you are experiencing hemorrhoids. Lemons can help you because they thin the bloodstream and reduce inflammation that may be causing you discomfort. A simple glass or two of lemon water throughout the day can leave you feeling great.<br /><br />If you have hemorrhoids, lifting heavy objects will only make things worse. Any activity that causes pressure on your veins can cause more swelling, which, will cause more discomfort and pain.<br /><br />You can use cream to relieve yourself, but don't use it all that often. While they don't actually provide any treatment, they do slightly numb the affected area. Without prior approval from your doctor, you should use these creams for no longer than a week. When you use them more than you should, you can actually increase your risk of pain.<br /><br />To reduce the pain associated with hemorrhoids, try to avoid consuming foods that cause excess gas. Passing gas could cause painful inflammations. You will feel that burning discomfort if you eat gas-causing foods, so avoid them.<br /><br />Use ice to stop hemorrhoid pain. Hemorrhoids usually involve a lot of discomfort and pain. An ice pack will help reduce the swelling and pain. Alternate ice packs and warm compresses. If you relax in a nice warm bath, and use an ice pack when you're out of the bath, the swelling of your hemorrhoids will go down, and you'll be much more comfortable.<br /><br />Eat whole wheat bread to facilitate the digestive process. This will also reduce skin irritation. Whether you're eating a big plate of spaghetti or a submarine sandwich, opting for whole wheat is a smart choice.<br /><br />Don't loiter on the toilet. Sit only when you're ready to go. If you use the time to catch up on your reading, you may not notice that you are straining to go at the same time. The act of sitting alone is enough to put strain on your hemorrhoids via gravity. Never sit down unless you're really ready to go.<br /><br />The most important thing you can do to prevent hemorrhoids is to avoid straining during bowel movements. Straining also makes existing ones worse. If adding more fiber to your diet is not enough, place your feet on a stepstool during bowel movements. This makes the bowel easier to pass since you're now in a squatting position.<br /><br />If you have some olive oil in the kitchen, then you have a great hemorrhoid home remedy. It may sound unbelievable, but olive oil can help you relieve the pain and swelling of hemorrhoids. However, only use olive oil to treat external hemorrhoids. It's not for use on the internal hemorrhoids.<br /><br />Add more fiber rich foods to your diet. Some foods that are full of fiber are fruits and vegetables, whole grains, brown rice, and seeds. Generally, eating a healthy diet reduces the risk of hemorrhoid formation.<br /><br />This information can prove to be very valuable when dealing with or trying to prevent future flare ups. Use the hints provided along with your doctor's advice to help ease your hemorrhoid pain and discomfort.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4d9a9070443bb5879f318a2cbe4cae49" url=""><![CDATA[Manage Your Hemorrhoids With These Helpful Tips<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQvdGhpbmdzLXRoYXQteW91LXNob3VsZC1rbm93LWFib3V0LWhlbW9ycmhvaWRzLw__" target="_blank">How To Treat Hemorrhoids at Home</a><br /><br />There's no way around it; hemorrhoids are just about the most unpleasant thing ever. Keep reading for ideas and tips that will help you to prevent or treat this uncomfortable, embarrassing condition. Although it may seem that there is no end in sight, take heart in knowing that there are a variety of treatment options.<br /><br />Eat a diet that is rich in high fiber foods. More fiber equates to softer stools. This allows you to use less force on the commode, therefore minimizing pain and discomfort that occurs with straining and pushing. Supplements, fruits, and vegetables can all be beneficial sources of fiber.<br /><br />If you are a hemorrhoid sufferer, take stool softeners or laxatives on a regular basis. If forceful effort is required for your bowel movements, then you're giving yourself more pain than you need and might even be opening the door to more issues.<br /><br />The scratching of hemorrhoids must not be something that you do. Itchiness is the most infuriating symptom of hemorrhoids! The normal reaction is to scratch the itch because it makes you feel better for a short time, but it can delay the healing process for your hemorrhoids. Hemorrhoid sufferers should concentrate on more effective treatments and avoid the urge to scratch.<br /><br />You can actually very gently push some of your hemorrhoids right back inside your anus. If your hemorrhoids have not expanded too much, they should fit inside. This prevents you from rubbing them on your clothing when you sit and keeps them from being injured. If this hurts too much, your hemorrhoids might be too big.<br /><br />A lot of people become surprised when they discover that something as simple as water can soothe their hemorrhoids. Soak the anal region in a warm bath for 10 minutes per day, and apply a cold compress made by soaking a towel in cold water. There are toilet baths that you can buy in any drug store.<br /><br />Although it is common for hemorrhoids to cause blood after a bowel movement, it is always a good idea to consult your doctor to rule out all other possible causes. Traces of blood in your stool may also indicate a more troubling condition, one of which is rectal cancer. Move forward by having a doctor diagnose the condition. Your doctor can tell you the exact cause of your rectal bleeding. Hopefully, it's nothing more serious than hemorrhoids; if so, your doctor can prescribe a medication or other treatment for you.<br /><br />Ensure you're getting plenty of water if you're trying to prevent hemorrhoids from bothering you. To make sure your stools stay soft and loose, drink a minimum of eight glasses of non-alcoholic beverages every day.<br /><br />Perhaps the most effective method for preventing hemorrhoids is also extremely simple. When you have to defecate, don't ignore it. Allowing feces to stick around in the large intestine causes the body to absorb water, which means additional strain is required to get rid of the feces. Straining can cause hemorrhoids to strain, so it should be avoided at all costs.<br /><br />One of the biggest causes of hemorrhoids is having to push hard when trying to have a bowel movement. It can also worsen existing ones. Try increasing the amount of fiber you consume, and keep yourself well-hydrated. Also, consider using a low stool to rest your feet on while you are using the toilet. This brings your body into a squatting position, which often helps you to have a bowel movement.<br /><br />If your hemorrhoids have swollen to the point where they are outside your body, try stuffing them back inside. Make sure to use clean hands in order to prevent bacteria and excess inflammation around the hemorrhoid. If you have experienced an emerging hemorrhoid and, at least temporarily, pushed it back inside, it is important that you immediately consult with your doctor.<br /><br />Bread made of whole wheat is good to eat because it aids digestion and helps hemorrhoid issues. It may lessen the redness and skin irritation. Whether you're eating a big plate of spaghetti or a submarine sandwich, opting for whole wheat is a smart choice.<br /><br />Try squatting when you go to the toilet rather than sitting upon the seat. It will make the movement pass easier, plus it will stop painful flare-ups of hemorrhoids. It can be awkward in the beginning, but you will get used to it and notice that you aren't in as much pain anymore.<br /><br />As said earlier, hemorrhoids are a very common medical ailment and can almost always be treated at home without a doctor's intervention. By keeping the things you need in your house, you can make sure the attacks aren't as bad. Applying the guidelines that you have just read allows you to opt for treatment in the comfort of your own home.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7eb6b4570961a612e8f33aac7a5ef6e7" url=""><![CDATA[Causes And Cures Of A Hemorroid Flare Up<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQvaXQtaXMtcG9zc2libGUtdG8tdHJlYXQtaGVtb3JyaG9pZHMteW91cnNlbGYv" target="_blank">Click this link right here now.</a><br /><br />Home treatments are widely available and include topical creams, medicated wipes and warm sitz baths. Good prevention techniques include drinking more water, taking stool softeners, and incorporating more fiber into your diet. This article will also help you contend with external hemorrhoids.<br /><br />Drink enough water to stay hydrated and supplement your diet with high fiber items if you suffer from hemorrhoids. When you soften your stool, you can help relieve any hemorrhoids that might be causing you stress and pain. You can ingest simple fruits,such as melons and papaya, to soften your stool and get it moving. Fiber-rich vegetables, such as okra and cabbage, can also be very beneficial. Also, be sure to stay hydrated by drinking lots of water.<br /><br />If you cannot get enough fiber through your food, add a fiber supplement to your daily routine. Many fiber supplements are powders that you can add to water, juice, or other beverages. Most drug stores sell these kinds of supplements. In order to prevent the likelihood of hemorrhoids, make this drink during your morning routine.<br /><br />Stay hydrated. For you to keep stools soft and loose, you should be drinking at the very least eight glasses of water.<br /><br />A good tip to help you avoid getting hemorrhoids is to try exercising the anus. If you do not use these muscle often, the blood flow to them may be restricted. This lowered blood flow can cause hemorrhoids. Take five minutes each day, every three to four hours, to flex your anus muscles, making sure to hold this position for at least five seconds before releasing.<br /><br />It can be difficult to clean yourself properly when you have hemorrhoids, but doing so is a critical part of personal hygiene. Moist wipes are a better alternative to toilet paper due to the fact that they feel better and achieve a better clean. Hemorrhoid swelling and pain can be relieved by a sitz bath of warm water. About 20 minutes of soaking should provide some relief.<br /><br />Adding vitamin A to your diet can help with pain and swollen veins from hemorrhoids. Carrots have tons of vitamin A in them, so eating them or drinking their juice is a fast way to get the amount needed to fight hemorrhoids.<br /><br />To help you deal with hemorrhoid symptoms, include items like whole grains, fruit and vegetables in your diet. By keeping your diet simple and well-rounded, the easier it becomes to manage your condition.<br /><br />Olive oil is a cheap home treatment for hemorrhoids. The oil itself can reduce itching and swelling of the hemorrhoids. Of course, this only applies to the treatment of external hemorrhoids. This method of treatment is not for use internally.<br /><br />One hemorrhoid prevention method is surprisingly simple. Don't delay moving your bowels. Water is constantly reabsorbed from stool as long as it remains in your system. As a result, ignoring the need to defecate causes the stool to become drier and harder, which will require additional straining when you do go. Straining exacerbates hemorrhoids and should be avoided.<br /><br />One home remedy for hemorrhoids is the use of olive oil. Olive oil has been known to alleviate the discomfort of hemorrhoids and reduce their swelling. Only use olive oil on hemorrhoids that are on the outside of your body. It's not for use on the internal hemorrhoids.<br /><br />While the cause is most likely hemorrhoids, you should always consult with your doctor. There are much more serious causes of bloody stools, such as cancer, which should be ruled out. Save yourself the anxiety and grief by scheduling an appointment with your doctor. Your doctor can tell you the exact cause of your rectal bleeding. Hopefully, it's nothing more serious than hemorrhoids; if so, your doctor can prescribe a medication or other treatment for you.<br /><br />Because you've now learned some excellent tips for preventing and treating hemorrhoids, it's likely that you're on the right path towards avoiding this very discomforting condition. Implement these hints and tips to minimize your risk of developing this condition in the future.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1110bca34e52d821ce585169f997f6f2" url=""><![CDATA[Natural Cures For The Occurance Of Hemorriods<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQvbGl2aW5nLXdpdGgtaGVtb3JyaG9pZHMtY2FuLWJlLXBhaW5mdWwtYW5kLWlycml0YXRpbmcv" target="_blank">Click this link over here now.</a><br /><br />Hemorrhoids are a painful condition. They can, however, be treated at home using a number of inexpensive options. Wipes, including some containing witch hazel, can be used when cleaning the area. This article provides useful suggestions for coping with the painful and irritating symptoms of hemorrhoids, and some tips for prevention as well.<br /><br />It is common to use slices of tomatoes to shrink hemorrhoids. The acid contained in tomatoes is terrific for reducing vein swelling. If can curb the effects of hemorrhoids, if you also eat healthily.<br /><br />Eat foods that are high in fiber. This will make your stool much softer. You body will be able to rid itself of soft stool with ease, which will help to avoid some of the pain that comes from having a bowel movement when you have hemorrhoids. There are supplements that contain fiber that can be purchased and used as a stool softener.<br /><br />Swelling of hemorrhoid tissue and the associated pain can often be alleviated with a warm sitz bath. Fill the tub between six and twelve inches high with water. Doing so should help strengthen blood flow and alleviate some of the pain. Keep your knees bent while you sit. You want to give yourself enough time to let the water cool down before you leave.<br /><br />When soaking your hemorrhoids in a bath, keep your knees bent and your feet pulled back towards your thighs. Warm water helps inflammation and swelling go down and helps relieve pain associated with hemorrhoids. Warm water allows the flow of blood to your hemorrhoids, lessening the pain and swelling. Take these baths as often as you want, and you should quickly see some relief.<br /><br />If your hemorrhoids are manageable, try to push them back inside your body. Doing so should reduce the pain you feel when sitting and will also serve to protect the hemorrhoid from injury, which can lead to irritation, swelling and bleeding. Remember to be gentle, do not try too hard or you might make it worse.<br /><br />Some foods produce more gas than do others, and this can be a complicating factor when you have hemorrhoids. Passing gas can strain the rectum and cause hemorrhoid inflammation. There is nothing worse than the burning discomfort from the foods that cause gas, so steer clear of them.<br /><br />The purchase of a donut cushion is something anyone suffering hemorrhoids should think about. This type of cushion supports your rear end while minimizing pressure in the hemorrhoid region. You sit on this cushion, and you will then be much more comfortable and relaxed than just sitting elsewhere without the added cushioning.<br /><br />Having a bit of caffeine can not only make you more alert, but it can help with hemorrhoids. Caffeine can stimulate your bowels and help prevent constipation or stiff stool, which can both lead to hemorrhoids.<br /><br />The scratching of hemorrhoids must not be something that you do. Itching can be the most annoying and uncomfortable symptom that comes as a result of hemorrhoids. The normal reaction is to scratch the itch because it makes you feel better for a short time, but it can delay the healing process for your hemorrhoids. Use treatments to actually cure the problem instead of just placating the itch.<br /><br />If your goal is to keep hemorrhoids at bay, make sure that you are adequately and properly hydrating your body! In order to keep your stools loose and soft, make sure that you are drinking at least eight glasses of water and other non-alcoholic beverages each and every day.<br /><br />An enema will cut down on the amount of hemorrhoid pain you are experiencing. Soak two cloves of diced garlic in two cups of water that is boiling for thirty minutes. Once the water has cooled to room temperature, it is ready to use. The recommended treatment plan is one garlic enema per day.<br /><br />The very private nature of hemorrhoids' affected areas makes it very difficult for many adults to openly seek advice from their friends or families. Fortunately, the information that you have just read is sure to answer at least a few of your questions about the symptoms and treatments that are associated with hemorrhoids.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4ef1a8d2382d82c43405d585dee8abca" url=""><![CDATA[Tips To Help Your Soothe The Agony Of Hemorrhoids<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQvaGVtb3JyaG9pZHMtYWN0aW5nLXVwLWNoZWNrLW91dC10aGVzZS10aXBzLw__" target="_blank">Check out this site right here.</a><br /><br />Hemorrhoids are a condition that affects people from all walks of life. People often ignore hemorrhoids or don't know how to relieve the pain and itching because nobody's ever given them anything to try to help them feel better. For you, this is about to change. You will be able to learn a lot about proper hemorrhoid care in the article that follows.<br /><br />Make sure you get enough fiber to get rid of your painful hemorrhoids. Remember, failure to include enough fiber in your diet deprives your body of nutrients and results in hard stools that are difficult to pass. Psyllium husks, as well as linseed, are both fiber supplements to help keep you regular.<br /><br />It is possible to push a hemorrhoid back into the anus yourself. This treatment should only be performed for small hemorrhoids and with gentleness and care. Hemorrhoids can be protected inside your anus and may be less likely to get irritated or bleed.<br /><br />Although it is common for hemorrhoids to cause blood after a bowel movement, it is always a good idea to consult your doctor to rule out all other possible causes. Blood after a bowel movement can mean there is a serious problem, like cancer or internal bleeding, that should be addressed immediately. Ease your worries by having a physician diagnose the problem. By knowing precisely what you are dealing with, you can start to address the problem.<br /><br />You can reduce irritation and pain by making a paste with water and powdered myrrh. Use equal parts pure water and myrrh. About a teaspoon of each should be enough. Allow the myrrh paste to absorb into the skin for help with reducing hemorrhoids. You can find the powdered myrrh in most health stores or beauty stores.<br /><br />Avoid foods that cause constipation or gas to reduce the pressure on your hemorrhoids. The strain on the rectum caused by passing gas may inflame your hemorrhoids. Avoiding foods that cause you gas will help you avoid that burning sensation.<br /><br />Though it may take some time, hemorrhoids can be lessened and healed gradually with supplements of vitamins and minerals. Supplements and vitamins fill the gaps that your current diet might not be filling. You might also want to check into Venapro and see how it can help reduce hemorrhoids you may have, over time.<br /><br />Squatting over the toilet instead of sitting down will keep you from having hemorrhoid flare ups. This position may seem unnatural when you first try it, but you'll quickly get used to both the position and the fact that your hemorrhoids aren't as inflamed as they used to be.<br /><br />Excessive straining while having a bowel movement is one of the causes for hemorrhoids. Drinking plenty of water and increasing your fiber intake is a great way to avoid hemorrhoids. Squatting could also aid in quickly passing bowel movements. One way to acquire the best body positioning is to use a small stool to rest your feet while you are seated in the bathroom. Hemorrhoids are actually less common in parts of the world in which people squat to eliminate fecal matter.<br /><br />Don't loiter on the toilet. Sit only when you're ready to go. A lot of people like to read while on the toilet, however, this is not recommended because you could be straining unconsciously. Use gravity to your advantage by making sure you need to go to the toilet before you enter the bathroom.<br /><br />This article made it clear that hemorrhoids are prevalent across the population. Most people do not know how to properly handle hemorrhoids though. Usually, it is because they have never been provided with this advice. Apply the advice given to you in this article to permanently eliminate your hemorrhoids.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="40650a9a5c9f3170d243e2f707624414" url=""><![CDATA[Make Your Hemorrhoids Disappear With This Advice<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQvZ2V0LXJpZC1vZi1wYWluZnVsLWhlbW9ycmhvaWRzLXdpdGgtdGhlc2UtdGlwcy0yLw__" target="_blank">Visit this site over here.</a><br /><br />Hemorrhoids are a painful ailment experienced by most people at least once. Women who are carrying unborn children tend to develop them routinely, both before and after the birth. Strain, due to constipation, is the frequent cause of hemorrhoids in both men and women. The article below provides some excellent tips to help you avoid this common condition.<br /><br />Drink plenty of water if you suffer from frequent hemorrhoids. Remaining well-hydrated will ensure that your stools remain soft. You should avoid alcohol and caffeine.<br /><br />Add lemon juice to your water if you want to help your hemorrhoids. Lemon has a lot of soothing properties, which can lessen the irritation that you may get from hemorrhoids. Constantly drinking lemon water throughout the course of your day will make it a much better one.<br /><br />Consider using a homemade enema to ease your hemorrhoids. Steam two cut up cloves of garlic in two cups of steaming water for a half hour. Allow the water to cool down. Then, when it's at room temperature, use the water to provide yourself with an enema once per day.<br /><br />To prevent or avoid worsening hemorrhoids, you should not sit on the commode for a long time while trying to have a bowel movement. This position, coupled with the strain on your muscles will irritate your delicate tissue and prevent healing. You should wait until you are certain you need to pass stool, before heading to the bathroom.<br /><br />Taking certain vitamins and supplements is effective for dealing with hemorrhoids. If you aren't getting enough nutrients from your diet, supplements and vitamins can help provide them. Consider taking Venapro. This supplement helps reduce and prevent hemorrhoid problems.<br /><br />Do not use laxatives if you are constipated and have hemorrhoids. The thing about these type of medications is that they are developed to only assist you with one certain type of bowel movement. Persistent bowel troubles may mean it is time to alter your diet so as to achieve more regularity.<br /><br />Seat yourself in a tub that has been filled with about 12 inches of warm water with both knees slightly elevated. Soaking the affected area in warm water will help ease the pain and reduce the inflammation. When the water's only a little warm, more blood will flow to the submerged areas, providing pain relief and swelling reduction. Soak as frequently as you feel the need, and enjoy the immediate relief it brings.<br /><br />Tomato slices have proven to help some people with the size of their hemorrhoids. The acidic properties of tomatoes can reduce swelling when applied to swollen veins. If you combine this method with a nutritious diet, you should be able to successfully fight off hemorrhoids for years.<br /><br />Ice can be used to reduce hemorrhoid pain. These sores can be very painful. An ice pack can reduce both pain and swelling. Alternate the use of an ice pack with the use of a warm compress. You can also use this technique while taking a warm bath. Simply bring an ice pack with you, and alternate between sitting in the tub and sitting on the ice pack. This can help to relieve the discomfort caused by the pain, swelling and itchiness of hemorrhoids.<br /><br />This article began by describing the facts you need to know about hemorrhoids and added that, fortunately, they are easily treatable. It is almost never necessary to have surgery, and recovery takes place in the home. When properly educated about the home treatment possibilities and common instigators of hemorrhoids, coping with their ailment is much easier.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5078d60d2579dbb37863a5f9b557d52d" url=""><![CDATA[Candid Tips And Advice For Dealing With Hemmorhoids<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQvaGVtb3JyaG9pZC1pbmZvcm1hdGlvbi10aGF0LWV2ZXJ5b25lLXNob3VsZC1rbm93LWFib3V0Lw__" target="_blank">How To Treat A Hemorrhoid</a><br /><br />Many people suffer from hemorrhoids. In fact, nearly 50% of men and women have had to deal with them by the time they're 50. The itching, pain, and bleeding may be difficult to handle. Luckily, though, there are many effective ways to treat hemorrhoids. There are things you can do at home to lessen the symptoms of hemorrhoids. This article may give you ideas on how to treat them.<br /><br />Ice and heat applications can ease hemorrhoid pain. If you alternate between applying ice and heat, you can promote quick healing. You should apply ice to the area for 10 minutes every day, and then follow that with heat for approximately 20 minutes.<br /><br />While the cause is most likely hemorrhoids, you should always consult with your doctor. Blood in your stool can be a symptom of many serious health problems, including cancer. You can ease your mind visiting a doctor to get the problem diagnosed. Your doctor can tell you the exact cause of your rectal bleeding. Hopefully, it's nothing more serious than hemorrhoids; if so, your doctor can prescribe a medication or other treatment for you.<br /><br />A good way to relieve the discomfort of hemorrhoids is a sitz bath after each bowel movement. This will help soothe the irritation that remains afterwards. When finished with your bath, ensure that you pat the anal area until it's dry instead of rubbing it.<br /><br />Lifting heavy items can cause hemorrhoids. The strain of lifting heavy objects is similar to the strain required to force feces out of the body. If you have recurring hemorrhoids, avoid lifting any heavy objects altogether.<br /><br />Stay away from the foods that cause you intestinal gas. The strain you put on your rectum to pass gas can easily cause your hemorrhoids to become inflamed. You will feel that burning discomfort if you eat gas-causing foods, so avoid them.<br /><br />You can avoid further injuries to hemorrhoids by pushing them back in your anus. If the hemorrhoids aren't too large, you might be able to push them back up inside. Doing so also prevents your clothing from chafing against the hemorrhoids. If they are too big or already injured, don't do this.<br /><br />Steer clear of caffeinated beverages, as well as foods that are spicy and hot in nature. Both of these effects can aggravate your symptoms. Spicy food could cause your hemorrhoids to inflame and burn, so avoid it.<br /><br />There are simple ways to prevent hemorrhoids, and it's just a matter of knowing what they are. Do not wait if you have to go to the bathroom. The longer your stool remains inside your large intestines, the more your body will reabsorb water, making it harder for you to defecate, so it'll require straining. This straining will aggravate hemorrhoids, so you should avoid doing it.<br /><br />Gently push any hemorrhoids back into the anus. It is typically pretty easy to nudge a few small hemorrhoids back inside. It can keep them from becoming more tender or inflamed from injuries, such as being chafed by clothing or toilet paper. If they're too big or painful, don't do this and risk injuring them.<br /><br />You may have checked many places for advice on how to best treat your painful hemorrhoids. We are glad that you chose to read this article. Use the ideas we have provided and you should find yourself feeling better very soon. Just be sure to consult a doctor if needed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb74d3799f81d15a3f27044227b5d481" url=""><![CDATA[Are You Suffering From Hemorrhoids? Keep Reading To Find Out<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQvZW1iYXJyYXNzZWQtdG8tYXNrLWFib3V0LWhlbW9ycmhvaWQtb3B0aW9ucy1maW5kLWhlbHBmdWwtaGludHMtaGVyZS0yLw__" target="_blank">Click this site right here.</a><br /><br />Common treatments for hemorrhoid attacks are sitz baths, eating fiber-rich foods, drinking more water and taking an NSAID analgesic. It's very rare that a case of hemorrhoids is so severe that it requires surgery. This article can help you to understand the causes, and to find effective relief measures for hemorrhoids when they do occur.<br /><br />A simple remedy you can use at home is applying ice, then heat. Alternating these two methods shrinks the hemorrhoid, which allows it to heal quicker. A 10 minute application of ice can be followed by 20 minutes with a moist heat application for maximum results.<br /><br />A pre-bathroom walk can help deal with constipation. Walking helps to get the body going and can prepare the bowels for movement. This will lessen the strain of passing the stool which could further irritate your hemorrhoids. Walk briskly for at least ten minutes.<br /><br />Whole wheat bread is great to consume for digestion purposes and can improve hemorrhoids. It can also reduce irritation and redness on your skin. When making your sandwiches, choose wheat bread and bypass white versions.<br /><br />Drinking aloe vera juice helps to loosen stools, making it easier to pass them. If the aloe has a disagreeable flavor, improve by adding some apple juice. Recommended dosages are there for a reason; make sure to follow them, even with something as innocuous as Aloe Vera juice. If you use too much, or repeat the treatment too soon, you could wind up with stomach problems.<br /><br />If your hemorrhoids are manageable, try to push them back inside your body. You can reduce any pain you have and it can even prevent more swelling or bleeding. If you decide to do this, be extremely gentle and don't do anything to worsen the condition.<br /><br />One way to help treat hemorrhoids is to run a sitz bath after going to the bathroom. Sitz baths are effective in cutting down on post-bowel movement itches and irritation. When you are done taking your bath, be sure to pat your anal area dry rather than rub it.<br /><br />Taking the right vitamins and supplements may provide some long-term help with hemorrhoids. Supplements and vitamins could fill voids in nutrition that is not filled by your diet alone. A supplement called Venapro may be helpful in preventing or reducing hemorrhoids.<br /><br />Stock up on over-the-counter hemorrhoid treatments, such as creams, ointments, and suppositories. Your local drugstore should stock a wide range of appropriate products. While they cannot eradicate the hemorrhoids, they can numb the area and provide some relief. These shouldn't generally be used more than a single week.<br /><br />Never rely on laxatives as a method of eliminating hemorrhoids, as they are not meant to be taken on an ongoing basis. They will only provide temporary relief of your discomfort.<br /><br />Now that you know a little more about preventing, treating and relieving the irritating symptoms caused by hemorrhoids, you will be better armed to fight them if they appear again. Revisit these tips any time you need help or support when dealing with a hemorrhoids outbreak.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="91f7dae3e150f8e5198650c25abb3b7e" url=""><![CDATA[Have Hemorrhoids? Use These Tips To Help<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQ_" target="_blank">Best Treatment for Hemorrhoids</a><br /><br />Passing soft stools reduces your risks of developing hemorrhoids. Go to the bathroom as often as possible to prevent stools from building up. You want to drink more water and exercise more overall while taking in your necessary and recommended daily intake of fiber. This article can supplement this advice, to reduce the possibility of hemorrhoids.<br /><br />If your stool contains blood, do not be alarmed, as it is common for hemorrhoids to bleed. Just make sure you eat extra sources of fiber or a special softener product to help you pass stools more easily. Hardened stools may be the cause of irritation to hemorrhoids, which can lead to bleeding.<br /><br />There are actually a lot of things in your own kitchen that you can use to relieve yourself from hemorrhoids. Something as simple as an ice pack from your freezer can provide you with ample relief. The ice pack can help with decreasing soreness from your hemorrhoids. Ice packs made from home can decrease hemorrhoids swelling when they are put on the area that's affected.<br /><br />One of the most effective products that is commercially available for the treatment of hemorrhoids is a hemorrhoid pad. They are safe and help to relieve the irritation and burning sensation caused by hemorrhoids. Some are medicated with ingredients, like witch hazel, and work a little like pads used by women during their period.<br /><br />When hemorrhoid pain gets intense, it is best to stay away from any food that creates gas. The effort of passing gas can irritate both internal and external hemorrhoids. Avoiding gas-causing foods is always a good idea.<br /><br />If you have hemorrhoids, you should find a stool softener that you can take on a regular basis. If you have to push really hard when to pass bowel movements then you could be causing a lot of pain to yourself, and potentially cause yourself more pain and problems.<br /><br />You can use witch hazel to help deal with the uncomfortable side effects of hemorrhoids. Witch hazel is an astringent that will shrink or constrict the hemorrhoid tissue, bringing relief and healing. You can add witch hazel in a sitz bath. You can also apply it using a cotton ball, but only leave it on for about 10 minutes.<br /><br />Talk to your doctor to make sure it is hemorrhoids. Traces of blood in your stool may also indicate a more troubling condition, one of which is rectal cancer. Put your mind at ease by having the problem diagnosed. If it does end up being hemorrhoids, your physician can direct you towards the best treatment options.<br /><br />If you don't know whether you've got a hemorrhoid, it's vital that you talk to your doctor. It can be tricky to correctly differentiate between a polyp and a hemorrhoid, and this confusion can lead to unnecessary panic. Even if you're relatively sure what the problem is, it's always good to get it diagnosed by a professional.<br /><br />Don't wait on the toilet for the urge to go. Only sit down on it when you're ready to have your bowel movement. If you use the time to catch up on your reading, you may not notice that you are straining to go at the same time. Be ready to go to the bathroom when you sit on the toilet because gravity affects your hemorrhoids.<br /><br />This article began by describing the facts you need to know about hemorrhoids and added that, fortunately, they are easily treatable. It is almost never necessary to have surgery, and recovery takes place in the home. When properly educated about the home treatment possibilities and common instigators of hemorrhoids, coping with their ailment is much easier.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dc297a0cf4684db2657ed42ad6028211" url=""><![CDATA[What You Need To Know When You Are Suffering From Hemorroids<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQ_" target="_blank">How to Treat a Hemorrhoids</a><br /><br />Nearly half of all fifty year olds have had hemorrhoids at some point in their life. It is difficult to deal with the itchy, painful symptoms of hemorrhoids. Luckily, there are many treatments that have proven effective in dealing to them. Making lifestyle adaptations and applying home treatments can do wonders. This article will provide you with many different ideas for treating hemorrhoids.<br /><br />A good way to get rid of hemorrhoids is to ensure you get the most fiber you can. This is especially important for those people who hate fruits and vegetables that contain a lot of fiber, as not eating enough can cause nutritional deficiency and rock solid poop. One alternative to eating fruits and vegetables for fiber is a limseed or psyllium supplement.<br /><br />Squatting is an easy way to use gravity and the natural tension of your body to ease bowel movements and avoid causing hemorrhoids. This position may seem unnatural when you first try it, but you'll quickly get used to both the position and the fact that your hemorrhoids aren't as inflamed as they used to be.<br /><br />Carrying a cushion around with you may make you a little self conscious, but it will provide relief from hemorrhoids. You may feel uncomfortable using it at work, but when you are riding in your car or at home it can help to relieve a great deal of the pain making your life a bit easier.<br /><br />Even though your hemorrhoids itch, you should resist scratching them. The act of scratching them can open the region to infections, as well as create further complications. If you cannot handle the itching, wet a cloth and gently pat the affected area. The itching may be from that area being unclean, so patting using a wet cloth can help clean it and relieve some itching.<br /><br />When consumed often, certain healthy foods lower your chances of developing hemorrhoids. These include products made with whole grains, fresh fruits and veggies, and unsalted nuts. A well-rounded diet will enhance your comfort levels.<br /><br />If you are dealing with hemorrhoids, it is encouraged that after each bowel movement you sit in a sitz bath. These baths will help minimize the itchiness and irritation that can flare up after bowel movements. Once you finish taking the bath, pat your rectum dry instead of rubbing it.<br /><br />In order to deal effectively with a hemorrhoid problem, avoid sitting on the toilet for extended periods while waiting for a bowel movement. Being in this low sitting position could cause undue tension on your hemorrhoids, aggravating them and troubling the healing process. Do not go into the bathroom until you know your bowel movement is imminent.<br /><br />If you must use a cream to reduce the discomfort of your hemorrhoids, try to do it as infrequently as possible. These products don't actually cure the problem, instead they're just a band-aid solution. Speak with your doctor if you find that using these creams is necessary for longer than one week. Over-using certain creams can cause more damage than good.<br /><br />Most hemorrhoids are caused by straining the sphincter muscles and others near them. Since this is the case, if you suffer from this problem, you should take notice of the pressure you put on this area when moving your bowels and during other activities.<br /><br />The very private nature of hemorrhoids' affected areas makes it very difficult for many adults to openly seek advice from their friends or families. Fortunately, the information that you have just read is sure to answer at least a few of your questions about the symptoms and treatments that are associated with hemorrhoids.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24818d57b678a1cc12d9eca1ff53e9d7" url=""><![CDATA[Things To Look For To Know If You Need A Doctor's Help For<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQ_" target="_blank">How to Treat a Hemorrhoids</a><br /><br />No one really enjoys talking about hemorrhoids. There are probably several people close to you who have had to deal with this uncomfortable condition. Whether your hemorrhoids are external or internal, you can benefit from the following advice on treatment and prevention methods.<br /><br />If you are dealing with painful hemorrhoids, then you should think about purchasing a donut cushion. This cushion is designed specifically for your bottom, and it makes you feel better when dealing with hemorrhoids. By just sitting on it, you will be more relaxed than you would be sitting on surfaces without it.<br /><br />You do not have to suffer needlessly through a bout of hemorrhoids with no relief at all. It is recommended you use a sitz bath a few times each day, for approximately 10 minutes or so each time. A cold compress can relieve some of the pain and swelling.<br /><br />One of the best and most effective solutions to get long-term hemorrhoid relief, is to add more fiber to your diet on a daily basis. Items of food that are rich in fiber include pastas, oatmeal and whole grain breads. Fiber cuts down on strain that can lead to hemorrhoids, and it also increases general bowel motility.<br /><br />Anal exercises can help to prevent hemorrhoids. By not using the muscles in your anus, there may not be enough blood flow, which can cause hemorrhoids. Flex your anal muscles and hold for five seconds, then relax the muscles. Repeat for five minutes, several times a day.<br /><br />Draw a warm bath and sit in it with your knees bent. Warm water will soothe the pain and inflammation of a hemorrhoid quickly and effectively. Slightly warm water helps blood flow to the affected area, keeping pain and swelling to a minimum. Whenever you need some pain relief, hop in the tub, and you'll soon find you're feeling better.<br /><br />When you squat on the toilet instead of sitting while going to the bathroom, it'll be easier for you to pass stool and will help to prevent hemorrhoids. It can be awkward in the beginning, but you will get used to it and notice that you aren't in as much pain anymore.<br /><br />Make sure that your hemorrhoids don't come into contact with items that have dyes, oils or fragrances in them, as this can exacerbate things. Even brief contact with these ingredients may cause sharp pain, burning and inflammation.<br /><br />Ingesting grape seed oil will help you to reduce the pain and swelling associated with hemorrhoids. This helps your body fight off infections and helps to reduce or eliminate hemorrhoidal bleeding.<br /><br />One hemorrhoid prevention method is surprisingly simple. Don't delay moving your bowels. Water is constantly reabsorbed from stool as long as it remains in your system. As a result, ignoring the need to defecate causes the stool to become drier and harder, which will require additional straining when you do go. Straining exacerbates hemorrhoids and should be avoided.<br /><br />Drinking a lot of water helps prevent hemorrhoids, as well as soothe those that already exist. Drinking lots of water helps digestion in general, but it especially improves bowle movements. Hemorrhoids can be hurt by constipation, or you can cause new ones. Make sure you drink at least 8 glasses of water a day to soften your stool, as this will lessen your chances of getting hemorrhoids.<br /><br />Hemorrhoids can be aggravated if you sit for long periods on the toilet. Sitting in this manner can strain and irritate your hemorrhoids, which makes it much harder for them to heal. Resist the urge to strain, and wait until you feel the urge, before you go to the bathroom.<br /><br />By applying the knowledge in the above article, you'll be better informed, and better able to manage hemorrhoids pain. Of course, one of the best ways to fight this condition is to begin with prevention. By using both these methods and proper medical care, you will live a life free of hemorrhoids.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7c22d0d51c85d8ce2c07ab03540ee8c" url=""><![CDATA[Hemorrhoids Don't Have To Be A Problem Anymore<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQ_" target="_blank">How to Treat a Hemorrhoids at Home</a><br /><br />Internal hemorrhoids are typically inside the walls of the rectum, while hemorrhoids that are external are usually under the skin surrounding the anus. Although external hemorrhoids are much more painful, both of these types can be effectively prevented and treated by applying recommended treatments. In this article you can find different ways to reduce hemorrhoid effects that are bothering you in your life.<br /><br />Draw a warm bath and sit in it with your knees bent. The warm water will relieve the itchiness and pain due to hemorrhoids. Warm water will help blood to get to the hemorrhoid, and it will get rid of swelling and pain. This can be repeated as frequently as you wish, and you'll experience quick relief.<br /><br />Having a good grasp of the causes and symptoms of hemorrhoids is important for anyone afflicted by them. Learn as much as you can about hemorrhoids if you are suffering from them. To make things simple, nerves and veins get swollen and sensitive and cause your skin to flare up and become irritated.<br /><br />Increasing the amount of vitamin A you consume is an easy way to help reduce the pain and swollen size of the veins causing your hemorrhoids. Carrots and juice will help you get vitamin A into your body, and that will help relive the pain of hemorrhoids.<br /><br />To help with relieving the discomfort of hemorrhoids, try adding a little lemon to your drinking water. There are many calming properties in lemons which help to reduce hemorrhoid inflammation. To improve your daily well-being, try incorporating lemon water into your diet!<br /><br />As difficult as it must seem, you should avoid scratching hemorrhoids. Although the itching is absolutely maddening, it will only get worse if you scratch. Scratching will make it feel better for a second or two, but it will actually make the hemorrhoid swell more and slow the healing process. Instead, look for medicated products or homeopathic remedies to provide itch relief.<br /><br />Good hygiene routines in the bathroom will assist in lowering your odds of getting hemorrhoids. Using a combination of quality soft toilet tissue that does not break, and moistening wipes after each bowel movement, can be effective.<br /><br />One risk factor for hemorrhoids is pushing too hard when defecating. Eating healthier foods and drinking plenty of water will allow the stools to come out easier. To avoid straining, you may also want to try squatting. When you sit on the toilet, use a small stool or similar object for support beneath your feet. Hemorrhoids aren't common in those places in the world where the people squat to defecate.<br /><br />Sit in a lukewarm bath while raising your knees. The water helps to sooth your pain and reduce inflammation. A warm soak stimulates circulation in the area, reducing swelling and pain; this is the key to finding relief. Do this as often as necessary, and you will feel better in no time.<br /><br />When external hemorrhoids emerge, see if you are able to press them back from whence they came. Make sure your hands are clean to avoid infections. Then, schedule an appointment at your doctor's office as soon as possible.<br /><br />Perhaps the most effective method for preventing hemorrhoids is also extremely simple. Don't put off having bowel movements. The longer the stool stays in the large intestine, then your body will reabsorb more water, which means the stool will get harder causing you to strain more for elimination purposes. Existing hemorrhoids can be extremely aggravated by pushing and straining.<br /><br />With so many treatments available for hemorrhoids, finding an effective treatment is easy with the proper tools and information. Unless there's an extreme case of hemorrhoids, surgery is typically not recommended. By becoming knowledgeable about the causes and prevention of hemorrhoids, it is hoped that you can help your body receive a little relief.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="788d052ffda4d51b24ba10266d6ad769" url=""><![CDATA[Cope With Your Hemorrhoids With These Tips<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25hdHVyYWxyZW1lZHlmb3JoZW1vcnJob2lkcy5uZXQ_" target="_blank">Best Treatment for Hemorrhoids</a><br /><br />The most effective method for staving off hemorrhoids is to make sure all stools are soft and do not require straining and force to be passed. Doctors advise you to listen to your body's natural urges to determine whether or not you should try to use the restroom. It's also important to eat lots of fiber, drink plenty of water, and exercise regularly. The article below contains advice for the prevention and treatment of hemorrhoids.<br /><br />A simple remedy you can use at home is applying ice, then heat. Alternating these two methods shrinks the hemorrhoid, which allows it to heal quicker. A 10 minute application of ice can be followed by 20 minutes with a moist heat application for maximum results.<br /><br />You can gradually get hemorrhoids under control by taking enough vitamins. Consider using supplements, in addition to changing your diet. Supplements and vitamins could fill voids in nutrition that is not filled by your diet alone. Be sure to consider supplements like Venapro that have been shown to reduce the occurrence of hemorrhoids, over time.<br /><br />When your hemorrhoids itch, it is sometimes tempting to scratch them. You have to avoid scratching so you don't tear your skin. If this happens, you will be in much more pain than you would have been in otherwise. You also have a greater chance of getting a bacterial infection.<br /><br />Drinking aloe vera juice helps to loosen stools, making it easier to pass them. If the aloe has a disagreeable flavor, improve by adding some apple juice. Recommended dosages are there for a reason; make sure to follow them, even with something as innocuous as Aloe Vera juice. If you use too much, or repeat the treatment too soon, you could wind up with stomach problems.<br /><br />Minor hemorrhoids can be dealt with by pushing them back into the anus. While not everyone is up for this process, with some preparation and care you can push smaller hemorrhoids back into the anus. When outside the anus, hemorrhoids can be much more easily irritated and likely to bleed.<br /><br />Try to abstain from lifting anything heavy if you want to avoid irritating, existing hemorrhoids and causing new ones to erupt. Your body is subjected to the same stress when lifting heavy objects as it is when you forcefully strain to have a bowel movement. Do not lift heavy objects if you suffer from frequent hemorrhoids.<br /><br />Never scratch hemorrhoids, even if they itch. If you scratch them, you can get an infection, and cause a lot of damage to the affected area. If you cannot handle the itching, wet a cloth and gently pat the affected area. Itching often comes from the area being dirty, so patting will both clean it and help relieve the itching.<br /><br />If you don't know whether you've got a hemorrhoid, it's vital that you talk to your doctor. Not everyone can tell the difference between a hemorrhoid and a polyp and this can cause a lot of undo panic on your part. Schedule a quick check-up with your doctor if you are concerned about any growth.<br /><br />Consider using witch hazel as a treatment for discomfort and pain. Witch hazel has natural astringent properties that work to shrink the swollen tissue and soothe the pain and itching. Soak a cotton ball with witch hazel and apply it to the affected area. Leave it in place for five or ten minutes. Witch hazel is also a good addition for sitz baths.<br /><br />You may have checked many places for advice on how to best treat your painful hemorrhoids. We are glad that you chose to read this article. Use the ideas we have provided and you should find yourself feeling better very soon. Just be sure to consult a doctor if needed.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>