<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="6a7fe6f2256213a64525c4ae82e7bb07" url=""><![CDATA[Hi there,<br/><br/>Hi there everybody,
<br />I'm hoping you all can be my friends, <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />Hope to see you in my friend list soon, <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/laugh.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />I'm in for anime and I don't care weather who you are just I want everybody to be happy like me,
<br />So Chat soon,
<br />Bye nice to meet you. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angel.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/laugh.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="19a4222f733ff771a7b860bddc444d86" url=""><![CDATA[Clans<br/><br/>Hi there,
<br />Me Ivory3610 is the same person as Ivory393 as you know,<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/laugh.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />I have a clan Animax_1
<br />It is a clan where we can meet more friends,
<br />Hope you join, <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/laugh.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="15b8242f207ec27bd138f5ab5e2419cb" url=""><![CDATA[Links<br/><br/>Maybe there is something you can't understand but I just hope to give you some pictures to have a look, thats why I have links. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />I haven't add much links, but if you want you can see the links at Ivory393,
<br />So sorry,
<br />But I just want to be friends ok,
<br />Hope to meet,
<br />Nice to be your friend,
<br />Greetings,
<br />Ivory3610 <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="95ac7cb73f9f12627cf64942abe77f92" url=""><![CDATA[Thanks<br/><br/>Thank as you all accept my friendship........
<br />I just hope now is to know you all better...
<br />But I think I have a chance on that..... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/laugh.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6d4b3ffe1ded625034319a9424df8c4" url=""><![CDATA[female comebacks<br/><br/>Man: Where have you been all my life?
<br />Woman: Hiding from you.
<br /><br />Man: Haven't I seen you someplace before?
<br />Woman: Yes, that's why I don't go there anymore.
<br /><br />Man: Is this seat empty?
<br />Woman: Yes, and this one will be if you sit down.
<br /><br />Man: Your place or mine?
<br />Woman: Both. You go to yours, and I'll go to mine.
<br /><br />Man: So, what do you do for a living?
<br />Woman: I'm a female impersonator.
<br /><br />Man: Hey baby, what's your sign?
<br />Woman: Do not enter.
<br /><br />Man: How do you like your eggs in the morning?
<br />Woman: Unfertilized.
<br /><br />Man: Your body is like a temple.
<br />Woman: Sorry, there are no services today.
<br /><br />Man: I would go to the end of the world for you.
<br />Woman: But would you stay there?
<br /><br />Man: If I could see you naked, I'd die happy.
<br />Woman: If I saw you naked, I'd probably die laughing.
<br /><br />Man: If I could rearrange the alphabet I'd put u and i together
<br />Woman: Really, I'd put f and u together
<br /><br />If you repost this you will get a phone call 37 minutes after you repost
<br />this....
<br /><br />If you don't resend this then your love life will be [[doomed]] for eternity.
<br /><br />ladys REPOST THIS AS &quot;female comebacks&quot;
<br /><br />guyz REPOST THIS AS &quot;don't let this happen...&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c15eb980fd86bccdfbc3fa296d11f8a4" url=""><![CDATA[Things A Girl Would Love<br/><br/>THERE ARE 44 THINGS A GUY SHOULD DO FOR A GIRL
<br /><br />1-touch their waist
<br />2-talk to them
<br />3-share secrets
<br />4-give her your jacket
<br />5-kiss them slowly
<br /><br />are you remembering this?
<br /><br />6-hug her
<br />7-hold her
<br />8-laugh with her
<br />9-invite her somewhere
<br />10-let her be with you when you're with your friends
<br /><br />keep reading
<br /><br />11-smile with her
<br />12-take pics with her
<br />13-pull her onto your lap
<br />14-when she says she loves you more, deny it. fight back
<br />15-when her friends say i love her more than you, deny it. fight back and
<br />hug her tight so she cant get to her friends. it makes her feel loved
<br /><br />Are you thinking about someone?
<br /><br />16-always hug her and say i love you when you see her
<br />17-kiss her unexpectedly
<br />18-HUG HER FROM BEHIND AROUND THE WAIST
<br />19-tell her shes beautiful not sexy!
<br />20-tell her the way you feel about her!
<br /><br />..20 you need to show her you mean it too
<br /><br />21-kiss her on the lips
<br />22-DONT ask her to buy you stuff. you buy HER stuff
<br />23-TELL HER WHAT FEELS GOOD
<br />24-make her feel loved
<br />25-always listen to what she has to say
<br /><br />i hope every girl gets treated this good...
<br /><br />26-don't lie to her!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
<br />27-dont cheat on her!!!!!!!!!!!!!
<br />28-take her anywhere she wants
<br />29-txt messege or call her in the morning and tell her have a good day at
<br />school, and how much you miss her
<br />30-be there for her when ever she needs you, &amp; even when she doesn't need
<br />you, just be there so she'll know that she can always count on you
<br /><br />are you still reading this, you better be its important
<br /><br />31. Hold her close when she's cold and she can hold you too.
<br />32. When you are alone hold her close and kiss her.
<br />33. Kiss her on the cheek; (it will give her the hint that you want to kiss them).
<br />34. While in the movie, put your arm around her and then she will
<br />automatically put her head on your shoulder, then lean in and tilt her chin
<br />up and kiss her lightly.
<br />35. Dont ever tell her to leave even jokingly or act like you're mad. If
<br />shes upset, comfort her
<br /><br />remember this next time you are with her
<br /><br />36. When people diss her, stand up for her.
<br />37. Look deep into her eyes and tell her you love her.
<br />38. Lay down under the stars and put her head on your chest so she can
<br />listen to the steady beat of your heart, Link your fingers together while
<br />you whisper to her as she rests her eyes and listens to you.
<br /><br />39. When walking next to each other grab her hand.
<br />40. When you hug her hold her in your arms as long as possible
<br /><br />MAKE SURE SHE KNOWS SHES LOVED
<br /><br />41. Call her at night to wish her sweet dreams.
<br />42. Comfort her when she cries and wipe away her tears.
<br />43. Take her for long walks at night.
<br />44. Always Remind her how much you love her.
<br /><br />you'll never know when she needs just a lil more love
<br /><br />If you are a girl send this on as Things A Girl Would Love and if you are a
<br />guy send this on as What we Should do......You have 5 minutes to send this
<br />on
<br />If you dont send this on in 5 minutes you will have HORRIBLE relationships
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3dd4dfd573bc220146c4e1b293cf6f2a" url=""><![CDATA[HURT BY THOUSAND FOORT KRUTCH!<br/><br/>Drop the ball, watch it fall far below
<br />Suck you in, hold your breath
<br />The undertow creeps in slow
<br />Everyone owns a gun deep inside
<br />It's just a matter of how much you let it slide
<br /><br />Drop the ball, watch it fall far below
<br />Suck you in, hold your breath
<br />The undertow creeps in slow
<br />Everyone owns a gun deep inside
<br />It's just a matter of how much you let it slide
<br /><br />Help me help you they wont be there
<br />Help me help you they won't see
<br /><br />It hurts when you need me
<br />And I can't break your fall
<br />It hurts when you can't see
<br />And it hurts
<br /><br />Drop the switch, scratch the itch, watch it grow
<br />Inch by inch, the cutting board, watch it swing to and fro
<br />Everyone carries one deep inside
<br />It's just a matter of how much you let it slide
<br /><br />Wash it off, take the loss, let it go
<br />Take it in, drink it up, we can just take it slow
<br />Everyone carries one deep inside
<br />It's just a matter of how much you let it slide
<br /><br />Help me help you they wont be there
<br />Help me help you they won't see
<br /><br />It hurts when you need me
<br />And I can't break your fall
<br />It hurts when you can't see
<br />And it hurts
<br /><br />It hurts when you need me
<br />And I can't break your fall
<br />It hurts when you can't see
<br />And it hurts
<br /><br />And it hurts when you're lonely
<br />And I'm standing right beside you there
<br />And it hurt when you told me
<br />That you told me that you tried this on your own
<br /><br />Hope you never hurt
<br />Hope you never cry
<br />Hope you never lose your way tonight
<br />Hope you never crumble
<br />Hope you never fall
<br />Hope you never throw away the
<br /><br />Drop the ball, watch it fall far below
<br />Suck you in, hold your breath, watch it swing
<br /><br />It hurts when you need me
<br />And I can't break your fall
<br />It hurts when you can't see
<br />And it hurts
<br /><br />It hurts when you need me
<br />And I can't break your fall
<br />It hurts when you can't see
<br />And it hurts
<br /><br />And it hurts
<br />And it hurts
<br />And it hurts
<br />And it hurts
<br />And it hurts
<br />And it hurts
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e094e67d2c23ae5046584bf4c7292184" url=""><![CDATA[Answer<br/><br/>Do I look like I would be a good friend?
<br />[] yes
<br />[] no
<br />[] don’t know
<br /><br />Do I look like...
<br />[] a player
<br />[] one time thing
<br />[] Good BF/GF
<br />[] Slut
<br /><br />If you saw me for the first time would you talk to me?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br /><br />AM I...
<br />[] smart?
<br />[] cute?
<br />[] funny?
<br />[] cool?
<br />[] romantic?
<br />[] a *freak*?
<br />[] gangsta?
<br />[] loveable?
<br />[] adorable?
<br />[] trustworthy
<br />[] compassionate?
<br />[] great to be with?
<br />[] attractive?
<br />[] mean?
<br />[] well known?
<br /><br />On a scale of 1-10 (10 being the highest), rate me..
<br />[] 1
<br />[] 2
<br />[] 3
<br />[] 4
<br />[] 5
<br />[] 6
<br />[] 7
<br />[] 8
<br />[] 9
<br />[] 10
<br /><br />Are you going to repost this so I can answer for YOU?
<br />[] yes
<br />[] no
<br /><br />what would you want me to be to you?
<br />[] Friends
<br />[] Girl/boy friend
<br />[] Friends with benefit
<br /><br />And do u want my screen name?
<br />[]yes
<br />[]no
<br /><br />Name one thing you would like to do with me...
<br />[] ________________________
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e860a34ec53dc577b2570dd4dcaccea9" url=""><![CDATA[Wat's up.... buzy?<br/><br/>I'm.....
<br />Buzy yesterday exam ends and today English Camp...... 23 more days exam again oh my god...... so in pressure.....
<br />But! it is fun in English camp just that I lost my temper there a while......
<br />How about you all exam??? or wat.......
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9c8ccfc76009f5088c6d78e782b88c5" url=""><![CDATA[Frez!!!<br/><br/>Hey! there!
<br />I haven't seen any add of frez this few weeks!!!<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" />
<br />So if you can help call some frez to add me I'm happy to be everyone frez as you all know we online at different time so it is kind of bored if you are the pnly one online so I hope your frezs can be mine too!!!!!! ok! so hope to get good news...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a34d6b4720c38c3ad885547e0605bf84" url=""><![CDATA[friends!<br/><br/>Hye!
<br />Do you all like to have more and more friends?
<br />I do so how about introduce us to your friends and add us to be friends..........
<br />Sometime,
<br />We might not see anyone online we are on so it is boring but if we have more friends we will have more chance chatting with each other........
<br />And don't forget to join my clan animax_1 and Anime_cute.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e3545779c09a09c0091594efe357f435" url=""><![CDATA[Sorryyyyyyyyyy...........<br/><br/>It's quite a long time since I write a blog message as I was quite bz...
<br />I'm sorry really...
<br />Now it is holiday quite boring....
<br />So...
<br />I hope 2 share something with U...
<br />Do U know Fahrenheit ?
<br />It is a chinese boy band... Quite cute!!! ^.^ lol!!!
<br />I'm hoping 2 post some of their pictures...
<br />_______________________________________
<br /><br />They R having a concert this week actually but Jiro Wang's leg was hurt...
<br />So it is postpone to next yr March!!!
<br />So sad the tickets was all sold out...
<br /><br />Sssaaaddddd........... sob...
<br />_________________________________________
<br /><br />Anyway,
<br />though I'm sad...
<br />Happy holiday!!!!
<br />2 everyone...
<br />Have a relaxing, peaceful and most of all enjoy Ur holiday!!!
<br />____________________________________________
<br /><br />Best Wishes,
<br />Amber
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>