<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="747b46666e6591723bb80801a1bc7168" url=""><![CDATA[Incredible Tours of Incredible North East India<br/><br/>Northeast India is incredibly beautiful. It is one of the most sought after holidaying destination in India. Studded with so very beautiful attractions, natural tourism and exciting sightseeing spots, Northeast India is the ideal gateway where tourist can relax, rejuvenate and relieve the mind, heart and soul from the stressful life. It is one such tourism destination that is incomparable and alluring that entice the tourists from all over the world. 
<br /><br />Northeast India has so many wonderful sightseeing spots and tourism destination that allures great number of visitors from all over the world. Among the many some of the exciting tourism destinations that are worth to visit and explore during Northeast India tours are Darjeeling, Pelling, Sikkim, Gangtok, Jorethang, Namchi, Kurseong, etc. These are some of the exciting destinations that are worth to visit and explore. 
<br /><br />Most of the tourists planning for Northeast India tour love to visit Darjeeling. Blessed with the scintillating sightseeing and alluring attractions, Darjeeling is one of the most exciting destinations where tourists can savour in the scintillating natural beauty and visit to some exciting attraction with immense pleasure and joy. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling has so many attractions that include visit to Padmaja Naidu Himalayan Zoological Park, Dhir Dham Temple, Botanical Garden, Darjeeling Himalayan Railway, etc. These are some of the exciting attractions that are worth to visit and explore during <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank"><strong>Tours to Darjeeling</strong></a>. 
<br /><br />Along with Darjeeling tour, one can also enjoy visit to exciting sightseeing spots like Mirik, Rock Garden, Tiger Hill, Singamari Ropeway and more. Along with that one can also go for tours to many exciting destination like Sikkim, Namchi and Gangtok. 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL3Npa2tpbS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><strong>Darjeeling Sikkim Tours</strong></a>can be well organised as these are the best two tourism destination of Northeast India that is highly preferred by the tourists. Sikkim is one of the highly preferred destinations and no wonder, the state is visited by thousands and hundreds of tourists from all over the world. 
<br /><br />So come and enjoy vacation in this incredible Northeast India and take back home incredible memories to relish in forever. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank"><strong>Darjeeling Tour</strong></a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank"><strong>North East Tours</strong></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2dhbmd0b2stdG91cnMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><strong>Tours to Gangtok</strong></a>. Find more information to visit at <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com</a></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5adb86e54503841d43238801704b682c" url=""><![CDATA[Delightful tour of Manali<br/><br/>Manali is amazingly beautiful blessed haven on earth with refreshing beauty of nature. Manali is located in the Kullu valley in Himachal Pradesh. Rolling hills, snow capped mountains, fruit laden orchards, colonial building, emerald meadows covered with blossoming wildlife flowers have made Manali a touristy hill station in India. Both the honeymooners and adventure travelers attracts by heli-skiing, hiking, river rafting and mountaineering. The couples who want to make their honeymoon ravishing and enchanting love to visit Manali in Himachal Pradesh.
<br /><br />Manali Tour Package offers to a chance to have a wonderful experience with the feeling of natural beauty in their pure form. If you want to play with snow and want to witness snowfall, the chilling climate of Manali is pleasant for you. Most visiting places like Solang Valley, Vashisth Hot Water Spring, Manu temple, Hadimba Temple, Rohtang Pass, Mountaineering Institute, Banjar, Larji Hot Water Spring, Katrin, Nehru Kund, Bajaura, Koti, Jagatsukh, Arjuna Gufa, Rahala Waterfalls, etc are magnetism for tourists in Manali. The environments and views of snow capped mountains and rolling hills feel you Manali in the form Switzerland in India.  
<br /><br />The pleasant and romantic character and atmosphere of this place makes it an ideal destination for <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vbWFuYWxpLXRvdXJpc20uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Manali Tourism</a></strong>. Apart from Manali there are many places to visit in Himachal Pradesh. Five major zones in Himachal Pradesh are Shimla, Kullu and Manali, Kangra-Dharamshala- Palampur, Dalhousie and Chamba and Paonta-Nahan. Rajgarh Valley popularly known as the peach valley is a lush green valley in sirmaur district. People are dynamic and hardworking here and also you can visit to the famous Baru Sahib Gurdwara in this valley. Pragpur is a small village seems to hold the seed of much of Kangra’s rural beauty. Himachal Tour Packages will give you a prospect to a wonderful visit of the natural places and have a break from full of traffic and crowded places.
<br /><br />The New Bilaspur can be truly described as the first planned hill town of the country. Gliding through cool and enchanting waters of the lake will give you the pleasure in <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vaGltYWNoYWwtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Himachal tours</a></strong>. Shimla is the capital town of Himachal Pradesh and it is built over several hills and connecting ridges. Kullu known as a Valley of Gods has plentiful temples. The Dhashehra festival of Kullu is world famous. Kangra is one of the most picturesque in Himachal Pradesh which was anciently known as ‘Trigarta’. Dharamshala and Palampur are the fascinating spots in Kangra Valley with the surrounding of tea gardens, pine forests, deoder and snowy peaks. In the midway between Kalka and Shimla, solan is situated with the fine climate to visit for all the season. Chamba is a milky and honey valley is known for the meadows, temples, paintings, streams and lakes. Two charming and beautiful places in chamba are Dalhousie and Khajjiar which make chamba a tranquil spots to visit for tourists.  
<br /><br />Those who want to go in the middle of natural beauty and experience the haven can choose the Himachal tours. This journey will make your holiday memorable and cherishable moment ever in your life. Book the Himachal tour package at your budget and preferences and spend lovely time in these gorgeous hill stations of Himachal Pradesh in a delightful and outstanding way.
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tours related topics. He has authored many books on <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vbWFuYWxpLWhvbmV5bW9vbi1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Manali Honeymoon Packages</a></strong> , <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank">Manali Tour Package</a></strong> and <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vaGltYWNoYWwtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Himachal Tour Packages</a></strong> . Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c6dc42501716e6061eacf6242ad476fd" url=""><![CDATA[Tour to Mist Kissed Romantic Darjeeling Hills<br/><br/>Darjeeling is the land of mist kissed hills. Located far in the corner of Northeast India near to the very own Sikkim State, Darjeeling has emerged to be the heavenly hill station, located in the foothills of Kanchan Junga. It is one of the finest among the entire tourism destination and is one of the most visited hill station in India. It is amazingly gifted by the nature and has so many alluring tourism attractions and sightseeing spots that make the tours more enjoyable and delightful. Some of the exciting sightseeing spots and alluring attractions to visit during Darjeeling tours are beyond scope and they offer truly mesmerising options to enjoy vacation with incredible experiences. 
<br /><br />Some of the alluring sightseeing spots and tourism attractions that are worth to visit and explore during <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a></strong> is mist kissed tea gardens of Happy Valley Tea Estate, Rock Garden, Batasia Loop, Padmaja Naidu Himalayan Zoological Park, Peace Pagoda, etc. These are some of the excellent and alluring sightseeing spots which are worth to visit and explore during Darjeeling tours. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling is the holidaying destination of all season but most of the tourists flow during the summer season as during this time the temperature remains cool and pleasure that gives tourists to escape from the heat of the sun. Here tourists during the summer time can relax under the cool shade of the Kanchan Junga which seems to be freshly covered by the snow and tour to the nature blessed sightseeing spots that adorns your days in Darjeeling with pleasant experiences. Truly speaking this alluring hill station is home to many exciting and alluring sightseeing spots and more of all, home to incredible attractions. 
<br />Darjeeling is renowned as the popular and scenic hill station since the time of the British Era. It is very popular and so most of the tour package to Northeast offer tour or holidays in Darjeeling options. Darjeeling is not only popular for its alluring natural beauty but the refreshing tea gardens and the UNESCO World Heritage, Darjeeling Toy Train also draw major attention of the tourists from all over the world. The place it truly one of the most sought after destination and more of all its refreshing tea gardens are the major attraction of tourists. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling is also very popular for trekking and adventure tours. The Himalayan landscape offer tourists especially the adventure seekers wonderful opportunity to enjoy ultimate adventure tours and treasure incredible experiences to relish in forever. One can enjoy trekking to Manay Bhanjyang and Sandakphu. Climb through the dense forest of Pine trees and rhododendrons we well as steep trails with steams overflowing answering the wild calls of the birds. Trekking in Darjeeling is something very exciting as one can enjoy alluring tour with exciting and alluring vacation with ultimate experiences. Trekking in Darjeeling also offer tourists to enjoy ultimate view of the snow capped Himalayas and alluring beauty of the nature with outstanding experiences. 
<br />Well <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">tours to Darjeeling hills</a></strong> is something that one will always love to enjoy for long time as the heavenly beauty will engulf the heart and offer incredible experiences to relish in forever. So come and enjoy ultimate holidays with immense pleasure and joy and take back home lots of memorable memories to relish in forever. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on guide for tour <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East tour packages</a></strong>, <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL3BlbGxpbmctdG91ci5odG1s" target="_blank">Pelling tours</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL3BlbGxpbmctdG91ci5odG1s" target="_blank">Pelling tours</a></strong> and <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL3Npa2tpbS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Darjeeling Sikkim tours</a></strong>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="82870e176497024f15e3d01f3ed6a8fa" url=""><![CDATA[Manali, Dalhousie and Shimla the Most Sought After Destinati<br/><br/>Himachal Pradesh in India is the most wonderful and beautiful tourist destination which easily will attract the vacationers from all over the globe. This astounding destination is located in the north of India which easily attracts the vacationers for their peaceful and wonderful vacation. The world of Himachal is a magical land which is globally known for its snow capped mountains and astounding landscapes. This amazing destination is truly the most beautiful and wonderful destination which is speckled with numerous fabulous hill town which easily will overcast magical spurt on your visit to the wonderful world of Himachal. 
<br /><br />The exotic hill resorts and fabulous hotels easily attract the vacationers from all over the globe. The hotels and resorts offer the vacationers wonderful stay along with all the comforts and luxuries, warm hospitality and the delicious cuisines truly make your stay more delightful and wonderful. Apart from all these there are numerous other executive services which easily attract the vacationers from all over the globe. Newlywed couples, leisure vacationers, family vacationers, nature lovers and adventure enthusiasts easily attract the tourist from all over the globe. Some of the major tourist destinations which easily attract the tourist from all over the globe are such as listed below:
<br /><br />Shimla
<br />Shimla is lovingly called as ‘Queen of Hill Stations’ which easily attract the vacationers from all over the globe. This beautiful hill town is located in the North West Himalayans which is blessed with the entire natural bounties which one can think off all. This wonderful Shimla is draped in forest of pine, rhododendron and oak. Shimla experiences pleasant summers and mild and snowy winters which easily attract the vacationers from all over the globe. Shimla will offer the vacationer which retains a colonial aura and the grand old buildings easily will attract the honeymooners and other vacationers for the most wonderful vacation. Some of the major tourist attractions and destinations which easily enhance the Shimla Tourism are such as the Ridge, the mall, Christ Church, Indian Institute of Advanced Studies, Prospect Hill 2155 metres, Shimla State Museum etc. 
<br /><br />Manali
<br />Manali is situated at altitude of 2050 meter above the main sea level and which is situated at a distance of 40kms from Kullu in the state of Himachal Pradesh. Snow caped mountain peaks, verdant valleys, fruit laden orchards, adventure sports, majestic mountains, lush landscapes, scenic trekking routes, beautiful meadows, relaxed atmosphere and serene ambiance are the forte of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vbWFuYWxpLXRvdXJpc20uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Manali tourism</a></strong> which truly elates the vacationers from all over the globe. Some of the major attractions which are very worth to visit with any Manali tour packages are such as Rohtang Pass and Solang Valley, Bijli Mahadev Temple, Hadimba Devi Temple and Vashisth Village. 
<br /><br />Dalhousie
<br />Dalhousie is one of the most splendid and most demanded hill stations which easily attract the vacationers from all over the globe. The scenic beauty and the superb climatic conditions easily attract the vacationers in this magnificent hill town. This beautiful hill town is nestled in the lap of incredible Himalayan mountain range which is placed at an average height of 8000 feet. This astounding hill station spreads over area of 14 sq km which picturesquely spreads over five hills. Some of the major sites which are worth to visit with any Dalhousie tour package are such as Panch Pulla, Church of Scotland, Satdhara falls and numerous alike. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20_" target="_blank">Manali tour packages</a></strong>, <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vZGFsaG91c2llLWRoYXJhbXNoYWxhLXRvdXJzLXBhY2thZ2VzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Dalhousie Tour Package</a></strong> and <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vbWFuYWxpLWhvbmV5bW9vbi1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Honeymoon in manali</a></strong>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb0ab7afe06b9ad489c5ba0fc86d374a" url=""><![CDATA[North East An Enigmatic Mystery<br/><br/>North eastern India is like a mystery unresolved. This enigmatic locale seduces one with its endearing and fleeting splendor. Northeast Tour offer experiences which are ever new in every visit  and will marvel you with novel surprises every time. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling is the appropriate place to start the expedition of North East. This verdant hill station located in Indian state of West Bengal is situated in the foothills of Mount Kanchenjunga. One can have the sight of Mount Kanchenjunga, the third largest peak in the world from all through Darjeeling. Darjeeling Himalayan Railway which is declared a world heritage site by UNESCO is the primary attraction. This railway is run on meter gauge and steam engines pull the “toy trains”, as they are fondly called. Other important attraction of Darjeeling Tour is the chance to witness sunrise from atop Tiger Hills. Seeing the sun rise up over Mount Kanchenjunga is a charming sight. Other attractions are Batasia loop, Chowrasta, Rock Garden, Ganga Maya Park, Peace Pagoda, Lloyd Botanical Garden, Padmaja Naidu Himalayan Zoological Park and Himalayan Mountaineering Institute.  The adventure of trekking and white water rafting can be had. Darjeeling tea would be an apt souvenir to take home, its aroma and taste being without parallels. 
<br /><br />Neighboring Sikkim is a biodiversity hot spot. Owing to gradations in altitude, diverse flora enriches the state. The region which homes such a variety plants in such a small area will be rare. Thereby the trek in Sikkim will be nature lover’s delight.  The capital of Sikkim, Gangtok is connected to Darjeeling through road. <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2dhbmd0b2stdG91cnMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Tours to Gangtok</a></strong>, situated at a height of thousand six hundred and seventy six meters, will be unforgettable with its temperate weather and friendly people. The scenery of surrounding hills from the town is breathtaking, especially the sight of Mount Kanchenjunga. 
<br /><br />There is much scope for trekking, mountaineering, river rafting and other nature oriented activities which are also the part of <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling Tourism</a></strong>. Momo, Wai-Wai, thukpa and other noodle based foods are popular in Gangtok. One can visit Himalayan Zoological Park which keeps the fauna of Himalayas in natural habitat. The zoo homes Himalayan Black Bear, barking deer, snow leopard, leopard cat, Tibetan wolf, masked palm civet, red panda, spotted deer and other animals. Then, there is Jawaharlal Nehru Botanical Gardens. The main places to visit in Sikkim are Rumtek Monastery, Tsongma lake, Nathu la pass, Baba Mandir,  Gurudongmar lake  and Dzongri trek.
<br /><br />The attractions the seven sister states of North east India offer is plainly marvelous.  They are Arunachal Pradesh, Assam, Meghalaya, Manipur, Mizoram, Nagaland and Tripura.
<br /><br />Arunachal Pradesh attracts many tourists. The main attractions include Tawang, an endearing town renowned for its Buddhist monastery, Ziro which is famous for its cultural festivals, Namdapha tiger project in Changlang and Sela Lake with Bamboo bridges overhanging the river. Arrangements for rafting and trekking can be had. Rich in wildlife, Arunchal Pradesh perhaps has the highest diversity of mammals in India.
<br /><br />Assam is famous for its large number of National parks and wildlife sanctuaries. It is the corridor to sister states. The main tourist attractions are Gauwhati, Brahmaputra, Jorhat, Majuli, Golaghat, Jatinga, Tezpur, Hajo, Goalpara, Chapanalla waterfall etc. 
<br /><br />Manipur with its rich culture, charming greenery and moderate climate is a tourist’s heaven.  Some places of interest in Manipur are Imphal, Shree Govindajee temple, Keibul Lamjao National park,  Loktak lake,  Churachandpur, Moreh etc.  
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Tours Packages to North East</a></strong>, <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Darjeeling Tour</a></strong> and <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL3BlbGxpbmctdG91ci5odG1s" target="_blank">Pelling Tours</a></strong>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com</a>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9ec0932bc826d6c32d70e15a7c858a74" url=""><![CDATA[Top Things to Do and See during Darjeeling Tours<br/><br/>Things to do and places to visit during tours to Darjeeling hills :
<br /><br /><strong>Joy Ride-</strong> The two feet narrow gauge train rides powered by steam engine is what draws tourists as it is only here that you will experience the slow, chugging, a time apart ride of your life
<br /><br /><strong>Chowrasta/Mall road-</strong> This is a delight to be relished at leisure because it was built for people to relax and leisure around. There are small eateries and restaurants around it providing standard meals to luxury dining. Also for the religious ones there is the Mahakal temple (observatory hills) to worship and pay respects to Gods and Goddesses. Also in and around this place one can find the Rhesus monkey playing and jumping tree to tree, signifying all forms and walks of life is respected.
<br /><br /><strong>Padmaja Naidu Zoological Park-</strong> A must visit to animal lovers. It houses a large number of wild animals ranging from the small deer to the mighty Bengal Tiger. The main attraction however is the Red Panda- an endangered species almost extinct from Mother Nature bounty.
<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Tenzing Rock-&lt;/b&gt; For those who love the sport of rock climbing and also for those who’d want it for experience, there is Tenzing rock. Here one can scale the rock with or without the help of experts and have adrenaline rush rappelling down the rock. It is one of the most visit places during <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tours to Darjeeling hills</a>.
<br /><br /><strong>Lebong Tea Gardens -</strong> Enjoy the freshness and aroma of the famed Darjeeling tea gardens and take a walk in the lush tea gardens here. While away time drinking tea and absorb the beauty of the hills.
<br /><br /><strong>Peace Pagoda-</strong> This is a place where one at any time may visit and feel the peaceful aura that envelopes it. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling is a place which cannot be described in a nutshell. The more one describes about the scenic beauty and aura of this place the more it pours in. The beauty and splendor is so vast and appealing that one needs to see it to feel it, planning <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a>. One cannot contain its beauty in words and therefore I would suggest a visit to the “Queen of Hills” Darjeeling.  
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2thbGltcG9uZy10b3Vycy5odG1s" target="_blank">Kalimpong tours</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2thbGltcG9uZy10b3Vycy5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour packages</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour operator</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="11f6fb4a5e22526e578cb42e27a51d05" url=""><![CDATA[Visit Himachal Pradesh and explore its awe-inspiring attract<br/><br/>India is home to the breathtaking attractions and destinations, having their distinctive features. Well if you are looking for hill stations in India, where you can take your family and friends and spend some quality time together away from the hustle bustle of life, then look no further than Himachal Pradesh, one of the finest and prosperous states, located at northern part of India. This state has gained popularity because of its stunning world-renowned hill stations named as the capital city Shimla, queen of hill stations Manali and the land god’s Kullu and etc. Every year tourists from across the world visit to this state in the hordes with different holidaying objective be it honeymoon, family holiday, adventure and many. Nature has gifted this state with such amazing attractions whose significance is just beyond the words and visual descriptions. In other words to explore all the hill stations of Himachal is just like a dream comes true.
<br /><br />Globally famous ‘Queen of Hill Stations’, Shimla is the summer capital of India and of course one of the most sought after tourist destination draws the attention of different kind of visitors. Home to the awe-inspiring attractions, it is one such place which depicts the perfect blend of natural attractions and colonial architecture, as it if spotted with so many colonial houses which were made by Britishers during their rule in India.  By visiting to this place, tourists have an opportunity to explore the natural attractions while enjoying the great shopping experience in Mall Road. Some of the best attractions that can be explored through <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><strong>Shimla tour packages</strong></a> include Jakhu Hill, Glen, Chail, Kufri, Summer Hill, Kamna Devi, Tara Devi, and many others.
<br /><br />Shimla is one such state where there is no dearth of attractions and enjoyment any more as it has so many things to offer to every kind of visitors. Apart from it’s ranging of attractions there are so many things that can be experienced during Shimla tours such as its well-cultured people, exotic restaurants, fascinating culture and excellent hotels and accommodations offers all the luxuries to the visitors and make them feel special.
<br /><br />Apart from Shimla you can also visit to Manali lovingly called ‘Switzerland in India’ considered an ideal place for honeymoon couples and adventure-thrillers. Picturesque landscapes, snow-lade peaks, mesmerizing waterfalls, lush green meadows and apple laden orchards makes Manali stunning and amazing. Some of the best attractions that can be explored through <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank"><strong>Manali tour packages</strong></a> include Devi Hadimba Temple, Rohtang Pass, Solang Valley, Rahala Waterfalls, Kullu and many others.
<br /><br />Apart from Shimla and Manali you can also visit Dharamsala famed as the holy abode of Tibetan Charismatic Leader Dalai Lama and houses the Tibetan Government in exile. Apart from its spiritual importance it is also popular with its admiring natural vistas. Some of the best attractions that can be explored through Dharamsala tour package are Triund, Kareri, Dharamkot, Dal Lake, Nurpur and many others.
<br /><br />Dalhousie is another attraction of tourist’s interest in Himachal and undoubtedly one of the most visited hill stations in India. Popular with several adventure activities like skiing, trekking, mountaineering, camping, it is must seen place of Himachal Pradesh. Khajjar, Lojali, Bakrota and etc are the popular attractions that can be explored through Dalhousie tour package.
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vbWFuYWxpLWhvbmV5bW9vbi1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank"><strong>Honeymoon in Manali</strong></a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20va3VsbHUtbWFuYWxpLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZS5odG1s" target="_blank"><strong>Kullu Manali</strong></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><strong>Shimla Tourism</strong></a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="161fab873e6974fa4a394a353075d349" url=""><![CDATA[The Divine Altars of Darjeeling<br/><br/>With the magnificent Kanchendzonga painting the horizon and lush green hills arising from the fertile plain of West Bengal is the Queen of hills known as Darjeeling. It is a tourist haven and has been the attraction of many foreigners and Indian tourists since the advent of time. Known mostly for its scenic beauty and awesome weather conditions, it is flocked by scores of tourists every year. However it is not only the scenic beauty and cool weather that attracts tourists. The majestic and divine temples that stand here have an aura of their own that brings people to be in peace and tranquility at their shrines. 
<br /><br />With the help of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling Travel Agent</a> feel the welcoming nature of Darjeeling for people and cultures of all walks of life has made it home to different religious backgrounds. One can find monasteries, temples, churches, mosques and pagodas dotting the beautiful and God fearing hills.
<br />North East Darjeeling presents a few among the most well known places of interest and worship here:-
<br /><br />Bhutia busty monastery- this Buddhist monastery is one of the oldest monasteries in Darjeeling. Destroyed by the earthquake of 1934, and later rebuilt by the king of Sikkim this is a landmark as old as Darjeeling herself. On visiting the monastery one can sense an aura of peace and tranquility that will leave him feeling blessed by the gods. Also to admire is the great architecture and the paintings on the walls of the monastery. The second floor also houses a library containing many old Buddhist books.
<br /><br />Ghoom monastery- on the highest elevation point of Darjeeling was built this age old monastery by Lama Sherab Gyatso in the year 1875. The monastery is from the Gelug school of Buddhism. Centuries old traditions are still instilled in the monks here.
<br /><br />Dali monastery- established during the 1900’s, this monastery was built by Kyabie Thuksey Rinpoche of the Kargyupa sect. Dali monastery’s main aim at the time was to preserve the ancient Buddhist teachings. The brightly painted walls in the monastery are a sight to be seen. “Chams” a religious dance is also performed here on auspicious days of the Buddhist calendar.
<br /><br />Japanese temple- the calm aura that this place resonates with is so peaceful and quiet that even footsteps seem too loud. Also known as the Nippozan Myohoji Buddhist temple was established by the Fuji Guru. The temple stands just near the Peace Pagoda and is built in pure Japanese architecture. The philosophy of the temple stands on peace and spirituality.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling package tours</a> also include the most holy shrines in town such as:-
<br /><br />The Mahakal temple- on the apex of the Darjeeling observatory hill is this holy sanctum both for the Hindus and Buddhists. The sound of the bells tolling and ringing combined with the chatter of monkeys altogether gives it its charm and sanctified atmosphere. A number of devotees flock this place to seek blessings and peace in their lives as is bestowed upon this place.
<br /><br />Senchal Dham- this temple is located at the highest place in town and is considered to one of the holiest places. The high elevation of this temple adds to the beauty and charm of the temple. The tiger hill observatory is also just a walk away from this temple.
<br /><br />Dhirdham Temple- located nearby the town’s railway station which is home to the toy train of Darjeeling, a heritage steam engine, lies this holy temple. To look at it resembles the Pashupati temple of Kathmandu and is a temple regularly visited by devotees for blessings and to pay homage. 
<br /><br />St. Andrews Church- built during the 1800s this colossal church looking over Darjeeling town is a figure that must be seen. The church holds service every Sunday and one can attend it. The building is colossal and has seen centuries pass by bringing changes along with them. 
<br /><br />Bishops house- this too built during the late 1800s is a wonderful church to see and worship in. Although it lies in the vicinity of town itself, it is remarkably clean and quiet. This particular church has a wonderful canopy of fir and other trees sheltering it. This church also served as a summer retreat for the Archbishop of Calcutta.
<br /><br />The sanctified aura with the acceptance of the hill towards all visiting or staying has given life to the many temples, monasteries, churches and mosques that have stood centuries along with her. Come feel the sanctity of beautiful Darjeeling as she shows you her religious side with Darjeeling tours. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">North East Darjeeling</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East tours</a>. Find more information to visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d907ed6e9aa0b64498ae77218685a386" url=""><![CDATA[Himachal Pradesh the Ideal Gateway to Hill Station Holidays<br/><br/>Dalhousie is a beautiful hill station in Himachal Pradesh established in 1854 by the British Empire. It was named after the British Viceroy Lord Dalhousie. It was meant for the summer retreat for the British troops and bureaucrats. It is built in and around the five hills, located on the western edge of the Dhauladhar mountain ranges of the Himalayas. It is surrounded by the beautiful snow-capped mountain. Scottish and the Victorian architecture are very much prevalent in the bungalows and the churches in the town. Dalhousie is known as a gate way to the hill station.
<br /><br />Dalhousie with its beautiful mountain and thick forest of deodar trees attract many tourists from near and far. Tourism in this place is soul refreshing because it is the quietest hill station in India. Tourism here is very calm and quiet and one can enjoy the nature in a relaxed manner. During winter Dalhousie experiences a very heavy snow fall leaving the tourists with everlasting fun. Tourism here is at its peak during winters. There are also many picnic spots which will let the tourists enjoy their holidays. There is 8 days 7 nights vacation and the destination covered is Delhi, Chandigarh, Dharamsala and Dalhousie. The nearest airport Gaggal (Kangra) 140- from Dalhousie. The nearest rail head is at Pathankot whish is well connected to Amritsar, Jammu, Delhi and Jalandhar. Onward journey from Pathankot to Chamba and Dalhousie is by Road. 
<br /><br />Himachal Pradesh is one of the most exciting place to visit for vacation. Shimla is the capital of the Himachal Pradesh. The town is spread over the ridge measuring of the 12 km and it is perhaps the biggest hill station of the world, it is the tourist resort in the real sense of the world. We can travel to Shimla by Rail, Air and by Road traffics. A <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Shimla tour package</a> provides us with deluxe and super deluxe rooms. In season times it is financially less than the off season.
<br /><br />The Kullu Valley has an ancient town in its lap called Manali. It is also known as the ‘summer capital of the India’.  Manali’s main asset is its proximity to the snow line. Manali is a very exclusive hill station with unspoiled beauty. The nearest airport to Manali is that of Bhuntar which 52 km from Manali is. From Bhuntar one can take a bus or taxi to Manali. The scenic beauty of the Kullu- Manali can be best enjoyed on a bus or a taxi. The nearest railhead is that of the Joginder Nagar and this narrow gauge railway station is 95km away from Kullu. At the Manali bus stand there are two booths where computerized reservation is done. The reservation can be done one month in advance. There are lots of places to stay in Manali; Hotels like Hotel Tourists, Sunshine guest house are famous in Manali. Water Rafting is also done in Manali for adventurous purpose. Mountaineering institute is also a source attraction for the tourists to travel to Manali. It is a very ideal place for nature lovers, explorers, history lovers. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vaGltYWNoYWwtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Himachal Tours</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vaGltYWNoYWwtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Manali Tour Package</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20va3VsbHUtbWFuYWxpLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZS5odG1s" target="_blank">Kullu Manali</a> . Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a17bf23eab1d2758c07584f13bbb527" url=""><![CDATA[Slow Chugging Ride in the Queen of Hills Onboard the Toy Tra<br/><br/>Famed worldwide for its picturesque beauty magnified by the majestic Kanchendzonga range as the backdrop, Darjeeling has had a lot of travelers from all over the world who come to get away from the hectic life and feel the radiance of beauty here. What better way to enjoy the beauty of the Queen of hills than a joy ride in the heritage toy train that slowly chugs its way through and around the hills letting you enjoy beauty with out any hurry.
<br /><br />Puffing out a column of smoke and whistling as she makes her slow but steady climb up the hill the blue colored steam engine looks magnificent. Over and around the green hills she climbs with no hurry making sure that the travelers onboard have a majestic Darjeeling tour. 
<br /><br />Built in between the early years of 1879 -1881 this blue steam engine is old as Darjeeling herself. Thus when a mention of Darjeeling is there the majestic toy train is beside her to give company as she has been doing from centuries ago. This steam powered train runs over a narrow 2 feet gauge and is one of the few such trains that remain in this sophisticated technological world. With <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour packages</a> enjoy the hurry free train ride which gives you enough time to take in the beauty and possibly capture it with your cameras. 
<br /><br />At present the steam engine powered joy ride goes up to Ghoom which is the former world’s highest railway station. The tracks wind through the town as it makes it way out toward Ghoom which is also the highest elevation point of Darjeeling. Watch small children wave to you with innocent smiles on their faces, cars passing honking their horns and behind it all lays the backdrop the majestic Kanchendzonga from which flows the green hills. The train circles around a loop before disappearing into a tunnel at the memorial grounds for the brave Gorkha’s known as Batasia loop. This memorial grounds have been established for those Gorkha soldiers who gave up their lives for India. 
<br /><br />One of the most famed writers Mark Twain said “The most enjoyable day I've spent on earth is of mixed ecstacy of deadly fright and unimaginable joy.&quot; after his first toy train ride to Darjeeling. When such famous writers have memorialized the toy train of Darjeeling in their undying words, then a ride on it should be a must when in the queen of hills.
<br /><br />The toy train has also been declared a world heritage train by UNESCO. Thus a ride on this train makes it a world heritage ride, something that again makes it a class apart than the other train rides.
<br /><br />When one takes a ride in this chugging train and looks at the yonder hills they can see the hills of Sikkim too. This too is a beautiful state that is a four hour drive from Darjeeling. One of the most beautiful places in Sikkim would be Pelling which is 135 km away from its capital city Gangtok. This place is home to the famous Pemayangtse monastery and Sangachoeling monastery. These two monasteries are among the oldest monasteries in Sikkim with Pemayangtse monastery being established at 1705 and the Sangachoeling monastery in 1697. Pelling also is home to the Khecheperi lake where it is believed that when leaves from the nearby trees fall into the lake, the birds that reside there swoop down and pick it up. Travel to this mystical and picturesque land with <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL3BlbGxpbmctdG91ci5odG1s" target="_blank">Pelling tours</a> and be awed by the beauty and aura of this place. 
<br /><br />With two beautiful places lying side by side each radiating with its own beauty and charm, it becomes a double treat to the travelers who come to holiday here. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East Darjeeling</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling travel agent</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a28f8d6943c5a9a6d42bd2edadbcfbbb" url=""><![CDATA[The Well-Known Hill Stations in Himachal Pradesh<br/><br/>Himachal Pradesh is one of the beautiful places in India and it attracts many tourists throughout the year. The landscape of the Himachal is amazing and beautiful. Himachal is blessed with sheer topographic diversity and pristine natural beauty. The state is curbed with the Tibetan plateau east, Jammu and Kashmir to the north and Punjab to the west. Shimla is the popular tourist’s destination within the state, it is also known as the” Queen of hills”. It is also well-known for its art and handcrafts.
<br /><br />Magical Manali which used to be “summer capital” of the British still retains it freshness and tourist come here to revive themselves from the roasting sun of the plains. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank">Manali tour packages</a> offers you with fascinated snow covered mountains, lush green valleys, fresh fruits orchids, and many more. Manali is also famous among the honeymoon couples; it is a paradise for the honeymooners to start a new life and create moments which will be cherished forever.
<br /><br />Kullu-Manali in Himachal Pradesh is a beautiful hill station with many religious places also known as the “abode of Gods”. Kullu-Manali lies in the mighty Himalayas on the one side with River Beas cutting across; it is filled with many lush green valleys, golden meadows, grazing herds, apple orchards, swift flowing rivers and many more. There are many adventure sports in Manali. One can go for thrilling and exciting trekking in the Kullu-Manali region which offers the best soft, medium and hard trekking opportunities, Jeep safari which is a journey over the Manali-Leh road through a immense mountain desert is a very memorable experience, if one has the desire to see the glaciers it is possible through skiing in the Solang valley which is 13km away from Manali, white water rafting in the Beas River is also exciting for those who wants thrill in their life, and fishing is also done to some extent.
<br /><br />Shimla is the biggest hill station in the world and is often known for winter holiday resort. It looks beautiful under the thick covered snow which is a major attraction for the tourists, it also has the open air ice skating which is famous among the tourists. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Shimla tourism</a> is amusing and it offers lots of opportunities for the tourists to explore this beautiful place full of natural beauty. The Mall and the Ridge are the major hold of the tourists in Shimla, Kurfi and Narkanda are also famous because of the snow covered land and skiing in winter season. Shimla combined with its nearby places is truly similar to heaven on earth and perfect for the tourism. Shimla tourism offers everlasting reminiscences in the heart and mind of the tourists.&lt;p&gt;
<br />Shimla tour packages takes you to the mesmerized snow covered mountain, verdant greenery of the forest, blue lakes which will make you feel enveloped in the cool breeze of Shimla. It also provides u with rich flora and fauna which is hotspot diversity. One can also enjoy the sights of Kurfi like Indira Gandhi Holiday Home and also enjoy the horse ride in the apple orchids. The packages are set according to the preferences and budget of the tourists.
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20va3VsbHUtbWFuYWxpLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZS5odG1s" target="_blank">Kullu Manali</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Shimla Tour Packages</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vbWFuYWxpLWhvbmV5bW9vbi1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Honeymoon in Manali</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9f8c0bb466846eaabe6895d81364030" url=""><![CDATA[Top Places to Visit during North East India Tours<br/><br/>North East India is enigmatically blessed with unmatched natural beauty. Undulating hills with vast stretches of tea gardens, revitalizing waterfalls, fast flowing rivers, vast stretches of tea gardens, dense forest, bird sanctuaries, picturesque lakes and more importantly exciting range of sightseeing spots all make Northeast India the most sought after tourism destination. It is the land of scenic glory and no wonder tourists from across the nook and corner of the globe, come here to enjoy ultimate vacation with immense pleasure and delights. 
<br /><br />North east India has so many alluring tourism destination and sightseeing spots. It is home to some of the finest and magnetizing attractions that engross the visitors and offer those lots of excitement that pull them again and again for North east tours. 
<br /><br />Well if you are really interested in exploring the wonderland of North East India, just go through this article and you will get some ideal about the important tourist places to visit and explore. 
<br /><strong>Assam</strong>
<br /><br />Call it a green paradise or the land with mystic charm, Assam has its own incredible attractions that entice thousands and hundreds of tourists from across the globe. It is the land with scenic beauty and no wonder it has so many enigmatic tourism attractions that engross tourists to enjoy vacation as well as explore so many touristic spots with comfort and luxury. Assam is truly an incredible state and so come and explores this mystic land with immense pleasure, fun and joy. Some incredible attractions that are worth to visit and explore during Assam tours are Digboi, Tezpur, Sibsagar, Majuli, Hajo, Chandubi Lake, Kaziranga National Park, Da Parbatia, Jatinga, Agnigarh and Cole Park. 
<br /><br /><strong>Darjeeling Tour</strong>
<br /><br />Located in the cozy lap of the Kanchan Junga, Darjeeling is one of the most sought after tourism destination entices thousands and hundreds of tourists from across the nook and corner of the globe. It is the land of scenic wonderments and no wonder; tourists from across the globe come here to enjoy the tours with immense pleasure and delights. Some of the alluring tourism attractions that are worth to visit and explore during Darjeeling tours are Tiger Hill, Observatory Hills, Padmaja Naidu Himalayan Zoological Park, Himalayan Mountaineering Institute, Batasia Loop, Chowrasta, Japanese Peace Pagoda, The Mall, etc. Along with that one can also go for memorable and enjoyable toy train journey, which is must for one and all during Darjeeling visit. So just book the tailor made <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour package</a> and explore the enigmatic charm and splendour with immense pleasure and delights.  
<br /><br />If you have enough time or spare 3 days in hand you can visit to Sikkim a picturesque state endowed with the sheer charm and beauty of the nature. During Sikkim tours you have wonderful opportunity to visit so many exciting tourist places which include Jawaharlal Nehru Botanical Garden, International Flower Festival, Nathula La Pass and the Old Silk Route, Changu Lake, Yumthang Valley, Samdruptse (Wish Fulfilling Hills), Gangtok, Pemayangtse, etc. You can also go for Pelling tours to enjoy the captivating view of the nature and well organised sightseeing spots and tourism attractions.
<br /><br />So plan your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">tour packages to North east</a> and enjoys ultimate vacation in the glory of the nature and take back home incredible memories to relish in forever and ever. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank">Darjeeling tours</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East Tours</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East Tour Packages</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a81d58c8240e68402d4ab93fba470ae8" url=""><![CDATA[Darjeeling Top Enigmatic Tourism Attractions and Sightseeing<br/><br/>Covered delightfully with the mist kissed hills and revitalizing greenery, the picturesque town of Darjeeling is globally famous for its outstanding natural beauty. It is the land of scenic wonderment and no wonder the town is visited by tourists from across the nook and corner of the globe. It is the land of scenic wonderments and no wonder enjoying vacation here in this cool and charming hill station of Darjeeling is a rewarding experience. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling has so many alluring tourism attractions and so is the reason it has become the most sought after destination that entice tourist for perfect and memorable hill station tours. Here one can enjoy lovely and memorable natural tour, explore the scintillating sightseeing spots as well as explore that enigmatic charm of the nature with immense pleasure and delights.
<br /><br />Some of the enigmatic sightseeing spots and tourism destinations that are worth to visit and explore are 
<br /><br /><strong>Padmaja Naidu Himalayan Zoological Park</strong>
<br /><br />Established in the year 1958 on 14 August, in the Birch Hill, Padmaja Naidu Himalayan Zoological Park is one of the most sought after tourist destination that is visited by tourists from across the globe. It is the land of scenic wonderment and entices thousands and hundreds of tourists from across the nook and corner of the globe. The park is located just few minutes’ walk from Chowrasta. Inside the part there are so many Himalayan animals and birds as well as Red Panda which is one of the major tourist attractions of PNHZp or Darjeeling Zoo. 
<br /><br /><strong>Darjeeling Tea Gardens </strong>
<br />Darjeeling tea takes the pride and occupies an indelible place in the long list of India tourism. Globally renowned for its high quality as we all aroma, Darjeeling Tea is world famous and is considered to be the best tea leaves in the world. There are around 78 tea gardens in Darjeeling hills which are accorded with the title. Darjeeling tea are grown as the height of 600 metres to 2000 metres above the sea level and requires more then 50 % waterfall and Darjeeling do not lack in this. The slopping terrains, cool and moist climatic conditions and the required average of rainfall give Darjeeling tea its unique flavour and aroma. Ambootia, Happy Valley, Puttabong, Soureni, Singla, Vah Tukvar, Orange Valley, Ringtong, etc are some of the most popular tea gardens from where the world’s best tea leaves are extracted. 
<br /><br />Well talking about the tourists places and sightseeing attractions, there are so many exciting tourism destination to visit and explore. Some of the enigmatic sightseeing spots to visit during Darjeeling tours are Rock Garden, Batasia Loop, Japanese Temple, Observatory Hill, The Mall, Chowrasta, Dhir Dham Temple, Singamari Ropeway, etc. These are some of the few attractions that are worth to visit and explore during Darjeeling tour. 
<br /><br />There are lot more hidden treasures that enhance the splendour of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tourism</a>. So if  you really want to see all, just book one from the many <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour packages</a> and explore the enigmatic and unparallel charm of this world famous hill station Darjeeling with immense pleasure, happiness and ecstasy. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East Tour Package</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East tours</a>. Find more information visit at <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com/</a></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a05b7da81af16e7b80b35b0ff4703746" url=""><![CDATA[Visit World’s Most Desirable Attractions with North-East T<br/><br/>There are so many attractions and destinations world-wide having their distinctive features but none is beautiful as like Darjeeling, undoubtedly the most sought after tourist destination. Located at north-eastern part of India, it is frequently visited by different kind of visitors all the year round. Whatever you are planning for be it honeymoon, family holiday, adventure or whatever you are looking for cultural tour, sightseeing, or simply looking for several stunning elements of nature, it perfectly knows how to make it possible in Darjeeling literally called the ‘Land of Thunderbolt’. 
<br /><br />Home to matchless attractions and enigmatic beauty, Darjeeling is an exotic hill station located in the state of West Bengal. Majestically located in the Lesser Himalayas, it presents tourist a breathtaking view of majestic Himalayas and especially of the world’s third highest peak the Kanchenjunga as well as presents picturesque sceneries with a brilliant view of snow caped mountain laced with plush tea gardens. The significance and splendour of this place is just beyond the words and visual delight, once you visit to this place you will find several reasons that why any one should choose it as their holidaying destination. Apart from there are so many things that gives this place an international recognition and enhance  the popularity of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tourism</a> world-wide such as its exotic resorts, unique culture, warm friendly people and plush luxurious hotels gives almost every facilities to the visitors.
<br /><br />Well in terms of natural attractions it has not any competitor but along with its innumerable attractions this hill station is well-renowned of the Darjeeling Himalayan Railways fondly called toy train that operates between the towns of new Jalpaiguri to this hill station. The Darjeeling Himalayan Railway is an outstanding example of ingenious railway engineering and is considered the first and most brilliant example of a hill passenger train. An essential part of Darjeeling tour packages and established in the year 1881, it is not only an engineering genius but also offers travellers with the most breathtaking views of nature and leave them spellbind. This well-organized railway still retains most of its original features.
<br /><br />Darjeeling tour would not be completed unless you do not go for jeep ride to Tiger hill another popular tourist attraction that generally conducted at the morning time to watch the sun rising from behind the Himalayan ranges lending a golden hue to snow capped peaks. It is one of the most famous attractions which seek a flock of tourists.
<br /><br />Apart from Darjeeling you can also visit to the state of Sikkim famous for its charismatic beauty and incomparable attractions.  Picturesque landscapes, amazing sightseeing, snow-laden peaks and all time soothing climatic conditions makes Sikkim one of the finest places in the planet. Due to the soothing climatic conditions, it also considered an ideal place for several fun-filled activities. Some of the best attractions of Sikkim tour packages include Phensang Monastery, Chungthang, and many others.
<br /><br />Apart from Sikkim and Darjeeling there are many other attractions of tourist’s interest such as Gangtok the capital city of Sikkim and an essential part of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North east tour package</a>. Chose the tailor made holiday package and make your vacations a remarkable experience. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour packages</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Tours to Darjeeling hills</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Tours to Darjeeling</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3b6232366c8337ad3da5d023f6879d8a" url=""><![CDATA[Himachal Pradesh the Dream Desire for all the Tourists<br/><br/>Himachal Pradesh in India is the most prominent states in the Northern India. This pretty state is truly of the fascinating destinations which basically entice all sorts of vacationers from every length and breadth of the whole world. This state is very pretty and is speckled with numerous tourist attractions and wonderful location. Himachal Pradesh is beautifully nestled in the immense Himalayans which basically attract the vacationers from all over the globe. This pretty state is of the major destinations where the vacationers come to enjoy their most pleasant holiday. 
<br /><br />Every kind of vacationers is welcome with open arm as this amazing state is beautifully speckled with brilliant tourist attractions and destinations which leave the vacationer spell bound on their visit. This pretty location is intensely lucky by the nature and is bliss for the vacationers all year long. There are numerous destinations in the state and truly all are sheer wonders which will overcast magical spurt on your visit.
<br /><br />Some of the major tourist attractions and destinations which easily entice vacationers as on their <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vaGltYWNoYWwtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Himachal tour package</a> are such as listed below:
<br /><br />Manali
<br /><br />Manali is located at Himachal Pradesh, at the finish of the valley, on the National Highway which ends up in Leh. The beauty of the landscape here is beyond words. The River Beas is another stunningly pretty spot of Manali which runs through the town. The imposing beauty of Manali compels lots of couple to start their newly married life at Manali itself. The tourist attractions of Manali instill the spirit if thrill and adventure inside you. For example you can try out canoeing, rafting and kayaking on the waters of Beas River at Manali. Some of the major tourist attractions and destinations to explore with any Manali tour package are such as Solang Valley, Banjar, Arjun Gufa, Tibetan Monastries and many alike easily lure all the vacationers from all over the globe. 
<br /><strong>
<br />Kullu</strong>
<br /><br />Kullu is another scenic hill station located near the picturesque hill station of Shimla. This wonderful hill station is beautifully endowed by the amazing and mighty Himalayans at backdrop and the splendid valleys look like picture book of a fairytale. Truly the splendid valleys, sprawling hills, enchanting lakes, breathtaking waterfalls and numerous alike easily attracts vacationers from all over the globe. This wonderful destination is home to splendid ancient temples which also attracts vacationers from all over the globe. Some of the major tourist attractions and destinations which easily attract the vacationers are such as Raghunath Temple; Excursions from Kullu, Jagannathi Devi Temple, Fairs and Festivals easily allure the vacationers from all over the globe for amazing vacation.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20va3VsbHUtbWFuYWxpLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZS5odG1s" target="_blank">Kullu Manali</a> truly will give you a unique experience which will always be remembered throughout your life.
<br /><br /><strong>Shimla</strong>
<br /><br />Shimla is the capital city of Himachal Pradesh and the most sought after tourist destination in the entire world. This hill town is truly the most visited and explored on your visit to Himachal and truly your visit to the serene world of Himachal would not be considered as worth one until you visit and explore the beguiling hill town of Shimla. Some of the major tourist attractions and destinations to visit and explore with Shimla tours are such as Himachal State Museum and Library, Christ Church, Shimla State Museum and numerous alike which easily entice vacationers from all over the globe. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank">Manali tour package</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Shimla tours</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vaGltYWNoYWwtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Himachal Tours</a>. Find more information visit at <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com/</a></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24602be3a4523d836b4f004e96c4cc30" url=""><![CDATA[Darjeeling the Favorite Hill Station Among the Tourists<br/><br/>The state of West Bengal has a very beautiful and charming hill station, Darjeeling which is well known for its tea and tourism. Darjeeling tea is famous worldwide for its freshness and best aroma and its tourism is also famous throughout India as well as abroad. It is a popular place among the foreigners. It is a calm and silent Hill Station popular for its many interesting places to visit. It is also well known for its scenic charm, snow clad mountains and its extensive tea gardens. 
<br /><br />The pleasant and the moderate weather of Darjeeling attract many tourists from across the globe. Best season to come for Darjeeling tour is from September to June. The climatic condition of Darjeeling can be compared to that of the United Kingdom. It receives extreme rainfall in the months of July and August. The maximum temperature during summers does not exceed 25 degree and during winters it falls to -2 degree. 
<br /><br />There are many interesting places to visit in Darjeeling with any of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour packages</a>. The most famous is the Tiger Hill which is the sunrise view point over the Kanchenjunga. Taking the view of first rays of the sun fills the tourists with awe and surprise, the view of the great eastern Himalayas and the Mount Everest is also visible from here. Tea gardens and the process of manufacturing tea are also interesting and worth to see. Mall road which is a linking road to Chowrasta is a relaxing place for the tourists; here they can catch the view of exotic scenic beauty of nature that they have never seen before. 
<br /><br />Others places to visit in Darjeeling are Himalayan Zoological Park, Botanical Garden, Mahakal Mandir, Dhir Dham temple and others too. Some of the famous once are the Batasia Loop, Buddhist Monasteries, Japanese Peace Pagoda, Dhir Dham temple, War Memorial, National History Museum and Himalayan Mountaineering Institute.
<br /><br />In Darjeeling we can also find many Wildlife Sanctuaries which is the preserver of many endangered and rare species. It also has wide variety of plants, animals and birds. For observing Wildlife closely one can visit Himalayan Zoological Park, Snow Leopard Breeding Centre, Mahananda Wildlife Sanctuary and Jaldapara Wildlife sanctuary. Trekking and Darjeeling Himalayan Railway are the main attraction of the tourists.
<br /><br />Darjeeling is a charming place with extravagant places to visit. Every year thousands of tourists come to visit this outstanding place booking from the many available <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">package tour to Darjeeling</a>. The accommodations provided by the Darjeeling hotels are world class. They give the tourists the best opportunity to see and witness the beauty of Darjeeling. The Heritage Hotels in Darjeeling are the best place to stay which will gives you the best facilities accompanied by best service and hospitability. The stay in the tea estates is also a very good option with a life time experience; they can enjoy the peaceful stay away from the busy life of the city. Some of the well known hotels in Darjeeling are Hotel Mayfair, Cedar Inn, Sinclair, Elgin group of Hotels, Windermere and many more.
<br /><br />Darjeeling is a peaceful place bestowed with all the elements of nature by the Almighty. It is a perfect Gate way for the nature lovers, trekkers, honeymooners and almost a desired place to enjoy for all the age groups people.
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tourism</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">tour packages to North East</a>. Find more information visit at <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com</a></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c0fbcb8a8edcbae0ca3710a2439027d5" url=""><![CDATA[Manali the Irresistible Hill Station of Himachal Pradesh<br/><br/>The legends have it that a fish that was saved and brought up by a man named Varvasvata who later warned him of a flood that would drown the earth. The fish advised the man to build an ark strong enough to survive the raging flood so that he may be saved from the disaster. It is said that the great ark of Varvasvata is said to have landed here after the great flood that submerged the earth and life restarted here.
<br /><br />The natural beauty that binds this beautiful hill station of Manali is immaculate. Located at a height of 6400 ft above sea level in the state of Himachal Pradesh this hill station is simply amazing. The key to the revenue generated here is the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vbWFuYWxpLXRvdXJpc20uaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><strong>Manali tourism</strong></a> and the tourism that is so vibrant here is due to the great natural beauty surrounding this place.
<br /><br />The snow capped mountains that almost always have a sea of clouds swirling towards the summits, the lush green meadows, valleys and hills covered with coniferous forests, raging rivers, ancient temples, artistic monasteries, adventure sports and the wonderful people here are what makes this place a beauty. Come discover this great hill station located in the lap of the Himalayas overflowing with beauty with the help of our Manali tour packages. 
<br /><br />The must do and see places when on a Manali tour would be: -
<br /><br />Hidimba temple- One of the most revered temples lying in the bosom of this wonderful hill station would be the Hidimba temple. The temple is constructed over a huge rock that has mushroomed out from the bounty of Mother Nature this place has an amazing sanctified aura. 
<br /><br />Rohtang Pass- This is the highest point of the Manali-Keylong road. The views that one gets from here of the towering mountains are simply amazing. The mountains with a sea of clouds near the summits are a grand sight that needs to be seen when here. 
<br /><br />Vashist Hot water springs- Nature has also blessed this place not only with natural beauty but also with rejuvenating hot springs. These hot water springs are enriched with sulphur and it is said to relive you of the various ailments you may be suffering from. A dip in one the springs are sure to wash away any tiredness and stress you may be feeling. 
<br /><br />Solang Valley- this is one of the most popular destinations that tourists flock to. The best thing about this valley is that it changes with the seasons. The summer and spring season carpets this valley with lush green grass and blossoming flowers making it an ideal picnic spot while the winter blankets it with a thick layer of snow making it one of the most frequented ski grounds. The picturesque views that one sees from this place is spellbinding.
<br /><br />Waterfalls- there are a number of cascading waterfalls here in Manali and some of the most visited ones are Rahala falls, Jogini falls and Jana falls.
<br /><br />The adventure sports that Manali is well known for are paragliding, trekking, skiing, snowboarding, white water rafting etc. The adventure sports here are a great way to witness the beauty of nature with a hint of excitement.
<br /><br />Another destination that lies within the vicinity of this spectacular place of beauty is Shimla. One can enjoy the spoils of Shimla’s beauty by taking our <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><strong>Shimla tour</strong></a>. Witness the beauty that lies in this beautiful hill stations with our services and take away a memories as beautiful as the hill stations you would be visiting.
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank"><strong>Manali tour packages</strong></a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20va3VsbHUtbWFuYWxpLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZS5odG1s" target="_blank"><strong>Kullu Manali</strong></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank"><strong>Manali Holiday packages</strong></a>. Find more information visit at <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com</a></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a19fe767d18fb70e08950946108081f4" url=""><![CDATA[The Ethnic States of North East India<br/><br/>The cultural and ethnic states of North India is well known as the “Seven sisters and one brother”. The states share its international boundaries with China, Bhutan, Bangladesh, Burma and Nepal. Arunachal Pradesh, Assam, Manipur, Mizoram, Meghalaya, Nagaland and Tripura are the seven sisters with Sikkim as the Big Brother. With over hundred and sixty six tribes with linguistic, cultural and traditions the place is worth a visit. 
<br /><br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North East tour packages</a> serve you with fascination tourist destination. The gate way to the North east is Assam. The rolling hills, the lush green tea garden, picturesque landscapes, cascades waterfalls Assam is truly amazing. The Brahmaputra River that flows through Assam is a resource of rich and fertile alluvial soil. Arunachal Pradesh is the biggest state of the North East located on the eastern Himalayas synonyms with land of the rising sun. The snow capped mountains, the misty hills, serene flowing rivers, monasteries, gompas, rarest collections of flora and fauna Arunachal Pradesh is a lifetime adventure experience.
<br /><br />The North East tours are unique in its own way. Completely different states compared to other states of India which has escaped the influence of Sanskrit and has evolved with their own beliefs, conventions, traditions, customs, law and orders. Take the divine and the cultural tour where time stands still in the verge of civilization. The tribal dominant area has eloquent charm with similar as well as distinctive features. These tribal areas are highly sensitive due to urbanization and globalization which has forced the tribal to give up their tribal lures to adjust with the modern world.
<br /><br />Tour packages to North East are available online where one can opt for the cheapest and the best holiday package. The mesmerizing natural bounties of Mizoram the second state with highest literacy rate, Manipur, Meghalaya, Tripura along with Nagaland where the Nagas catches the early bird is worth a visit.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour packages</a> offers you a relaxing and a recreation vacation like no other hill resorts does. Enter the town hidden in the mist and open up viewing the majestic Kanchenjunga the third highest summit in the world. Sit back and take a joy ride on the Heritage Toy Train offering you the scenic natural beauty of Darjeeling. The Ghoom station located on the elevation of two thousand two hundred and twenty five meters above sea level is the second highest station of the world. Batavia the memorial ground of the Ghurkhas, the ultimate soldiers. Here the train almost turns to an angle of three hundred and sixty degrees catching its own tail. The panoramic view of the Kanchenjunga and the Dali Monastery are of splendid pleasure. The Japanese Peace Pagoda, Tiger Hill the sunrise point, the Observatory Hills and Chowrasta a sitting room for all are some of the hot spot of Darjeeling.
<br /><br />Trekking in Darjeeling is a long carried legacy of the hills. The foot hills of Himalayas are excellent trekking zone. Trek to Phalut and catch the glimpse of breath taking views. Treks are available all the year around but the month of march- April is the peak season. The blooming of rhododendrons and magnolias leaves you spellbound. Tastes the local “guras ko rakshi”, a local alcohol made by fermented flowers of rhododendrons and view the red pandas in the wild. Pull yourself to the limits and enjoy the sweet results of the sweat. Your Darjeeling tour without a trek is incomplete.
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Tour packages to North East</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling Tourism</a>. Find more information to visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f422eb9269dc23071e48f4021246ee1c" url=""><![CDATA[Darjeeling the Queen of Hills That Is Located In the North E<br/><br/>The Queen of Hills is located in the vast state of West Bengal and goes by the name Darjeeling. The name Darjeeling is derived from the word Dorjee-ling which literally translates into “the land of thunder”. The awesome weather conditions, scenic beauty, world famous tea gardens, the UNESCO world heritage toy train, friendly people and many other things indigenous to the hills of Darjeeling make it one of the most visited hill stations in the world.
<br /><br />Tour packages to north east provided by us also includes this queen of hills that is enveloped by beauty. The first sight that will greet you as you arrive to this mesmerizing town of beauty would be the majestic Kanchendzonga looks as if its been painted on the horizon. This is a sight that will put a smile upon your face and warmth in your heart. The road that leads to this hill station is also filled with beauty. You will see a great number of trees that line the roads of Darjeeling. The trees range from Rhododendrons, fir, pine, magnolias, teak and add to the charm of the place. The drive to this queen of hills itself is a holiday as the natural beauty that you get to see on the way to Darjeeling is spellbinding. Take a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour package</a> and feel the beauty of nature come alive from the moment you start your journey uphill from the plains of Siliguri.
<br /><br />Darjeeling tours provide you with a lot of places to see and things to do in this hill station which will make your stay here an incredible one. There are a lot of things to see and do here and a few of the recommended ones by <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">north east tour packages</a> would be:-
<br /><br />Joy ride- take a tour of the beautiful hills aboard the UNESCO world heritage toy train and witness the beauty of the hills at a slow peaceful pace. The toy train is powered by a steam engine which is almost as old as Darjeeling herself. A ride on this train is a must for without it your trip to the queen of hills would be incomplete.
<br /><br />Tiger hill observatory- this is the highest point of the town and the views of the majestic Kanchendzonga range from here is breath taking. The sunrise that one can see from here is mesmerizing. The play of colours seen during the sunrise on the high snow capped mountain peaks is spellbinding. One should make it a point to witness this beauty of nature come alive when in the hills of Darjeeling.
<br /><br />Padmaja Naidu Zoological Park- the zoo of Darjeeling is well known for its endangered inhabitants. The red panda, clouded leopard, royal Bengal tiger, snow leopard and the Himalayan black bear are the main attractions of the zoo.
<br /><br />Adventure sports- north east tours also is synonymous to adventure due to the terrains that provide excellent grounds for adventure. The adventure sports that are available here in the Queen of Hills are trekking, rock climbing, whitewater rafting, parasailing etc. Feel the thrill of adventure flowing through your veins when you take part in these adventure sports.
<br /><br />There are many other things to do places to see in this beautiful queen of hills and is only well known when visited.
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tours</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Tour packages to north east</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">north east tours</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="afadd6af35f7d42d8d9273fa83d2df9" url=""><![CDATA[Himachal Pradesh the Only State with the Chain Paradise Hill<br/><br/>Himachal Pradesh is the only state in India with the most number of hill stations. It is one of the most beautiful and charming state surrounded by the Himalayas and thick Deodar forest and apple orchards in the northern India. Perfect located in the lap of the Himalayas, Himachal Pradesh today is one of the most admirable tourist destinations for its charm and glory of nature possess by it. 
<br /><br />The state by name means abode of snow and in fact, most of the areas are of the state are covered with snow and are alluring beyond words to express. It is a magical land with scintillating hills covered with snow on the exotic lush green vegetations giving immense of services for tourist across the globe. Manali, Shimla and Kullu are some of the popular tourist hot spots of the state. They can impressive and delight the heart of every single visitor coming to for tours in it.
<br /><br /><strong>Manali-snow paradise</strong>
<br /><br />It is one of the main tourist spot where tourists often embark to enjoy the chilly atmosphere of mountains and hills and enjoy incredible extraordinary thrilling adventure expeditions. Situated in the northern end of Kullu valley, this charming hill station of Himachal Pradesh has become a hot spot for summer escape amidst the appealing magical atmosphere of cool and appealing climate. Manali tour packages wonderful opportunity to enjoy the thrilling adventure of high rocky mountain path walk, trekking in the thick forest and rock climbing to give you an exhilarating unforgettable adventure experience during holiday trip. There are also many options beside adventure and also adventure in the most different ways like sightseeing, valley sporting games, skiing and paragliding are some of the activities undertaken by tourism mostly in Manali and Kullu.  
<br /><br />With <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20va3VsbHUtbWFuYWxpLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZS5odG1s" target="_blank">Kullu Manali</a> tour packages you can relish the popular Rohtang pass, explore the marvels such as Rozy falls, Rahala waterfalls and enjoy the Solang Valley. It also gives a wonderful sightseeing opportunity to experience the awesome Hidimba temple, Monasteries and Vashist Hot Springs. 
<br /><br /><strong>Shimla- queen of the hills </strong>
<br /><br />Shimla serve as the capital city of the state and also a popular hub for tourist to gather during tours. It is often referred to as the queen of the hill stations for its superiority by nature.  Shimla is most popular for its services of hotels and lodgings and the best site for local hang out in malls, streets and ridges in the heart of the city. Hotels and tourist amenities servicing works have made the city the biggest industry site for tourism services. If you wish to experience the culture and traditional lifestyle of this culture blundered state visit take up Shimla tour packages and you will experience all your desire wishes in it. The buildings dotted on the streets, churches, malls and every site of this city will inspire you about the rich culture and heritage of Himachal Pradesh the mixture land of Tibetans and Indians. 
<br /><br />Himachal Pradesh offers different hills stations with different excitements with travel packages to enjoy nature and its marvels. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vZGFsaG91c2llLWRoYXJhbXNoYWxhLXRvdXJzLXBhY2thZ2VzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Dalhousie tour packages</a> are also one of its travel packages that will refresh your life. Take up the packages and receive the undulating gratification possible.   
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank">Manali tour packages</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Shimla tour packages</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Shimla tourism</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="290bac0225465cc33287b46c5df6d7e1" url=""><![CDATA[Find unbeatable attractions with north east tour package<br/><br/>Well holidays have always been the best way to unwind, relax and it is the only way when one can spend some quality time with family and friends. If there is a feeling like stress and anxiety in your mind just because of your hectic schedule of life and for that purpose if you wish for an exotic holidaying destination then look no further than Sikkim and Darjeeling, a most visited destination of India. 
<br /><br />Often referred as the ‘land of Thunderbolt’, Darjeeling is one of the beautiful hill stations well-renowned for its enigmatic beauty and virgin natural attractions. Nature has gifted this town with such heavenly attractions whose significance is just beyond the words and visual delight. Every year from different parts of the world, people visit this town in a great numbers with different holidaying purpose, be it honeymoon, family trip, or adventure also. Due to several romantic trekking trails and towering peaks including Kanchenjunga it is also considered an ideal place for several adventure and fun-filled activities.
<br /><br />Picturesque landscapes, sprawling grasslands, vast tea gardens, cascading waterfalls, meandering rivers, wildlife parks, blissful climate and ranges of floras and faunas make this place not less than paradise on earth. Apart from its heavenly attractions there are many other things that give this place an international recognition and enhance the popularity of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tourism</a> world-wide such as its exotic resorts, warm-friendly people, unique culture and excellent five star hotels and accommodations. Whatever may your purpose of visiting, it perfectly knows how to make it possible in this stunning land. 
<br /><br />There are many attractions that one can experience while visiting this place but Darjeeling tour would not be completed unless you do not for toy train tour, one of the prime attractions in this beautiful town. Officially known as Darjeeling Himalayan Railway, the Darjeeling toy train transports passengers through lower reaches of the Eastern Himalayas to the rolling hills and lush green aromatic tea plantations of Darjeeling. Toy train tour is full of excitement, thrill and never-ending holidaying experience. 
<br /><br />Apart from there are many other attractions of tourists interest named as Batasia loop, Bhutia Busty Gompa, Botanical Gardens, Chowrasta, Dhoom Gompa, Observatory hills. Apart from these attractions you can also visit to Tiger Hill considered an ideal part of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour packages</a>. Well-renowned for eye-catching sun-rise, Tiger hill is located about 11km from the main town, set an altitude of 2555 meters above the sea level.
<br /><br />Well if you wish to explore some other attractions of nature while playing with snow then must head to Sikkim, one of the beautiful state or hill stations in northeast region. Categorized into four districts, it is one of the greatest tourist attractions gathers large number of visitors every year. Well renowned for natural virgin attractions, scenic waterfalls and stunning monasteries, it is one such state whose significance is just beyond the words and visual delight. Some of the stunning attractions that one can explore through Sikkim tour packages include Do-Drul Chorten, Saramsa Garden, Jawaharlal Nehru Botanical Garden, Water Garden and many. 
<br /><br />Apart from there are many other attractions that one can explore through North east tour package such as Along, Pasighat, Mirik, Halflong and many more.
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Tour packages to north east</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North east tour package</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cf52aa17f29196c6dd48e7a26f5699a3" url=""><![CDATA[Enjoy Attraction with Nature during This Vacation with Manal<br/><br/>Manali is a popular tourist destination located at the corner end of the northern Kullu valley in Himachal Pradesh. It is a charming hill station situated at a height of 2050 m in the Himalayas on the side of the Beas River. It is a staging point for many adventure lover and summer escapers for vacations and weekend makers. The magical charms of the awesome image of snow filled landscape have been the main attention of tourist worldwide. 
<br /><br />Ladakh, Lahaul, Spiti and Rohtang are located near Manali and are also included among the top fascinating popular tourist wanted attractions of Manali tour package.  
<br /><br /><strong>Awesome sites that will give thrill Manali tours are as follows:</strong><strong>
<br /><br />Solang Valley</strong>
<br /><br />It is a splendid valley between Solang village and Beas Kund. This valley offers awesome spectacular view of glaciers and snow capped mountains and peaks of the great Himalayas. The place is well known for its adventurous sports of both winter and summer besides it the valley also holds numerous fascinating sites such as Rahalla waterfalls, Hadimba temple and a shrine of Lord Shiva on the top of the hills. Trekking, skiing, skating, parachuting, Zorbing and paragliding are some of the commonly undertaking activities of this site. Solang valley is a common attraction of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20va3VsbHUtbWFuYWxpLXRvdXItcGFja2FnZS5odG1s" target="_blank">Kullu Manali</a>. So, if you are traveling for any of this destination you can easily take a route through it and experience its heart griping hospitality and excellent services offered by tourism in this site.
<br /><br />Other popular attractions are Rohtang Pass, Kothi and Vashisht spring. They are included almost in most of Himachal Pradesh popular hill tourist packages. You can enjoy relish them with Shimla tour packages or Manali tour packages. There is no different for Himachal tourism to differentiate. So, for best experience always go for travel packages and get as much delight and satisfaction from tourism services. 
<br /><br /><strong>Shimla-Lovely snow queen of Himachal Pradesh </strong>
<br /><br />It is a popular hill station hunted by tourist. Shimla is one of the best sites for holiday retreat in summer and is often known for its Victorian architecture which reflects in certain areas of the Mall and The Ridges. This charming capital city of Himachal Pradesh is a heritage site which was once discovered by the British and found it to be one of the best summer estates. Shimla blessed with bountiful natural wealth with the atmosphere of peace and tranquility. 
<br /><br />Shimla tourism offers unique attractions of an open air skating rink, distant view of snow clad peaks, Shimla seven hill attractions, vibrant mall, intriguing architectural grandeur, gaiety theatre and many other wonderfully alluring and amazing sites are found in this small charming hill station. 
<br /><br />There are also many colonial edifices, ancient temples, intricate churches, quaint cottages and many other sightseeing marvels offered with Shimla tour packages. Purchase them for exhilarating fun trip.   
<br /><br />Other similar enigmatic sites like Dalhousie is also one of the most interesting site and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vZGFsaG91c2llLWRoYXJhbXNoYWxhLXRvdXJzLXBhY2thZ2VzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Dalhousie tour packages</a> are also highly demanded by nature lovers.  
<br /><br />The place like Manali, Shimla and Dalhousie are the examples of tourist places in India which captivates the imagination of tourist worldwide. Visit it and experience them for life time experience. 
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Shimla tour packages</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20v" target="_blank">Manali tour package</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tYW5hbGl0b3VycGFja2FnZS5jb20vc2hpbWxhLW1hbmFsaS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Shimla tourism</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.manalitourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.manalitourpackage.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cbaccbc215da79b695e5bd05061745ce" url=""><![CDATA[Darjeeling the Queen of the North Eastern Hills<br/><br/>Darjeeling is a beautiful hill station of north east India situated at an altitude of about 2590 meters. It is the most charming Himalayan city in the Indian state of West Bengal and is an internationally renowned well popular tourist destination of the country. This particular destination is popular for its quality tea production and Darjeeling mesmerizing Himalayan railway which is often called as a toy train of Darjeeling and is recorded as UNESCO World Heritage Site. Darjeeling today is one of the most popular sought after international tourist destination of the world.
<br /><br />Apart from the world recognized attraction of Himalayan railway and tea, this awesome tourist destination of north eastern India is a tourist hot spot which have earned international fame for the magnificent view of the sunrise over Kanchenjunga and the great eastern Himalayan Mountains. Even the world’s highest mount Everest peak appears to hesitant rays of the early morning sun and it often paints the peak in pale gold which is the core beautify and attraction found in this site. You can experience them with Darjeeling tour. 
<br /><br />Its scintillating scenery can drench the heart of every traveler and gives you the true feeling of breathtaking peace and tranquility that often unwinds ailments of life. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank">Darjeeling tourism</a> is one of the most nature attach tourism that will help you to rejuvenate life at the same time give you the true ecstasy of mingling with nature.  
<br /><br />The places such as Tiger Hill, Batasia Loop and the War memorial, the Ava art Gallery, Chowrasta and Mall, Rock Garden and Ganga Maya Park, Peace Pagoda are some of the popular and awesome sightseeing tourist attractive sites. The places like the oldest Botanical Garden of Lloyd Botanical Garden with varieties of flora is famous for its two living fossils is also a common ground for lovers and couples often spend hours basking in this beautiful site. Other popular ideal site for hanging out during tours and travels included in <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour packages</a> are the nightingale park or Shrubbery Park and places like Padmaja Naidu Himalayan Zoological Park and Happy Valley Tea Garden are some of the popular sites hunted by leisure escapers from across the globe. 
<br /><br />If you are a true tour thriller, make sure to explore all the possible sites in your given time instead of dropping again and again in the same destination to relish different attractions found in it. Sikkim tour packages is also one of the most striking packages to explore the in and out wonders of Darjeeling for the best travel experience. Ghoom Monastery and other numerous monasteries found in Darjeeling mostly are inherited or are founded by the Buddhist monks of the Tibetans. 
<br /><br />North east tour package has become quite popular for its outstanding hospitality and services rendered with free and friendliness of local people. With most of packages you can enjoy excellent culture, foods, shopping and true adventure experience of trekking and other nature involvement. 
<br /><br />If you are looking forward for an extra-ordinary thrills to undertake during this vacation. The best site you can always rely is the hill stations for adventure cruise and forest expedition highly facilitated sites.       
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Darjeeling tour</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">North east tour package</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL3Npa2tpbS10b3VyLXBhY2thZ2UuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Sikkim tour packages</a>. Find more information visit at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c2a8b43a9b946777ab194e778b800fd3" url=""><![CDATA[Darjeeling the Most Charming Hill Station in India<br/><br/>Darjeeling a beautiful and charming hill station in the State of West Bengal is popular for its everlasting natural charm and the fragrance of the tea gardens. Every year many travelers from India as well as abroad travel to this place to witness its beauty in natural form and experience the pleasant climate which is a very good remedy for the tourists who gets tired from the scorching heat of the plains. It is a quiet hill station with many interesting places to visit. Spending holidays in these extraordinary place will create such memories that will be very hard to forget and will also be cherished for a lifelong. 
<br /><br />Darjeeling is considered to be the best hill station in India as it offers the best Darjeeling tourism for the tourists and the visitors. Darjeeling tours take you to hilly region which is completely different and unique from the plains. It also takes you to the beautiful locations like Observatory hill from where the tourists can observe the different mountain ranges including Kanchenjunga on a clear day, another beautiful location that is highly admired and liked by the tourists are the a pleasant and cool walk through the Mall Road which provides the tourists with cool and refreshing air, the trees and the greenery are found in plentiful through this road, this road leads to the main road popularly known as Chowrasta. The unspoilt beauties of this charming place have been attracting many tourists and providing them an excellent opportunity to spend time in the abode of nature and also get a chance to bath themselves in the freshness of pure and pristine nature.
<br /><br />Darjeeling is truly a treasure located in and around the mighty Himalayas. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank"><strong>Tourism in Darjeeling</strong></a> is famous around the world as it offers the tourists and the visitors with many exciting and thrilling places that will leave a pleasing effect on the tourists. The tea tourism of Darjeeling is the best as compared to other places. The varied landscape, the pleasant weather and the most important the slopes of the tea gardens are the main source of tourism in Darjeeling, apart from this the joyous and the meandering ride of the “toy train” is really a remarkable experience in Darjeeling. It also offers adventure activities like trekking, rock climbing, ropeway rides, boating in the lakes and much more such activities.
<br /><br />Darjeeling is the dream destination for all the tourists and the travelers as it is a perfect destination for all kinds of vacation and it is truly a heaven for the newly married couples to celebrate their honeymoon in this serene place without any and noise and the hustle of the city life. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank"><strong>Tours to Darjeeling</strong></a> takes you to the interesting places like aromatic tea gardens, tiger hill, Senchal Lake, Botanical garden, Mall, Chowrasta and many others places too. It also gives you an opportunity to visit lush green places like Mirik, Pelling, Kalimpong etc . It is an idle place for the tourists to relax and get lost in the past by memory lane. Tour in this place will create many memories that will always linger in their mind as a good memory.&lt;p&gt;
<br /><br />Surendra Rawat is an eminent analyst and writer in Travel &amp; Tourism related topics. He has authored many books on tour guide for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL2RhcmplZWxpbmctdG91cmlzbS5odG1s" target="_blank"><strong>Darjeeling tourism</strong></a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank"><strong>North East Darjeeling</strong></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYXJqZWVsaW5ndG91cnBhY2thZ2UuY29tL25vcnRoLWVhc3QtdG91ci1wYWNrYWdlcy5odG1s" target="_blank"><strong>tour packages to North</strong> East</a> Find more information visit at <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.darjeelingtourpackage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.darjeelingtourpackage.com</a></strong>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>