<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="65-XX" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="a56d9fe621e9526094c9894dd22ca714" url=""><![CDATA[POSITIVE<br/><br/>A husband and wife are getting ready for bed.  The wife is standing in front of a full-length mirror taking a hard look at herself.
<br /><br />&quot;You know, dear,&quot; she says, &quot;I look in the mirror, and I see an old woman.  My face is all wrinkled, my boobs are barely above my waist, and my butt is hanging out a mile.  I've got fat legs, and my arms are all flabby.&quot;
<br /><br />She turns to her husband and says, &quot;Tell me something positive to make me feel better about myself.&quot;
<br /><br />He studies hard for a moment thinking about it and then says in a soft, thoughtful voice,
<br />&quot;Well, ..there's nothing wrong with your vision.&quot;
<br /><br />Services for the husband will be held Saturday morning at 10:30 at St Anselm's Memorial Chapel. Female friends of the family are invited
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4329fa2e6b67a90e1fcb7dbfe6bf6731" url=""><![CDATA[F.D.A.<br/><br/>It has come to the attention of researchers of the Food and Drug Administration that previously unanticipated complications result when Viagara is taken along with Ex-Lax.
<br /><br />Both products tend to act together and magnify the effects of the other.  The researchers have concluded that the result is that you end up both coming and going at the same time.
<br /><br />It *really* gets complicated when Prozac is taken with the other drugs, because then, you really don't give a shit if you're cumming or going!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ddf5fa03359c17aa3be2dff765269f46" url=""><![CDATA[THE DENTIST<br/><br/>HAVE YOU EVER BEEN GUILTY OF LOOKING AT OTHERS YOUR OWN AGE AND
<br />THINKING, 'SURELY I CAN'T LOOK THAT OLD.  WELL.. YOU'LL LOVE THIS
<br />ONE.
<br /><br />MY NAME IS ALICE SMITH AND I WAS SITTING IN THE WAITING ROOM FOR MY
<br />FIRST APPOINTMENT WITH A NEW DENTIST. I NOTICED HIS DDS DIPLOMA,
<br />WHICH BORE HIS FULL NAME.
<br /><br />SUDDENLY, I REMEMBERED A TALL, HANDSOME, DARK-HAIRED BOY WITH THE SAME NAME HAD BEEN IN MY HIGH SCHOOL CLASS SOME 40-ODD YEARS AGO.  COULD HE  BE THE SAME GUY THAT I HAD A SECRET CRUSH ON, WAY BACK THEN?   UPON SEEING HIM, HOWEVER, I QUICKLY DISCARDED ANY SUCH THOUGHT.
<br /><br />THIS BALDING, GRAY-HAIRED MAN WITH THE DEEPLY LINED FACE WAS WAY TOO OLD TO HAVE BEEN MY CLASSMATE.
<br /><br />AFTER HE EXAMINED MY TEETH, I ASKED HIM IF HE HAD ATTENDED MORGAN PARK  HIGH SCHOOL.
<br /><br />&quot;YES. YES, I DID. &quot; HE GLEAMED WITH PRIDE.
<br /><br />&quot;WHEN DID YOU GRADUATE?&quot; I ASKED.
<br /><br />HE ANSWERED , &quot;IN 1959.  WHY DO YOU ASK?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;YOU WERE IN MY CLASS!&quot;, I EXCLAIMED.
<br /><br />HE LOOKED AT ME CLOSELY.  THEN, THAT UGLY, OLD, BALD, WRINKLED, FAT ASS,  GRAY-HAIRED, DECREPIT SON-OF-A-BITCH ASKED, &quot;WHAT DID YOU TEACH?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1ca9b7ff3be3f37b25604453d4d1b856" url=""><![CDATA[Difference<br/><br/>What is the difference between girls aged: 8, 18,  28, 38, 48, 58,68, and 78 ?
<br /><br />At 08 - You take her to bed and tell her a story.
<br />At 18 - You tell her a story and take her to bed.
<br />At 28 - You don't need to tell her a story to take  her to bed.
<br />At 38 - She tells you a story and takes you to bed.
<br />At 48 - You tell her a story to avoid going to bed.
<br />At 58 - You stay in bed to avoid her story.
<br />At 68 - If you take her to bed, that'll be a story!!
<br />At 78 - What story???? What bed??? Who are you???
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4a515edbbf158ac664f5a3670b8d324f" url=""><![CDATA[NICE ANSWER<br/><br/>A woman takes her 4 year old son in for his yearly well child visit to the doctor. 
<br /><br />The doctor asks the little boy,  &quot;Do you know your name?&quot; 
<br /><br />He tells her yes my name is, &quot;Timmy.&quot;  
<br /><br />And Timmy, do you know your mom's name? 
<br /><br />Yes her name is Mommy, said Timmy.  
<br /><br />And what is Mommy's real name and little Timmy says, it's &quot;Tammy.&quot;
<br /><br />That is great the doctor told Timmy. 
<br /><br />Then the doctor asked, and what is your daddy's name?  
<br /><br />Timmy said it is daddy.  
<br /><br />Finally the doctor asked, and what does mommy call him?  
<br /><br />Timmy looked up innocently and replied, &quot;Asshole.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="18e5f029166fa6ef97a8cce0c566e405" url=""><![CDATA[FLORIDA DRIVERS<br/><br/>Two elderly Floridaladies were out driving in a large car.
<br /><br />Both could barely see over the dashboard. As they were cruising along they came to an intersection. The stop light was red, but they just went on through.
<br /><br />The woman in the passenger seat thought to herself,  &quot;I must be loosing it, I could have sworn we just went through a red light.&quot;
<br /><br />After a few more minutes they came to another intersection and another red light, and again they went right through.
<br /><br />This time the woman in the passenger seat was almost positive the light had been red. .... She was getting nervous and decided to pay very close attention to the road and the next intersection to see what was going on. 
<br /><br />At the next intersection, sure enough, the light was definitely red, no mistake, and they went right through.
<br /><br />She turned to the other woman and said, &quot;Mildred!  Did you know we just ran through three red lights in a row?  You could have got us killed!&quot;
<br /><br />Mildred turned to her and said, &quot;Oh, am I driving ...?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="36967f50014a5d3b6d2e675ff90f72b" url=""><![CDATA[EVER WONDER<br/><br/>Been around before but will refresh your memory
<br /><br />All good questions. . . 
<br /><br />Can you cry under water?
<br /><br />How important does a person have to be before they are considered
<br />assassinated instead of just murdered?
<br /><br />Why do you have to 'put your two cents in'.. but it's only a 'penny for
<br />your thoughts'? Where's that extra penny going to? 
<br /><br />Once you're in heaven, do you get stuck wearing the clothes you were
<br />buried in for eternity?
<br /><br />Why does a round pizza come in a square box? 
<br /><br />What disease did cured ham actually have? 
<br /><br />How is it that we put man on the moon before we figured out it would be
<br />a good idea to put wheels on luggage? 
<br /><br />Why is it that people say they 'slept like a baby' when babies wake up
<br />like every two hours? 
<br /><br />If a deaf person has to go to court, is it still called a hearing? 
<br /><br />Why are you IN a movie, but you're ON TV? 
<br /><br />Why do people pay to go up tall buildings and then put money in
<br />binoculars to look at things on the ground? 
<br /><br />Why do doctors leave the room while you change? They're going to see you
<br />naked anyway.
<br /><br />Why is 'bra' singular and 'panties' plural? 
<br /><br />Why do toasters always have a setting that burns the toast to a horrible
<br />crisp, which no decent human being would eat? 
<br /><br />If Jimmy cracks corn and no one cares, why is there a stupid song about
<br />him?
<br /><br />Can a hearse carrying a corpse drive in the carpool lane ? 
<br /><br />If the professor on Gilligan's Island can make a radio out of a coconut,
<br />why can't he fix a hole in a boat? 
<br /><br />Why does Goofy stand erect while Pluto remains on all fours? They're
<br />both dogs!
<br /><br />If Wile E. Coyote had enough money to buy all that ACME crap, why didn't
<br />he just buy dinner? 
<br /><br />If corn oil is made from corn, and vegetable oil is made from
<br />vegetables, what is baby oil made from?
<br /><br />If electricity comes from electrons, does morality come from morons?
<br /><br />Do the Alphabet song and Twinkle, Twinkle Little Star have the same
<br />tune? 
<br /><br />Why did you just try singing the two songs above?
<br /><br />Did you ever notice that when you blow in a dog's face, he gets mad at
<br />you, but when you take him for a car ride, he sticks his head out the
<br />window? 
<br /><br />Do you ever wonder why you gave me your e-mail address in the first
<br />place?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="671024bf14c4ed643e97a47cf92dff83" url=""><![CDATA[THE COWBOY<br/><br/>The cowboy sat on a stool drinking a beer as the Mexican, also dressed in western garb sat next to him.
<br /><br />There was a slight nod as they looked at each other. Soon the cowboy ordered another and bought one for the Mexican also. When their glasses became empty the cowboy bought again. Then a third time the cowboy bought again and the Mexican grinned and spoke something but the bar-tender never knew what he said. Then the cowboy seemed to be infuriated and stood up suddenly drawing his gun and shot the Mexican dead...
<br /><br />At the cowboys hearing the judge the judge asked the cowboy, &quot;Why did you suddenly become enraged for no apparent reason and shoot this individual dead.
<br /><br />&quot;Well, the cowboy explained, I tried to be friendly and he began calling me names and insulting me for no reason and finally I got mad&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;What names did he call you that made you so mad that you wanted to kill him&quot;?, asked the Judge.
<br /><br />&quot;Well, answered the cowboy, three times I bought him a drink, and each time he grinned in my face and called me Grassy Ass...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d991c806a7ec462db00ffed1cdb26a1c" url=""><![CDATA[THE NUN<br/><br/>A nun, badly needing to use the restroom, walked into a local hooters. The place was hopping with music and loud conversation and every once in a while the lights would turn off.  Each time the lights would go out, the place would erupt into cheer.
<br /><br />However, when the revelers saw the nun, the room went dead silent. She walked up to the bartender, and asked, &quot;May I please use the restroom?&quot;
<br /><br />The bartender replied, &quot;OK, but I should warn you that there is a statue of a naked man in there wearing only a fig leaf.&quot;  &quot;Well, in that case I'll just look the other way,&quot; said the nun. So, the bartender showed the nun to the back of the restaurant.
<br /><br />After a few minutes, she came back out, and the whole place stopped just long enough to give the nun a loud round of applause. She went to the bartender and said, &quot;Sir, I don't understand. Why did they applaud for me just because I went to the restroom?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Well, now they know you're one of us,&quot; said the bartender, &quot;Would you like a drink?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;But, I still don't understand,&quot; said the puzzled nun.
<br /><br />&quot;You see,&quot; laughed the bartender, &quot;every time someone lifts the fig leaf on that statue, the lights go out. Now, how about that drink?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c9376bbcddef057ffbc3757667de3804" url=""><![CDATA[SOCIAL SECURITY<br/><br/>After retiring, I  went to the Social Security office to apply for Social Security. The  woman behind the counter asked me for my driver's license to verify  my age. I looked in my pockets and realized I had left my wallet at  home. I told the woman that I was very sorry, but I would have to go  home and come back later.
<br /><br />The woman said, &quot;Unbotton your shirt.&quot;
<br /><br />So I  opened my shirt revealing my curly silver hair.
<br /><br />She said, &quot;That  silver hair on your chest is proof enough for me&quot;, and she
<br />processed  my Social Security application.
<br /><br />When I got home, I excitedly told my  wife about my experience at the Social Security office.
<br /><br />She said,  &quot;You should have dropped your pants... you might have  gotten
<br />disability, too.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13e8b1887a92a84e10c0fbb275ac02d5" url=""><![CDATA[QUESTION<br/><br/>How come it takes 6 men to carry a man to his grave
<br />but only one woman to put him there?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="704a8ea731be6e90c8bd5c3c428696bc" url=""><![CDATA[COMMUTER<br/><br/>A lady on a commuter train was reading a newspaper article about life and death statistics. Fascinated, she turned to the man next to her and asked, &quot;Did you know that every time I breathe somebody dies?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Really,&quot; he said, &quot;have you tried mouthwash?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a8595a5146d435af713817808e5658ef" url=""><![CDATA[TWO BOYS<br/><br/>Two boys were closely examining bathroom scales 
<br />on display at the department store. 
<br /><br />&quot;Have you ever seen one of these before?&quot; one asked.
<br /><br />&quot;Yeah, my mom have one,&quot; the other replied.
<br /><br />&quot;What's it for?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;I don't know,&quot; the second boy answered.
<br /><br />&quot;But every time she stands on it she gets really pissed.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="308923c0f3ac99bebcdf51bd7f7cb32" url=""><![CDATA[GAME WARDEN<br/><br/>A hunter just tagged his deer as the game warden walked up. &quot;Where's
<br />your license,&quot; asked the warden. 
<br /><br />&quot;Don't know,&quot; said the hunter.
<br /><br />&quot;OK, you're under arrest for no license. Follow me to the road, and help
<br />me drag the deer,&quot; said the warden.
<br /><br />&quot;No way,&quot; said the hunter. &quot;You drag it.&quot; 
<br /><br />Two hours later, after the warden had dragged the deer to the road, the hunter said,
<br /><br />&quot;Now I remember,
<br />my license is in my back pocket!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ab144225f16ae92489e29a9f5e89d116" url=""><![CDATA[DOG BITE<br/><br/>A man walked in a park and wanted to sit down for a while, so he found the nearest bench and sat down next to a man with a dog at his feet.  &quot;Does your dog bite?&quot; he asked.
<br /><br />&quot;No.&quot; was the reply.
<br /><br />A few minutes later the man reached over to stroke the dog, and the dog took a huge chunk out of his hand. Nursing his now injured hand the man first man says, &quot;I thought you said your dog doesn't bite!&quot;
<br /><br />The second man said indignantly, &quot;That's not my dog.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4111f636715f8bd29b9cab5205db2998" url=""><![CDATA[MAGIC<br/><br/>A woman is complaining to her friend about her marriage.
<br /><br />Her friend says, &quot;Yeah, I understand, I guess there isn't anymore magic in your life.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Oh, no, there's still some magic! Every Saturday night he disappears!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbd38a80542af200d38ce388dbac894e" url=""><![CDATA[TWO OLD DRUNKS<br/><br/>Two old drunks in a bar.  The first one says, &quot;Ya know, when I was 30 and got an erection I couldn't bend it even using both hands.
<br /><br />By the time I was 40, I could bend it about 10 degrees if I tried really hard.
<br /><br />By the time I was 50, I could bend it about 20 degrees, no problem.
<br /><br />I'm gonna be 60 next week, and now I can almost bend it in half with just one hand&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;So&quot;, says the second drunk, &quot;what's your point?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Well, &quot;says the first, &quot;I'm just wondering how much stronger I'm gonna get!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8b63a3f07fc5ce2863ecde478b81048b" url=""><![CDATA[OUT OF THE MOUTHS OF BABES<br/><br/>A 5 yr. old and a 4 yr. old are upstairs in their bedroom. 
<br /><br />&quot;You know what?&quot;, says the 5 yr. old, &quot;I think its about time we start swearing.&quot;
<br /><br />The 4 yr. old nods his head in approval. &quot;When we go downstairs for breakfast I'm gonna say 'hell,' and you say 'ass', OK?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;OK.&quot; The 4 yr. old says with enthusiasm.
<br /><br />The mother walks into the kitchen and asks the 5 yr. old what he wants for breakfast.
<br /><br />&quot;Awe, hell mom, I guess I'll have the Cheerios.&quot;
<br /><br />Whack!! He flies out of his chair, tumbles across the kitchen floor, gets up, and runs upstairs crying his eyes out.
<br /><br />The mom looks at the 4 yr. old and asks in a stern voice, &quot;And what do YOU want for breakfast, young man?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;I don't know,&quot; he blubbers, &quot;but you can bet your ass it won't be Cheerios.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fd8101a695d9a58528d6de603695e1f0" url=""><![CDATA[LITTLE JOHNNY<br/><br/>Johnny was at his first day of school. The teacher advised the class to start the day with the pledge of allegiance, and instructed them to put their right hands over their hearts and repeat after him.
<br /><br />He looked around the room as he started the recitation, &quot;I pledge allegiance to the flag...&quot; When his eyes fell on Johnny, he noticed Johnny's hand over the right cheek of his buttocks.
<br /><br />&quot;Johnny, I will not continue till you put you hand over your heart.&quot;
<br /><br />Johnny replied, &quot;It is over my heart.&quot;
<br /><br />After several attempts to get Johnny to put his hand over his heart, the teacher asked, &quot;Why do you think that is your heart?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Because every time my Grandma comes to visit, she picks me up, pats me here, and says, 'Bless your little heart,' and my Grandma wouldn't lie.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7b7d20d00bd06400a8aba1e095fc7f49" url=""><![CDATA[Think before you speak<br/><br/>Here are six reasons why you should think before you speak -the last one is great! 
<br /><br />Have you ever spoken and wished that you could immediately take the words back... or that you could crawl into a hole?
<br /><br />Here are the Testimonials of a few people who did....
<br /><br />FIRST TESTIMONY:
<br />I walked into a hair salon with my husband and three kids in tow and asked loudly, &quot;How much do you charge for a shampoo and a blow job?&quot;  I turned around and walked back out and never went back My husband didn't say a word...
<br />he knew better. 
<br /><br />SECOND TESTIMONY: 
<br />I was at the golf store comparing different kinds of golf balls. I was unhappy with the women's type I had been using. After browsing for several minutes,  I was approached by one of the good-looking gentlemen who works at the store. He asked if he could help me. Without thinking, I looked at him and said, &quot;I think I like playing with men's balls.&quot; 
<br /><br />THIRD TESTIMONY:
<br />My sister and I were at the mall and passed by a store that sold a variety of candy and nuts. As we were looking at the display case, the boy behind the counter asked if we needed any help. I replied, &quot;No, I'm just looking at your nuts.&quot;  My sister started to laugh hysterically. The boy grinned, and I turned beet-red and walked away. To this day, my sister has never let me forget. 
<br /><br />FOURTH TESTIMONY : 
<br />While in line at the bank one afternoon, my toddler decided to release some pent-up energy and ran amok. I was finally able to grab hold of her after receiving looks of disgust and annoyance from other patrons. I told her that if she did not start behaving &quot;right now&quot; she would be punished. To my horror, she looked me in the eye and said in a voice just as threatening, &quot;If you don't let me go right now, I will tell Grandma that I saw you  kissing Daddy's pee-pee last night!&quot;  The silence was deafening after this enlightening exchange. Even the tellers stopped what they were doing. I mustered up the last of my dignity and walked out of the bank with my daughter in tow . The last thing I heard when the door closed behind me, were screams of laughter. 
<br /><br />FIFTH TESTIMONY:
<br />Have you ever asked your child a question too many times?  My three-year-old son had a lot of problems with potty training and I was on him constantly. One day we stopped at Taco Bell for a quick lunch, in between errands It was very busy, with a full dining room. While enjoying my taco, I smelled something funny, so of course I checked my seven-month-old daughter; she was clean. Then I rea lized that Danny had not asked to go potty in a while. I asked him if he needed to go, and he said &quot;No.&quot;  I kept thinking, &quot;Oh Lord, that child has had an accident, and I don't have any clothes with me.&quot; Then I said, &quot;Danny, are you SURE you didn't have an accident?&quot;  &quot;No,&quot; he replied.  I just KNEW that he must have had an accident, because the smell was getting worse. Soooooo, I asked one more time, &quot;Danny, did you have an accident ? This time he jumped up, yanked down his pants, bent over, spread his cheeks and yelled &quot;SEE MOM, IT'S JUST FARTS!!&quot;  While 30 people nearly choked to death on their tacos laughing,
<br />he calmly pulled up his pants and sat down. An old couple made me feel better,
<br />thanking me for the best laugh they'd ever had!
<br /><br />LAST BUT NOT LE AST TESTIMONY: 
<br />This had most of the state of Michigan laughing for 2 days and a very embarrassed female news anchor who will, in the future, likely think before she speaks. What happens when you predict snow but don't get any!  We had a female news anchor that, the day after it was supposed to have snowed and didn't,  turned to the weatherman and asked: &quot;So Bob, where's that 8 inches you promised me last night?&quot;   Not only did HE have to leave the set, but half the crew did too they were laughing so hard! 
<br /><br />Now, didn't that feel good?
<br />Pass it on to someone you know who needs a laugh and remember ...we all say things we don't really mean, so think before you speak .
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="648001f26b7096531de8eb2f871e1316" url=""><![CDATA[THE GOOD NAPKINS<br/><br/>THE GOOD NAPKINS...ahhhhh...the joys of having girls...
<br /><br />My mother taught me to read when I was four years old &gt;&gt;(her first mistake).
<br /><br />One day, I was in the bathroom and noticed one of the cabinet doors was ajar, I read the box in the cabinet. I then asked my mother why she was keeping 'napkins' in the bathroom. Didn't they belong in the kitchen?
<br /><br />Not wanting to burden me with unnecessary facts, she told me that those were for &quot;special occasions&quot; (her second mistake).
<br /><br />Now fast forward a few months....It's Thanksgiving Day, and my folks are leaving to pick up my uncle and his wife for dinner Mom had assignments for all of us while they were gone.
<br /><br />Mine was to set the table.
<br /><br />When they returned, my uncle came in first and imediately burst into laughter.
<br /><br />Next came his wife who gasped, then began giggling.
<br /><br />Next came my father, who roared with laughter.
<br /><br />Then came Mom, who almost died of embarrassment when she saw each place setting on the table with a &quot;special occasion&quot; napkin at each plate, with the fork carefully arranged on top.
<br /><br />I had even tucked the little tail in so they didn't hang off the edge!!
<br /><br />My mother asked me why I used these and, of course, my response sent the other adults into further fits of laughter.
<br /><br />&quot;But, Mom, you said they were for special occasions!!!&quot;
<br /><br />Pass this on to your girlfriends who need a good laugh or anyone who has a daughter!
<br /><br />&quot;Life is too short for drama and petty things, so kiss slowly, laugh insanely, Love truly and forgive quickly.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ccc9cd28653e27f86788284202ded978" url=""><![CDATA[CASE DISMISSED<br/><br/>A young woman who was several months pregnant boarded a bus. When she
<br />noticed a young man smiling at her she began feeling humiliated on account of her condition. She changed her seat and he seemed more amused. She moved again and then on her third move he burst out laughing................ She had him arrested.
<br /><br />Then the case came before the court, the young man was asked why he acted in such a manner. His reply was:
<br /><br />When the lady boarded the bus I couldn't help noticing she was pregnant.
<br /><br />She sat under an advertisement, which read: 'Coming soon: 'The Gold DustTwins'. 
<br /><br />I was even more amused when she sat under a shaving advertisement,
<br />which read:  'William's Stick Did The Trick'. 
<br /><br />Then I could not control myself any longer when on the third move she
<br />sat under an advertisement, which read: 'Dunlop Rubber would have prevented this accident.'
<br /><br />The case was dismissed.........!!!!!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2e1fa946ec4fb90ea300cba4fb4ca8c8" url=""><![CDATA[SOUTHERN GRANDMA<br/><br/>In a trial, a Southern small-town prosecuting attorney called His first
<br />witness, a grandmotherly, elderly woman to the stand.
<br /><br />He approached her and asked, &quot;Mrs. Jones, do you know me?&quot; She responded, &quot;Why, yes, I do know you, Mr. Williams. I've Known you since you were a young boy, and frankly, you've been a big disappointment to me. You lie, you cheat on your wife, and you manipulate people and talk about them behind their backs. You think you're a big shot When you haven't the brains to realize you never will amount to anything more than a two-bit paper pusher. Yes, I know you.&quot;
<br /><br />The lawyer was stunned! Not knowing what else to do, he pointed across the room and asked, &quot;Mrs. Jones, do you know the defense attorney?&quot; She again replied, &quot;Why, yes, I do I've known Mr. Bradley since he was a youngster, too. He's lazy, bigoted, and he has a drinking problem. He can't build a normal relationship with anyone and his law practice is one of the worst in the entire state. Not to mention he cheated on his wife with three different women. One of them was your wife. Yes, I know him.&quot;
<br /><br />The defense attorney almost died.
<br /><br />The judge asked both counselors to approach the bench and, in a very quiet voice, said, &quot;If either of you idiots asks her if she knows me, I'll send you to the electric chair.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2821e4cff4ac95917916b8a546571087" url=""><![CDATA[TWO OLD MEN<br/><br/>Two old guys talking.  The first one says, &quot;Ya know, when I was 30 and got an erection I couldn't bend it even using both hands.
<br /><br />By the time I was 40, I could bend it about 10 degrees if I tried really hard.
<br /><br />By the time I was 50, I could bend it about 20 degrees, no problem.
<br /><br />I'm gonna be 60 next week, and now I can almost bend it in half with just one hand&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;So&quot;, says the second drunk, &quot;what's your point?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Well, &quot;says the first, &quot;I'm just wondering how much stronger I'm gonna get!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>