<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="a20fd1baa0dcc571222567a529ebd2d8" url=""><![CDATA[it made me cry<br/><br/>Love starts with a Smile, 
<br />Grows with a kiss, 
<br />And ends with a tear 
<br /><br />Don’t cry over anyone 
<br />Who won’t cry over you 
<br /><br />Good FRIENDS are hard to find, 
<br />Harder to leave, 
<br />And impossible to forget 
<br /><br />U can only go as far as u push 
<br /><br />Actions speak louder than words 
<br /><br />The HARDEST thing to do 
<br />Is watch the one u love, 
<br />Love somebody else 
<br /><br />Don’t let the past hold u back, 
<br />You’re missing the good stuff 
<br />LIFE’S 2 short 
<br />If u don’t look around 
<br />Once in a while u might miss it 
<br /><br />A BEST FRIEND 
<br />Is like a 4 leaf clover, 
<br />HARD to find 
<br />And LUCKY to have 
<br /><br />Some people 
<br />Make the world SPECIAL 
<br />Just by being in it 
<br /><br />BEST FRIENDS 
<br />Are the siblings 
<br />God forgot to give us 
<br /><br />When it hurts to look back, 
<br />And u r SCARED to look ahead, 
<br />U can look beside U 
<br />And UR BEST FRIEND 
<br />Will always be there for U 
<br /><br />TRUE FRIENDSHIP “NEVER” ENDS 
<br /><br />Friends are forever 
<br />Good friends are like STARS 
<br />U don’t always see them 
<br />But u know they are always THERE 
<br /><br />Don’t frown 
<br />U never know 
<br />Who is falling in love with your smile 
<br /><br />What do u do 
<br />When the only person 
<br />Who can make u stop crying 
<br />Is the person who made U cry? 
<br /><br />Nobody is perfect 
<br />Until you fall in love with them. 
<br /><br />Everything is okay in the end 
<br />If it’s not okay 
<br />Then it’s not the end!! 
<br /><br />THANK YOU FOR BEING SUCH 
<br />A GOOD FRIEND TO ME!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a9eeeb1bdeb9d905917474ff8622e3f9" url=""><![CDATA[MY X<br/><br/>tell him i hate him 
<br />tell him i never wont to see him again 
<br />tell him i wont him to die 
<br />just dont tell him i seed thins with tears in my eyes and down my face
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ac41552a08ecd6204c52e323398bec40" url=""><![CDATA[its deep<br/><br/>Dear Mr. President,
<br />Come take a walk with me.
<br />Let's pretend we're just two people and
<br />You're not better than me.
<br />I'd like to ask you some questions if we can speak honestly.
<br /><br />What do you feel when you see all the homeless on the street?
<br />Who do you pray for at night before you go to sleep?
<br />What do you feel when you look in the mirror?
<br />Are you proud?
<br /><br />How do you sleep while the rest of us cry?
<br />How do you dream when a mother has no chance to say goodbye?
<br />How do you walk with your head held high?
<br />Can you even look me in the eye
<br />And tell me why?
<br /><br />Dear Mr. President,
<br />Were you a lonely boy?
<br />Are you a lonely boy?
<br />Are you a lonely boy?
<br />How can you say
<br />No child is left behind?
<br />We're not dumb and we're not blind.
<br />They're all sitting in your cells
<br />While you pave the road to hell.
<br /><br />What kind of father would take his own daughter's rights away?
<br />And what kind of father might hate his own daughter if she were gay?
<br />I can only imagine what the first lady has to say
<br />You've come a long way from whiskey and cocaine.
<br /><br />How do you sleep while the rest of us cry?
<br />How do you dream when a mother has no chance to say goodbye?
<br />How do you walk with your head held high?
<br />Can you even look me in the eye?
<br /><br />Let me tell you 'bout hard work
<br />Minimum wage with a baby on the way
<br />Let me tell you 'bout hard work
<br />Rebuilding your house after the bombs took them away
<br />Let me tell you 'bout hard work
<br />Building a bed out of a cardboard box
<br />Let me tell you 'bout hard work
<br />Hard work
<br />Hard work
<br />You don't know nothing 'bout hard work
<br />Hard work
<br />Hard work
<br />Oh
<br /><br />How do you sleep at night?
<br />How do you walk with your head held high?
<br />Dear Mr. President,
<br />You'd never take a walk with me.
<br />Would you?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="11180a23b4be373abb8e3e27b8874c69" url=""><![CDATA[zach i will love u more than u will ever know R.I.P my only<br/><br/>When I 1st meet u I was think 
<br />don’t tell me u love me
<br />don’t tell me those lies 
<br />But u did u love me 
<br />The way I love u still
<br />I know u r up there looking over me 
<br />Saying what r u doing to ur self
<br /><br />I know u wont me to live my life  
<br />u always say to me u love me with all ur heart
<br />I know u do
<br />I trust you more than you will ever kow
<br />The 1st date at the moves 
<br />We hade been going out 4 3days
<br />We where all ready in love 
<br />When I see think that reminds me of u
<br />I get that feeling 
<br />You know that one we didn’t  know what it was 
<br />but we both got it on that 1st date
<br />I don’t even reamer most of the move
<br />We spent most of the time “looking” at each other
<br />I have the move out happy feet
<br />But I cant see it when ever I go to I just cry 
<br />But I wont to and I will when I’m ready 
<br />And no one at home 
<br /><br />But I’m not over u I will never be
<br />no one will ever on what it is like 
<br />4 there b/f to die when u r going out 
<br />They only way they will know 
<br />what it is like is if it happens to them 
<br /><br />those moments we shared
<br />I’m sure you where the real thing
<br />we where happy together
<br />Yes zach and me where happy 
<br />We smiled and mente it
<br />I don’t think I’ll ever b happy now 
<br /><br />Your where something more than life
<br />u where ever think to me 
<br />you were my life 
<br />your heart was just like my 
<br />Our heart where broken and we fixed them
<br />Now it back to the beginning 
<br /><br />i screaming out ur name
<br />My heart hurts so much as i miss 
<br />you like fuck
<br />why did you tell me you loved me 
<br />why did you tell me you where coming back and ur not
<br />When that is all I wont is u back with me
<br />did you forget all we did 
<br />all I seed u where ever think to me 
<br />u where the only thing I hade left 
<br />What ever happen we where going to forgiven each other
<br />I’m trying so hared to forgiven u
<br /><br />When I go to bed at night I’m Hoping not to get up ever agene
<br />And if I have to 4 it to b with u by my side 
<br />Same time I don’t know what has happened to me
<br />Then nest thing I know 
<br />There is blood ever where 
<br />my wrist r fucked but I don’t feel any think 
<br />I don’t know if I’m living
<br />Its just not the same with out u
<br /><br />i tried to ask my self y u did it to me
<br />U seed I was the only think keeping u alive
<br />Was it same think I did 
<br />I think to my self what it cod b
<br />What ever it was I so sorry &lt;3
<br />I wood do any think to have u back
<br /><br />i don't understand any think any more
<br />i showed u all my love 4 you
<br />I still have it all 
<br />And that the reason I hear to day
<br />I LOVE u more that any think zach 
<br />R.I.P zach Xoxox
<br /><br />We will b going out 4 ever now
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e45824473b1ef76a0a063014cfa3d482" url=""><![CDATA[to u boys<br/><br/>&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE ACTS SHY.
<br />&gt; &gt;--hug her.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE RUNS AWAY FROM YOU.
<br />&gt; &gt;-chase her
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE PUTS HER FACE NEAR YOURS.
<br />&gt; &gt;- kiss her
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE KICKS &amp; PUNCHES.
<br />&gt; &gt;- hold her tight
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE IS SILENT.
<br />&gt; &gt;- tell her you love her
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE IGNORES YOU.
<br />&gt; &gt;- tickle her--itll get her attention
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE PULLS AWAY.
<br />&gt; &gt;- grab her by the waist and never let her go
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN YOU SEE HER AT HER WORST.
<br />&gt; &gt;- tell her how beautiful you think she is
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE SCREAMS AT YOU.
<br />&gt; &gt;- scream i love you back
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN YOU SEE HER WALKING.
<br />&gt; &gt;-sneak up behind her and put your arms around her waist.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE'S SCARED.
<br />&gt; &gt;-hold her and tell her you wont let anything happen to her.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHEN SHE LOOKS LIKE SOMETHINGS THE MATTER.
<br />&gt; &gt;- talk to her--and listen to what she has to say
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;WHILE SHE HOLDS YOUR HANDS
<br />&gt; &gt;- rub her hand
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d1f1c4720f434d003fc41bc1bf8d17d" url=""><![CDATA[lol<br/><br/>A girl asked a boy if she was pretty.
<br />He said no.
<br />She asked him if he wanted to be with her forever.
<br />He said no.
<br />She then asked him if he would cry if she walked away.
<br />He again said no.
<br />She had heard too much.
<br />She needed to leave.
<br />As she walked away, he grabbed her arm and told her to stay, he said,
<br />&quot;You're not pretty, you're beautiful. I don't want to be with you forever, I need to be with you forever. I wouldn't cry if you walked away, I would die.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7aa5cec44789ac21de92bed37222a931" url=""><![CDATA[Girl+boys Facts<br/><br/>Girl Facts:
<br /><br />When a girl bumps into your arm
<br />while walking with you,
<br />she wants you to hold her hand.
<br /><br />When she wants a hug,
<br />she will just stand there.
<br /><br />When you break a girls heart,
<br />she still feels it when
<br />you run into each other 3 years later.
<br /><br />When a girl is quiet,
<br />millions of things are running through her mind.
<br /><br />When a girl is not arguing,
<br />she is thinking deeply.
<br /><br />When a girl looks at you with eyes full of questions, she is
<br />wondering how long you will be around.
<br /><br />When a girl answers, &quot;I'm fine,&quot; after a few seconds, she is not at all fine.
<br /><br />When a girl stares at you,
<br />she is wondering why you are playing games.
<br /><br />When a girl lays her head on your chest, she is wishing for you to be hers forever.
<br /><br />When a girl says she can't live without you,
<br />she has made up her mind that you are her future.
<br /><br />When a girl says, &quot;I miss you,&quot;
<br />no one in this world can miss you more than that.
<br /><br />When a girl is mean to you after a break-up, she wants you back, but she's scared she'll get hurt and knows you're gone forever.
<br /><br />When a girl says she loves you,
<br />she really means she loves you.
<br /><br />Guy Facts:
<br /><br />When a guy calls you,
<br />he wants to be with you.
<br /><br />When a guy is quiet,
<br />he's listening to you...
<br /><br />When a guy is not arguing,
<br />he realizes he's wrong.
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I'm fine,&quot; after a few minutes, he means it.
<br /><br />When a guy stares at you,
<br />he wishes you would care about him and wonders if you do.
<br /><br />When you're laying your head on a guy's chest, he has the world.
<br /><br />When a guy calls/texts/comments you everyday, he is in love with you.
<br /><br />When a (good) guy tells you he loves you, he means it.
<br /><br />When a guy says he can't live without you, he's with you until
<br />you're done.
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I miss you,&quot;
<br />he misses you more than you could have ever missed him or anything else.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c09dd1f3ccbfd4abedf5757ab0dcafbb" url=""><![CDATA[Brown Eyes<br/><br/>Blue Eyes
<br />People with blue eyes last the longest in relationships. They are kind, pretty or handsome,very good kissers and are really hot. They always fall in love with their closest friends and never understand why. They are very funny, outgoing and don't care what people think or say. They are very satisfying and love to please. Are straight up WARRIORS when necessary. If you repost this and you have blue eyes you will have the best kiss sometime in the next 5 days.
<br /><br />Green Eyes
<br />People with green eyes have the most passion put into relationships,honest and trustworthy, they have long lasting relationships. People with green eyes are also the most beautiful, are fun and outgoing, love to make people laugh, random as hell. They long for the touch of another. People with green eyes are very sexy and very attracted towards the opposite sex. tend to cover up true feelings, get scared over relationships.You will meet/stay with the person you're going to spend the rest of your life with if you repost this.
<br /><br />Hazel Eyes
<br />People with hazel eyes are very loveable. They are really hot and are awesome to be around. They don't enjoy 'pet names'. They don't care what people think or say. They are lovers, not fighters. But if you mess around, they'll knock you out. They are very satisfying and they love to please. They can exceed your pleasure standards. They are very laid back, chilled and love to just be around. They like to party to love to have fun fight when they have to and they're good kissers and good in bed if u r with a hazel u are lucky and out going trustworthy a very good friend and they are very funny and fun to be around. If you repost this and have hazel eyes then you will be happy soon with the person who is on your heart.
<br /><br />Brown Eyes
<br />Either sexy as hell or are adorable. Loves to make new friends. Their relationship tends to be very honest because if they aren't truly in love, then the relationship won't work. They fall easily for their best friends. Will do anything for that special person. Kind and polite. Enjoys being with their guy/girl. LOVES to party. Can make ANYONE laugh or cheer them up. Loves to please the one they care for or love. Repost this if you have brown eyes and you will find the one that you are meant to be with within the next 7 min.
<br /><br />repost this with your eye color and you are sure to get what you deserve hurry up times ticking
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e50d247f070a97fc1451e840958035ac" url=""><![CDATA[that fucked up<br/><br/>Guy: &quot;Can we have sex right now?&quot;
<br />Girl: &quot;Can we do what?&quot;
<br />Guy: &quot;You know, can I be your first, finally?&quot;
<br />Girl: &quot;Um.....no.&quot;
<br />Guy: &quot;Why?&quot;
<br />Girl: &quot;Because, 1. you have a girlfriend, who happens to be my friend.......&quot;
<br />Guy: &quot;So, if you don't tell, I won' tell.&quot;
<br />Girl: &quot;Besides that, I'm waiting for someone special. Someone that I want to be with for the rest of my life to be my first.&quot;
<br />Guy: &quot;I'm not special to you?&quot;
<br />Girl: &quot;You're my friend. That's all.&quot;
<br />Guy looks forward and keeps driving. 5 minutes pass....... Guy starts to run his hand up the girl's thigh.
<br />Girl: moves his hand, &quot;Don't touch me!&quot;
<br />Guy: tries to kiss her.
<br />Girl: screams, &quot;Would you stop.&quot;
<br />Guy: continues trying.
<br />Girl: moves to the back seat
<br />Guy: parks on an abandoned street and gets in the backseat with the girl
<br />Starts to kiss her..
<br />Girl: pushes him off and scoots over, &quot;Please, don't do this.&quot;
<br />Guy: &quot;Don't do what, I know you want it, I can see it in your eyes.&quot;
<br />Moves over to her and starts to unbutton her pants.
<br />Girl: pushes him harder and says, &quot;No, don't.&quot;
<br />Guy: getting aggravated, punches her and tells her to stop &quot;playing hard to get&quot;.
<br />Girl: crying, continues to fight.
<br />Guy: punches her harder, pulls her pants off, and holds her down.
<br />Girl: screams as he penetrates her, &quot;NO, please don't do this to me!&quot;
<br />Guy: puts his hand over her mouth.
<br />An hour passes.........
<br />Guy: pulls back and wipes himself off.
<br />Girl: sits on the corner of the seat, sobbing.
<br />Guy: looks at her and says, &quot;You better not tell anybody about this. If you're really my friend, you won't tell anybody. You know I love you.&quot; He reaches out his hand to touch her cheek.
<br />Girl: pulls back, &quot;Just take me home, now.&quot;
<br />Guy: says, &quot;Alright.&quot; Gets in the front seat and drives her home.
<br />2 months later.........
<br />Girl: &quot;Doctor, what's wrong with me. I haven't had my time of the month in 2 months.&quot;
<br />Doctor: looks at her, &quot;You haven't been having your &quot;time&quot; for a reason.&quot;
<br />Girl: looks at him and says, &quot;Why?&quot; dreading the answer that she was sure to receive.
<br />Doctor: &quot;You are pregnant.&quot;
<br />Girl: faints.
<br /><br />The story gets out that she is pregnant, and people start looking to the guy. He claims that it isn't his because she was sleeping with every guy in the school(which was a lie). He goes to her and tells her, &quot;I'm telling you, if you lie to people and say that I raped you, I'll kill you.&quot;
<br /><br />The Girl is completely devastated. First, he took her virginity and got her pregnant....then he lied about it. So completely depressed......the girl commits suicide by drug overdose.......
<br />Girls, if this story touched you, repost it as &quot;That's Fucked up&quot;
<br />Guys, if this story touched you, repost it as &quot;I'll kill any fucker who does this&quot; if you care
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="401b58f53e8e156fbb90095317b0d6b3" url=""><![CDATA[do it<br/><br/>Kiss me:
<br />Hug me:
<br />Date me:
<br />Get tipsy with me:
<br />Kill me:
<br />Love me:
<br />Hate me:
<br />Hold me:
<br />Lie to me:
<br />Hurt me:
<br />Sing with me:
<br />Dance with me:
<br />Grind with me:
<br />Touch me:
<br />suck me
<br />Cuddle with me:
<br />Let me make a move on you:
<br />Make a move on me:
<br />Play with me:
<br />Watch a movie with me:
<br />Get me a B-day gift:
<br />Caress me:
<br />Let me borrow your car:
<br />Let me see you naked:
<br />Be there for me:
<br />Buy me a drink:
<br />Take a shower with me:
<br />Watch porn with me:
<br />Bring me around your friends:
<br />Give me a massage:
<br />Take me to the club:
<br />Go to sleep with me:
<br />Do me:
<br />Drink vodka with me:
<br />Look if i was naked:
<br />Take advantage of me:
<br />Let me take advantage of u:
<br />Hangout with me:
<br />Take care of me if I wasn't feeling good:
<br />Hold hands with me:
<br />Do something incredibly sweet for me:
<br />Give me a lap dance:
<br />Let me give you a lap dance:
<br />Tell me you love me:
<br />Let me call you:
<br />What would you do if you woke up next to me:
<br />Will you repost this so i can do the same for u
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6eefd5dd2159d3b74286ff6ca02523af" url=""><![CDATA[mummy i love u<br/><br/>Mommy... Johnny brought a gun to school,
<br />He told his friends that it was cool,
<br />And when he pulled the trigger back,
<br />It shot with a great crack.
<br />Mommy, I was a good girl, I did what I was told,
<br />I went to school, I got straight A's, I even got the gold!
<br />But Mommy, when I went school that day,
<br />I never said good-bye,
<br />I'm sorry Mommy, I had to go, But Mommy, please don't cry. When Johnny shot
<br />the gun, He hit me and another,
<br />And all because Johnny, Got the gun from his older brother.
<br />Mommy, please tell Daddy; That I love him very much,
<br />And please tell Chris; my boyfriend; That it wasn't just a crush.
<br />And tell my little sister; That she is the only one now,
<br />And tell my dear sweet grandmother; I'll be waiting for her now, And
<br />tell my wonderful friends; That they always were the best; Mommy, I'm not
<br />the first, I'm no better than the rest.
<br />Mommy, tell my teachers; I won't show up for class,
<br />And never to forget this, And please don't let this pass.
<br />Mommy, why'd it have to be me? No one deserves this,
<br />Mommy, warn the others, Mommy I left without a kiss.
<br />And Mommy tell the doctors; I know they really did try,
<br />I think I even saw a doctor, Trying not to cry.
<br />Mommy, I'm slowly dying, With a bullet in my chest,
<br />But Mommy please remember, I'm in heaven with the rest. Mommy I ran as
<br />fast as I could,
<br />When I heard that crack, Mommy, listen to me if you would,
<br />I wanted to go to college; I wanted to try things that were new,
<br />I guess I'm not going with Daddy, On that trip to the new zoo.
<br />I wanted to get married, I wanted to have a kid,
<br />I wanted to be an actress, Mommy, I wanted to live.
<br />But Mommy I must go now, The time is getting late,
<br />Mommy, tell my Chris, I'm sorry but I had to cancel the date.
<br />I love you Mommy, I always have, I know; you know it's true, And Mommy all
<br />I wanted to say is,&quot;Mommy, I love you.&quot;
<br /><br />***In Memory of The Columbine Students Who Were Lost***
<br />Please if you would,
<br />Pass this around,
<br />I'd be happy if you could,
<br />Don't smash this on the ground.
<br />If you pass this on,
<br />Maybe people will cry,
<br />Just keep this in your heart,
<br />For the people who didn't get to say &quot;Good-bye.&quot;
<br />Now you have 2 choices,
<br />1) Repost and show people you care
<br />2) Ignore it and you have just proven you are a heartless mole
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="56adf08c3821f176d9f82a1431b62dae" url=""><![CDATA[i'm $24:50<br/><br/>Here's the deal. You look it over the following list and see how many of these things you have done. BUT you have to ADD up the money amount along the way. Then post the amount that you are as the title of the bulletin.
<br /><br />PS: the smaller the better!
<br /><br />1. Had sex: $6.00
<br /><br />2. Smoked: $5.00
<br /><br />3. Got drunk: $5.00
<br /><br />4. Went skinny dipping: $3.00
<br /><br />5. Kissed someone of the opposite sex: $4.00
<br /><br />6. Kissed someone of the same sex: $4.00
<br /><br />7. Cheated on a test: $2.00
<br /><br />8. Fell asleep in class: $1.50
<br /><br />9. Been expelled: $5.00
<br /><br />10. Been in a fist fight: $3.00
<br /><br />11. Given oral: $5.00
<br /><br />12. Got oral: $5.00
<br /><br />13. Prank called the cops: $3.00
<br /><br />14. Stole something: $2.00
<br /><br />15. Done drugs: $5.00
<br /><br />16.Dyed your hair: $0.50
<br /><br />17. Done something with someone older : $3.00
<br /><br />18. Went out with someone OVER 18 (if your under 18): $4.00
<br /><br />19. Ate a whole thing of oreos: $0.50
<br /><br />20. Cried yourself to sleep: $1.00
<br /><br />21. Said you love someone but didnt mean it: $1.00
<br /><br />22. Been in love: $4.00
<br /><br />23. Got caught doing something that you shouldnt have been doing: $1.00
<br /><br />24. Went streaking: $4.00
<br /><br />25. Got arrested: $5.00
<br /><br />26. Madeout with someone: $2.00
<br /><br />27. Peed in the pool: $0.50
<br /><br />28. Played spin the bottle: $1.00
<br /><br />29. Done something you regret: $5.00
<br /><br />Now add up and post as &quot;I COST $ _ _._ _&quot; if u do not repost u will have 5 years of bad luck
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6207be5aebf12c95a0c6a3602c75ea76" url=""><![CDATA[The World's Hardest Riddle<br/><br/>I turn polar bears white
<br />And I will make you cry.
<br />I make guys have to pee
<br />And girls comb their hair.
<br />I make celebrities look stupid
<br />And normal people look like celebrities.
<br />I turn pancakes brown
<br />And make your champane bubble.
<br />If you sqeeze me, I'll pop.
<br />If you look at me, you'll pop.
<br />Can you guess the riddle?
<br /><br />97% of Harvard graduates can not figure this riddle out,
<br />But 84% of kindergarten students were able to figure this out,
<br />In 6 minutes or less.
<br />Can you guess the riddle?
<br />Just repost this bulletin with the title;
<br />&quot;The World's Hardest Riddle&quot;,
<br />And then check your inbox.
<br />You should get a message,
<br />with the correct answer in it.
<br />AND TRUST ME;
<br />IT WAS THE MOST SIMPLEST THING YOU WOULDNT HAVE GUESS
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="85c1570c5ebac63a7585af3ce9e4e246" url=""><![CDATA[fun game<br/><br/>fun game
<br />There is at least one person on your facebox list that wants to root the hell out of you.
<br /><br />So lets play the root or run! game.
<br /><br />The rules are simple... if you want to fuck the person who posts this, send them a message saying, &quot;Yep, i'd tap that.&quot;
<br /><br />SCARED? This SHIT's funny!
<br /><br />YOU HAVE TO RE-POST THIS!! and see who replies.
<br />There is at least one person on your facebox list that wants to
<br />do u so!!!
<br /><br />repost this as &quot;fun game??&quot;
<br /><br />so whats it goin to be?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ad2a77fde4f74191fb9c1de0047e934" url=""><![CDATA[daddy please no<br/><br/>There are not enough words to describe how rong and sick this is! It is just rong!
<br /><br />you are one sick person if you dont repost this i feel for you if
<br />this doesnt touch you because this is just wrong. read this. its disgusting
<br /><br />Walking in my nighty; rubbing my eyes
<br />My fathers sitting on the sofa with his friend
<br />He pats the seat in the middle; i sit
<br />Shivering so cold; a quilt he lends
<br /><br />&quot;Jessy you love me don't you&quot; a smile; his
<br />Their breathe spirts weep
<br />&quot;Daddy you know i do; what is it?&quot;
<br />He smiles at his friend; his hand creeps
<br /><br />His friend takes my hand; looks me in the eyes
<br />Daddys creeping up my nightie; cold hands
<br />I try to pull his hand away;
<br />their grip is strong!
<br />They look at one another; nod; something planned
<br /><br />I feel my palms sweat; Daddys under my knickers
<br />&quot;Daddy im going to bed! Night&quot; Pulling again
<br />But there grip is to strong for weak me
<br />I look at both; and ask, who are these men?
<br /><br />His fingers going up me; pulling away
<br />His friend leans forward; a kiss? Why?
<br />His toungue moving mine; my eyes squint
<br />Lean back and away; &quot;Why are you doing this?&quot;
<br />No answer, i feel the pain inside me; him
<br />Chucks the quilt on the floor; me to
<br />I try and scamper away, but im not fast
<br />&quot;O Daddy please, i love you&quot;
<br /><br />His friend; pulling at my nightie
<br />And my Dad pulling my pants down
<br />His friend pinning my hands to the floor
<br />As my Dad lies himself on the ground
<br /><br />I squirm; as Daddy friend pulls me up
<br />And places me ontop of Daddy; thrusts within
<br />I cry; i bite; i scratch; i slap; i fail
<br />&quot;O Daddy please you win you win!&quot;
<br /><br />I can feel my skin rip; my virginity breaking free
<br />I can feel the blood seep down my leg
<br />&quot;Daddy your hurting me please&quot;
<br />I plead to him and his friend; not even a beg
<br /><br />Daddys laughing; why does he laugh?
<br />His friend shoves himself in my mouth and moans
<br />Tieing my hands together; moving in and out
<br />&quot;Ride me Jessy&quot; He laughs and groans
<br /><br />They smile at one another; laugh to
<br />They roll me over and spread me wide well
<br />My daddy sits on my face; himself in again
<br />While his friend talks and pushes himself inside
<br /><br />I can hardly breathe; i gag for air
<br />I cough and splutter; cry and weep
<br />I beg and plead; but its no use
<br />Theyve already made me hurt and bleed
<br /><br />I stare into his eyes; that look upon me
<br />This is not my Dad; where is he?
<br />If he was still here; would he care
<br />Would he actually even; see?
<br /><br />Finally they get of and lie me on the sofa
<br />My cheeks blouchy from tears and pain
<br />They play with them selfs; all over me
<br />Rub it in; making me feel the shame
<br /><br />&quot;Why Daddy? Please tell me why?&quot;
<br />Dad looks at his friend; and waves him away
<br />&quot;Jessy i love you&quot; he smiles and kisses my cheek
<br />&quot;Is that all you have in your heart to say?&quot;
<br /><br />He puts my nightie on me
<br />he walks me to my bedroom door
<br />Ever since that night; His friend
<br />And himself every Friday come back for more
<br /><br />&quot;Night sweet Girl; You are my life&quot;
<br />Closing the door, tears still down my face
<br />Still the smell of him and his friend
<br />Fade into me like disgrace
<br /><br />I watch the Moon go down; the sun come up
<br />&quot;Jessy its school&quot; Knocking at my door
<br />I cant help but cry; weep in pain
<br />Because im so scared he wanted more
<br /><br />But one night daddy took it too far
<br />Daddy and his friend came back for one last shot
<br />They were worried they would get caught
<br />So he and his friend took me to a cemetary lot
<br /><br />I was blindfolded and my hands were tied back
<br />&quot;Daddy please!! Not tonight!&quot;
<br />Daddy and his friend both had their last fun
<br />After that i tried to put up a fight
<br /><br />I begged daddy &quot;Please no more!&quot;
<br />All he could say &quot;Shut up, you stupid Bitch!&quot;
<br />Daddy unblindfolded me at last
<br />He said I love you so much
<br /><br />He went back into the car and pulled out a bat
<br />&quot;Daddy I swear I wont say a thing!!!!&quot;
<br />I was dead
<br />After only one swing..........................
<br /><br />**... Please if you care for all the children and women who have been raped
<br />repost this bulletin with the Headline &quot;daddy please no&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="611eeb3ef7ba30d4284e52b7293a56c" url=""><![CDATA[i was 400 only having fun<br/><br/>This is fun to do. Just read the 'offence' and if you've done it, you
<br />owe that fine. Keep going until you've read each 'offense' and Added up your total fine. When you are done Title your it 'My fine is $........' You don't have to confess your answers, just the Amount of your fine.
<br /><br />Smoked pot -- $10
<br />Did acid -- $5
<br />Ever had sex at church -- $25
<br />Woke up in the morning and didn't know the person next To you -- $40
<br />Had sex with someone on MySpace -- $25
<br />Had sex for money -- $100
<br />Ever had sex with the a Puerto Rican -- $20
<br />Vandalized something -- $20
<br />Had sex on your parents' bed -- $10
<br />Beat up someone -- $20
<br />Been jumped -- $10
<br />Crossed dressed -- $10
<br />Given money to stripper -- $25
<br />Been in love with a stripper -- $20
<br />Kissed some one who's name you didn't know -- $0.10
<br />Hit on some one of the same sex while at work -- $15
<br />Ever drive drunk -- $20
<br />Ever got drunk at work, or went to work while still drunk -- $50
<br />Used toys while having sex -- $30
<br />Got drunk, passed out and don't remember the night before -- $20
<br />Went skinny dipping -- $5
<br />Had sex in a pool -- $20
<br />Kissed someone of the same sex -- $10
<br />Had sex with someone of the same sex -- $20
<br />Cheated on your significant other -- $10
<br />Masturbated -- $10
<br />Cheated on your partner with their relative or close friend -$20
<br />Done oral -- $5
<br />Got oral -- $5
<br />Done / got oral in a car while it was moving/stationary -- $25
<br />Stole something -- $10
<br />Had sex with someone in jail -- $25
<br />Made a nasty home video -- $15
<br />Had a threesome -- $50
<br />Had sex in the wild -- $20
<br />Been in the same room while someone was having sex -- $25
<br />Stole something worth over more than a hundred dollars -- $20
<br />Had sex with someone 10 years older -- $20
<br />Had sex with someone under 21 and you are over 27 -- $25
<br />Been in love with two people or more at the same time -- $50
<br />Said you love someone but didn't mean it -- $25
<br />Went streaking -- $5
<br />Went streaking in broad daylight -- $15
<br />Been arrested -- $5
<br />Spent time in jail -- $15
<br />Peed in the pool -- $0.50
<br />Played spin the bottle -- $5
<br />Done something you regret -- $20
<br />Had sex with your best friend -- $20
<br />Had sex with someone you work with at work -- $25
<br />Had anal sex -- $80
<br />Lied to your mate -- $5
<br />Lied to your mate about the sex being good -- $25
<br /><br />Tally it up and Title it...'My Fine Is...'
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7c60b8739a842e8acd4077f2a490d1c8" url=""><![CDATA[LOVE<br/><br/>did u ever fall 4 someone u no u shouldENT?
<br />try hard to fight ur feelings but couldn't
<br />u fall deeper with each passing day but try hard to hide it in possible
<br />way
<br />hes only a friend and nothing else
<br />a simple glance turns a stare but u pretend that dont care
<br />it not right 4 u 2 be is that why u hide it so no one can see it?
<br />but how long will pretend keep lying that he just a friend 
<br />perhaps ur feelings u can never show perhaps its wrong 4 him to knoW
<br />ur friendship cant be risked over thiS so being his girl is an IMPOSSIBLE WISH
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f3e4d55dd79d9ef325b0e43a2861b36a" url=""><![CDATA[its all ok<br/><br/>Everything is okay in the end
<br /> If it’s not okay Then 
<br />it’s not the end
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="609dd5982a0cd6c84938cf736fb5aa09" url=""><![CDATA[I DONT NO WHAT I AM CAN SOME TELL ME<br/><br/>Nerd 30% Sporty 15% Emo 18% Slutty 21%, Girly 12%
<br /><br />EMO
<br />[X] You own at least 3 black shirts
<br />[ X] You like skinny jeans
<br />[ X] You're listening to music right now
<br />[ X] You have more than 300 songs on your ipod/mp3
<br />[ ] Have attempted suicide
<br />[X] Like the color black
<br />[X] Hate girly girls
<br />[X] Have kissed the same sex
<br />[ ] Like to be alone
<br />[ ] Hate popular music [rap,hip hop,etc.]
<br />[X] Keep hair in front of your face (most of the time)
<br />[ ] Hate your STEPDAD (MAJORLY)
<br />[X] Life sucks for you 
<br />[X] Have been called emo
<br />[ ] Dislike the colors pink
<br />[ ] Own thick-rimmed glasses
<br />[ ] Complain a lot
<br />[X] Own a studded belt
<br /><br />Total:12
<br /><br />SLUTTY
<br />[ ] Own more than 3 miniskirts
<br />[X] Have kissed more than 5 people
<br />[X] Have been called a slut
<br />[X] like to drink (only sometimes)
<br />[X] You wear dark eye makeup
<br />[ ] Wear low cut shirts
<br />[ ] Have been called a tease
<br />[X] Flirt
<br />[ ] Go to parties/sleepovers at least 2x a week
<br />[X] wear tight clothing 
<br />[ ] own 5 tube tops
<br />[ ] Like wearing swimsuits so people can see your body
<br />[X] Sit on the opposite sex's lap 
<br />[X] People hate you( DONT PEOPLE HATE U 2)
<br />[X] It's nice to be naughty Sometimes
<br />[ ] You cuss because you think its fun
<br /><br />Total: 10
<br /><br />Sporty
<br />[ ] own at least 5 jerseys
<br />[ ] Have 10 trophies
<br />[X] Wear hair in ponytail like everyday
<br />[ ] Love sports
<br />[ ] Own 5 sweatpants
<br />[ ] Don't wear makeup sometimes
<br />[ ] Have/do played lacrosse
<br />[ ] Played more than 2 sports
<br />[ ] Play sports
<br />[ ]Can play a sport if you've never played it before
<br />[X] You play/have played basketball
<br />[ ] you play/have played baseball-softball
<br />[X] You play/have played soccer
<br />[ ] You run/ran track
<br />[X] You play/played football
<br />[ ] You are/have been a dancer/cheerleader
<br />[ ] Been called a jock
<br />[ ] Have set a record
<br />[ ] Are friends with your coach
<br />[ ] Love watching sports
<br />[X] can do 15 pushups without getting tired
<br /><br />Total: 5
<br /><br />GIRLY
<br />[X] own at least 4 polos
<br />[ ] Own atleast 4 bright t shirts
<br />[ ] Own at least 4 designer bags
<br />[ ] wear ribbons in your hair
<br />[ ] Love pearls
<br />[ ] Only like popular music
<br />[ ] Read tons of magazines
<br />[ ] Love shopping
<br />[X] Go to mall usually at least once a week
<br />[ ] Voted prom queen
<br />[ ] Dating/dated a jock
<br />[ ] Love attention
<br />[X] wear makeup
<br />[ ] Are ditzy
<br />[ ] Wear heels 
<br />Total: 3
<br /><br />NERDY
<br />[ ] wear your pants above your hips
<br />[ ] wear glasses-contacts
<br />[ ] have/had braces
<br />[ ] On Math team
<br />[ ] like spending time with your parents
<br />[ ] You and your best friend like discussing what book you've read over the weekend
<br />[ ] have been called a nerd
<br />[ ] are/was bullied
<br />[ ] love to learn
<br />[ ] you have read a book in the past month
<br />[ ] like/liked your teachers
<br />[ ] Watch history channel
<br />[ ] never go anywhere on the weekends
<br />[ ] You've won an award for eading/writing/any other nerd thing
<br />[ ] Have been called weird
<br />[ ] Scared to talk to the opposite sex
<br />[ ] Don't have pics of yourself on myspace/friendster
<br />[ ] You read on your last spring break
<br />[ ] have your own website (My Space)
<br />[ ] your homeschooled (was till a couple of years ago)
<br />[ ] wear pocket protectors
<br /><br />Total: 0
<br /><br />If you haven't noticed The parts represent the 5 high school stereotypes
<br /><br />Multiply each number by 3 then repost as &quot;Emo ...%, Slutty...%, Sporty...%, Girly...%, Nerd...%
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6c7b351a486b6b19804cf29991b2802b" url=""><![CDATA[I've done 29 out of 40 Blonde<br/><br/>[X] Gum has fallen out of your mouth 
<br />when you were talking.
<br />[X] Gum has fallen out of your mouth when you were NOT talking.
<br />[X] You have run into a glass/screen door.
<br />[] You have jumped out of a moving vehicle.(NOP BUT I HAVE FELL OUT)
<br />[X] You have thought of something funny and laughed, then people gave you weird looks.
<br /><br />So far: 4
<br /><br />[X] You have run into a pole( WHEN PISSED)
<br />[] IT IS possible to lick your elbow NO
<br />[X] You just tried to lick your elbow.
<br />[X] You never knew that the Alphabet and Twinkle twinkleLittle Star have the same rhythm.
<br />[X] You just tried to sing them.
<br /><br />so far:8
<br /><br />[X] You have tripped on your shoelace and fallen.
<br />[X] You have choked on your own spit.
<br />[] You have seen the Matrix and still don't get it.
<br />[] Your hair is blonde/ish
<br />[] People have called you slow.
<br /><br />So far:10
<br /><br />[X]You have accidentally caught something on fire
<br />[] You tried to drink out of a straw, but it went into your nose/eyes.
<br />[] You have caught yourself drooling.
<br />[X] You've fallen asleep in class
<br />[X] If someone says &quot;fart&quot; you laugh.
<br />[X] You Just Said Fart And Laughed
<br /><br />So far:14
<br /><br />[X] Sometimes you just stop thinking.
<br />[X] You are telling a story and forget what you were talking about
<br />[] People are often shaking their heads and walk away from you
<br />[X] You are often told to use your &quot;inside voice&quot;.
<br />[X] You use your fingers to do simple math. 
<br /><br />So far:18
<br /><br />[] You have eaten a bug
<br />[X] You are taking this test when you should be doing something important
<br />[X] You have put your clothes on backwards or inside out, and didn't realise it
<br />[X] You've looked all over for something and realised it was in your hand or pocket
<br />[] You have broken a Kitchen Appliance
<br /><br />So far:21
<br /><br />[X] You sometimes post bulletins because you are scared that what they say will happen to you if you don't, even when you know it won't happen to you.
<br />[X] You forget when you break things and go to use them later
<br />[] You have jumped out of a moving vehicle.
<br />[X] You didn't notice that the last question was on here twice
<br /><br />So far:24
<br /><br />[X] Your friends know not to use big words around you
<br />[X] You sometimes tilt your head when you're confused
<br />[]You have fallen out of your chair before
<br /><br />So far:26
<br /><br />[X]When you're laying in bed, you try to find pictures in the texture of the ceiling.
<br />[X] The word &quot;umm&quot; is used many times a day by you.
<br />[X] You've tried to say something smart and someone asked what it meant and you didn't know.
<br /><br />So far:29
<br /><br />Repost this as I've done __ out of 40 Blonde Moments
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="74b72a769a3a82ac8d12e481152573d" url=""><![CDATA[xXx Cute Test xXx i got 40<br/><br/>xXx Cute Test xXx
<br />Body: HOW CUTE ARE YOU?
<br /><br />(NO CHEATING)
<br /><br />SEE YOUR RESULTS AT THE END OF
<br />THE TEST.
<br /><br />1. WHAT COLOR HAIR DO YOU
<br />HAVE?
<br /><br />[-]Brown
<br />[-]Red
<br />[ ]Blonde-dirty blonde
<br />[ ]Black
<br />[ ] Other
<br /><br />2. OUT ON A DATE WOULD YOU WANT
<br />TO:
<br /><br />[-]Go to a party
<br />[ ]Go out to eat
<br /><br />3. WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE COLOR
<br />OUT OF:
<br /><br />[ ]Baby-Pink
<br />[ ]Yellow
<br />[-]Baby-Blue
<br />[ ]Turquoise
<br /><br />4. PICK YOUR FAVOURITE HOBBY OUT
<br />OF:
<br /><br />[ ]Talking
<br />[ ]Singing
<br />[-]Taking Long Walks
<br /><br />5. IF YOU COULD PICK A STORE OUT
<br />OF THE FOLLOWING, WHICH WOULD IT BE?
<br /><br />[ ]Hollister
<br />[ ]Old Navy
<br />[ ]Aeropostale
<br />[-]none
<br /><br />6. WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE PLACE
<br />OUT OF THE FOLLOWING?
<br /><br />[ ]Hawaii
<br />[-]London(best fashion) 
<br />[ ]Florida
<br /><br />7. IN THE SUMMER WOULD YOU
<br />RATHER GO TO:
<br /><br />[ ]The Beach
<br />[-]Somewhere Cooler
<br /><br />8. WHAT IS YOUR BIRTHDAY MONTH?
<br /><br />[ ]January
<br />[ ]February
<br />[ ]March
<br />[ ]April
<br />[ ]May
<br />[ ]June
<br />[-]July
<br />[ ]august
<br />[ ]September
<br />[ ]October
<br />[ ]November
<br />[ ]December
<br /><br />9. WOULD YOU RATHER:
<br /><br />[ ]Chill at home
<br />[-]Go out with friends
<br /><br />10. WHAT IS YOUR FAVOURITE
<br />INSTRUMENT OUT OF:
<br /><br />[ ]guitar
<br />[ ]Bass guitar
<br />[-]Drums
<br />[ ]The Triangle
<br /><br />**************************************************- - - **
<br /><br />**ANSWERS**
<br />1.
<br />a. brown= sexy [5points]
<br />b. red = smart [2 points]
<br />c. blonde= playful [4 points]
<br />d. black= caring [3 points]
<br />e. other = wild [5 points]
<br /><br />2.
<br />a. go to a party = playful [2 points]
<br />b. go out to eat = romantic [5 points]
<br /><br />3.
<br />a. baby-pink = cute [2]
<br />b. yellow = loud [3]
<br />c. baby-blue = cool [5]
<br />d. turquoise = sexy [5]
<br /><br />4.
<br />a. Talking = active [2]
<br />b. Singing = determined [2]
<br />c. Taking Long Walks = daring [5]
<br /><br />5.
<br />a. Hollister = tasteful [7]
<br />b.Old Navy= laid back [2]
<br />c. Areopostale= stylish [5]
<br />d.none=rebel [5]
<br /><br />6.
<br />a. hawaii = you like being around
<br />people [2]
<br />b. London = You are quiet, and like the
<br />cold [2]
<br />c. florida = You like to party! [5]
<br /><br />7.
<br />a. beach = tan, likes the sun [5]
<br />b. somewhere cooler = pale and original [2]
<br /><br />8.
<br />a. January = popular [5]
<br />b. February = lovely [5]
<br />c. March = rebellious [5]
<br />d. April = the person everyone loves!!! [5]
<br />e. May = happy [5]
<br />f. june = chills a lot [5]
<br />g. July = Adorable [2]
<br />h. August = ballin' [5]
<br />i. September = quiet [2]
<br />j. October = out-going [3]
<br />k. November = pimpin' it [5]
<br />l. December = warm [5]
<br /><br />9.
<br />a. home = quiet, romantic [3]
<br />b. go out with friends =crazy [5]
<br /><br />10.
<br />a. guitar = cool [3]
<br />b. bass-guitar = mellow [2]
<br />c. Drums = crazy [5]
<br />d. Triangle = simple [2]
<br /><br />SCORES!!!!
<br />UP TO 17= LOUSY GET A LIFE MAN
<br /><br />18-20= OKAY
<br /><br />21-35= Rather Cute!
<br /><br />36+=REAAAAAAAALLLLLLY HOTT...!!!!!!!!!!!
<br /><br />NOW REPOST THIS IN THE NEXT 2
<br />MINUTES
<br />AND YOU WILL HAVE GOOD LUCK
<br /><br />REPOST AS: &quot;Cute test&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="38368cc6962aa547c381114b0048714" url=""><![CDATA[this or that<br/><br/>oooh
<br />lets play &quot;this or that&quot;
<br />...c'mon
<br />...you know you want to
<br /><br />1. black or white=black
<br /><br />2. night or day=night
<br /><br />3. nightmare on elm st or friday 13th
<br />..... (freddy or jason) =freddy
<br /><br />4. play school or sesame st=play school
<br /><br />5. pants or shorts=pants
<br /><br />6. loud or quiet=loud
<br /><br />7. read or watch=watch
<br /><br />8. english or maths=maths
<br /><br />9. typed or handwritten=typed
<br /><br />10. primary school or highschool=HIGH skool
<br /><br />11. emo or chav=emo
<br /><br />12. superman or spiderman=superman
<br /><br />13. fruit or veg=fruit
<br /><br />14. sailor moon or captain planet=captain planet
<br /><br />15. the beatles or the rolling stones= rolling stones
<br /><br />16. friends or lovers=friends
<br /><br />17. sunny or raining=sunny and raining
<br /><br />18. messy or tidy=messy
<br /><br />20. a lover or a fighter=a fighter
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="64cb9835edabcaa1bf9704b3dae16603" url=""><![CDATA[do it 4 me ever one<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />Y= Yes, N = No, M = Maybe.
<br /><br />Would/will you?
<br />[_] come to my house to do nothing at all but chill?
<br />[_] fight me?
<br />[_] fuck me?
<br />[_] kiss me?
<br />[_] lick me?
<br />[_] let me kiss you?
<br />[_] watch a movie with me?
<br />[_] go out to dinner with me?
<br />[_] let me drive you somewhere?
<br />[_] take a shower with me?
<br />[_] drink with me?
<br />[_] take me home for the night?
<br />[_] let me sleep in your bed?
<br />[_] Sing car karaoke w/ me?
<br />[_] re-post this for me to answer your questions?
<br />[_] Lock me in your room and take advantage of me?
<br />[_] let me make you breakfast?
<br />[_] help me with homework?
<br />[_] tickle me?
<br />[_] let me tickle you?
<br />[_] stick up for me if i was being put down?
<br />[_] instant message me?
<br />[_] greet me in public?
<br />[_] hang out with me?
<br />[_] bring me around your friends?
<br />[_] be down with me no matter what?
<br />[_] go out to dinner me?
<br /><br />DO YOU...
<br />[_] think im cute?
<br />[_] think im serious?
<br />[_] think im a good person
<br />[_] think im conceided?
<br />[_] want to kiss me?
<br />[_] want to cuddle with me?
<br />[_] want to hook up with me?
<br />[_] want to *Do* me?
<br />[_] think I would do you?
<br /><br />AM I...
<br />[_] smart?
<br />[_] cute?
<br />[_] funny?
<br />[_] cool?
<br />[_] romantic?
<br />[_] a *freak*?
<br />[_] gangsta?
<br />[_] loveable?
<br />[_] adorable?
<br />[_] trustworthy
<br />[_] compassionate?
<br />[_] great to be with?
<br />[_] attractive?
<br />[_] mean?
<br />[_] well known?
<br /><br />HAVE YOU EVER...
<br />[_] thought about hooking up with me?
<br />[_] found yourself wanting a kiss from me?
<br />[_] wished I were there?
<br />[_] had a crush on me?
<br />[_] wanted my number?
<br />[_] had a dream about me?
<br />[_] been distracted by me?
<br />[_] wanted to see my private part?
<br />[_] looked at my page more than ten times?
<br /><br />ARE YOU...
<br />[_] happy you know me?
<br />[_] horny?
<br />[_] thinking about me?
<br />[_] wanting to call me to talk about these things?
<br />[_] going to repost this?
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angel.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="11ec57624777ae7db6cf930dae625644" url=""><![CDATA[f-up<br/><br/>hey ever one what u up to?
<br />and me well u dont wont to no
<br />i have just been runing and runing 
<br />crying my eye out there so red ever think is well FU*D up
<br />yep it is
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>