<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="20">
		<document id="88f4bed214a5a34b33c9a7ea0c61e56e" url=""><![CDATA[examination and vacation<br/><br/>I have just one examination left before clinical clerkship.<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/book.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />The examination is OSCE; objective structured clinical examination.
<br />Well, it is clinical skill test.
<br /><br />After that I have a vacation.
<br />I am going to England and Brussels.
<br />So excited about that.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8fbafb34233ece4b451d0b44179fddb2" url=""><![CDATA[a happy new year<br/><br/>A Happy New Year every one.
<br /><br />I bought sacred lot in shrine which tell my fortune this year and it is too bad.
<br />Never mind. Not everything is bad. I am good at finding good thing.
<br /><br />I visit my family during new year holiday.
<br />I met the girl. I always meet her I went to my home town for 6 years.
<br />Just eat food together. She is not my girlfriend, yet.
<br /><br />This time I met her twice. I like her. 
<br />she gives me the ax 6 years ago.
<br />I am too bad because that time I said I love her on email.
<br />I know it is really bad. She said no, of course.
<br /><br />She live in Knasai and I live in Kanto. It took 7,8 hours to meet her.
<br />I am student and she is too. we do not have money too.
<br />She is working at Kyoto from this April as a PT.
<br />I am thinking of working here after graduateing university. 
<br />Still fur way.
<br /><br />I thought she was waiting for me to say I love you.
<br />Or I just want to. I do not know.
<br />But I did nothing. I was odd. We talk about friend's marrige and nothing improtant.
<br /><br />I want to have a big heart. I will try, next time. 
<br /><br />I am studying medicine but no teacher tells me about love disiese. hehe
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9f0168b04471de006b9b626ffaf21f9" url=""><![CDATA[Lucy<br/><br/>I am watching ER5 now.
<br />Lucy knight is the med student. (I've wathced season 6, so I also know her end.) 
<br />This is the first rotation of her and tommorow I am going to hospital for the first day.
<br />So I understand her very much. She is really good student.
<br />I am not so good student. so I never interrupt my supervisory doctor.
<br /><br />Well, this time is called pre Bed Side Learning. Only 1 week attending. 
<br />Cardiovascular internal medicine I am involved.
<br />The problem is I am not good at EKG. Have to learn harder!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7eda230453b65df61f7d3f0a937d54b8" url=""><![CDATA[tests<br/><br/>I am in the middle of examination weeks.
<br />a lots of test I have.<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/book.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />I've done half. one more week and I'll have short holiday.<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wub.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />I wish I could go abroad on holiday if we do not have soccer match.
<br />Never mind! we will win!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d4e16a3efffbd75013242c0c32a223d7" url=""><![CDATA[4<br/><br/>I have finished watching ER3 and now watching ER4.
<br />Elizabeth Corday is finally there. Very British. I like it.<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbaab659a1942ee828a471f308ffb37" url=""><![CDATA[3-19<br/><br/>nurse and doctor is different. I mean the way of thinking is slitely different.
<br />Kelly said to Carol kinds of thing that you have to change the way as a doctor.
<br />Nurse is not just on scientific position. Doctor doesn't but doctor have to be close to the science.
<br />Ya, EBM; evidence based medicine.
<br /><br />I think the patiant and doctor is perfectly deferrent. People doesn't understand medicals unless who are to be in this unusual world. Nurses help to bridge this gap, like I used to be. They do wonderful work. 
<br /><br />We doctor (though I'm still med  student) have to try hard to realize that we are struggling with is leal life and all of them have individual history and family and friends. That's prety simple and everyone know but in our strange situation, we have to try.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1f1a96e25142b7ec0e514ee5c66ee1fe" url=""><![CDATA[SMSs<br/><br/>How many SMSs do you register?
<br />I'm on .....  mixi(Japanese biggest one), this BingBox, hi5, yubitoma(Japanese old one), bebo and WAYN. I also have a blog site and easy homepage on university's server.
<br /><br />It's toooooooooooo much, init? I'm usually browsing mixi to find old friends and hi5 to get some friends. Here is kinds of writeing lesson in English by myself. I spend a lot time thesesdays.
<br />But sometime I've got the people who I haven't talked to for ages. I like to meet old friends and I guess everyone is.
<br /><br />How are you guys? You also addicted to SMS? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/book.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3163724b3462cec3e78a24da15148746" url=""><![CDATA[~14<br/><br/>I have not written but I've been watching ER3 everyday(not on holidays).
<br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />There are a lot of problem in American system. 
<br />Suicide, Medical accident in bad situation, gun shots, ...
<br />Too busy for every stuff. And too many lawyer(you know what I mean)
<br /><br />Medicine is not money first business.
<br />Japanese government have to  realize it now.
<br />10 years later, people will realize that Mr.Koizumi was as stupid as J.W.Bush.
<br />He is a good person maybe, and good politician (his Liberal Democratic Party won the election dramatically), but the policy are good just for strong people. It is tough for weaker. 
<br />And new Prime Minister Mr. Abe have to learn more.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="981aadc57231bbfd6bc0650a604fb2db" url=""><![CDATA[3-8,9<br/><br/>8.Union Station  9. Ask Me No Questions, I'll Tell You No Lies.
<br /><br />Stupid Dr. Green, after Susan Luis left. 
<br />That is loveshickness.
<br /><br />I have not had such a girl who made me odd for long time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ff8ae1c3b3c1a089fb39bdfebce30444" url=""><![CDATA[7 No Brain No Gain<br/><br/>What does AWOL stand for?
<br />The answer is absent without leave.
<br />I love to learn this kind of expression in ER.
<br /><br />Sorry for Dr. Green, Susan is leaving.
<br />But never mind, I know shi is coming back and Dr. Green will met Elizabes.
<br />(I have watched ER 6 and 9 already.)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b5faf81962c06531bb530c10f008a1ac" url=""><![CDATA[Sleepy<br/><br/>I had been sleeping till noon today.
<br />I am not good at getting up in time. 
<br /><br />In the afternoon I was in the class. I had enough sleep but still sleepy.
<br />After the class, I went to do some reserch about the MS with friends.
<br />and then I went to library to do some study<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/book.gif" alt=":)" />, but sleepy again.
<br />Actually I was asleep for a while.
<br /><br />Sleeping day it is!! So I should go to bed soon... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c4ab2074cbe0e7dd97305595a38517c" url=""><![CDATA[5. Ghosts and 6. Fear of Flyin<br/><br/>I love Benton basically, but this time I am disgusted at his attitude.
<br />He made a big mistake and he did not  recognize it.
<br />Infant is not little adult, is it. 
<br />Dr. Abbey Keaton did show a great attitude, though.
<br />People made mistake and we have to learn from it.
<br /><br />Anyway I wanna ride a chopper.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4b35cb7fe2f79877067e0e4a2c46e116" url=""><![CDATA[Last Call<br/><br/>ER 3's 4th one is 'Last Call'
<br />I have watched this one before.
<br />Doug were with nuknown girl and she was dead the next day.
<br />Doug had not known about her. She was sick. And she should not have had alchool.
<br />He is a tipical playboy and there are no real female friend.
<br /><br />Dr. Benton is lovely and smart person. The pediatrician said to him ' You should learn ourside the OR.' It is true. However skillful and smart with less kindness is also needed in the OR.
<br /><br />I try not to realize that is people who have his/her own life I am facing.
<br /><br />Sometimes I feel the sense of medical staff and ordinal people is different.
<br />You can see the case easily in suit case. 
<br />We medical staff can't be just with patient. We have to be professional for medical divelopment.
<br /><br />Always good doctor for patient is difficult, init?  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bf93df6e57de036a62785d53e42b7fc2" url=""><![CDATA[Don't Ask Don't Tell<br/><br/>Dr. Luis and Dr. Green, I think they could be good couple. 
<br />How do you think? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />Doctors especially in this hospital is too busy. 
<br />People who are not concerning with medicine have difficulty to understand the situation, I think.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sick.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fe84da10dbc9a93654258e951b98e907" url=""><![CDATA[ER3 -1,2<br/><br/>I am watching a TV series ER for my medical english studying.
<br />It is really good drama. I can learn general English, american hospital,
<br />case study and medical ethical problem.
<br />I can watch this in the library of my uni. They bought all the DVD. Fantastic!
<br /><br />Well, my english level is not so high yet, so I do not understand detail.
<br />Furthermore I have not finished the course about diseases. 
<br />I do not know what is chemo7.
<br /><br />The important thing is to keep listening with concentrate and build vocaburaries.
<br />And have a fun!!
<br /><br />Today I watched   ER&amp;#8546;.
<br />  Dr. Carter, I Presume
<br />      and
<br />  Let the Games Begin
<br /><br />It is not now I believe, but how busy intern residency in States is!!
<br />No sleep for intern? It is rediculous. It is dangerous for patient as well.
<br />But young doctors are so tough. I have to be fit. hehe
<br />Doctor has big responsibility. It is scarely sometimes. One mistake could kill people.
<br /> To get broad knolege and familiar with new paper. 
<br /> To choose correct or better way anytime.
<br />How difficult it is. But that is a doctor. And I will be...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bb592983557a2c90e7d502506aab2b93" url=""><![CDATA[won the game<br/><br/>My favorite american football team Excaliburs won the match today. 
<br />Tough game, but they did really well. It was fantastic to be in the studium when my team won!
<br />I was audience on the stand. I should have been on the pitch with my teammate. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />I was athletic trainer and I left the team last winter for I wanna to play myself.
<br />now I am a member of medical student's soccer club. They are one of the best 
<br />team in Japan. But just among medical students. No future professional is playing 
<br />in our league. They are training hard but not so strictly.
<br />We drink a massive alcohol after the match. We have training session only 3 times
<br /> a week. The american football players devote everything for american football. I wanna support them.
<br /><br />After the match, former teammate and coaches gave me a best smile.
<br />The team doctor say come to support me soon.
<br />I am going to be a doctor and wanna work in sports medicine field.
<br />I love this team. But I want to be with soccer forever as well.
<br /><br />Anyway what I have to do now is study medicine's basic. 
<br />I want to be orthopedist at the moment. I know if I go to work in the pitch as well,
<br />I need broad knowledge. Internal medicine, dopings, psycology and psychiatry...
<br /><br />Too be tough and study hard, and meet many people. That's what I should do now.
<br />Wait a moment, Excaliburs!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a48a0853c249804fc017ce377f68a901" url=""><![CDATA[I love footbaaaaall!<br/><br/>This time I mean American football. I am a soccer player but I was a member of american football team in my university. I was not player. I was a athletic trainer(AT).
<br />I have no certification. Japanese football team usually has student AT.
<br />Some of them are future AT, but some is studying things just for the team.
<br /><br />I quit AT last year but I still love my football team called 'Excaliburs' cool name, init?
<br />Tomorrow we have the first match of the season.
<br />I am so exited about it.
<br />I would like to see many touch downs and intercept.
<br /><br />fingers clossed!!
<br /><br />meshi
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f53419319fb3faf4bfc6c3deedd2adc8" url=""><![CDATA[football<br/><br/>I bet Argentin won the World Cup. But I lost. 
<br />German is very good team. German spirits is still there.
<br /><br />I have samurai spirits. Some English manager told teammate
<br />when they send me a pitch. 'Kamikaze is coming.'
<br /><br />I was surprized that English know the word Kamikaze.
<br />It means the God wind that save Japan from Enemy invading across Sea.
<br />In WW2 we use this word. 'Kamikaze Tokkotai' 
<br />It is sad histry. Tokkotai was killing themselves. They drove the plane and collapsing 
<br />to enemy, like 9.11. 
<br /><br />I hope the tero is over. People liveing together respect each other.
<br />No war.
<br /><br />However I like competition in rule. Olympics, World Cup.
<br />Powerful spiritrs are beautiful. 
<br />Enjoy world cup. 
<br /><br />meshi
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eea6f8527a27374b520398dc21521221" url=""><![CDATA[TOEFLE<br/><br/>You know? When foreign students want to study at the university In stats, 
<br />the test TOEFLE is very important. (IELTS in ENGLAND)
<br /><br />I would like to have practice in hospital in States, so I also need TOEFLE score.
<br />Furtheremore, USMLE STEP1 is necesarry for some teaching hospital.
<br /><br />I am not good at language even at Japanese. It is verrrrrrry tough to study medicine in English.
<br /><br />The important thing is to be get used to reading, listening, and speaking English.
<br />I've been in England, playing football (I mean soccer) for a year. Speaking bad English.
<br />After the year my grammer and vocabulary is still less.
<br /><br />What I did after the period is reading all Harry Potter, watching ER, reading English text like Robbins. 
<br /><br />I will practice here to write the essay for writing section of TOEFL TEST.
<br />Laugh at my stupid sentenses...
<br /><br />Oh, no time left. I've got to go drinking with my pals....
<br />                                     Japanese Drunken boy    Meshi
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="26db9660446397db3ba3a0caaa94a782" url=""><![CDATA[<br/><br/>Wow, it was exciting game. Do you know what I am talking about?
<br />It's baseball game. Ichiro is great. Finally we Japanese are world champion.
<br /><br />Well I am footballer, (not american), so this summer in German is more excited for me.
<br /><br />I am training hard. Today I did resistance session among American football team's lads.
<br />I was Athletic trainer for them for 3 years. We know each other. I gave some of them very 
<br />hard work. But now, I am much wheaker than them. I would keep up with the lads.
<br /><br />Soccer is the best sports for me. I played against and with countless people. Especially in England, I was trainee, trialist, no-good-at-English-alien, Many players I playes with I can not remember the name. All of them are very nice to me. what a shame of me. 
<br /><br />I am still enjoying kicking the ball to beat other team. I am playing and arranging training.
<br />It is terribly tough work because we've got much to study to be a medical doctor.
<br /><br />I am knackered. go to cook and eat and sleep. 
<br />No more study English today!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>