<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="3cd640d8bd64429f8596dda3e0421fc6" url=""><![CDATA["Blessed are the Pure in Heart"<br/><br/>Blessed are the pure in heart 
<br />Blessed are the pure in heart; for they shall see God. 
<br /><br />Matthew 5:8 KJV 
<br />__________________ 
<br /><br />&quot;Suppose there is a righteous man who does what is just and right. He does not eat at the mountain shrines or look to the idols of the house of Israel. He does not defile his neighbor's wife or lie with a woman during her period. He follows my decrees and faithfully keeps my laws. That man is righteous; he will surely live, declares the Sovereign LORD. 
<br /><br />Ezekiel 18:5,6,9 NIV 
<br />__________________ 
<br /><br />To the pure all things are pure, but to the corrupt and unbelieving nothing is pure; their very minds and consciences are corrupted. They profess to know God, but they deny him by their deeds; they are detestable, disobedient, unfit for any good deed. 
<br /><br />Titus 1:15,16 RSV 
<br />__________________ 
<br /><br />With the pure thou will show thyself pure. 
<br /><br />Psalm 18:26 KJV 
<br />__________________ 
<br /><br />Who may ascend into the hill of the LORD? And who may stand in His holy place? He who has clean hands and a pure heart, Who has not lifted up his soul to falsehood and has not sworn deceitfully. He shall receive a blessing from the LORD and righteousness from the God of his salvation. 
<br /><br />Psalm 24:3-5 NASB
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8b1a4d96f19b6d9bca2851e6696e1964" url=""><![CDATA[Gentleness and calmness<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />A gentle answer turns away wrath, 
<br />but a harsh word stirs up anger. 
<br /><br />A hot-tempered man stirs up dissension, 
<br />but a patient man calms a quarrel.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="82af817584cdc7f98ac3cac7a30959d1" url=""><![CDATA[What a woman should be...<br/><br/>&quot;Let not yours be the outward adorning with braiding of hair, decoration of gold, and wearing of fine clothing, but let it be the hidden person of the heart with the imperishable jewel of a gentle and quiet spirit, which in God's sight is very precious.&quot; - Holy Book
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8ae59dfe49aea1db7a0259774872265b" url=""><![CDATA[Excerpt from Yahoo-Managing your Anxiety & Fatigue<br/><br/>8 Home Tips For Effectively Managing Anxiety and Fatigue
<br />Posted on September 19, 2012 by By YML Staff 
<br />For me at least there a few tried and true ideas that have helped me to cope with this type of nervous tension over the years. That said, you should talk to your doctor first before implementing any plan revolving around my ideas. Additionally, while exercise is a great way to eliminate stress hormones and trigger feel good endorphins it should be used only in moderation when you are really tired.
<br />*Slow down. Motivation and drive are important in whatever you do but there comes a time when you must slow to protect your health and renew your creative juices.
<br /><br />*Get enough sleep. Pretty simplistic, right! Numerous research studies confirm that not getting at least 8 hours of sleep every night will increase the odds for all kinds of serious health problems.
<br /><br />*Pay attention to your breathing. Both anxiety and fatigue deprive your body of oxygen and cause toxins to build up in the bloodstream. This in turn causes breathing to become shallow and/or labored. To counteract this use diaphragm breathing techniques along with a simple routine of taking 10 deep breaths, holding each one for a count of 3, and then slowly exhaling.
<br /><br />*Instead of exercise consider message or meditation.
<br /><br />*Don’t allow past problems to stress you out. This is not easy to do but if you can find a way to let go of the past and accept the fact that in life there always will be some things you simply cannot change you will have a fighting chance against fatigue driven anxiety.
<br /><br />*When and what you eat does matter. First, avoid items that heighten blood sugar levels or trigger the release of adrenaline; especially in the evening. Both simple and complex sugars are the biggest offenders. Caffeine is another one to watch out for.
<br /><br />*Skip the video games or television in favor of reading, a relaxing conversation, or listening to calming music.
<br /><br />*And finally, if you feel you need a little extra help consider one of the many safe and effective all natural herbal or homeopathic remedies specially formulated to reduce anxiety and support generally well-being.
<br /><br />About The Author:Robert D. Hawkins is an enthusiastic researcher and consumer advocate for natural health and natural living with over 10 years experience in the field. To discover more about anxiety along with information about safe and effective all natural herbal and homeopathic anxiety remedies
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="babca5054f8b6dab6066aa9b156558a5" url=""><![CDATA[how to deal with sunburn this summer<br/><br/>Another interesting article from yahoo:
<br /><br />Treatment For Your Sunburns
<br /><br />How to soothe your skin after staying under the sun too long
<br /><br />By Maui V. Reyes for Yahoo Southeast Asia
<br /><br />Summertime usually means tanning sessions at the beach. And while we can't stress enough the importance of wearing sunscreen (read about it and other sunscreen myths here), many still bake under the sun for long hours. Hence, many still eventually suffer from sunburn.
<br /><br />In anticipation of your sunburn woes, we rounded up these tips to help in treating the aftermath:
<br /><br />Burnt and still baking. Lots of people still continue gallivanting under the sun even when they're already burnt. That's because many believe that sunburn can't get any worse than it already is, which couldn't be farther from the truth: you're only damaging your skin even more!
<br /><br />Drink water while sunbathing. Dehydration is a frequent by-product of sunburns, so don't forget to drink lots of fluids when you're outdoors.
<br /><br />Determine the type of burn. There are different kinds of burns, and you should figure out which one you have to determine how to properly treat it.
<br /><br />First-degree burns involve reddening of the skin due to dilation of the vessels after sun exposure. These are the type of burns that feel warm to the touch, and seem to &quot;sting&quot; even when you're not under the sun. &quot;The treatment for this type of burn may be cold compresses and cool baths,&quot; says Dr. AJ Ramos-Braga, a dermatologist. &quot;Low potent topical steroids may also be given, but this shouldn't be applied on broken skin or open wounds.&quot;
<br /><br />You can also lessen the discomfort by taking pain relievers such as ibuprofen or acetaminophen. Try putting some Aloe Vera on the affected area to keep it moist and cool. Aloe Vera may also help the epidermis heal faster. Avoid using heavy creams though, since these require a lot of rubbing (the last thing your skin needs is to be touched!)
<br /><br />If you find your skin riddled with blisters, then congratulations, you've sunned yourself to a second-degree burn! It may be tempting to puncture these blobs of liquid, but it's best to leave them alone, as popping them is an invite for bacteria to come in and cause an infection. &quot;Blisters are used by the skin to heal the underlying damaged skin,&quot; explains Dr. Ramos-Braga. &quot;These will eventually 'fall off' when the skin is healed.&quot;
<br /><br />Try not to wear clothes that could rub against the blister. If the blister does pop, lightly cover it with bandage, making sure any tape doesn't touch the blister. Be sure to wash your hands very well before handling a blister, since they're prone to infection.
<br /><br />Pat, don't rub. Take cold showers when possible, to help soothe the burning sensation on your skin. Pat, not rub, your skin with a towel afterward, and follow with a generous slather of moisturizer on your dry, damaged skin.
<br /><br />Eat your fruits and vegetables. Lessen the severity of your sunburn by chowing down on food that's rich in antioxidants. This may help hasten your skin's recovery, as antioxidants fight of free radicals (which helped you get that burn in the first place). Oranges, spinach, eggplants, and berries are just some foods that are packed with antioxidants.
<br /><br />Don't peel your skin. As your burnt skin starts to peel off, you might be tempted to peel the skin off yourself to help the process along. Resist the temptation and just let nature take its course. &quot;'Peeling' cracked skin due to sunburn may cause minor breaks in the skin, which may eventually act as an entry for bacteria. This may cause infection,&quot; says Dr. Ramos-Braga.
<br /><br />Of course, you wouldn't be having this problem if you weren't so careless with sun protection in the first place. Keep in mind that there is no such thing as a &quot;safe&quot; tan, because getting that lovely shade on your skin means damaging your skin and exposing it to free radicals. In the end, an ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure—and quite literally, since it takes one ounce of sunscreen to cover your entire body! So next time, lather up with sunscreen and don't stay under the sun too long.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9939cc6b6b445ca54c970b51db2e26a" url=""><![CDATA[Estate Planning: 16 things to do before one dies<br/><br/>While many of us like to think that we're immortal, the old joke is that only two things in life are for sure: death and taxes. Not only is it important that you have a plan in place in the unlikely event of your death, but you must also implement your plan and make sure others know about it and understand your wishes - as Benjamin Franklin's famous quote goes, &quot;by failing to prepare, you are preparing to fail&quot;. If you've procrastinated on your estate planning, this article will help you get going in the right direction.
<br /><br />Must Do No.1: Physical Items Inventory
<br />To start things out, go through the inside and outside of your home and make a list of all items worth $100 or more. Examples include the home itself, television sets, jewelry, collectibles, vehicles, guns, computers/laptops, lawn mower, power tools and so on.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 2: Non-Physical Items Inventory
<br />Next, start adding up your non-physical assets. These include things you own on paper or other entitlements that are predicated on your death. Items listed here would include: brokerage accounts, 401k plans, IRA assets, bank accounts, life insurance policies, and ALL other existing insurance policies such as long-term care, homeowners, auto, disability, health and so on.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 3: Credit Cards &amp; Debts List
<br />Here you'll make a separate list for open credit cards and other debts. This should include everything such as auto loans, existing mortgages, home equity lines of credit, open credit cards with and without balances, and any other debts you might owe. A good practice is to run a free credit report at least once a year and make sure you close out any credit cards that are no longer in use.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 4: Organization &amp; Charitable Memberships List
<br />If you belong to certain organizations such as the AARP, The American Legion, Veteran's associations, AAA Auto Club, College Alumni, etc, you should make a list of these. Include any other charitable organizations that you proudly support or make donations to. In some cases, several of these organizations have accidental life insurance benefits (at no cost) on their members and your beneficiaries may be eligible. It's also a good idea to let your beneficiaries know what charitable organizations are close to your heart.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 5: Send a Copy of your Assets List to Your Estate Administrator
<br />When your lists are completed, you should date and sign them and make at least three copies. The original should be given to your estate administrator (we'll talk about him or her later in the article), the second copy should be given to your spouse and placed in a safe deposit box, and the last copy you should keep for yourself in a safe place.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 6: Review IRA, 401(k) and Other Retirement Accounts
<br />Accounts and policies where you list beneficiary designations pass via &quot;contract&quot; to that person or entity listed at your death. No matter how you list these accounts/policies in your will or trust, it doesn't matter because the beneficiary listing will take precedence. Contact the customer service team or plan administrator for a current listing of your beneficiary selection for each account. Review each of these accounts to make sure the beneficiaries are listed exactly as you like.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 7: Update Life Insurance &amp; Annuities
<br />Life insurance and annuities will pass by contract as well, so it's just as important that you contact all life insurance companies where you maintain policies to ensure that your beneficiaries are listed correctly.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 8: Assign TOD Designations
<br />Many accounts such as bank savings, CD accounts and individual brokerage accounts are unnecessarily probated every day. Probate is an avoidable court process where assets are distributed per court instruction, which can be costly. Many of the accounts listed above can be set up with a transfer-on-death feature to avoid the probate process. Contact your custodian or bank to set this up on your accounts.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 9: Select a Responsible Estate Administrator
<br />Your estate administrator will be responsible for following the rules of your will in the event of your death. It is important that you select an individual who is responsible and in a good mental state to make decisions. Don't immediately assume that your spouse is the best choice. Think about all qualified individuals and how emotions related to your death will affect this person's decision-making ability.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 10: Create a Will
<br />Everyone over the age of 18 should have a will. It is the rule book for distribution of your assets and it could prevent havoc among your heirs. Wills are fairly inexpensive estate planning documents to draft. Most attorneys can help you with this for less than $1,000. If that's too rich for your blood, there are several good will-making software packages available online for home computer use. Just make sure that you always sign and date your will, have two witnesses sign it, and obtain a notarization on the final draft.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 11: Review &amp; Update Your Documents
<br />You should review your will for updates at least once every two years and after any major life-changing events (marriage, divorce, birth of child, and so on). Life is constantly changing and your inventory list is likely to change from year to year too.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 12: Send Copies of Your Will to Your Estate Administrator
<br />Once your will is finalized, signed, witnessed and notarized, you'll want to make sure that your estate administrator get a copy. You should also keep a copy in a safe-deposit box and in a safe place at home.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 13: Visit a Financial Planner or Estate Attorney
<br />While you may think that you've covered all avenues, it's always a good idea to have a full investment and insurance plan done at least once every five years. If you're not looking to spend the money for professional help, there are several good books out there on getting your financial plan and estate in check. As you get older, life throws new curve balls at you such as considerations for long-term care insurance and protecting your estate from a large tax bill or lengthy court processes. Tips like having an emergency medical contact card in your purse or wallet are little things that many people never think of.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 14: Initiate Important Estate Plan Documents
<br />Procrastination is the biggest enemy to estate planning. While none of us likes to think about dying, the fact of the matter is that improper or no planning can lead to family disputes, assets going into the wrong hands, long court litigations and huge amounts of dollars in federal tax. At minimum, you should create a will, power of attorney, healthcare surrogate, trusts, living will, and assign guardianship for your kids and pets. Also make sure that all the concerned individuals have copies of these documents.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 15: Simplify Your Life
<br />If you've changed jobs over the years, it's quite likely that you might have several different 401(k)-type retirement plans still open with past employers or maybe even several different IRA accounts. While this normally won't create a big problem while you're alive (except lots of additional paperwork and account management), you may want to consider consolidating these accounts into one individual IRA account to take advantage of better investment choices, lower costs, a larger selection of investments, more control and less paperwork/easier management when assets are consolidated.
<br /><br />Must Do No. 16: Take Advantage of College Funding Accounts
<br />The 529 plan is a unique tax-advantaged investment account for college savings. In addition, most universities do not consider 529 plans in the financial aid/scholarship calculation if a grandparent is listed as the custodian. The really nice feature is that growth and withdrawals from the account (if used for &quot;qualified&quot; education expenses) are tax-free.
<br /><br />The Bottom Line
<br />Now you have the ammunition to get a pretty good jump-start on reviewing your overall financial and estate picture; the rest is up to you. While you're sitting around the house watching your favorite sports team or television show, pull out a tablet or laptop and start making your lists. You'll be surprised how much &quot;stuff&quot; you've accumulated over the years. You'll also find that your inventory and debts lists will come in handy for other things such as homeowners insurance and getting a firm grip on your expenses.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5e11a9a94ba7625dccf781f87adf755b" url=""><![CDATA[Good Parenting<br/><br/>How to be a good parent: top 10 tips
<br /><br />One of the nicest things about being a parent is that regardless of the circumstances of your own childhood, the moment you go from being ‘a girl or guy’ to being a parent, you suddenly ‘get it.’ That amazing feeling of exactly what it’s like to love something more than anything.
<br /><br />Here are Gurgles top ten tips on how to be a good parent…
<br /><br />1.Be involved in your child's life.
<br /><br />Being involved fully in your child’s life can be hard work, and more often than not means rethinking and rearranging your priorities. Lots of parents feel they don’t spend enough time with their children or that they have to sacrifice what they do for what the child wants. It’s important to get the balance right; if you work all week and can’t imagine a weekend looking after the children and need some ‘downtime’ yourself, make sure you make time for both. Take the children to the park, ice creams, read to them , spending quality time together but say ‘mummy/daddy needs an hour to catch up on emails/football etc’ to get the balance right.
<br /><br />2.Establish and set rules.
<br /><br />Make sure you and your partner stick to the same rules. It’s no good if Daddy comes home and lets the children have chocolate buttons after Mum has said they are only allowed a certain amount of chocolate if they are good! Establishing some ‘family rules’ with your children is a great way to communicate your expectations and be consistent in your parenting. Make sure there are no more than 3-5 house rules as too many can seem like lists and lists of rules which children would soon find tedious.
<br /><br />3.Avoid harsh discipline.
<br /><br />Many people use the same tactics their own parents used, and a lot of times that meant using really harsh discipline which can make children angrier and either more enclosed or more likely to take it out on others. Sometimes being a parent can make you very frustrated, especially when you have a whinging whining child (for no reason) and the child will not reason with you. The best thing to do in this circumstance is try not to make an issue out of the whinging by not getting cross. Laughing during a tense moment can ease the pressure off you and may even make the child stop the tantrum when they realise it really doesn’t work. Take a moment to stop, breathe, count to ten and carry on as normal with what you are doing. Your child will hopefully get the point that you are not interested in the tantrum and you can make light of it.
<br /><br />4.Explain your rules and decisions.
<br /><br />Always explain your rules and decisions so that your children know exactly why you are punishing/praising them and they can learn from this. For example, ‘Lucy, I am not going to give you your pudding until you finish your broccoli because you have to eat up your dinner before you can go on and have a desert’, rather than a simple no.
<br /><br />5.Treat your child with respect
<br /><br />Sometimes it’s difficult to understand the sheer dependency and enormity of raising children and parents do often view them as small beings who really should be grateful, have less tantrums, stop whinging, and stop arguing with their siblings etc. These are all ideal types of behaviour which we would love children to understand, but in truth, the ungratefulness, tantrums, whinging and so on, can be down to parents barking orders all day long, ignoring common courtesies toward the child, and in defiance, children ignore the parents altogether. The best approach would be to treat your child as respectfully as you yourself would like to be treated.
<br /><br />6.Help them feel safe
<br /><br />It is very important for children to feel safe and this can start at home by hanging family portraits around the house, or pictures of them with their siblings in their bedrooms -a great way of giving them a sense of belonging.
<br /><br />Try not to argue with your spouse in front of the children. If they are sleeping, argue quietly. Children may feel insecure and fearful when they hear parents bickering. Also, children will learn to argue with each other the same way as they hear their parents argue with each other. The best way to deal with this is to show them that when people disagree, they can discuss their differences peacefully.
<br /><br />7.Do Something Familiar.
<br /><br />Children love routine and ritual, and if there is a special thing you  and your children love doing, make time to make it part of your day/week. A particular story you always read before bedtime or something you always say to them before they go to bed. Children love the repetition of something lovely and will remember these little loving moments as they get older.
<br /><br />8.Read together
<br /><br />No matter whether you have a tiny baby or a wriggly toddler, they all love to be read to. You may need to adapt what you read slightly, more colourful bold books for babies, and simple, funny or sweet stories for toddlers. A 4-5 year old will be able to handle slightly more complex story and interesting illustrations. Reading with your child creates a perfect bonding time together.
<br /><br />9.Find out one important thing about your child’s day.
<br /><br />Although this really applies to slightly older children, finding something important about what they did at nursery or the childminders or even if they had a day out with daddy, is very important. It shows that you are interested in what they do and involved in their world. As they get older this can work as they may tell you the good things but also comfortable enough to tell you their worries and fears.
<br /><br />10. Don’t worry about the previous nine items.
<br /><br />Just when you think you’re doing ok as a parent, then along comes an article like this one to make you feel like you are not doing the job right!? Of course, that’s not the point. All the goals we’ve listed are worth aiming for, but no one will ever accomplish all of them, every day. So don’t beat yourself up trying to do the impossible. If expectations seem to high, be realistic about it and try not to judge yourself against other parents… remember they are probably feeling like you do as well.
<br /><br />A good way to look at how to become a good parent, is to try and enjoy the time you have with your little ones. Take a step back, take a breath, look at these little people you have created and spend time with them. It’s these moments with your children that make them feel loved. Leave the washing for another few minutes, have that chat with a friend on the phone a bit later and take those extra moments to spend with your children.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aa63eb8314875618f944bba2bc02783b" url=""><![CDATA[In pursuit of peace (from yahoo)<br/><br/>Pursue Peace and Unity of Spirit
<br /><br />How wonderful it is, how pleasant, for God’s people to live together in harmony! It is like the precious anointing oil running down from Aaron’s head and beard, down to the collar of his robes.
<br /><br />It is like the dew on Mount Hermon, falling on the hills of Zion.  That is where the Lord has promised his blessing—life that never ends.
<br /><br />Psalm 133 TEV
<br />__________________ 
<br /><br />Better to eat vegetables with people you love than to eat the finest meat where there is hate.
<br /><br />Hot tempers cause arguments, but patience brings peace.
<br /><br />Proverbs 15:17,18 TEV 
<br />__________________ 
<br /><br />Continue to love each other with true Christian love.
<br /><br />Don't forget to show hospitality to strangers, for some who have done this have entertained angels without realizing it! Don't forget about those in prison. Suffer with them as though you were there yourself. Share the sorrow of those being mistreated, as though you feel their pain in your own bodies.
<br /><br />Hebrews 13:1-3 NLT
<br /><br />__________________
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cf96404ae8e88edcee389b4513b5c971" url=""><![CDATA[In pursuit of happiness (from yahoo)<br/><br/>3 Keys to Lasting Happiness – by Gretchen Rubin
<br /> Happiness expert Gretchen RubinWhen I talk to people about happiness,one question that often arises is, &quot;Sure, happiness has many elements. But if you had to pick the most important thing, what is the key to happiness?&quot; It's a question that can be answered in different ways, depending on what framework you use to ponder the issue, but if I had to choose, I think there are three keys to happiness. 
<br />The first key? Self-knowledge 
<br />&quot;Know yourself&quot; is advice that people have been doling out for thousands of years - &quot;Know Thyself&quot; is inscribed on the Temple of Apollo at Delphi, the monument from ancient Greece that still stands today - and it's also one of the most challenging. 
<br />As part of my happiness project, I identified my 12 Personal Commandments - the 12 principles that I want to guide my actions and thoughts - and the first, most important commandment is, &quot;Be Gretchen.&quot; 
<br />Why is it so hard to know ourselves? You'd think that nothing could be simpler or more obvious. After all, you're hanging out with yourself all day long. But in fact, it's so easy to be distracted by the way we wish we were, or the way other people expect us to be, that we lose sight of what's true about ourselves. 
<br />Related: 70+ Bedroom Decorating Ideas 
<br />For instance, I've finally admitted to myself that although I can choose what I do, I can't choose what I like to do. I wish I had a passion for music, but I just don't. Along the same lines, I've admitted that just because something is fun for other people doesn't mean it's fun for me, and vice versa. Rollerblading, drinking wine, shopping, cooking, doing crossword puzzles...so many people find these activities fun, but I don't. Everyone in my family lying around reading in their pajamas? Ah, that sounds like fun. 
<br />The fact is, we can build a happy life only on the foundation of our own natures, interests, and values. I've found that the more faithfully I'm able to &quot;be Gretchen&quot; in my daily life, the happier I become. 
<br />The second key to happiness: anticipation 
<br />If the future holds no pleasant promise - well, it's very hard to be happy. Anticipation is the first stage, and a critical one, of enjoying a happy event. The other three stages are: 
<br />Savoring: Enjoying something in the moment (remember to turn off your cell phone!). 
<br />Expression: Giving voice to your pleasure to heighten your experience (think of crowds cheering at a baseball game, for example). 
<br />Reflection: Looking back on happy times (for example, by pulling out the photo album). 
<br />No matter what your circumstances, if you have something to look forward to, you bring happiness into your life well before the event actually takes place; you grab more happiness from a happy event, because it makes you happy even before you experience it. In fact, sometimes the happiness of anticipation is greater than the happiness of the actual experience - that's known as &quot;rosy prospection.&quot; 
<br />Related: 5 All-Time Best Haircuts 
<br />We should all be able to flip through our calendars and see at least a few pleasant things scheduled for future weeks. If your life is a parade of obligations, dreaded tasks, unpleasant encounters, and mandatory appearances, take a minute to figure out something that you'd find fun, and make time for it. Wish you had time to walk in the park with your dog? To work on a craft project? To have coffee with your sister? Schedule it on your calendar like you would a dentist appointment. Even before it happens, you'll get a happiness boost every time you anticipate it. (Also, if you put it on your calendar, you'll be far more likely to actually do it.) 
<br />However, as you're considering ways to amplify your sense of happy anticipation, don't forget happiness key number one. Just because something is fun for other people doesn't mean it's fun for you. Be honest about your likes and dislikes. Don't pretend that you like visiting museums or going on bike rides if you don't. Your fun may not look like other people's fun. I myself love to help other people clean out their closets. Skiing, no way--but cleaning out a friend's closets? That I anticipate with relish. 
<br />The third answer is ... love 
<br />No surprise there. Ancient philosophers and modern scientists agree: Strong relationships with other people are critical to a happy life. We need close, long-lasting relationships; we need to belong; we need to give and receive support - perhaps surprisingly, giving support is just as important to happiness as getting support. Not only does having strong relationships make it far more likely that you'll take joy in life, but studies show that it also lengthens life (incredibly, even more than stopping smoking), boosts immunity, and cuts the risk of depression. 
<br />For most of us, time, energy, and money are in short supply, so when we're trying to figure out how to get the biggest happiness bang for the buck, it's wise to spend on strengthening bonds with family, friends, and coworkers. Should you splurge on a new pair of boots or on a train ticket to your college reunion? Should you stay home watching TV or make plans to meet a friend? A decision that strengthens your ties to other people is likely to make you happier. 
<br />As I've thought about ways to strengthen the loving relationships in my life, I've discovered a paradox: To connect more deeply with people, I need to build my independent happiness. 
<br />This paradox became clear to me as I reflected on a haunting passage from Bob Dylan's strange, brilliant memoir, Chronicles: Volume One. He writes: &quot;I looked at the menu, then I looked at my wife. The one thing about her that I always loved was that she was never one of those people who thinks that someone else is the answer to their happiness. Me or anybody else. She's always had her own built-in happiness.&quot; 
<br />Related: Living Room Makeover Ideas 
<br />That's what I strive for now - to have my own &quot;built-in happiness.&quot; By being emotionally self-sufficient, I free myself (well, admittedly, only somewhat) from depending on other people to boost me up or letting them drag me down. When I have my own built-in happiness, I don't act like a happiness vampire who sucks happy energy from other people or craves a lifeblood of praise, affirmation, or reassurance to support my happiness. 
<br />I've realized, too, that happy people make other people happy. Because of a powerful psychological phenomenon called emotional contagion, people &quot;infect&quot; each other with their moods, and when I'm happy, I help lift others up. Also, when I feel happy myself, I have the emotional where-withal to turn outward to think about other people, to take an interest and to try to help. Unhappy people tend to become isolated, defensive, and preoccupied with their own problems. Therefore, while some people argue that it's selfish to be happy, we should be selfish - if only for selfless reasons. 
<br />Looking back at these three keys to happiness, I realize that English essayist Joseph Addison managed to sum it all up in a single sentence: &quot;Three grand essentials to happiness in this life are something to do, something to love, and something to hope for.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be29629b04f68d6e78e26e504defb404" url=""><![CDATA[Self Esteem - excerpt from Yahoo<br/><br/>Ten tips to boost your self esteem
<br />Acknowledge your strengths
<br /><br />We are all good at something or the other. Sit down and write about all the strengths you think you have. Do not over-analyse! Next, try to do things that bring out this quality into the open. This will help hone your strengths further, and also gain outside recognition. Also, do not forget to appreciate yourself for all your strong points and talents – it goes a long way in improving your self esteem.
<br />Do not put up with crap!
<br /><br />Do not put up with people who are mean to you, even those who tell you they love you. Draw clear boundaries. Tell them you don’t like to be talked to that way. Ask them to talk to you nicely, and be assertive when you do so.
<br />Lose those negative friends.
<br /><br />It’s time you lose friends who are constantly bitching or putting another down. Such people are likely to do the same behind your back, and they can leave you feeling critical and judgmental of others. Instead surround yourself with loving, positive people who are supportive and kind.
<br />Take in compliments
<br /><br />Many have a difficulty in accepting compliments. There are numerous nice things people might say each day, which your mind wouldn’t have even registered. Many other times, people refuse to take a compliment saying something like “Oh, I didn’t do much.” or simply shrugging it off. From now on, when someone pays you compliment, breathe, accept it, and say thank you!
<br /><br />When you begin to do this, you’ll see your self esteem rise to new levels.
<br />Do not berate yourself
<br /><br />Nobody achieves anything by berating oneself. You’ve made a mistake, OK – acknowledge it. There is no need to beat yourself up for it. Even the world’s greatest have made umpteen mistakes, and continue to make them. Give yourself permission for goof ups and even those BIG mistakes. This permission can be very liberating.
<br />Accept yourself
<br /><br />Accept the good, bad and ugly sides to you, everybody has them. All of these aspects make you who you are. When there is complete acceptance of self, one experiences a feeling of centeredness within and that will naturally bring out a person brimming with self confidence and self esteem.
<br /><br />Here are some self acceptance exercises that experts suggest. The mirror exercise: Look really deep, and see the person that is you in the mirror with love. Experts warn that some people might find it hard to look at themselves in the mirror that way. Give it time, allow the feelings to swell up. Experience the grief, the pain and keep trying to look at yourself. Another suggestion is to start off with positive affirmations, as they are fairly easy. Keep telling yourself, “I accept myself just the way I am”. Positive affirmations are known to have a great effect.
<br />Keep a gratitude diary
<br /><br />When you focus too much on all things going wrong, it can pull you down.
<br /><br />Every night, before you go to bed, write down 10 things you are thankful for. Many times one goes through without recognizing all that’s going right. This exercise helps you focus on all the good things in your life. Making you feel worthy.
<br />Respect yourself 
<br /><br />Eat healthy and well, exercise, sleep well. When you respect yourself, you’ll notice how others too will begin to reflect that, lifting your spirits and your self esteem.
<br />Dress smart!
<br /><br />Yes, clothes don’t make the man, but they do affect the way one feels about himself/herself. When you don’t look good, it affects the way you walk, sit and interact with people. So use this to your advantage and invest in looking good. This doesn’t mean you have to spend tonnes of money on grooming. Small things like bathing, washing your hair and wearing neat, pressed clothes can make a difference.
<br />Smile
<br /><br />You have heard the phrase: “Smile and the whole world smiles with you, frown and you frown alone.” It’s amazing what a simple smile can do to enhance a person’s appearance. It has the power to alter the mood of a place you walk into. So carry your smile with you wherever you go.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="11a936f3a7e1460e03c3add6728d9b74" url=""><![CDATA[Having Lunch While Working - selection from Yahoo<br/><br/>To call it a working lunch hardly seems fair to what the meaning of a working lunch used to be.
<br /><br />More than ever employees across the board are skipping out on going out midday for lunch to stay in for a quick desk lunch bite that requires little more than a few chews before it's back to the grindstone. A study conducted last year by human resources consulting firm Right Management showed that 65% of workers will not only eat at their desk but also opt out of taking a break period. And while it has been proven in studies that taking a break is good for you in both improving your overall job performance and keeping morale high, it continues to get tossed to the wayside in favor of one little big word: productivity. Jobs are still scarce, duties keep piling up for short staffed companies, employees are coming in earlier and staying later to get as much done as possible and schedules are increasingly difficult to coordinate whether you plan on eating with a coworker or not. [More from Forbes: Time management secrets anyone can use]
<br /><br />The desk lunch does have an incredible allure to it of being within close proximity to your workload and without all of the time consuming extras of going out (i.e. waiting for a table, waiting to take a group order, waiting for the check) that the group lunch of old can't boast. Continuing to stay seated throughout the day may not only prove to be a health risk, but at the same time it may be your only option. A short staff, as the USA Today reports, doesn't get the option to relieve a worker for lunch and even if so, that relief may not fall within a time in which you're actually hungry at.
<br /><br />Avoid the risk of falling into the desk lunch zone with these tips that you'll make a break for. [More from Forbes: Basic steps towards work-life balance]
<br /><br />Turn Your Lunch Hour Into a Run
<br /><br />In Brisbane, Australia this is already well underway for executives ditching the office altogether to go running for 20 to 30 minutes with just enough time leftover to suit back up for the rest of the workday. Working as both a stress reliever and mood elevator, legal counsel Amanda Barbera refers to it as &quot;the lunch-hour bolt&quot; explaining that, &quot;… it lets me make a quick snatch for the endorphins I'm addicted to. I find it easier to get away from work during lunch because everyone knows you're there for the day and you'll be coming back!&quot;
<br /><br />Whether running alone or with a group or even just going outside for a walk, find a way to get outside at some point during your midday break. And now that the weather is slowly growing nicer, this is an even more appealing alternative to catch a few rays outside with. [More from Forbes: The happiest companies for young professionals]
<br /><br />Eat a Protein-Filled Breakfast
<br /><br />Should you have to take a regularly scheduled lunch hour at a time in which you don't feel hungry, eat breakfast before you head into the office in the morning. Whole grains and protein in particular will help keep you full for the day with additional healthy snacks in between including fruit, yogurt, and granola. I recently replaced our traditional office candy basket with a big jar of fresh fruit options for my employees- out with the 2:30 feeling and in with the Vitamin C!
<br /><br />Lunch in the Break Room
<br /><br />It may not be the furthest place from your desk but for a change of pace take your lunch in the break room. Be sure that the break room in question is also one that you'd actually feel compelled to walk into though and stay for awhile. Keep it clean, brightly lit, include a flat screen television if possible, have plenty of plasticwear and napkins on hand and the snack cabinets stocked. [More from Forbes: 8 easy tips to move more at work]
<br /><br />Take a Work Lunch Field Trip
<br /><br />If you work with a smaller team, surprise them by scheduling in a work lunch for everyone to attend. Close the office down for a few hours and enjoy a leisurely meal out at a nearby eatery. Not only will this be a pleasant change of pace all around, but it'll also be a great way for the office to spend some time just talking and relaxing for a bit. Work for the remainder of the day will be much easier to concentrate on and I'm willing to bet that it won't make you miss that &quot;desk lunch&quot; option one bit.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b383307f085f2533e790de5e65d1974e" url=""><![CDATA[Bonding With Mom - selection from Yahoo<br/><br/>There is no perfect family. But perhaps the most complex relationship within a family is the one between mother and child.
<br /><br />Think about it: your mother sacrifices so much to bring you into the world. You're dependent on her for the first few years of your life, until you grow up and start to become independent. There is a constant struggle between the two: mothers strive to parent their children, while children make every effort to be independent from their mothers.
<br /><br />Sadly, it is one relationship the child might never understand until he or she becomes a parent. And sometimes, it might not even make much of a difference.
<br /><br />The good news is, all is not lost. You can still improve on your relationship with your mother. Here are a few starting points:
<br /><br />Have boundaries. Mothers become too clingy to their kids, wanting to fix everything for them. And while children find this convenient, they may end up resenting their mother for not letting them do things themselves.
<br /><br />&amp;quot;My friend's mom was always 'cleaning up' after him, and it totally crushed his self-esteem,&amp;quot; says Pat*, an events planner. &amp;quot;And when his mom would look upset or hurt about it, he would end up 'mothering' her!&amp;quot; Likewise, always fussing over your mother might make her feel inadequate as a parent—she is, after all, the one who should be doing the fussing!
<br /><br />As an adult, let your mom know that there are certain problems that you yourself have to deal with, not her. Be prudent about what you share with your mother, particularly if you feel that telling her your problems will only cause her anxiety. And try not to fuss over her, as well.
<br /><br />Be realistic. You may not exactly be like the Gilmore Girls, and that's okay. Stop trying to make your relationship with your mother the same as those you see on TV—and don't even think of comparing it to your friends' own relationships with their moms.
<br /><br />Every mother is different, and while not all have a knack to be nurturing, the fact is, she's still your mom. &amp;quot;I wished that my mom was the 'bonding' type whom I could talk to about boys while growing up,&amp;quot; shares Fran, a musician. &amp;quot;But the sooner I accepted that she just wasn't like that, I stopped being so resentful toward her. We now have a healthier relationship because I've stopped expecting her to be the kind of mom I wanted her to be.&amp;quot;
<br /><br />Agree to disagree. You are your own person—and so is your mom. Which means you probably don't share the same opinions when it comes to certain things, like work, relationships, and parenting.
<br /><br />The thing is, disagreements can be healthy when both parties are mature enough to realize that it's nothing personal. Disagreements only get ugly when moms feel rejected by their kids for having a different opinion; kids, on the other hand, feel like their moms disapprove of their beliefs, making them become defensive.
<br /><br />&amp;quot;I'm a single mom and I live with my parents, so it's a constant struggle to raise my daughter with them around the house because they always give their two cents on how to raise her,&amp;quot; says Rowena, a freelance writer. &amp;quot;I learned to just take their opinions with a grain of salt. At the end of the day, my daughter is still my daughter, and I know what's best for her.&amp;quot;
<br /><br />*names have been changed
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1807d3d95e448a65423aae1ff98589b2" url=""><![CDATA[What you eat is what you are - selection from yahoo<br/><br/>Although there are a million things out in the market today that will promise to make you gorgeous, nothing beats natural beauty sources. You are what you eat is what people usually say, so why not eat yourself beautiful with these edibles that will help you keep your skin and hair lovely, even without beauty products.
<br /><br />1.    Tomatoes
<br />Delicious whether eaten fresh or canned, tomatoes contain lycopene that is said to help with preventing premature aging and wrinkles. It also acts as an antioxidant for those who love lying under the sun.
<br /><br />2.    Spinach
<br />Beta-carotene is not only found in carrots. Spinach contains a high amount as well. Aside form protecting your eyes it has been said that it also improves skin that is prone to being oily or to acne.
<br /><br />3.    Wild Salmon
<br />Omega-3 Fatty Acids are salmon’s strongest weapons. It contains Vitamins B and D and antioxidants that help prevent puffy skin, redness and loss of elasticity.
<br /><br />4.    Oysters
<br />More popularly known as aphrodisiacs, oysters also are a good source of zinc which helps rebuild collagen, which in turn helps with the repair and renewal of our skin.
<br /><br />5.    Sweet Potato
<br />Who would have thought the lowly kamote is actually a beauty food. Like spinach, it contains massive amounts of Vitamin A (Beta-Carotene) which helps keep skin smooth and youthful and offers protection from the sun.
<br /><br />6.    Dark Chocolate
<br />Choose one with at least 70% cocoa and you will be treated to a chocfull of anti-oxidants, an increase in blood flow which helps with our skin’s hydration.
<br /><br />7.    Eggs
<br />Hair loves protein and it is actually made of a kind of protein called keratin. Consume them for a boost of protein that will go through your body or for more direct benefits, apply a mixture of olive oil and eggs for an all-natural mask for your hair.
<br /><br />8.    Yogurt
<br />Aside from being tasty, yogurt also contains a lot of calcium which does wonders for our teeth, nails and bones. Remember to pick low fat to steer clear from unwanted extra calories.
<br /><br />9.    Avocado
<br />A great supply of unsaturated fatty acids, this fruit will keep your skin smooth and nerves strong. Mash up and eat with milk or add a few slices to your chicken sandwiches to incorporate into your diet.
<br /><br />10.    Nuts
<br />Although known for their high fat content, they are also loaded with nutrients like zinc, omega-3 fatty acids and Vitamin E. Incorporate almonds, walnuts, cashews or sesame seeds into your diet to help prevent cell damage and promote skin elasticity.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1b3b0ae96cf0066130bd0a6e75dc4e68" url=""><![CDATA[Excerpt from Yahoo...five foods that reduce inflammation<br/><br/>SALMON 
<br />Research shows that the healthy omega-3 fatty acids found in salmon seem to decrease the production of inflammatory proteins. In fact, a diet high in omega-3 fatty acids may decrease inflammation to the same extent that aspirin and other nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory medications do. However, most of us eat far too many omega-6 fatty acids (which are found in other protein sources such as chicken and oils such as corn or safflower oil) and not enough omega-3 fatty acids. Experts believe that this imbalance can actually promote inflammation. Aim for 2-3 servings of fresh or frozen wild or canned sockeye salmon each week. Not a salmon fan? Omega-3 fatty acids are also found in walnuts, flaxseed, and enriched eggs. 
<br />BEANS 
<br />Choosing a non-meat protein source, like beans, at several meals each week can also help prevent the imbalance of omega-6 fatty acids. Also, beans are high in fiber, which helps to stabilize the blood sugar. This is important because big spikes or dips in blood sugar can lead to an inflammatory response in the body. Aim for one meatless day per week, choosing plant-based proteins instead of meats. 
<br />BERRIES 
<br />Antioxidants like vitamins A and C, which are found in high levels in berries, can help fight inflammation by protecting the body from damage that leads to inflammation. Other fruits and veggies have high levels of antioxidants as well. Eating a variety of colorful fruits and vegetables each day will ensure you are getting plenty of these powerful nutrients. Aim for 5-9 servings of colorful produce each day. 
<br />GREEN TEA 
<br />To amp up your antioxidant intake even more, add a few cups of green tea to your daily diet. Green tea contains high levels of antioxidants, specifically a compound called EGCG, which research has shown to be particularly effective in reducing inflammation. Aim for 3-4 cups of freshly brewed green tea each day.
<br />OATS 
<br />Oats and other whole grains not only contain important nutrients like selenium, which research has shown to help fight inflammation, they are also an additional source of fiber. Fiber, as mentioned above, helps to stabilize blood sugar levels and prevent an inflammatory response. Aim for a minimum of 25 grams of fiber per day and 3-6 servings of whole grain foods like oats, quinoa, or whole grain bread each day. Focus on including some of these foods into each of your daily meals and not only will you be eating better, you will also be taking an easy step towards preventing disease brought on by inflammation.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="baad20b515405bcf3977ca86ce8da1fd" url=""><![CDATA[ten cellulite-busting foods from yahoo<br/><br/>Ginger
<br /><br />One cause of cellulite is poor circulation, so eating foods such as ginger that boost blood flow can help to improve its appearance. As well as being good for circulation, ginger is also good for detoxification and strengthening the lymphatic system, which can help with the circulation of lymph fluid and toxins that can accumulate in fat pockets under the skin, contributing to the bumpy appearance of cellulite.
<br /><br />Asparagus
<br /><br />Asparagus is another food with circulation-boosting properties. On top of this, asparagus is a great stress reliever due to its abundance of folic acid, which can help to stabilise a stressful mood. As prolonged levels of stress can increase fat storage on the body, adding foods such as asparagus to your diet can help to reduce the appearance of cellulite.
<br /><br />Avocados
<br /><br />While anyone fat, thin, young or old can suffer from cellulite, ageing does tend to increase the visibility of cellulite due to the loss of elasticity and thinning of skin. Therefore, try eating foods rich in Essential Fatty Acids (EFAs) which can help to strengthen skin and keep it supple and elastic. Avocados are a particularly rich source of EFAs, as well as being high in many essential nutrients.
<br /><br />Oily fish
<br /><br />Another top food for keeping the skin in good condition is oily fish, which is high in skin-strengthening omega-3 fatty acids. As an added bonus, the fatty acids present in oily fish are also good for reducing inflammation and boosting the cardiovascular and lymphatic systems, making them a good choice for keeping cellulite at bay.
<br /><br />Dark, leafy greens
<br /><br />Dark green leafy vegetables such as spinach and kale are rich in an antioxidant called lutein, which research has shown is good for helping the skin to retain its moisture and elasticity and increase its lipid levels - all good news for those suffering from cellulite. On top of this, leafy greens are nutrient-rich and are good for the circulation and detoxification.
<br /><br />Cranberry juice
<br /><br />A sluggish lymphatic system is one of the primary causes of cellulite, so those wishing to reduce its appearance should try boosting their intake of cranberry juice, which is noted for its abilities to cleanse the lymph system. This powerful juice helps to emulsify stubborn fat deposits in the lymphatic system so that they are more easily flushed out the system.
<br /><br />Bananas
<br /><br />Bananas are a rich source of potassium, which is helpful for reducing cellulite in many ways. Firstly, potassium helps to reduce water retention which can be a leading cause of cellulite. Furthermore, potassium can help to support the lymphatic system and ensure it works efficiently at circulating fluid and cleansing the body of impurities.
<br /><br />Whole grains
<br /><br />Whole grains are packed with fibre, which is an essential for keeping your body running smoothly. Fibre helps speed up the process of detoxification and clear out waste products that can build up in your system, often leading to cellulite. Eating whole grains also helps to keep the heart healthy and boost circulation to cellulite-prone areas.
<br /><br />Papaya
<br /><br />Eating plenty of fresh fruit and vegetables is one of the best ways to detox the body and reduce the appearance of cellulite, and papaya is a particularly good choice of fruit. Papaya is not only rich in potassium - one of the most important nutrients when it comes to battling cellulite - but it is also high in antioxidant beta-carotene, which can help prevent damage to body tissue.
<br /><br />Berries
<br /><br />To help keep skin firm and taut and disguise the appearance of cellulite, try adding some vitamin C to your diet to help boost your skin's collagen levels. Berries are a particularly good source of vitamin C, as well as being extremely high in the antioxidants necessary for fighting toxic waste, which can slow down the lymphatic system and accumulate in cellulite-prone areas. Read more on realbuzz.com...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f18f04ec8268e8f9d32ce456bc23fec5" url=""><![CDATA[Losing weight by not eating after dark (from yahoo)<br/><br/>Make your final meal of the day one that sets with the sun in order to lose weight.
<br /><br />That's the overriding conclusion of a recently published study which found that eating after dark could be a contributing factor to obesity.
<br /><br />It's a theory that correlates the metabolic cycles of different organs to eating schedules, researchers explained in the study published online in the journal Cell Metabolism last week. While other studies have examined how nighttime eating affects the body's circadian rhythms, the latest research also underscores how this unhealthy habit relates to the cycles of particular organs.
<br /><br />&quot;Every organ has a clock,&quot; said lead author of the study Satchidananda Panda of the Salk Institute in a statement. &quot;That means there are times that our livers, intestines, muscles, and other organs will work at peak efficiency and other times when they are -- more or less -- sleeping.&quot;
<br /><br />Eating a ham and cheese sandwich before bed or tucking into a pint of ice cream at midnight, however, could sabotage weight loss efforts by throwing off the normal metabolic cycles of these organs.
<br /><br />For the study, researchers put groups of mice on a high-fat diet but restricted their eating hours to eight hours a day. Another group was given unrestricted access to the food.
<br /><br />What they found was that despite consuming a diet high in fat, mice that were restricted to a structured eating schedule showed improvements to their metabolic and physiological rhythms, gaining less weight and suffering less liver damage.
<br /><br />They also showed lower levels of inflammation compared to the rats which were given unfettered access.
<br /><br />Another study published in the journal Obesity found that eating late at night when the body wants to sleep interferes with the body's natural circadian rhythms and could likewise contribute to obesity.
<br /><br />Meanwhile, if the late-night munchies do strike, consider indulging chip cravings with pretzels and low-fat cheese or sour cream dip, and ice cream with low-fat chocolate milk or yogurt, advises LiveStrong.com.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e630ff7502bf21a7c4849727553b516e" url=""><![CDATA[Excerpt from Yahoo...vital tip for women<br/><br/>Top 10 worst female health habits
<br /> Wearing heels
<br />More and more of us are opting to wear heels on a daily basis, and this could be bad news for our health. High heels affect our posture, put pressure on joints, and can lead to a range of conditions including arthritis, hammer toes, back pain and tendon injuries – and that’s before you take into account any heel-related accidents! To minimise damage, limit your heels to 1.5 inches for daily wear, and wear insoles to help reduce the pressure on joints. 
<br />Carrying a heavy handbag
<br />With the rising number of gadgets and accessories the majority of women haul around, many of us are carrying around several pounds of weight on our shoulders every day. As a result, lots of us are also putting our long term health at risk. While you may not feel the effects right now, lugging around a heavy handbag can lead to serious back problems and neck pain as well as poor posture. Don’t wait until the damage is done – do your health a favour and try clearing out all non-essential items and switching to a smaller bag. 
<br />Sleeping in makeup
<br />Most of us have succumbed to the temptation to sleep in our post-party makeup at some point. However, leaving makeup on overnight – along with the dirt and oil that naturally accumulates on skin throughout the day – is a quick route to clogged pores, congested skin and spots. Sleeping with mascara and eye makeup on can also affect your health by causing eye irritation, bloodshot eyes or even infection. 
<br />Matching men drink for drink
<br />From networking drinks to first dates and social events, there are many instances when women may feel compelled to keep up with the drinking habits of the opposite sex. However, women not only tend to weigh less than men but they have less body water to dilute the alcohol, which means they tend to get more drunk more quickly. To minimise the risks of alcohol on your health, try to keep within the recommended guidelines for alcohol consumption and alternate alcohol with soft drinks. 
<br />Wearing the wrong bra size
<br />It is thought that more than 70 per cent of women are wearing the wrong bra size. However, wearing a badly fitted bra can not only affect the look of your clothes, but research suggests it can cause a range of health problems including back, neck and breast pain, breathing difficulties, poor posture, skin irritation, circulation problems and even irritable bowel syndrome. Rather than guessing your size, make sure you get measured to ensure you are getting the support you need. 
<br />Worrying and harbouring regrets
<br />Stress is damaging to both our physical and mental health, and women are twice as likely as men to suffer from stress-related disorders, as well as having higher rates of depression and anxiety. While it is thought there may be biological reasons for this, worrying about the future and dwelling on regrets can also add to our problems, with research suggesting that women are more than twice as likely as men to harbour regrets over lost loves and broken relationships. 
<br />Obsessing over appearance
<br />While both genders suffer from body insecurity, many women tend to overly obsess over their idea of the “perfect” body. Research findings published in the journal Obstetrics &amp; Gynecology found that 16 per cent of the normal or underweight women studied believed themselves to be overweight, while a study commissioned by Dove found that 90 per of women wanted to change at least one aspect of their appearance. Body insecurity not only affects our mental health, but it can also lead to physical damage caused by extreme diets, yo-yo dieting, eating disorders and cosmetic surgery. 
<br /> Woman looking in the mirror
<br /><br />Emotional eating
<br />While comfort eating affects both genders, research has suggested that men are more likely to reinforce positive emotions with food, while women comfort eat when they’re sad. Women are also more likely to satisfy their cravings with sweet, high-calorie foods. Rather than letting your waistline suffer next time you’re feeling blue, try distracting yourself from cravings by doing something you enjoy, or boost your endorphins and health with an uplifting workout. 
<br />Not getting enough sleep
<br />Not only can lack of sleep make us look and feel at our worst, but insufficient shut-eye can also lead to increased accidents, calorie consumption and heart disease risk. Unluckily for women, statistics suggest that sleep problems affect more women than men, while a study by the University of Michigan found that women are more than twice as likely to give up sleep to care for others. Unfortunately, sleep has been found to affect women’s blood pressure and mood more than men’s, making it imperative that you do your best to get a good night’s sleep. 
<br />Putting themselves last
<br />Not only are women more likely to compromise their sleeping habits to care for children and others, they are also prone to putting their own wants and needs at the bottom of a hectic to-do list of chores and obligations. To avoid running yourself into the ground, learn to sometimes say no to those requests and commitments that are less than essential, and make sure you set aside some “me” time each week to do something enjoyable just for you. Read more on realbuzz.com...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13d1e87a5d27a4ae565dd688b643661a" url=""><![CDATA[Excerpt from Yahoo...keeping a relationship longer<br/><br/>How do you keep your relationship going?
<br /><br />By Marie Calica for Yahoo! Southeast Asia
<br /><br />More than 15 years ago, I met an 80-something-year-old man in the Intensive Care Unit waiting room. My late father was in critical condition then, while this man's son who had suffered a heart attack was a few stalls away from my dad. Tito Paquito was this octogenarian's name, and we would see each other every day when it was our turn to keep watch over our respective family members. His wife, Tita Virgie, was a very sweet and beautiful woman who joined him every so often. They would have their packed lunch side by side, would meet with the doctors together, and sat in silence on the hard, uncomfortable plastic chairs of the ICU waiting room. The two had been college sweethearts, I found out during one of our lengthy conversations. And the way they looked at each other and spoke to one another inspired me to want that kind of relationship when I grow old.
<br /><br />Different people have different ways of keeping their relationship going, and so I asked several couples in long-term relationships what their secrets are to staying together:
<br /><br />Take them for who they are—warts and all. &quot;To make one's love last is, from the onset, to accept the other person is a gift from God together with that person's strengths and frailties, seeing that these are complimentary to one's own strengths and frailties. Then, from day to day, consciously make the effort to affirm each other in that love. As the old adage goes: 'take me for better or for worst, but don't take me for granted.'&quot;—John and Peggy, married 44 years
<br /><br />Know your partner's language of love. &quot;We all love the idea of a fairy tale ending, but life's not like that—at least not all the time. When we put our partner in a box and expect them to do things because you do them that way or your best friend's husband or wife does it that way, we'll be disappointed when they don't live up to it. Understand how your partner expresses their love, and appreciate that.&quot;—Deena and David, married 21 years
<br /><br />[Professional advice on making marriage last]
<br /><br />Don't sweep issues under the rug. &quot;There are times when we forgo confrontation to keep the peace. That's good sometimes, but if either of you suddenly becomes irritable, then it's time to talk.&quot;—Suzi and Paolo, married 11 years
<br /><br />Go long distance. &quot;Being apart has its benefits. The distance is a good thing in a way because you don't ever get 'tired' of the relationship. It also helps ensure that we have a life outside the relationship, which is a healthy thing, long distance or not. It's easier these days of course. When he took his masters some years back, we connected via fax, ICQ, and email only (those were the days when the tech world was transitioning from Wordstar to Word, from DOS to Windows).&quot;—Rowena and Jonathan, together 16 years
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="699ca7ef345af087e3e9c921ac3a0565" url=""><![CDATA[Tips to keep your man from straying (excerpt from yahoo)<br/><br/>By Pierra Calasanz-Labrador for Yahoo! Southeast Asia
<br /><br />When the movie No Other Woman came out, it struck a chord among millions of married Pinays—what would we do if an Anne Curtis clone walked into our husband's life?
<br /><br />Oh, the very thought strikes panic in our hearts and opens up a Pandora's Box of questions: Would we pack our bags and leave at the first sign of his indiscretion? Would we play the role of the long-suffering wife and look the other way? Or, would we fight fire with fire, with Cristine Reyes verve in all her negligee glory and mama Carmi Martin's one-liner winners ringing in our ears? (&quot;Panahon na para i-pack up yang si Lucy Torres mo. Ilabas mo na diyan si Gretchen Barretto!&quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />Hang on—why even wait for things even get to that point? The best defense is a good offense, and the key is to know what makes our hubbies happy, so he won't even consider straying. Easier said than done, right? So here are some tips from domestic goddesses (and regular men) on how to keep your man in line:
<br /><br />Tip#1: Be attentive and affectionate. After the passion fades, sometimes our interaction with hubby is reduced to a perfunctory good night kiss. Don't stop showing your love and affection! Shares Anna*, &quot;I try to keep the romance alive. We go out on dinner and movie dates without the kids. We also still talk about our dreams and what we're going to do in our old age. It helps that we laugh a lot together!&quot; You don't need to sweep each other off your feet—random cuddling, holding hands while watching a TV movie, sweet daily rituals, and the occasional 'stolen moment,' will help keep your love fresh.
<br /><br />Tip#2: Look your best. Yes, he vowed to love you through thick and thin, waistline notwithstanding—but that doesn't mean you should let yourself go. &quot;Once a girl is 'off the market,' she kind of relaxes her effort to be attractive. But don't turn into a total slob!&quot; warns Kathy*. Caring for your health and body, keeping in shape, dolling yourself up nicely can be the greatest compliment you can pay him—and yourself. Bonus to looking your best: as you &quot;wow him everyday,&quot; you're also loving what you see in the mirror. And when you feel good about yourself, there's a tendency to make your partner feel good, too.
<br /><br />Tip #3: Exude confidence. Is your hubby such a Greek god or chick magnet that you're constantly on praning mode? Searching his pockets/wallet/going through his texts, bristling at the mention of any female colleagues, or stalking him without any provocation will only succeed in annoying him, and turning you into a suspicious, desperate, sorry mess. It can get really tiresome for a guy to deal with jealous rages or constantly reassure you of his love over and over again. Do listen to your woman's intuition—but before then, don't jump the gun. Treating him like you're sure he's going to cheat may actually tempt him to call your bluff!
<br /><br />Okay, so maybe you say you trust your guy, but you don't trust the women around him. Have a little faith in yourself. Yes, there will always be someone prettier, hotter or younger than you, but no one can ever be the YOU he fell in love with. Clinging desperately on to your man may give him illusions that he's too good for you—he should feel that he's lucky to have you, and not the other way around.
<br /><br />Tip #4: Don't nag, don't smother. Unless you want your guy to revert back to his rebellious teenage self, act like his hot, loving wife—not his mom or prison guard. &quot;When a guy feels 'sakal' or stifled in a relationship, his instinct is to escape,&quot; says Tony. &quot;And if there just happens to be someone who comes along who is sexy, fun and has no baggage or drama… patay.&quot; So go ahead, let him have his fill of computer games or basketball time with the guys—and he'll be happy to come home to his cool wife.
<br /><br />Tip #5: Spice things up. Says Migs*, &quot;Guys love the thrill of the chase.&quot; It only takes a little flirtation to spur their imagination. &quot;A husband thinks that he already has you, so he might be curious to know how it would be with someone they technically can't have. It's the 'what if' factor,&quot; continues Migs.
<br /><br />So how do you keep him from acting on his animal instincts? Bring out the domestic goddess in you. Spice things up with spontaneous gestures, go on &quot;second honeymoon&quot; trips, or (trump card) try new tricks in the bedroom. Keep things from getting stale, so that he's constantly amazed by you. Maintain the mystery, no matter how comfortable you are with each other.
<br /><br />Tip # 6: Show an interest in his activities. While it's important to nurture individual interests for your personal growth, find some shared activities as well so you can grow together. You don't have to be joined at the hip, but it really helps when you're supportive of his passions. Do you respond with a bored &quot;uhm-hmmm&quot; every time he tries to engage you in conversation about his activities? Would you rather he bond with someone else? When he spends a lot of time somewhere else (especially if it requires overnight stays and out-of-town events), there's always the temptation of falling for a colleague or teammate who &quot;gets him.&quot; So don't belittle his hobbies.
<br /><br />Tip #7: Keep it special. It's easy to take things for granted after years and years of marriage, kids, and morning breath. Someone's bound to feel overworked and under-appreciated, and the danger comes when an outside force starts showing some of that attention that's sorely lacking at home.
<br /><br />Complacency is the devil—so make things special every day. It can be as simple as saying thank you after every meal/errand/chore, thoughtfully surprising each other with a favorite snack, or treating him to a relaxing massage after a long day. Says Andrea, &quot;I treat him with respect; I try not to brat out and pick fights. I tell him I appreciate that he takes care of us. And on his end, I suppose he realizes that he has a partner for life, that I'm there for him no matter what. It's not a fleeting romance—it's a real relationship.&quot;
<br /><br />*Not their real names
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bf6d067b1a0b6022891be8e8fd230a3b" url=""><![CDATA[Female Qualities that Women should Develop (excerpt -yahoo)<br/><br/>Female quality 1: She has a life of her own
<br /><br />Say ‘cheerio’ to the helpless heroine from classic literature, and ‘well, hello!’ to the contemporary independent woman. It’s important to show that you’re self-sufficient when you’re trying to impress a man, and it’s equally as important to maintain this when you’re in a relationship. The average modern man doesn’t want a lady to be clinging onto him all the time – it makes him feel suffocated. Rather than ditching your friends and family to spend time with a new love interest, make sure you keep separate plans in your diary at all times. Never feel as though you wouldn’t have a life if this person wasn’t in it; get out there and show that you have a vibrant lifestyle aside from him. A relationship should enhance your life, not rule it. 
<br /><br />Female quality 2: She is honest and loyal
<br /><br />Be honest with your love interest. If you tell them that a) you’re married and going through a particularly difficult divorce; <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> you have a strange obsession with feet; or c) anything else that could potentially make them run for the hills, then you’ve done the right thing. Okay, maybe hold back on option b for now, but you see what we’re getting at. Anything that they may find out further down the line and could put them off should be made clear from the outset, or you risk wasting the time of you both. Don’t sugar-coat anything – if this man likes you enough, he will want to help you through difficult situations rather than leaving you to it. If either you or your love interest can’t accept the truth about one another’s past or present lives, you shouldn’t think about getting together because you won’t be able to look to the future. 
<br /><br />Female quality 3: She looks after herself
<br /><br />This is one thing that hasn’t changed since the days of our most distant ancestors; men like a woman who takes a pride in her appearance and vice versa. We’re not talking about being a tall, slim supermodel – it’s not all about looks – but a little primping and preening here and there goes a long way. There’s no need to dress up in a ball gown and tiara for a date, but do wear something that accentuates your fantastic figure. Wear makeup to highlight your natural features; style your hair to compliment your face; and spritz on your favourite scent to boost your confidence – hello gorgeous! Styling yourself to make you feel your best leads to a more confident you and that’s another trait that men look for in women. 
<br /><br />Female quality 4: She is self-confident
<br /><br />Gone are the days when the timid damsel in distress attracted the handsome, strong man; nowadays, being needy attracts little more than a few raised eyebrows. Despite coming across as confident, rarely do the celebrities you see in the media feel as bold and confident as they look. It’s all about faking it. Instead of zoning in on your weaknesses, develop and maximise your strengths to put you in the right frame of mind. Make sure you use your body language to your advantage, as this can help you to fake confidence when really you might prefer it if the ground were to swallow you up. Stand tall, make eye contact, and smile, for an instantly more confident you. 
<br /><br />couple on beach
<br />Female quality 5: She is mature and well-spoken
<br /><br />Baby talk can be cute but don’t use it too often, sugar bunny. Your average modern man likes his woman to be able to hold down an intellectual conversation as well as having a good sense of humour, and cutie-overload could put him off. Talk about interesting topics and be sure to listen to him as well as inputting your own thoughts and ideas into the conversation. Hold back on slang words for your first few dates and avoid swear words too, as they come across as uncouth. 
<br /><br />It is a truth universally acknowledged that a modern man looks for different qualities in a woman than he may have done in the 1800s and – whilst no man is ever the same and may look for different qualities in a woman – it’s a good idea to take these tips on board to boost your dating potential.  Read more on realbuzz.com...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6a2ebd1df6a0eb1de6892d00c479c936" url=""><![CDATA[Men's Point of View on Women (excerpt from yahoo)<br/><br/>7 things women do that drive men mad
<br />RealBuzzRealBuzz – Mon, May 28, 2012 5:00 PM PHT
<br /><br />Annoying female habit 1: Making an anniversary out of everything
<br /><br />What is it with women turning the nice little things in life into a grand gift-exchanging, champagne-popping ceremony? We return home from a normal day at work to be met with a candle-lit dinner and an expensive looking gift but, quite frankly, it makes our heart stop. Have you done something wrong? Is it your birthday? My birthday? Oh silly me, it’s the anniversary of the first time we looked at each other. Please refrain from doing this, ladies. We have a hard enough time getting event dates right without being shouted at for not buying the dog a card to celebrate the anniversary of his first vaccination.
<br /><br />Annoying female habit 2: Piling the bed with cushions
<br /><br />One would be mistaken for thinking that a bed is for sleeping in. We go to get our head down for the night, only to find the bed piled sky-high with strategically placed cushions that leave no room for us. What’s more, only a couple of these cushions actually have a purpose. We don’t need the tiny heart-shaped one or the big fluffy one that makes us sneeze – just a normal pillow to rest our head on will suffice. We don’t adorn the bed with DIY tools and model cars, so please tame your OCD (Obsessive Cushion Disorder) and stop making an elaborate display out of our bed so we can get down to the important stuff.
<br /><br />couple on bed of cushions having pillow fightcouple on bed of cushions having pillow fight
<br /><br />Annoying female habit 3: Asking us what we’re thinking
<br /><br />It’s a classic example of how women like to test us, and possibly trick us into making the cardinal sin of admitting that we weren’t thinking about her at that particular moment. One minute we’re enjoying a cuddle, the next they’re hurling that question at us when we’re least expecting it. They say it so fast that we don’t have chance to make up a false reply or even to think straight, which leads us to stutter and then be accused of thinking of our ex. Asking what we’re thinking is basically a nice way of saying ‘you aren’t allowed to have private thoughts, unless they’re about me’.
<br /><br />Annoying female habit 4: Saying ‘I’m fine’, when you’re not happy
<br /><br />So she stood in front of the television while the football was on, we got a bit iffy and snapped, and now all sorts of issues have been bought up. Then she says it – that passive-aggressive statement that marks the start of the dreaded silent treatment: “I’m fine”. Erm, are you really fine because you’ve just screamed at us until you’ve gone red in the face, and now you’re laying face down on the bed crying. If you’re unhappy just outline the problem and then we can sort it out and carry on as normal. Or – even better – don’t outline the problem and let us watch the football in peace.
<br /><br />Annoying female habit 5:  Using sex as a weapon
<br /><br />One of the most annoying things that a woman can do is deny her man of sexual privileges. Some women seem to take great pleasure in using our weakness to their own advantage through the classic ‘if you don’t do this, we’re not having sex’ scenario. If you’re going to stop us from doing one thing, please don’t let it be sex. We don’t stop you from eating and drinking, so please don’t mess with our basic human needs either.
<br /><br />Annoying female habit 6: Being over-emotional
<br /><br />You cry at funerals, you cry at weddings, you cry at happy films, you cry at sad films. This makes us feel awkward because we just don’t know what to say or do when you’re sat sobbing all over our freshly ironed shirt. Where do all these tears come from? We think women should just have an annual crying day where they get together and cry for twenty four hours, before coming home and being normal for the other 364 days of the year. It would solve a lot of our problems.
<br /><br />Annoying female habit 7: Incessant talking
<br /><br />We’ve heard that women are estimated to say around 20, 000 words a day – which is an awful lot compared to the paltry 7, 000 estimated for men – so we understand that she needs to get her daily nattering fix, but why is it always at the most inappropriate times? She was quiet all the way through the family dinner when we needed her to break the awkward silence, but as soon as we start getting to the competitive part of a multi-player game with our friends, she just won’t shut up about how cute the neighbour’s cat looks when it sits next to the rose bush. To make it even more annoying, the actual part of the story she was getting at whilst rambling on about the neighbour’s cat, was that the cat’s owner now works at the grocery store down the road. Ladies, if you’re going to talk, pick the right moment and please, just get to the point. Read more on realbuzz.com...
<br />Follow us on Facebook
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a307d347ce8c729ff746f9566e542afd" url=""><![CDATA[For a Better & Clearer Vision (excerpt from yahoo)<br/><br/>Eat Fish and benefit from it
<br /><br />In yet another study touting the benefits of omega-3s in healthy aging, a new study out of Canada has found that choosing fish for dinner could help stave off age-related vision loss.
<br /><br />In normal aging, vision loss results from the accumulation of a toxic molecule at the back of the eyes which builds up in the retina. But after feeding lab mice with an omega-3 fatty acid known as docosahexaenoic acid or DHA, the research team out of the University of Alberta found that the nutrient -- found in oily fish like salmon -- prevented the buildup of the toxin which normally increases twofold as people age.
<br /><br />The Canadian study, announced last week, is the latest to build on research vaunting the benefits of omega-3 fatty acids in healthy aging. Research published earlier this year in the journal Neurology found that a diet low in omega-3 fatty acids may cause the brain to age faster.
<br /><br />Similarly, a study published last year in the Archives of Ophthalmology found that regular consumption of fish and omega-3 fatty acids reduced the risk of developing age-related macular degeneration in women, a condition that results in the loss of central vision and is the main cause of blindness in people over the age of 50.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2aa60ac9070659e736eadde9e472c734" url=""><![CDATA[Top 5 Benefits of Tea Tree - excerpt from yahoo<br/><br/>Chances are, you've seen &quot;tea tree oil&quot; or &quot;tea tree extract&quot; as a main ingredient in many skin and beauty products. You might even own a few of them. But did you ever wonder where it came from, and how your skin and hair could benefit from it?
<br /><br />Tea tree oil is a natural antibacterial disinfectant, something that aborigine tribes have known for thousands of years. The indigenous Bundjalung people of Eastern Australia have been using the leaves of &quot;tea trees&quot; (also known as melaleuca) to treat colds. It was in the 1920s when researcher Arthur Penfold reported on its antimicrobial activity that people (including pharmaceutical companies!) took notice of this wonder tree.
<br /><br />So how exactly does tea tree help you get beautiful skin and hair? Read on to find out: 
<br /><br />1. Treat acne. Experiencing a zit attack? Tea tree-infused acne meds can help tame acne flare-ups! In fact, a study published by the Medical Journal of Australia in 1990 states that a solution of 5% tea tree oil is just as effective as 5% benzoyl peroxide. Which explains why some dermatologists aren't shy about recommending the use of tea tree oil paired with glycolic acid to treat pimples.
<br /><br />2. Cure scalp conditions. From mild scalp irritation to a baby's cradle cap, tea tree's bacteria-fighting properties can help remedy your scalp problems. Tea tree-infused shampoos usually contain about 2 to 5% concentration of the oil (any more than that and it will be too strong) to rid the scalp of fungus and bacteria. It can also help unblock hair follicles to prevent even more bacteria build-up, all the while moisturizing the scalp.
<br /><br />3. Keep bugs away. If it can kill bacteria and viruses, it can most definitely act as an insect deterrent. Keep mosquitoes, fleas, lice, and flies away by rubbing a bit of tea tree oil mixed with a carrier oil, like mineral or sunflower oil (read the label—too much tea tree oil might be too strong for the skin!). Bonus: it can kill hookworms as well, which can penetrate through the skin.
<br /><br />4. Keep wounds clean. With all its microbe and bacteria-fighting powers, it's no wonder aborigine tribes also used tea tree to treat cuts and open wounds. Some have applied it directly on open wounds, boils, sores, cuts, and insect stings.
<br /><br />5. Helps calm eczema and dermatitis. Eczema is a skin condition, which may include dryness and skin rashes. Oftentimes, the skin gets itchy, starts to crust, then blister or crack. While corticosteroids are usually prescribed to treat this condition, some swear by the wonders of tea tree oil to help clear up their skin. If you'd like to try exploring tea tree in clearing up your skin, get a go signal from your doctor to try this tea tree bath: add 10 drops of tea tree essential oil and one tablespoon of extra virgin olive oil to a warm bath. Soak the affected area for about 20 minutes, giving the oils time to work its antiseptic magic on your skin.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6fbe9350756f40ae7853c9a04f5d1a42" url=""><![CDATA[Simple Troubleshooting on your car (from yahoo)<br/><br/>By Monico D. Mekaniko
<br /><br />Hi! I’m Monico D. Mekaniko and I’m here to give you easy driving tips to make your life less stressful when traveling using your motor vehicle. Every now and then I will also give you other motoring tips, vehicle purchasing tips and even motoring industry news and trends.
<br /><br />Let’s start with one of the most basic yet most frustrating scenarios. You’re all dressed up and already late for an important meeting. You hop into your car, switch on the ignition, and nothing happens. Your car won’t start. Kaput. Goodbye car, hello MRT and perspiration. Good luck with that important meeting, right?
<br /><br />Not necessarily so. Sometimes all you have to do is take a deep breath, roll up your sleeves and troubleshoot it yourself. It could take you a few minutes, but more important, you might save a lot of money from a needless check-up and you could still get to your meeting on time.
<br /><br />With today’s computer-controlled vehicles, the possibility of a no-start is less likely to happen, but it still does, so let’s try to help the hapless mortal motorists out there. For this particular discussion, however, we shall exclude carburetor-based vehicles. Seriously.
<br /><br />Key won't turn. First off, are you using the right key? I know it sounds silly but this does indeed happen, something like what call center agents encounter when callers complain about their computers, when in fact their computers are not even plugged in. Check your keys. If the key is too worn, try using your spare key. Key still won’t turn? Try forcing the steering wheel to one side, then the other, while trying to turn the key. You might have left your car parked with the front wheels turned all the way to one side. By turning it all the way to the left then right (depending on which direction your wheels are pointed) while turning the key, this releases pressure on the steering lock, allowing the key to turn.
<br /><br />Click or crank? First off, once you turn on the ignition, do you hear the engine’s cranking sound, or in Filipino, what they call “redondo”? If there is none and all you hear is a hollow click or a series of clicks like a woodpecker happily pecking away, that means there is no electrical current coursing through your system and ignition is not achieved. If you switch on the ignition and you hear the engine crank but it won’t start with your usual “vroom” from the exhaust, electricity is indeed coursing but somewhere along the system, ignition and combustion are not being achieved. If the engine does not crank, you might have a weak or dead battery. Or your battery connection cables are dirty or corroded. Put on some gloves, check if the cable connectors are firmly attached. See if there is corrosion or dirt and try to clean your battery posts a bit. Be careful not to use any metallic tool if you are not familiar with the car battery. Then try starting your car again.
<br /><br />Dead battery. Turn on the interior lights then try to start the car. If the light goes dim, your battery is the problem. This does not mean your battery is already useless, it only means that it does not have enough charge to start your car. Remember that your battery serves only to provide temporary power to start your car or use electrical accessories like the stereo when your engine is turned off. Once your engine is running, the charging system takes over, and this is where your voltage regulator and alternator go to work by continuously charging your car. If your battery is dead, you will need jumper cables, a battery booster box or another vehicle to jump start your battery. In which case you will need to call someone who can help with this operation instead of replacing your battery altogether. More on jump starting a car in future articles, this deserves an entire article altogether.
<br /><br />Faulty ignition switch. On the other hand, if you determine that your battery is okay, but the starter is still quiet and the engine does not crank, your ignition switch may be the problem. Switch the key to the “ON” position, taking care not to start it (read the engraved words around the switch). If on your dashboard you see that the red warning lights don’t light up, and assuming that your battery connections are clean as instructed above, the ignition switch is faulty. If the warning lights on your dashboard do light up, turn your key all the way to the “START” position. In most cars, the warning lights should turn off at this position. Now, turn on your headlights. When you try to start the car, the lights should either get dim or turn off. If they do, your ignition switch is not the problem. If not, you might need to have your ignition switch checked or replaced.
<br /><br />Starter connection. Corrosion may also affect any of your car’s electrical components like the starter. If someone is with you, you can test the connection by holding a circuit tester on the small wire connected to the starter (there are two wires, the other is smaller). Make sure you or any part of your body is not touching the engine, it could start all of a sudden. Have someone turn the key and check the current. If you see that there’s a current going to the starter but it still won’t spin, you need to change it.
<br /><br />Engine cranks but does not fire. So you switch it on to the “START” position and you hear the “redondo”. Remember that your car works based on what is called an internal combustion engine. For such an engine to start, a spark needs to ignite the fuel in the combustion chamber. A coil and distributor are needed to send spark to the spark plugs. If your engine is getting fuel, check if the wires leading to the coil and the distributor are not broken or loose. On some vehicles, you can check the coil by unhooking the wire going from it to the center of the distributor. Hold it against either the body or the valve cover and start the engine. If there is spark traveling from the end of the wire to the metal, the coil is good. Then you can inspect the rotor and contact terminals by removing the distributor cap. If there are black spots or no metal at all, you should replace your cap and rotor.
<br /><br />More on these in future articles. Till next time, this is Monico D. Mekaniko, Va-va-vroom!
<br /><br />***
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>