<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="14">
		<document id="bc01bc5b481eecafbfd51f6aec51249a" url=""><![CDATA[rate me ladies<br/><br/>Tell me what u think
<br />0 = ewwwwwwwwwwww!
<br />1 = Definetly not attractive.
<br />2 = Decent
<br />3 = Fine
<br />4 = beautiful
<br />5 = I'd do you.
<br />6 = Pretty damn sexy!
<br />7 = Lovable, I LOVE YOU!!!
<br />8 = I wanna make you my man/girl.
<br />9 = Just a friend.
<br />10 = Sexiest person I know!
<br />11 = Fuckin Handsome
<br />12 = Ya, I've checked you out a few times
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aebbf7ddee7333a5d663465c1bd299f" url=""><![CDATA[Answer This (girls only)<br/><br/>1. Your Name:
<br /><br />2. Age:
<br /><br />3. Fave Color:
<br /><br />4. Are you a virgin?
<br /><br />5. Are we friends?
<br /><br />6. Do you have a crush on me?
<br /><br />7. Would you kiss me?
<br /><br />8. ...with tongue?
<br /><br />9. Would you enjoy it?
<br /><br />10. Would you ever ask me out?
<br /><br />11.Would you make a move on me in a movie theater?
<br /><br />12. Would you take care of me when I'm sick?
<br /><br />13. Do you want to tell me something that you couldn't before?
<br /><br />14.Would you walk on the beach with me?
<br /><br />15. If you heard a rumor about me, would you defend me?
<br /><br />16. Do you/have you talk shit about me?
<br /><br />17. Do you think I'm a good person?
<br /><br />18. Would you let me sleep with you (in the same bed)?
<br /><br />19.Do you think I'm hot?
<br /><br />20. Would you change anything about me?
<br /><br />21.If so what?
<br /><br />22.Would u pleasure me?
<br /><br />23.Would you come over for no reason just to hang out?
<br /><br />24. Will you post this so I can fill it out for you?
<br /><br />25. What do you rate me outta 1-10?
<br /><br />26. Your phone number
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="206b635096ee9aa220c85eb6dc610277" url=""><![CDATA[questions<br/><br/>1. give me ur number?
<br />2. love me?
<br />3. let me kiss u?
<br />4. watch a film with me?
<br />5. have dinner with me?
<br />6. drive me somewhere?
<br />7. take a shower with me?
<br />8. be my gf/bf?
<br />9. tell me u think im cute?
<br />10. buy me a drink if i didnt have money?
<br />11. take me home for da nite?my house or ur house?
<br />12. let me sleep in ur bed?
<br />13. shag me?
<br />14. put dis on your blog 2 let me answer ur questions?
<br />15. do u think im funny?
<br />16. do u care about me?
<br />17. would u dance wit me?
<br />18. Anything else you want 2 do? lol
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9a7ff7cd78e7001895966ab8d39ab990" url=""><![CDATA[HAVE A GO<br/><br/>I died:
<br /><br />I kissed you:
<br /><br />I fell:
<br /><br />I lived next door to you:
<br /><br />I was drunk at a party:
<br /><br />I showed up at your house unexpectedly:
<br /><br />I stole something:
<br /><br />I was sleepy:
<br /><br />I told you I love you:
<br /><br />I told you I was lost:
<br /><br />I cried:
<br /><br />I was hospitalized:
<br /><br />I moved away forever:
<br /><br />WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT MY:
<br /><br />Personality:
<br /><br />Eyes:
<br /><br />Hair:
<br /><br />Family:
<br /><br />Smile:
<br /><br />Temper:
<br /><br />Friends:
<br /><br />WOULD YOU:
<br /><br />Keep a secret if i told you one?
<br /><br />Hold my hand?
<br /><br />Cook for me?
<br /><br />Loan me some money?
<br /><br />Talk on the phone for hours?
<br /><br />HAVE YOU EVER:
<br /><br />Lied to make me feel better?
<br /><br />Wanted to kiss me?
<br /><br />Wanted to kill me?
<br /><br />Thought I was unbearably annoying?
<br /><br />Hated me?
<br /><br />Wanted to tell me something but didn't?
<br /><br />Wondered about my sanity?
<br /><br />Wanted to do something to me?
<br /><br />Wanted to slap me?
<br /><br />More:
<br /><br />When and how did we meet?
<br /><br />Describe me in three words.
<br /><br />What was your first impression of me?
<br /><br />What do you think of me now?
<br /><br />What reminds you of me?
<br /><br />When's the last time you saw me?
<br /><br />What was the funnest thing we've done?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6fb4fc8494b046a1006bcc58a6ef4dac" url=""><![CDATA[My Creative Writing Essay<br/><br/> Passive Schizophrenic
<br /><br />Every single one of us have some sort of evil inside; another person, hiding in the shadows of our psyche. There is a mental border of control and sanity. But what happens when that border is crossed?
<br /><br />It was Sunday, May the thirtieth. I got up at around eight and had gone to Church with the family, just as I had every other Sunday of my life. I’m not a religious person but have never had a problem with exploring religions. You see, I am Agnostic; someone who doesn’t believe in a God, but doesn’t doubt the existence of one either. This day, however, would change my life forever. I still often ponder that, if a God does exist, He must have intended for this to happen. But why?
<br /><br />I had never seen her at Church before. But this was not the only reason I noticed her. She looked like an angel; eyes that could burn a thousand holes into anyone’s heart, and a smile that could melt it. She was sitting in the corner, about three metres away from me. Every now and then I would glance in her direction. I couldn’t help myself. Finally, after about an hour I muscled up the confidence to talk to her. “Hi, I’m Jonathan” I said staring right into her eyes.
<br />“Hey, I’m Melissa” she replied. Right then and there I felt my heart skip a beat. She had the sweetest voice I had ever heard.
<br />“Are you new to this church?” I asked.
<br />“Yeah, my mom and I moved here a week ago” she replied followed by a gorgeous smile.
<br />We chatted for a while and I really took an interest in her.
<br />After church she asked me, “Would you like to come around to my place for a swim later on?”
<br />I didn’t hesitate to answer. “Sure. What time? And where do you live?”
<br />She melted my heart again with that stunning smile and said “Anytime after three will be great. My house is number twenty-eight Eastwood Road.”
<br />I couldn’t believe it; she only lived four houses away from mine.
<br /><br />I made my way over to her house at about five minutes to three. I wanted to make a good impression. At exactly three I knocked on her door. She opened the door wearing the most amazing bikini I had ever seen. It was royal-blue in colour with black and white flowers printed on it. Actually, come to think of it, it wasn’t really the most amazing piece of swimwear I had ever seen, but the fact that she was wearing it made it seem like it was at the time. She introduced me to her mom. She was a tall and attractive lady, and I could see where Melissa got her looks from. After being introduced we went over to the pool.
<br />We spent nearly four hours in the pool talking about anything and everything: where we have been, what we would like to do and favourite things of all time. We soon discovered how much we had in common. After getting out of the pool our hands looked like they had aged about fifty years and she handed me a towel to dry myself with. We went inside and, wanting to seem like the most polite kid on the block, I offered to make us a cup of coffee. After we drank the coffee I decided that it was getting a bit late and that it was time to go home. I didn’t want to go home. I wanted to stay there forever. She gave me her number and I left. When I got home, I felt like calling her. But I didn’t; I didn’t want to seem desperate.
<br /><br />We spent the first six months getting to know each other and we became very close friends. The three years that followed was a time of love, friendship and many tears. I thought not even death could have ever hoped to destroy our friendship. I loved her in a way a brother would love his sister; and perhaps a little more. I am an only child, so I could never truly understand that kind of bond; but I think this brought me pretty close.
<br />We would always talk about everything: our problems, people we have an interest in etc. But I never told her how I felt about her. I couldn’t, it would change everything between us, and I would lose the sister I never really had. Throughout the three and a half years that we were friends I saw her go through many relationships. Every single one of them ended up hurting her, and that hurt me too. I would never have hurt her; I’d have made her the happiest girl alive. I didn’t think that there could ever be anything worse than staring into the eyes of the one you love, seeing all that hurt and pain, but knowing that there wasn’t anything I could really do about it. Her last relationship in particular hurt me dearly.
<br /><br />She had been dating a guy by the name of Steven Jenkins. He was 2 years older than her and seemed like a nice guy. But I always got this feeling that there’s another side to him. They dated for nearly a year and she said she was madly in love with him and was convinced that he loved her too.
<br />“I love him so much I gave myself to him” she once said.
<br />Those words hurt me the most, because I never thought that there could have been anyone else in existence capable of loving her more than I did. She later became pregnant and Steven ‘ordered’ her to get an abortion. But she refused. She believed that abortion was the same as murder. They constantly fought, and I would often find myself offering my shoulder for her to cry on. As time progressed the arguments became more intense until one day; he struck her. I only saw her about a week after it had happened; her arm still covered with the bruise. She managed to convince herself that it had been her fault and that she was asking for it. I never really understood that. I simply could not comprehend how a man could ever hit a woman.
<br /><br />I spent the next few months watching her belly grow. I was absolutely fascinated by the process. The doctors had told her that she was bearing a little boy. She would often allow me to place my hand on her belly so I could feel him move inside her. Perhaps he could feel me too; perhaps he could feel my love growing for him as I had felt him grow. I sometimes found my thoughts wondering off, fantasizing about the day the he was to be born, with me at Melissa’s side; holding her hand, being there every step of the way. I would dream about us getting married and taking care of him together; loving him as I did now; as if he were my own. Throughout this time Melissa and Steven’s arguments grew more aggressive, like a cancer, refusing to give up. I could never really understand why they were still together. But she was adamant that they still loved each other.  Then, he struck her again. This time it was worse; she ended up in hospital. We contacted the police and gave a statement. He was taken into custody but soon released after his father bailed him out. I’d had enough of it, and decided to confront him.
<br /><br />The next day I saw him at school. He was with some of his friends.
<br />“Now you listen to me very carefully,” I began, “if you ever touch her again, you’ll be signing your death warrant and engraving your name on your headstone.”
<br />He looked at me for a second, and simply smiled. I was about to turn around when he landed a hard right hander on my chin. I hit the floor so hard I could feel my brain rattle in my head like the tail of a Diamondback snake. He walked away, leaving me behind, lying on the ground holding my head firmly. I laid there for about 10 minutes and waited for my head to stop spinning. I proceeded to walked home. Upon my arrival my mom immediately noticed the bruise on my chin and the bump on my head.
<br />She asked me what happened but I simply answered, “Nothing”.  
<br /><br />Then, on the evening of November the fourteenth, I received a call from her mom. I knew something was wrong; her mom never called me. I could hear she was crying. I was curious as to what had happened; and then she told me.
<br />“John, Melissa’s dead”.
<br />Those are the last words I ever heard from her again. I felt my knees becoming weak and could no longer support my weight. I dropped to the floor like I had the day Steven punched me. It felt like my whole world had collapsed; and the truth is it did; she was my world. For days I stayed in my room, crying my heart out. I remembered reading a biology textbook in which it explained that our bodies were made up of seventy percent water. I didn’t doubt that anymore, the evidence was soaked up in my pillow.
<br />I decided that I needed to go to her house: the place where I felt true love for the first time. I still thought of it as her house, not as a crime scene, because I could still feel her presence; it was her house, and she was still there. The police were still investigating the area and after much pleading they allowed me to go inside, with the condition that an officer would escort me to make sure that I didn’t disturb any of the evidence. The officer told me that the police believed she had been raped and murdered while her mom was out shopping. I walked up the stairs and towards her room. I had never been in her room before, but it felt like I had. On her dressing table was a photo. It had a metal frame, in the shape of a heart, with the words “Best Friends” engraved on it. The photo inside it was of me and her which she took on the day we went to the beach. I felt my throat getting tight and I found it difficult to swallow. In her room was evidence of an argument and a struggle. I stood there, gazing at the room in which she took her last breath; and then I saw it. Sticking out from under her bed lay a broken bracelet. I quickly grabbed it while the officer wasn’t looking and put it in my pocket. I thanked the police and proceeded to go home. I went straight to my room to examine the bracelet. I had seen it before. On the inside read the name “Steven”. For weeks I sat in my room, still grieving, but planning my revenge.
<br /><br />One Saturday night I went to bed early and waited for my parents to go to bed. I then snuck out to my dad’s garage and found a shovel. I felt that I had to avenge Melissa’s death. I went to find Steven. I knew where to find him. He was at the usual bar, Tempo’s. It’s where he was every Saturday night. The night was cold, and in the distance I could hear the music coming from the bar. A cat, black as the night, and black as my heart walked towards me. His eyes fixed on me as if he knew my intentions. I found an alley from where I could see the bar. I made myself comfortable and waited. After about three hours Steven finally came out. He was alone. I waited until he walked passed the alley so I could run up behind him; and so I did.
<br /><br />I hit him over the head with the shovel; not once, not twice, but an amount which I lost count of.
<br />At first he was screaming “Stop! Stop!”, but I couldn’t; I wasn’t in control.
<br />It felt like something had taken over my body, conducting my every move as if I were a puppet. The more he screamed and struggled the harder I hit. There was blood everywhere, but I didn’t care. He killed me inside, he deserved to be punished. I had crossed that border of control and sanity, and there was no turning back. After some time his cries for help had stopped; the struggling seized. I knew he was dead. I had hit him so many times, I couldn’t lift my arms.
<br />I took a moment to catch my breath. I turned his body over and stared into his lifeless eyes. I felt this inner peace knowing I had accomplished what I set out to do. I sat next to his body, still looking at his eyes. I sat there for quite some time, gazing upon my victory; his corpse my trophy. I found a dustbin in the alley in which I could place his body. It took me a few attempts as the wheels on the dustbin kept rolling backwards, throwing the dustbin onto its side. I placed the bin next to a wall to avoid this and finally managed to place the body in it. But then, not far away, I heard voices. I quickly hid behind the bin.
<br />“What the heck is this?” someone asked.
<br />“It looks like blood” another answered.
<br />“This was it,” I thought, “they’re going to find me”
<br />“We should contact the police immediately” a voice said again.
<br /><br />It was quiet, I didn’t know if they were still there. I took a quick glance around the bin, but no one was there. I had to act fast.
<br />I quickly took the bin over to a nearby park. A must have been roughly half way there when, in the distance, I noticed a pair of distinctive flashing red and blue lights approaching me. I ran, still pushing the bin as fast as I could. The lights were approaching faster and faster. I ducked behind a bush and waited for the car to pass. My heart was pacing in sequence with the revs of the engine approaching me. It came closer and closer. The once silent night was suddenly shattered by a loud SCREEEEETCH as the car slammed on brakes. Through the leaves of the bush I could see the car.
<br />Moments later, I heard the driver shout, “You stupid cat!”
<br />“Thank God!” I thought to myself.
<br />The car drove off again. I sat behind the bush, waiting to see if there were any other dangers coming my way. There was none. I rushed to the park, faster than before.
<br /><br />Once I arrived after a time which seemed like an eternity I proceeded towards the North end of the park. There had been some renovations taking place there two weeks prior. I found the newly renovated garden along with a fresh new flower bed; completely out of sight and not a single source of light apart from the moon which gave me enough light to see what I was doing. I decided that this is where he would remain. I carefully removed the newly planted flowers and I began to dig with the shovel. I dug for about two hours to make sure the hole was deep enough, when suddenly; I heard the sound of leaves being crushed. I stood completely still, hardly a single breathe escaping from my mouth. I heard it again, this time louder, much closer. Then, from under one of the bushes appeared a small, furry black being. I let out a sigh of relief. It was a cat; the same cat that I had encountered before, and perhaps even the same cat that had jumped in front of the police vehicle. I recognized his eyes, once again, fixed on me just as before. After staring at this curious creature for a few seconds I continued with the disposal of the body. I pushed the dustbin, which still contained the body, in the hole and covered it with earth. I replaced the flowers and took a step back. It was perfect; no sign of disturbance whatsoever. I waited patiently to see if anyone had seen me. No one did. I made my way back home and snuck back into the house to find my parents still fast asleep having not noticed that I had been gone. They got up at eight and we all went to church; the very place I had met her.
<br /><br />That day I buried Melissa’s killer along with my love for her. It’s been almost five years now and no one has ever found him. Flyers with his photo were sent out and posters were put up with the hope that someone will come forward with some information. But no one did, no one could; I was the only one who really knew what happened.
<br />We all have an inner evil; it's just that often we are unaware of it until that time comes when something within us snaps. That's what sends us over the edge; to the other side of sanity. Love, jealousy, anger and rage are just some of the emotions that we feel and think we control, but there are moments when we lose grip over what we control. What we control becomes something that controls us.
<br />On that horrible night I met my inner evil; the other person whom I never even knew existed. But he did, and he was as real as the love I felt for Melissa. He scared me, and I hope I never have to meet him again. It has changed my life forever. Wherever I go, I’m always on the run; not from the authorities, but from the evil; from myself.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2f68d60f588528ed18d8c9862ecf29f3" url=""><![CDATA[friend application<br/><br/>01. Name -
<br />02. Age -
<br />03. Location -
<br />04. Hair -
<br />05. Eyes
<br />06. Most Outstanding Feature
<br /><br />Ok over and done with the formalities lets get down to the nitty gritty.
<br /><br />07. Do U wanna get to know me better -
<br />08. Will You Give Me Your Number (Private Msg) -
<br />09. WIll You give me ur msn -
<br />10. would u want me to call u regularly -
<br />11. Do You Smoke -
<br />12. Drink? -
<br />13. Do you Have any body piercing/tatoos -
<br />14. If I asked u out What would u say -
<br />15. Wat did u think about me (First impression)
<br />16. wat would u do/say if i kissed u on our first date -
<br />17. would u like to hold hands? -
<br />18. Wat do u think is romantic? -
<br />19. Hot Chips/Pizza -
<br />20. Are You Going To Put this up so i can tell u? -
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d4c50ae254588e5a1ec4559ce9ed0370" url=""><![CDATA[Lets c what u hav 2 say<br/><br/>1.) How many times a day would you kiss me?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />2.) Would you hold me?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />3.) Would you have sex with me?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />4.) Would you take me places?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />5.) Would you love me?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />6.) Would you lie to me?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />7.) If I was sick what would you do?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />8.) Would you leave me for one of my friends?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />9.) Want to have a future with me?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />10.) Would you listen to all my problems and help me solve them?
<br />Answer:
<br /><br />11.) Would you introduce me to your mom/dad?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />12.) Would you care about what I wore when we go out?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />13.) Would you hang out with me AND my friends?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />14.) If your friend tried to get with me what would you do?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />15.) Would you give me your myspace password?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />16.) If I gave you mine would you read all my mail?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />17.) If I said I loved you would you say it back?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />18.) How good do i look from 1-10?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />19.) How do you feel about me?
<br />answer: 
<br /><br />20.) Have i ever made you smile?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />21.) Want to spend the night with me?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />22.) Would we just chill together?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />23.) If you had an empty house would you call me to come over?
<br />answer:
<br /><br />24.) Are you gonna repost this so i can reply?
<br />answer:
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="754b7a43b354a98caf761115334bfeda" url=""><![CDATA[juz 4 fun<br/><br/>go out with me?
<br />give me your number?
<br />kiss me?
<br />let me kiss you?
<br />watch a movie with me?
<br />let me take you out to dinner?
<br />take a shower with me?
<br />be my bf/gf?
<br />have a fling with me?
<br />take me home for the night?
<br />Would you let me sleep in your bed?
<br />re-post this for me to answer your questions?
<br />have a relationship with me?
<br />Dance with me?
<br />Spank that ass?
<br />kiss me to death?
<br />Let me fuk you?
<br />Stick up for me if i was being put down?
<br />Carress my body?
<br />Play strip poker with me?
<br />Say yes if i asked you out?
<br />Get wasted with me?
<br />Greet me in public?
<br />Hang out with me?
<br />Bring me around your friends?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e3075efd40db1ab237d23ba68f405d14" url=""><![CDATA[Looking for a room mate in Adelaide<br/><br/>hey people, I'm lookin 4 a room mate 2 share a place with me in Adelaide. havn't found a place yet but thought it would b better if i found sum1 1st and then go crib huntin 2getha. any takers? id prefer a chick 4 obvious reasons lol but not 2 fussed abt it...sum1 in a similar age group as me would also b great. and of course sum1 who is reliable...coz if u fuck up ill lose the place 2 haha. check out my profile if u wanna know a little more abt me..add me, msg me or whateva. check ya later
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24420b513fecfb10b56684308c4a793e" url=""><![CDATA[hav fun<br/><br/>wats ya name:
<br />How old are ya:
<br />Sex:
<br />Do u like me:
<br />Do u love me:
<br />Wats da time:
<br />Where r u :
<br />Are we close:
<br />Wud u kiss me:
<br />Wud u fuck me:
<br />Hav u got a gf/bf:
<br />Will we eva get 2geva:
<br />R u a virgin:
<br />Have u eva seen me drunk:
<br />Have u eva got me drunk:
<br />Have u eva wantd 2 tel me sumfin:
<br />Describe me in 3 words:
<br />Have u eva told me a big lie:
<br />Have u eva fort of me as bf material:
<br />Wud u eva cheat on me:
<br />Wud u 4giv me if i cheated on u:
<br />Wud u eva marry me:
<br />Wud u eva h8 me:
<br />Wud u guv me ur numba:
<br />Wud u dance wid me:
<br />Wud u put dis on ya blog 2 c wat i write:
<br />Do u fink im funny:
<br />Rate me outa 10:
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="69a904faa756e421e0ea464869aee466" url=""><![CDATA[YES NO MAYBE<br/><br/>Would you makeout with me?
<br />[ ]Hell Yea [ ]Yes [ ]No [ ]Maybe [ ]already have
<br /><br />Would you sleep with me?
<br />[ ]In an instant! [ ]Yes [ ]No [ ]Maybe
<br /><br />Am I attractive?
<br />[ ]Eff no! [ ] Hot as hell [ ]Fine [ ]Cute [ ]Okay [ ]Beautiful
<br /><br />Do you think I'm a virgin?
<br />[ ]Yes [ ]No
<br /><br />Are you a virgin?
<br />[ ]yes [ ]no
<br /><br />I look like..
<br />[ ] A player
<br />[ ] a wife/husband
<br />[ ] One time thing
<br />[ ] Next bf/gf
<br />[ ] A friend
<br />[ ] A friend with benefits
<br />[ ] A possibility
<br />[ ] A loser
<br />[ ] A studmuffin
<br /><br />If you saw me for the first time would you talk to me?
<br />[ ] Yes [ ]No [ ]maybe
<br /><br />Would you rather.. ?? [choose what you'd do!]
<br />[ ] Hook up with me
<br />[ ] Cuddle with me
<br />[ ] Date me
<br />[ ] Friends
<br />[ ] Friends with benefits
<br />[ ] Marry me
<br />[ ] Have sex
<br />[ ] Smoke it up with me
<br />[ ] OTHER (give details)
<br /><br />On a scale of 1-10 (10 being the highest), rate me..
<br />[ ]1 [ ]2 [ ]3 [ ]4 [ ]5 [ ]6 [ ]7 [ ]8 [ ]9 [ ]10
<br /><br />What would you want me to be to you?
<br />[ ]Friend
<br />[ ] Girlfriend/Boyfriend
<br />[ ] Friend with benefits
<br />[ ] Husband/Wife
<br /><br />Would you give me a lap dance?
<br />[ ]Hell Yea [ ]Yes [ ]No [ ]Maybe
<br /><br />Would you come to my house and do nothing but chil or what would we do?
<br />[ ]Yes [ ]No [ ]That's it?[ ]other:_________
<br /><br />Could you just be friends with me?
<br />[ ]Yes [ ]No
<br /><br />Would you party with me?
<br />[ ]Yes [ ]No
<br /><br />Would you do totally random shit with me?
<br />[ ]Yes [ ]No
<br /><br />Are you going to repost this so i can answer for you?
<br />[ ]Yes [ ]No
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="720d5ff378a46c4d48a79939df823bd6" url=""><![CDATA[WOULD U<br/><br/>Would You...
<br />[] Push me into a wall and kiss me?
<br />[] Come To My House To Do Nothing But Chill?
<br />[] Slap Me?
<br />[] Slap me if i asked you to?
<br />[] Kiss Me?
<br />[] Let Me Kiss You?
<br />[] Watch A Movie With Me?
<br />[] Take Me Out To Dinner?
<br />[] Take A Shower With Me?
<br />[] Take Me Home For The Night?
<br />[] Let Me Sleep In Your Bed?
<br />[] Take Me Anywhere With You
<br />[] Repost This For Me To Answer Your Questions?
<br />[] Lock Me In Your room And Take Advantage Of Me?
<br />[] Let me lock you in your room and Take Advantage of you?
<br />[] Let Me Make You Breakfast?
<br />[] Make me breakfast?
<br />[] Tickle Me?
<br />[] Let Me Tickle You?
<br />[] Stick Up For Me Uf I Was Being Put Down?
<br />[] Instant Message Me?
<br />[] Greet Me In Public?
<br />[] Hang Out With Me?
<br />[] Hold my waist from behind while we are out?
<br />[] Bring Me Around Your Friends?
<br />[] Like me
<br /><br />Do You...
<br />[] Miss Me?
<br />[] Think I'm Sexy?
<br />[] Think I'm Cute?
<br />[] Think I'm Hot?
<br />[] Think I'm Ok?
<br />[] Think I'm Ugly?
<br />[] Want To Kiss Me?
<br />[] Want To Cuddle With Me?
<br />[] Want To Date Me?
<br /><br />Am I...
<br />[] Smart?
<br />[] Funny?
<br />[] Cool?
<br />[] Loveable?
<br />[] Adorable?
<br />[] Great To Be With?
<br />[] Attractive?
<br />[] Mean?
<br />[] Ugly?
<br />[] Gorgeous?
<br /><br />Have You Ever...
<br />[] Thought About Hooking Up With Me?
<br />[] Found Yourself Wanting To Kiss Me Non Stop?
<br />[] Wished I Were There?
<br />[] Had A Crush On Me?
<br />[] Wanted My Number?
<br />[] Had A Dream About Me?
<br />[] Been Distracted By Me?
<br /><br />Are You...
<br /><br />[] Happy You Know Me?
<br />[] Thinking About Me
<br />[] my friend?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1c6bac3b19d6915987c2b4ee567eec2f" url=""><![CDATA[WATSYANUMBA!!<br/><br/>Name:
<br /><br />Number: - - - - - - - - - - - -
<br /><br />Best time to text:
<br /><br />I dare you to copy and paste this and see how many numbers you get
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b55684acceaa630c85ec38d3b7571216" url=""><![CDATA[AAESS<br/><br/>THIS SCHOOL IS F*CKED UP!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>