<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="19">
		<document id="8ea67ed99b12c8a14fe0f57ae20a598f" url=""><![CDATA[The 2nd Most sweetest gift to me!!<br/><br/>Though its really very difficult for me to rate it as 1st or  2nd as such, but still after &quot;Mummy's toy car, she had gifted me way back, when I was a small kid&quot;, this was the second most sweetest gift I ever got from anyone. And if that happens to come from my Cutie Pie, My Sweetie Pie, My Most chweetest Little Sis Nupur, sone pe suhaaga!!
<br /><br />Last Friday as I had called home to tell mummy , what all things to send for me, as a friend was coming here to Delhi, Mummy told me that Nupur had sent a CHOCOLATE CAKE for me, and she had cooked that all alone!!! My cho cho chwweeetie sis!! Sunke aankhon mein aansoon aagaye. And since that friday, just was waiting, kab sunday subaha ho, train yahaan pahunche aur mein Suvendu se apna cake le sakun, I just couldn't wait for long. Sunday bhi aaya, but see my luck, the train had changed its route and so was late by 9 hrs. Finally it came, and with it Suvendu and my pyaari behna ka mere liye cake!! Suvendu se kyaa baat kartaa, mera to saara mind us cake ko taste karne ke upar hi dhyaan tha. Woh kya bol raha tha, kuch nahin sun raha tha. yeah, had become a bit selfish that time, but kyaa karun, jab apni chotti sis ki baat aati hei, to baaki sabko bhul jaate hein, hei naa???? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />And jaise hi Suvendu left with his friends to Gurgaon, It was like, kaise mein jaldi se ghar pahunchun aur woh cake taste karun. I knew woh cake jarur jarurat se jyaada meetha hogaa, I knew that, that was bound to happen, afterall meri cutie pie ke ungliaan bhi to usse banane mein use kiye gaye the naa!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> , ussi ki tarah bahut sweet, bahut pyaara sa cake hogaa, I knew! Right all the way, was just thinking, kab ghar pahunchu aur cake ko munh mein daalun!!
<br /><br />As soon as reached home, darbaaja band karte hi, without even changing cloths or freshening up, even without washing my hands, jaldi se us bag mein se saare cheezon ko kholke pehle us cake ko khaana thaa. heheheheheehe, <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> , it was as if, agar thodi derr hojaati to koi aur aake khaa jaayegaa which I couldn't let happen, jab ki ghar mein mere ilaawa aur koi thaa bhi nahin!! and jaise hi us cake ka pehle tukda munh mein daala. ummmmmmmmmmmm........., so so tasty.
<br />More than the taste, usmein jo pyaar bhejja tha Nupur ne, that can never be valued in any terms. Bade pyaar se banaya tha, uss cake ke bahari appearance se pata chal raha tha, must have given a lot of time in preparing that, ek ek tukdaa khaa raha tha aur uske smiling face ankhon ke saamne aajata tha. Usike share ke chocolates use kiye honge, may be. 
<br /><br />Sisters r God's most precious n bestest gift He has ever gifted anyone, and for me, Nupur is the most cutest Doll one can ever have, chaltaa phirtaa gudiya, pyaari si gudiyaa. Ab wohi gudiya itni baddi hogayi hei, ke apne bhai ke liye akele hi ek cake banaake bhejja!!! Soch ke hi, itna face pe smile aajaa raha tha aur aansoon bhi!
<br /><br />Kitna usse chidaaya, kitna pareshaan kiya hei meine, kabhi koi mauka nahin chhod ta hun, usse ghussa dilaane mein!! But still she is my most cutest little sis!! I am really very lucky to have this little angel with me. Bachpan mein to, always missed a doll to play with, but ab jab bhi koi mouka miltaa hei, apne chotti si pyaari si doll ke saath chidaake , usse pareshaan karke, uske baal khich taa hun. Thank  U Bhagwaanji, for giving this precious gift!! I can't never say enough Thanks to u for this special gift!
<br /><br />Hey Nupur, My Cutie Pie, My Sweetie Pie, Ur bhai will always love u, always remembers u!! Wherever I stay, chahe mein tumse saal mein ek hi baar milun, but still u r always in my heart, May God always bless u, shower on u all his Blessing !!
<br /><br />Lots n lots of hugs n dherr saara pyaar to my pyaari si, chotti si nanhi si gudiya, my cutie pie! Agar tum cake khate samaya, mere saamne hoti, I would have tweaked ur cute cheeks!!! Cho chweet of U, Little sis for ur cake!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cfdcf866d921c71794ed9b645de865ff" url=""><![CDATA[A funny questionare given by my sis.....<br/><br/>Today as my little sis gave me this questionare to fill up, now I am sitting here scratching my head, how to answer them, using the first letter of my name &quot;A&quot;....
<br />Anyways, lemme give a try...
<br /><br />Here are the rules as Varsha had put down(Hey sis, can't I play with the rules here?<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> : Use the 1st letter of your name to answer each of the following. They MUST be real places, names, things...NOTHING made up! If you can't think of anything, skip it. Try to use different answers if the person before you had the same 1st initial. You CAN'T use your name for the boy/girl name question.So here it goes...
<br /><br />Your Name: Amit
<br /><br />Famous Singer/Band: Anamika
<br /><br />4 letter word: Amit(hehehhehehehheehe, isseh better 4 letter aur kya ho saktaa hei?<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />Street: Avantika street
<br /><br />Color: Asian Paints....... howz that!!!
<br /><br />Gifts/Presents: Aishwarya Rai look-alike punching bags for practising BOXING!!!
<br /><br />Vehicle: Astra
<br /><br />Things in a Souvenir Shop: Ash tray(dekhaa, sab mein Ash ka name aaa jaata hei....)
<br /><br />Boy Name: Ashis
<br /><br />Girl Name: Ameesha
<br /><br />Movie Title: Ajay
<br /><br />Drink: Amul Dudh!!!
<br /><br />Occupation: Aaam lelo, aam!!!
<br /><br />Flower: Aaam khilne se pehle jo phool hotaa hei, wahi wala.....
<br /><br />Celebrity: Amitabh Bachhan
<br /><br />Magazine: ABC of Cricket
<br /><br />U.S. City: Alameda
<br /><br />Pro Sports Teams: ACC Sleepers Football Team 
<br /><br />Fruit: A for Apple.... yaad nahin hei kyaa????
<br /><br />Reason for Being Late for Work: 
<br />Always busy with pretty ladies .......hehehehheehuhuhuhuhuhuhuhuhu
<br /><br />Something You Throw Away: Ash
<br /><br />Things You Shout: 
<br />nahin, nahin, mein woh &quot;A&quot; word use nahin kartaa.....  ---- &quot;U a**h**e&quot;!!!
<br /><br />Cartoon Character: Archie
<br /><br />Thank God, its over... huh!!!
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Hey Varsha, so sorry, sis, I donno know many friends who blog , and those who blog, they won't fill such stuff for me..... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />So mere se hi kaam chalaa lo....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4a74cfc324cfa0259165586b57938cf5" url=""><![CDATA[A loving wife commits suicide!!!<br/><br/>Yesterday as I was going through the newspaper, this piece caught my eyes. Really it was very moving. A wife had committed suicide because her husband, who before marriage had always said that he loved her, but actually he loved her money more than her and had married her for that only. And as was expected, he started showing his real intentions just after marriage. The girl had married him, against the wishes of her parents, because she had always believed her love and her husband. How she must have felt, after knowing her husband's real intentions. U love someone more than anyone or anything else in this world and u get to know that all the love he was showering on u, was just all &quot;jhoot, all fareb&quot;. Ur whole world crashes down infront of your eyes, virtually. How could one be so heartless?
<br /><br />Though this is not the first time, that I was reading such a story of betrayal by a husband. But what moved me were the feelings of the wife. Even after so much had happened, she still loved her husband. The letters that she left behind, before committing suicide shows that in ample measures. Anyone would be moved after reading the letters.
<br /><br />Just a look:
<br />this was what was published in the newspaper,
<br />&quot;Her LAST Words!!
<br /><br />To Sumit (her husband)
<br /><br />Hardly 12 days to go before our third marriage anniversary on July 10. However, I know it would give you immense pleasure if we part company before that or, shall I say, if I walk out of your life. I know Sumit that you neither love me nor like me. you only tolerate me. What we have is one-sided love. Such affairs are seldom successful. I loved you from my heart but you probably thought my feelings were not genuine. I can't blame you for this; may be something was lacking in my love for you. I couldn't find a place in your heart.
<br />You loved me initially. Or, at atleast, it seemed so to me. Those were the best days of my life. You can live without me, but I can't. Everybody has to die. Some die soon, some very late. My days are over. I am happy that I am dying as a married woman and not as somebody who was dumped by her husband. My only request to you is to dress me up like a newly married bride for my cremation. Rest assured that neither you nor any of your family members will be blamed for my death. I am also writing to my father to ensure this. I want to end this by saying that nobody loved you as much as I did.
<br /><br />To Police
<br /><br />My husband or his family members are not responsible for my death. Nobody has forced me to take this decision. Please don't put the blame on anybody.
<br /><br />To Her Father
<br /><br />I will be gone by the time you receive this letter. You know that I can't live without Sumit. The problem is that Sumit doesn't want to live with me. Please don't regret anything. Only God decides how long can a person live. Please don't worry and also take care of mummy. Had there been a divorce, I would have died several times in your presence. I am helpless; I can't live without him. You have catered to all my whims and fancies. I hope you will also fulfil my last wish. Please ensure that Sumit doesn't suffer for my death. My soul will not rest in peace if something happens to him. Nobody is responsible for my death. It's all destiny&quot;.
<br /><br />Aren't these last words of hers touchy n moving? Kisika bhi dil ko chu jaayega! What it came out was that, the boy and the girl were in love, they married against the wishes of their parents. But after marriage, eventually the girl's parents had to relent. But probably the boy's parents never really accepted the girl as their daughter-in-law. So started the attrocities for dowry. And the most saddest part was that the boy just didn't help her wife out, he stood silently all along, while his parents were torturing his wife. He probably was conniving with them.
<br /><br />Har ladki ke kuch sapne hotey hein, abt her shaadi, koi essa pati mileyga usse jo usse bahut pyaar karega, bahut khush rakhega usse. When an Indian girl marries a boy, she leaves back everything , her parental home, her parents and everything with which she had grown up, spent all her life and comes to her husband's place, expecting to be, now, an integral part there in the new place. And if she gets this, it can really turn one's world upside down!
<br />I have always believed that if one puts himself/herself in others shoes and tries to feel the pain, tries to understand their feelings, one just won't be able to hurt anyone, whatsoever.Even though this was a case of suicide, but I will say this was infact a murder, she was forced to take this extreme step. For a married Indian girl, her husband is all, she can take refuge from, in case of all troubles. But what if her husband turns out to be the villain. And the reason was just money!!! 
<br /><br />Esse mat kiya karro, loggon. Paise to aaj hei, kal nahin hongey, aur shayad kal phir aa bhi jaaye, par agar koi ek baar wahaan chalaa gaya, to woh wapas phir kabhi nahin aataa.......
<br />Kisike bharosse ko kabhi mat toddo esse.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9b2d69edfbbd9014a4358162b789868c" url=""><![CDATA[Realize the value of ....<br/><br/>To realize
<br />The value of a sister
<br />Ask someone
<br />Who doesn't have one.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of ten years:
<br />Ask a newly
<br />Divorced couple.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of four years:
<br />Ask a graduate.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of one year:
<br />Ask a student who
<br />Has failed a final exam.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of nine months:
<br />Ask a mother who gave birth to a still born.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of one month:
<br />Ask a mother
<br />who has given birth to
<br />A premature baby.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of one week:
<br />Ask an editor of a weekly newspaper.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of one hour:
<br />Ask the lovers who are waiting to Meet.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of one minute:
<br />Ask a person
<br />Who has missed the train, bus or plane.
<br /><br />To realize
<br />The value of one-second:
<br />Ask a person
<br />Who has survived an accident...
<br /><br />To! realize
<br />The value of one millisecond:
<br />Ask the person who has won a silver medal in the Olympics
<br /><br />Time waits for no one.
<br /><br />Treasure every moment you have.
<br />You will treasure it even <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5879ea8cd455e839f0a653f3e5cc1f5e" url=""><![CDATA[This is what happens......<br/><br/>Yesterday I read this shocking news in the newspaper. It was like, how could someone do this?
<br /><br />Read on, this is what I had read .....
<br /><br />&quot;Two-day-old girl rescued from ‘grave’&quot;
<br /><br />In a shocking case, a couple tried to kill their two-dayold granddaughter by burying her alive on the outskirts of Utkoor town in Mahabubnagar district. But, miraculously, the infant was found and is now recuperating in a hospital. 
<br />   Abdul Rehman and Kusoora Begum whose family has seen the birth of seven daughters couldn’t take it anymore. Accordingly, they hatched a plan, dug a pit on the roadside and buried the little one. A farmer Ramu, on his way to fields, saw some stray dogs trying to dig a pit from which an infant’s hand was sticking out. He dug open the pit and found the baby girl still alive and crying. He alerted local SI Venkat Reddy who, in turn, shifted the girl child to a nearby hospital. As the hospital lacked proper facilities, the baby was shifted to Narayanpur area hospital. When her condition worsened, she was shifted to the Mahabubnagar district hospital and she is now out of danger. 
<br />Rehman said that he has seven granddaughters and it will be a burden for him to take care of the child of his second daughter Maharoon Bi, whose husband had deserted her. Two months after the marriage, Maharoon’s husband, Gani Saheb, left her and fled from the town, leaving the family in disarray&quot;. 
<br /><br />so, even today people look for a boy, not a girl. I am sure, if she had been a boy, however abject poverty they might have been facing, they wouldn't have done this.
<br /><br />I am just thinking, here I wanna adopt a baby girl, but as I have been told by the authorities, that according to Indian laws, a single male(unmarried) can't adopt a baby girl, so I can't. Yahaan here in India, when there have been so many cases of female infanticides happening, female foeticides, but agar koi chahata hei adopt karne keliye, he is not allowed.
<br /><br />Though there has never been any farkh for a boy or a girl for me, both are equal for me. But still then, I always have been fond of baby girls. May be becoz in my childhood I never got to play with dolls, may be becoz of my weakness for sisters, may be becoz I have always fond of watching little girls dressed up as little angels in some white dress and all.... whatever be the reason, its a fact that I always wanted a daughter, more than a son. 
<br /><br />The sight of small babies yawning, unke woh maassoom chehere, they look so cute, unke woh chotte chotte haath, chotte chotte ungliyan, their habbit of always clinging to their mummys...hehhehhehe, I love that.
<br />ofcourse for any baby, a mother is more essential than anything else, and may be, I can never be a mom for my future kids. But then, I would like to ask the authorities, that suppose tomorrow I get married and my wife dies ... so then should I have to get another wife for my kids??
<br /><br />I donno know, whether I will be able to adopt a cute little baby girl, my little princess or not.
<br />But I will wait for my turn, may be, I might be lucky.....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="51bffca925cef808bfec9b041b546670" url=""><![CDATA[Quite touchy...<br/><br/>Another piece of touchy article.....
<br /><br />A mother of two, Borivali resident Sunita Pawar’s story would have read like that of an average Mumbai housewife, except for the twist in the tale. 
<br />   A girl from a small town in Maharashtra, she moved into the city several years ago after marriage and continued to lead a sheltered life until July 11 last year. 
<br />   The widow of a police sub-inspector killed in the 7/11 train blasts, Sunita, 31, now works as a peon in a railway office, serving water and moving files from one floor to another. Her employer is the Railway Claims Tribunal (RCT), the same organisation which decided on her plea for compensation as a 7/11 victim — she returned there a few months after the ruling to join RCT as a peon. 
<br />   Sunita says she will never forget the day when her landlord at Borivali asked her to vacate the flat after her husband’s death. ‘‘In fact, that put me under immense pressure to get a job. If not for this job, I would have been on the streets with two kids,’’ she said. 
<br />   Although a year has gone by, Sunita shudders at the mention of the blasts. ‘‘Please don’t talk of it again and again, it’s haunting. It just reminds me of my utter bad luck,’’ she pleads. 
<br />   Wiping her tears, holding a bunch of files, Sunita is occasionally lost in thought about her carefree days. It takes some prodding to bring her back to talk about her present life as a class IV government employee. A small town girl married into the Pawar family of Dhule, she shifted to Mumbai in 1997, with her husband. The cocooned nature of her existence is apparent from the fact that she ‘‘didn’t even know Mumbai Central or CST until that day (July 11). My husband solved all the problems in a jiffy, where was the need for me to struggle outside,’’ says Pawar, who’s barely studied up to class X. Now, of course, Sunita leaves home at 7.30 am to board the crowded Borivali-Churchgate local to reach office by 9 am. 
<br />   ‘‘My younger son, in class V, still does not understand why I have to leave home so early and come back late. In fact, he still does not quite understand that his father will never come back,’’ says Sunita, trying to control her tears. Still in a state of part-denial, she wishes that her kids, who are in class V and VIII, grow up fast. ‘‘Both of them are so small. It will take so many years before they grow up to support me. How will I manage all their education expenses,’’ she says. 
<br />   The job, which she joined in October 2006, ‘‘is ok’’, she says. ‘‘There are good people in the office. They are helping me do my job and forget the past.’’
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a1a0f4095002ffeacb30319d934e0918" url=""><![CDATA[Rakhi is coming nearer.....<br/><br/>&quot;Resham ki ek dorri se
<br />   Band jaata hei eyh duniya!!&quot;
<br /><br />It's just a thread, a solemn thread, but still iss dhaagey mein itni taakat hoti hei, dillon ko baand deta hei. Some treat it just as a tradition, a sort of routine affair, while for some its means a lot, they keep waiting eagerly for the day to come, the most cherished day for them.
<br /><br />Bhai, behen ka pyaar -- A relationship which allows taking each other for granted, a bond which has no place for distrust, a companionship which has no place for boredom, a togetherness which is timeless --
<br />   when U have a sister, you get these all.
<br /><br />Har saal , is din ko kitne besabri se intazaar karta hun and as the day comes, khushi ka thikaana nahin rehta -- my most cherished day. As soon as a new year sets in, and as I buy a new calendar, I first look out for this day, kab aur kis mahine aayega yeh din and beshabri se intazaar karta rehta hun.
<br />Behne hote hi waise. There can't be , probably, anything or anyone more sweetier than sisters.
<br /><br />Par is saal, mere liye thoda different hoga shayad! Mein khush to hun, ke Rakhi phir se aa raha hei, par dil ke kisi kone mein thoda dukh bhi hei. Har saal ki tarah, is saal woh baat nahin rahega.
<br /><br />Though beheno ko kabhi compare kiya nahin jaa sakta. Behene to hote hein anmol gehne.. jinka kabhi value lagaya nahin jaa saktaa. Har bhai ke liye, uski har ek behen ek ek anmol heera hoti hei. But for me, since my bachpan, I always had this special weakness for Liza and Noopur, they were my lifelines.
<br /><br />How ecstatic I used to be, when they used to be around, when they used to come home. Unke saath bitaya hua woh har moment, meri zindegi keshayad most memorable moments 
<br />mein se hein! Unke woh pyaare se chehre, unke woh pyaari pyaari baatein, unke woh hassi, bahut yaad aayenge. 
<br /><br />Though I never had a single opportunity to spend a Raksha Bandhan day with them all these years, par woh mujhe Rakhi bhej dete the, ryt on time aur mein unhe apne letters and cards. Woh mere paas to nahin hote the, par when I used to tie their rakhis on my wrist, ek alag si khushi aa jaati thi. Miss to unhe bahut karta tha, har us Rakhi pe.
<br /> Par unke rakhis hotey the saath mein, to essa lagta tha jaise woh khud mere saath mein hein. Bahut chun chun ke bhejja jaata tha mere liye woh Rakhis, and I used to boast 
<br />of!! Saare Rakhis sambhal ke rakhe hein.
<br /><br />I still remember when once I didn't get Rakhis from them on time, Rakhi jaane ke 3-4 days baad milley the unke rakhis, and mein unse baat karna aur letters likhna band kar diya tha! Par kitne din unpe ghussa rehtaa? Unke woh pyaare pyaare se chehre jab 
<br />yaad aajate the, sab bhool jaata tha, hehehhe.
<br /><br />But so much has changed now, I wonder why? Woh baat aur nahin rahi. Why do people change? Why do children grow up?
<br />Kitna achaa tha, jab woh chotte bachey the...
<br />Liza, who used to be my most dearest sis, my &quot;pyaari bachi&quot; as I used to call her -- kitni badal gayi. Kya se kya hogayi. Jisse mein apna ideal maanta tha, jo mere liye
<br />inspiration thi, jiske unche unche marks dekh ke, aur padhne ko jii karta tha... jo aadarshon aur simplicity ki mishaal hua karti thi... no one had ever imagined ki there could be so drastic changes.
<br />Sometimes I wonder, woh pehle wale times, kya sab dhong tha... That can't be, itne kam ummar mein koi bacha kabhi dhong nahin kar saktaa. Then where did the things go wrong?
<br /><br />Ab essa kyun hogaya ki, uska munh bhi dekhne ko jii nahin kartaa. Do people really change so much and can they really change?
<br />Why do people play around with feelings?
<br />Kya wakai mein log apne faidey ke liye, loggon ko use kar sakte hein!!  Why don't they even think once?
<br /><br />Jhoot kitne dinno tak reh sakta hei...
<br />Insaan agar kisi ke nazzaron se gir jaaye, then
<br />its really very difficult to get back that same position. Galti ek baar ho sakti hei, do baar ho sakti hei, teen baar, chaar baar.
<br />but baar baar...no....
<br /><br />Mann ko samjhata deta hun, ke Now I have nothing to do with her, or with them anymore. Par is that so easy?
<br />Jinhe bachpan se apni jindegi se jyaada pyaar kiya ho, jo apne liye jeeta jaagte gudiya ho, woh achanak yun paraye kaise ho jaate hein?
<br />Is it that times have changed and I am not being able to adjust myself!
<br /><br />That day when mummy told me that Nupur got admission in engineering, itni khushi hui, par mein baat nahin kar paya. Kabhi kabhi
<br />sochta hun, ki Noopur ka kya kasoor hei ismein? Ek ne galti ki ho, to dusre ko kyun sajaa miley? I just hope Noopur doesn't change at all, chahe times change ho jaaye.
<br />I donno exactly remember when I had last written her a letter. Par kya karun, ussi ne to kaha tha ek din &quot;Bhaiya, jo dena, dono ko barabar dena&quot;. 
<br /><br />Yeh mein bhi jaanta hun, chahe log jitna bhi change ho jaaye, shayad unhe puri tareeke se
<br />bhoolna impossible hei, kabhi ho nahin sakega shayad.
<br /><br />Isbaar Rakhi shayad yahaan Delhi 
<br />mein baaki saare behno se dher saara pyaar milega, itne saalon baad wapas Delhi mein Rakhi manaunga, it surely will be a treat definitely. But it will perhaps never be the same, without Liza n Noopur's.
<br />Jo bhi ho, dard to hota hei, upar se sabko shayad bol bhi dun, ki I have nothing to do with them anymore, but sach to yeh hei ki perhaps that will be impossible.
<br />I just hope, kaash esa kuch ho, pehle jaisa sab hojaaye... wahi puraane din, wahi maasoomiyat, wahi chedd chaad, wahi ladhai jhgadey aur manaana wahi unka chilaana and all.... I wish I could TURN back the hands of the clock to those old times,
<br />and time ko aagey badhne hi naa dun...
<br />Kaash yessa ho paata....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5d094cbba24d8871cfc6dad538ab5a0d" url=""><![CDATA[A non-sense stuff, exclusively for Prasanna, my dear friend<br/><br/>Some days back, a very good childhood friend of mine happened to go through my blogs. He liked them (I am very pleased at that <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> ) but he was of the opinion that my blogs were more contemporary, more realistic. He wants to see my blogs to have more &quot;bakwaas&quot;, with virtually no meaning, the sort of the &quot;non-sense stuff&quot; for which I am so famous among my friends. So mera esse sensitive and emotional topics likhna usse achaa to laga, par thoda hajjam nahin hua. He wants to see the more of naughty, mischievous side of mine. So I had to oblige him with this non-sense stuff. 
<br />Afterall he has seen, read and has been tortured and endured all my non-sense for all these years....
<br />(Mind u, I am very good at producing these non-sense stuff, loggon ke dimaag kharaf karne mein, unke dimaag ko chaat ne mein maaharati haasil hei humein .... Thank U, Thank U, Thank u all.... I love U all..... ummmuuaaaa, ummmuuuaaahh <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> )
<br /><br />So this one is exclusively dedicated to Prasanna. I hope after reading this, u really would be &quot;prasann&quot;.....
<br /><br />SO here I go.......
<br /><br />Arreh, kya hua??
<br />achaa, words r not visible, meine kya likhaa, kuch dikhaai nahin de raha hei naa!!
<br />U see, kuch feelings can never be put into words!!
<br />Kuch baatein sabdon mein bayaan nahin kiya jaa saktaa, unhe mehsush karna padtaa hei. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Words mein kya rakhaa hei...
<br />BHAVNAAON ko samjho!!!!!!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6fa38a36405eddf20d1e36bab3fb87db" url=""><![CDATA[Hi guys n gurls!<br/><br/>See, I normally don't talk much, a very very chup-chap type of guy. So don't have much to say here. Just that, do whatever u want to, but try not to hurt anyone knowingly. Always do good to all, make everyone happy and just keep smiling always! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="76dac5b48cb8e074bfac091f83b19c2b" url=""><![CDATA[Funny Ads!!<br/><br/>Somedays back, I saw this ad of IODEX --- A man is walking down a lonely road, suddenly his eyes fall on a five hundred rupee note on the road, behind the dry leaves. He keeps on standing there, looks here and there, then downwards looking towards the note, it seems he is thinking something, stays there for a few minutes more, and finally moves away.
<br /><br />At first I thought, us aaadmi ke antaraatmaa usse woh note uthane se rok rahi thi. Usne shayad socha hogaa ki &quot;yeh note meraa nahin heiisse uthaa naa paap hogaa&quot;, so that's why he moved on perhaps -- that's what I had thought at first. But just then, this line comes out on the TV screen &quot;Iodex lagaaye -- aur peeth dard se chutkaarra paaye&quot;. 
<br />  It was like,  &quot;O God, hasaa hasaa ke maar daaloge kyaa?&quot;, I almost virtually fell off my bed, hasste hasste!
<br />  Really these guys think so much, I sometimes think, yeh log essa kya khaate hein, jo inke dimaag mein yeh dhaansuun ideas aate hein!! Waise bhi,I have always been a fan of those who think out of the box, sab se hatke jo sochte hein, jinke soch mein humour hotaa hei, I love such people. 
<br /><br />Unlike the yesteryears ads, which were very very simple and straight (Hema, sushmaa, Jaya aur rekha,sab ki pasand Nirma.... washing powder nirma, washing powder nirma....) ya phir that  &quot;ooho, Deepikaa jee, aaiye aaiyee, kya lenge aap!!&quot; But nowadays, almost all the ads are hatke, and with a pich of salt, I mean humour.
<br /><br />Some ads are very very cute, infact I love those ads which feature the small , cute babies, nanhe moone bachey. Like that johnson and johnson baby powder, woh chotta sa bachaa, her mother feeding her milk, and then he smiling, khaas karkejab woh yawn kartaa hei, uuuufffffff... that shot is cho chweet. then that other ad abt baby soap, a mother with her two sons (&quot;chotte ka khaana, bade kaa khilonaa, chotta jitnaa badmaash, bada utnaa hi masoom&quot;...) -- That ad has also such cute kids, ji kartaa hei, khaa jaaun..... they r cho cho chweet!!!
<br /><br />There are many more interesting ads --- like that odomos coil wala ad --- &quot;panch bata do jamuna nagar baasi, chey bataa ek vasant vihar nibashi, pehredaar chagan, chowkidar durjan aur guard sajjan aur sukhnagar ke sabhi naagrik apne apne gharron mein befhikar hoke so rahe hein, kyun ke inhi ki tarah sukh nagar ka chatta hua badmash Gugiya aur uska puraa gang odomos coil lagaake so raha hein!!!&quot; --- Good thinking gone behind this ad.
<br />  But there are some simple ads, yet they look appealing to me like this one ---
<br />&quot;Jaise uski aankh khulli, khel ne nikli chul buli, kabhi doud doud, kabhi bhag bhag, kabhi jhul jhul kabhi ghum gham....
<br />Ghar pahunchi to maa boli --- Munh haat dho lo chulbuli.
<br />Maa, jab munh haath ka yeh ho haal,to kya gande naa honge baal? tabhi....
<br />tabhi dhonaa hei sirf munh haat nahin, munh haath aur bal....
<br />Clinic plus lagaye roj!!&quot;
<br /><br />I am looking forward to many such more interesting ads, especially I am looking forward to see more and more cute, chotte chotte bachey, cute cute bachey, nanhe munhe bachey --- Bachon kaa naya naya chalnaa, unka woh smile karnaafor no reason, apne maaon ka faces ko apne chotte chotte unglion se fondle karnaa --- esse moments ko leke aur cute cute ads baney. I will be more than happy.
<br /><br />All the best, to all out there in the ad world!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6b79831cdd62c012b05a53e1822d1168" url=""><![CDATA[Maa............<br/><br/>Maa... Mummy as I call her, Mother, and various other names, har koi apne apne andaaz mein is LIVING GOD KO bulaata hei. 
<br />And I am sure, not many will contradict with me, when I say ki, for everyone, his/her mother is the best!! Bhai, jaayes baat hei.
<br /><br />When I was a small child, she used to tie my one leg to her shaadi ka palloo, and would continue her works, while i would be playing beside her, or most of the times, I would be on her back, while she would be working, essa bahut kam time hotaa tha, jab mein unse dur hotaa thaa. 
<br />Itna bada hogaya tha, but even till 10th std., mein apne haathon se khanna nahin khaa taa tha, mummy khilaa deti thi. Sote samaye agar Mummy mere side mein naa ho,to mujhe neend nahin aati thi, mummy's lap used to be my fave holiday spot. But jaise jaise bachey bade hotte jaatey hein, unki life mein aur bahut se naye naye log aa jaate hein, naye friends etc. Aaahistaa aahistaa We get busy in our own world, pursuing our goals, career And is bhid mein, kabhi kabhi hum woh bachpan ka humaara sab se pehlaa dost, our best friend ko nazar andaaz kar jaate hein, she would still be waiting for us, her eyes may be still be searching for her bundle of joy. But she never says anything, even if inside her heart, she may be longing to hug her bachaa. Hum jinke haath pakad ke chalnaa seekhe, aaj life mein itni tejh chalne lag gaye ke unhi ko hum bhul gaye. 
<br /><br />Why does this happen? Kya company ke CEO ka shaabaashi Mummy ke hug se jyaadaa comfort detaa hei? Wahi mummy jisko ek minute bhi chod ke reh nahin sakte the, aaj wahi mummy se baath karne mein bhi telephone ke calltime ko dekh te hein!! Baat baat pe chid jaate hein, Why do we forget those bachpan ke baatein? Hum kyun bhul jaatey hein, ki hum jab pehle pehle naye naye school jaate the,school se loaut ne ke baad, jab apne naye friends ke baare mein, school mein naya naye jo cheezen humaare saath hua tha, hum jab apne mummy ko bolte the, woh kitne attentively humaari baaton ko sunti thi, humaare friends ko woh apna friends banaa leti thi. Ab unki baat sun ne keliye , humaare paas jyaada time nahin hei!!
<br /><br />Its high time, material success ke peechey bhaagnaa chod ke, apne apno ko bhulnaa chod de. Warna, a time will come, when we would have everything, but still we will be feeling lonely!! Essa naa ho, ki bahut derr ho jaaye, and jitna bhi pukaare, woh wapaas naa aaye. Unka woh baallon ko sehlaana and bolnaa &quot;beta,sab thik hojaayega&quot;, yeh sun ne keliye kahin kaan naa tarash jaaye.
<br />I haven't yet seen all of the world, but I do know, ab tak jitna bhi dekhaa hun duniyaa, family se badhkar duniya mein kuch nahin hotaa hei, especially MAA........   
<br />Hum bhagwan ki puja karne mandir mein jaatein hein, par bhagwan ne to humaare ghar mein hi hei!! Humaare paas hei, and hum unki kadar nahin karte, I just imagine, jinke Maa yein nahin hoti, how they would be feeling that void?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ad8a7408ecc51ac430794dad4c738bb0" url=""><![CDATA[FAILURE DOESN'T MEAN .... U R FAILURE....<br/><br/>&quot;Failure doesn't mean U r a failure,
<br />   it means u haven't succeeded yet.
<br /><br />Failure doesn't mean U haven't accomplished anything,
<br />   it means u have learned something.
<br /><br />Failure doesn't mean U don't have it,
<br />   it means U have to do something in a    
<br />       different way.
<br /><br />Failure doesn't mean U r not good enough,
<br />    it means u r not yet perfect.
<br /><br />Failure doesn't mean U have wasted ur life,
<br />    it means u have a reason to start afresh.
<br /><br />Failure doesn't mean U should give up,
<br />    it means u must try harder.
<br /><br />Failure doesn't mean U will never make it,
<br />    it means it will take a little longer.
<br /><br />Failure doesn't mean God has abandoned u,
<br />    it means He has something better for u in 
<br />       store!!&quot;
<br /><br />A stonecutter hammers at his rock, perhaps a hundred times without as much as a crack showing in it.
<br />Yet at the hundred and first blow, it splits into two and that was not the blow that did it,
<br /> ----- but all that had gone before.
<br /><br />So Don't be unnerved by repeated failures, try to rectify the mistakes, learn from them, U will see that sometime in the near future, if u have been doing the hard labour, u will definitely get success!!
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="18a1a8b982efc094d1dd33d92c4b5bc1" url=""><![CDATA[A SIS, SHE CAN BE...... WHO ELSE........<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> She is sweet, loveable, naughty and kind, an extraordinary gift to mankind...
<br />who else but only a sister she can be, whose presence in every home is a necessity, to experience the gift of life , THE GIFT from God.
<br />For she is considerate and mischievous, affectionate and funny, a clown and a teacher, all that a sister should be...
<br /><br />She is a childhood partner in mischief and fun, sometimes acting as a mother by showing deep concern or behaving sometimes like a father and scolding lovingly, but a genuine friend all through one's life.
<br /><br />A sister is a gift of joy, treasured beyond words, she is life's most dearest gift -- the gift of love. She holds a special place that noone else can fill, she cares and understands in ways that only sisters will.
<br /><br />A sister's love is amazing, expressed rarely in words, but the sound of her loving heart, in her actions, is clearly heard.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> A sister makes u smile when u feel a little blue, becoz she herself shares the feelings that U do.
<br /><br />She is someone who always will care, and there's is nothing quite like, all the love that she shares.
<br /><br />A sister is a charmer in the things she does and says, she will wind u round her finger, with her sweet and dainty ways!!
<br /><br />She is always there when u need her to hold out her hand, her smile always tells u that she understands.
<br /><br />She is a friend u can talk with all night, she is there to depend on when things r not just right.
<br /><br />SISTERS KNOW WHEN TO YELL AT U AND WHEN TO HUG!
<br /><br />The difference between a sister and a friend is that with a sister, the link is indossoluble. Whatever the stormy disagreement or fight between u, whatever is said in the heat of the moment but she will always be there with u.
<br /><br />SISTERS HAVE THOUGHTFUL WAYS, WHICH MEAN SO MUCH MORE THAN WORDS CAN EXPRESS, FOR WHATEVER SISTERS DO AND SAY, HAVE A LOVING TOUCH ALWAYS!!
<br /><br />Sisters many a time quarrel with u and fight  but then, sisters also have a way of making things right.
<br /><br />The love of sisters always remains the same, even though a lot of other things , years and time may change.
<br />  They are everything which makes them sweet and nice.
<br /><br />What a difference it makes to have a SISTER with u --- SOMEONE TO LOVE AND TO HAVE SOMEONE TO LOVE U TOO!!!
<br /><br />Only they, who have got sisters can tell U how it feels to have a sister's love
<br />AND THEY, WHO HAVEN'T GOT ONE, CAN ONLY TELL WHAT THEY HAVE BEEN MISSING!!
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cc8f034f737da68830bcf216b77f3e79" url=""><![CDATA[SURF EXCEL --- Daag achey hein naa!!!<br/><br/>DYAAAAAA...SSSSHHHHHHH <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />  (A collision sound)
<br /><br />Yeh kya? Aap ne meri number plate tod di!!
<br /><br />To kya hua? Meri bhi to headlight gayii hei.
<br /><br />Papa ......
<br />Roko bete.
<br /><br />Aaap ko paise dene hi hongey.
<br />Kis baat ke paise?
<br /><br />I will show u.
<br />Kya dikhaayega, chasmish?
<br /><br />Haann,  haannnnnnn...
<br /><br />Hunnnn.....
<br />yeh leh <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/huh.gif" alt=":)" /> (splash...)
<br /><br />ARREH, YEH BACHEY KISKE HEIN??
<br />Nahin chodungaa tujhe.
<br />Arreh Rishi!!
<br />Monty!!!!!
<br /><br />Chaddi chod.
<br /><br />Esse kisise jhagdaa karte hein kya?
<br />Chalo ghar.
<br /><br />Agar kuch achaa karne mein daag lag jaata hei,to daag achey hei naa!!!
<br /><br />SURF EXCEL ---- Daag achey hein!!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />U must be wondering, why have I written this ad here? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />Arreh Bhai, advertisement hei!!
<br /><br />U see, I am trying to earn from commercials. I thought my blogs could also generate some money from ads.
<br /><br />Money matters, Honey!!!
<br />He he he Ha Ha Ha????? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="45c97630252c1ff54ed372c4e66df043" url=""><![CDATA[Meri Ankhein Khul gayii .............. us din!!!!<br/><br/>We all feel all along that we alone are the most unfortunate ones here, on this earth. Manno,jaise duniya ke saare mushibatte, saare takleefe kisine humme hi de diye ho! We keep on complaining for this and that .....
<br />BADE BADE PROBLEMS KYA, Chotte chottey bhi, humme bahut bade problems dikhte hein!!...................... &quot;Paani nahin aaa raha.....kitni garmi hei, uparse yeh powercut... etc, etc --- Yesse kain saare problems !!
<br /><br />When I had moved into my present rented home in Delhi in Dec,'06, it was winter. Us time kaafi thand thaa... Well, Delhi ki shardi is well-known world over. So even if when there was no fan in both of my rooms, their absence was hardly felt ever. But then slowly delhi ki shardi made way for the garmi to set in. Delhi is also not far behind in its reputation for garmi.
<br /><br />Starting from the first week of March, I began to feel the heat. Mine being on the ground floor, so a bit cooler than the other floors, but still one would need some air, some cool breeze. BUT WOH KAHAAN SE LAATAA MEIN?? Fan to thaa hi nahin. Mere paas tab paise bhi nahin the to buy a fan. Naya naya job, I had to save money for my family, I wasn't prepared to invest for a FAN. I kept on managing with the hand held pankhaa --- woh jo gaaon mein hotaa hei. Thank God, I had got it along, while embarking for Delhi. (Meri dur darshitaa aaj bhi kaam kartaa hei!!! Thank U, Thank U, Thank U all!!!!!)
<br /><br />But slowly and steadily, as the days passed on, the temperature started soaring in Delhi, it was getting unbearable. I was dying for a fan.
<br /><br />Mein soch raha tha --- &quot;Kaash.... Mera bhi koi grandfather-uncle (Papa ke koi dur dur ka rishtedaar, jinka koi immediate family nahin hotaa, mere ilaawaa) South Africa mein hotte!!!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> (Hehehhehehe, esse dur ke risktedaar jyaadatar South Africa mein hi paaye jaate hein, jo apni wasiyat kisike naam kar jaate hein!!!) Aur marne se pehle mere naam EK FAN chod jaate!!! Kaassssshhhhhhhhhhhhh......!!
<br /><br />Then haalat essi hogayi thi, I didn't have enough money left with me to buy a fan. WAHAAN ghar mein all were hell-bound ki mein woh POLAR-HI SPEED WINAIR model hi kharidun!!!!! (with 7 yrs guarantee ---- yahaan insaan ka koi guarantee nahin hei, fan ka kya hogaa?<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />I was feeling like &quot;See, howmuch sacrifice I am doing, at this tender age, for my family? Facing so much hardships, saving money!! How gr8 I am!!&quot; I would even boast of this self-sacrifice to my parents, while talking to then on phone. Then came my birthday,mummy gave me a present -- deposited money in my account TO BUY A FAN!!!!!Hehehhehehhehehe, quite a unique gift!! Indeed, it was such a nice bday present.
<br />Thank U so much, Mummy, I love u!! U r the best mom!!
<br /><br />Having got the money, &quot;mein nikla, O gaddi leke ....&quot;, Hey wait, ....... sorry, no gaddi.....
<br />please erase this song. I went for the bus, but didn't find a single one. Kept waiting there, but no bus came. I was quite excited then, ek mission pe jaa raha tha ---- TO BUY A CEILING FAN!! Couldn't wait there any more, paidal nikal gaya.
<br /><br />Mind mein planning bana raha tha, designs dekhleta tha, kaun sa fan lun??? Then suddenly raste pe jo jaa raha tha, after Rithala, as I turned to the right for sec-8, there my eyes fell on these jhuggis --- chotte chotte shelters (homes) made up of polythene sheets, right behind the ambedkar hospital bus stop. There were some 3-4 of these shelters or homes. I think, the laboureres and their families, who were working at the construction site of a Big Mall there, must be living there.
<br /><br />Then this thought came to my mind -- How on earth, these people , itni garmi mein ,un chotte chotte polythene sheet ke jhuggis mein rehte honge WITHOUT A FAN?? (I know they won't be having any). Yehi sochte sochte sector 8 pe pahunch gaya.
<br /><br />Humaare liye jo cheez itni common hoti hei (FAN), unke liye ek luxury hei!
<br /><br />All the boasts of mine fell flat on my face --- that I had been sacrificing so much for my family, wasn't buying a fan just to save some money for my family! May be, Bhagwan ne jana bujke, usdin mujhe bus nahin dilwaya, warnaa yeh mere dimaag mein nahin aataa.
<br />I didn't buy a fan, came back home. Abhi garmi to bahut hei, par jab mein unki baat soch taa hun, un jhuggi walon ki, I get inspiration to keep going with my hand-held pankha.
<br /><br />Hum ek fan nahin hei, to itnaa hungaaama kar dete hein, jinke paas koi ghar hi nahin hei, unkaa kya??? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />April is coming to an end, my roof of my rooms are still naked without FANs, and more garmi is set to come in the enar future. I have managed somehow, till now. But I know, very shortly in some few days, I will get myself a fan,it's getting unbearable now. But un loggon ki baat jarur yaad aati hei, I am still thinking --- HOW R THOSE PEOPLE MANAGING WITHOUT A FAN?
<br /><br />Bhagwan esse chotti chotti batton se humme kuch lessons dete rehte hein! Bas hum kabhi kabhi usse samajh nahin paatey.
<br /><br />&quot;JO SAMAJH GAYA, WOH INSAAN
<br />  JO NAA SAMJHAA, WOH INSANE!!!!&quot; <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />  hehehehhehehhehehehe!!
<br /><br />Waise, mein abhi tak nahin jaan paaya, kya FAN wakai mein bahut jaruri hei??? Agar hei, kya woh Rs. 1350 ka POLAR HI-SPEED WINAIR wala model hi best hei????? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e2582811d74ec902e887aa178fcebe44" url=""><![CDATA[My Most VALUABLE POSSESSION!!!<br/><br/>MY MOST VALUABLE POSSESSION --- Well, its something I have kept with outmost care, it means a lot to me. Bcoz it was given by My Cutie Pie -- My Sweetest Little Sis Nupur ---- A new year card.
<br /><br />When I had been in Vizag for a few days, way back in 2004 in the month of december, Nupur gave me this new year card on 31st dec, after returning from her tuitions. Its the most valuable gift, anyone has given me, bcoz she had bought this 4 by 6 inch card, from the money she used to carry with her, just incase she needed to tend to her cycle on the way!!!! The card might have been a simple one, with a picture of a small baby boy on it, but she carefully had selected it from the thousands of cards, --- usse pata hei,mujhe chotte bachey bahut pasand hein ---, andar card mein likhaa tha &quot;My Dearest Ritlu Bhai&quot;
<br />  HAPPY NEW YEAR 2005 , From Tuna Uncle,Tofanni aunty, Lizu and Nupuri&quot; ----
<br />     sab kaa naam likhnaa nahin bhuli woh, and aakhir mein apna naam, this is why I love her so much. 
<br />   Mein aaj bhi jab woh card kholtaa hun, to Nupur ki shurat mere samne aajaati hei, uski woh bachpan ke hastaa hua cheheraa --- (jismein uske aagey ke girre huye daanth bhi dikhte the), uske woh dono side chotti rakhna, aur mera unhe khich ke khol denaa and uska phir chilaanaa &quot;BHAAAAAAAAAAAAAIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII.......&quot; -- sab aankhon ke saamne aa jaa taa hei.
<br /><br />Sisters r always special, koi kisise badkar nahin hotaa, bcoz they all r God's gifts, but Nupur to meri Cutie Pie hei.
<br /><br />I was really touched by her gesture, gift bada ya chotta nahin hotaa, usse dene wale kaa feelings dekhaa jaata hei, jo us card mein jitna pyaar, jis sneha se Nupur ne diya tha, That's what matter most for me. I love u, Cutie and I always will!!
<br /><br />Mein tumhe humesha sataa taa hun, kabhi bhi koi maukaa nahin gawaataa hun tujhe ghussa dilaane mein,par phir bi,tu mujhe itnaa pyaar karti hei!!
<br /><br />Kal teri aur ek baat yaad aa gayi, tunne ek baar kaha tha naa, ki u have written only 3 letters in ur entire life!! Bcoz u hate writing letters. AND I AM THAT LUCKY GUY TO GET ALL THE 3 LETTERS!! Thanks, Nupur, Love U always!! Missing U!!
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8aadc1d75ef8e1fe639d0d0b37467d07" url=""><![CDATA[A NICE, SENSITIVE yet Entertaining MOVIE!!<br/><br/>&quot;MONSOON WEDDING&quot; -- by Mira Nair
<br /><br />Some days back, I got to watch this movie, probably for the 4th time, but still not a single time, I felt bored or left midway-- film hi itna simple, yet very sensibly and touchily banaya gaya hei. Pehli baar dekha tha, jaisa lagaa tha, is baar bhi jab dekha, waisa hi achaa lagaa!
<br /><br />Somewhat different movie, as far as we aam Indians are concerned as we have been fed with the masala stuff bollywood since childhood. Even as the movie starts, during the opening credits also, that music and the style is quite different. Infact that is it's noteworthy point -- not much fanfare in songs, all situation based, no hero, heroine dancing in the rain (though in the end, as the marriage is to take place, Rain Gods pour down heavily and everybody dance, but that was in the context), or around the trees, or a poor boy meets a rich gurl love story -- nothing of that sort. No violence as such as well! But what I liked most about this movie was the level of sensitivity with which the director made this movie. A movie about marriage, but all intrinsic details have been taken care of, what all goes before the supposedly &quot;saath-pheres&quot;! No nuance is missed. Every important facial expression and revealing reaction is there.
<br /><br />The two parents Naseerudin Shah and Lillette Dubey are getting their daughter Vasundhara Das married to US returned bridegroom Parvin Dabbas. Being their only daughter, Naseer and Lillette don't want to leave any stone unturned in making their daughter's wedding a memorable one, even if they have had to take debts. That particular scene where Naseer asks one of his friends for some money for the marriage, but instead is being ridiculed and feels offended -- was so beautifully portrayed and enacted on the screen, it was really very touchy. Esse situations mein naa jaane kitne maa baap padte hein, andaajja nahin hei. Afterall, not all are affluent enough to do a &quot;dhoom dhaam se apni beti ki shaadi&quot;, with all pomp and grandeur, with scratching themselves!!
<br /><br />Also another scene which was quite touchy for me was one scene, where at night, Naseer and Lillette come to Vashundhara's room, she is sleeping, and Nasseer says &quot;Bachey kitnejaldi baddey ho jaate hein!! Maanno, jaise kal hi baat hei, yeh bachi kitni chotti thi, yahin khelti kudti thi, aur kal is ki shaadi ho jaayegi and shashural chale jaayegi, humme chod ke!&quot;. I haven't really been able to make out why gurls only have to leave their parental homes after marriage, jahaan apni bachpan bitaaye ho, jinke saath life ke itne saare moments bitaaye ho, unhe chod ke jaana kyun padtaa hei? Kya unke parents akele nahin ho jaate hongey! Well,leave that.
<br /><br />Kitne finer details pe dhyaan diya gaya tha! Ek marriage se pehle is family ke rehne wale members ke life mein kya kya ho raha tha -- all were covered -- chahe woh unka youngest son, who is more interested in watching cookery shows rather than playing outdoor games (as often ridiculed by Naseer) and so being forced to sent to a boarding school ya phir unka maid-servant Alice ho, everyone got attention.
<br /><br />Wahaan dusre taraf, the prospective bride-to-be Vasundhara has been having a relationship with a much married man (working in TV Media), who was actually using her and wasn't actually ready to break all ties with his current wife or take divorce. This particular angle has also been dealt with a lot of falre and sensitivity both by the director and the actor playing the character -- Vasundhara. Young girls often fall for such relationships due to their immaturity, unhe khud ko pata nahin hotaa hei kewoh kya kar rahe hote hein, they don't really see the guile of the other partner (the married one), who actually just fulfils his lust. But these girls ultimately end up with emotional scars. But in this movie Vasundhara quickly realises her mistake, what blunder she was going to commit. Even more nicety of this character is that she decides to tell all about her past to her husband-to-be Parvin and not to keep him in the dark. Parvin has also played his small yet significant character to perfection, after all shaadi ho,aur dulhe ki baare mein kuch na aho, essa kabhi ho sakta hei?
<br /><br />Ghar mein saddi ho, aur ghar relatives se bharra na ho, essa kabhi ho sakta hei? Well, I don't know really, whether everyone likes this or not, having to share your room and your privacy, even if for a few days, with the relatives. But must say, sometimes these very relatives and the atmosphere -- the shaddi ka mahol can indeed be once in a lifetime experience, which one won't get often. This movie also has had this share. And with this comes the family friend played by Rajat Kapoor. And here starts another story -- kuch puraaney time ke burey yaadein phir se aa jaate hein into Shefali's life. Well Shefalli plays the character of Ria, niece of Naseer, whose father had died long back, when she was a child.
<br /><br />But she had a traumatic childhood, being abused by Rajat Kapoor, which no one knew all these years. Now this was such a sensitive issue, which not many films have shown. This issue has been so nicely dealt with here, you virtually feel for the character, what mental and physical trauma she must have gone through. Even in India, kuch familes mein esse perverts , such demons under the skin of humans, like the character played by Rajat Kapoor, do exist and inke shikaar bante hein kuch maasoom bachey, who mostly never are able to come out of this trauma. These children actually don't know how to react, jyaadatar kisiko kuch keh nahin paatey hein, apne andar hi ghut ghut ke reh jaatey hein and inki puri life mein scar reh jaata hei, jisse woh kabhi bhul nahin paatey hein. Really must say, the director has presented this issue in all reality, in the most sensitive way, even the character shefalli plays, her emotions and facial expressions seem so real, you actually feel like it had happened with you. Even more appealing was the shock Naseer gets when shefalli makes this revelation about Rajat Kapoor.Even if rajat had done a lot of favours to the family, had stood by them in their worst crisis time but that doesn't give him the licence to do such heinous crime. The stand that Naseer takes, asking rajat to immediately leave the marriage, was like -- I virtually clapped. Ek andar se khushi aa gayi, though I was expecting some more stringent punishment, kuch essa reaction, so that he never ever be able to do anything ever like that! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />In sabhi stories ke beech ek aur simple sidha sadha sa love story panap raha tha between the housemaid Alice and Mr. P.K. Dubey (or Dubeyji) played by Vijay Raaj -- playing the character of tent-house owner, responsible for making all the arrangements of caterring and decorations. Kitni khubbi se in simple loggon ki simple si love story ko screen pe deekhaya gaya -- this is waht is called giving equal importance to all characters. (yeah, bas dubeyji ke Maa ko jyaada footage nahin diya gaya tha!!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> )
<br /><br />Mujhe humesha sehi esse simple loggon ki lives mein interest rahi hei. Unke woh simple , unclattered thoughts, simple lifestyle and vurtually and actually jisse hum ek happy family bolte hein, woh darasal inke paas hi dekhe jaati hei, meri nazar mein. They mayn't be having enough money, the aisso aaram ki jindegi, bas do wakt ki roti mil jaaye, unke liye bas ho jata hei. But still, I feel, more than the wealthy people, these people have more chain ki neend. But sabse achi cheez, which I liked most in this part of the story, infact should I say the scene, was jab Aliceek kamre ko saaf karte samaya, finds the jewelleries and the saree of the bride for the marriage and she tries them on also. Shaadi har ladki ke life mein kitne saare umange leke aati hein, usne apne mann mein kitne saare sapney dekhe hote hei, even if she may be just a housemaid, from a poor family. The way Alice puts on all those jewelleries and looks in the mirror and then after a moment'spleasure, sab nikal ke rakh deti hei, as if telling to herself -- &quot;Alice, yeh sab tere liye sapney hein, apni haqeekat mein aaja. Mat bhul ke tu kya hei&quot; --- That scene was also so nicely portrayed. 
<br /><br />It has happened with me a lot of times, that while watching a movie or any particular scene, I get so emotional and so into the characters so deeply that I start crying <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />Here also the same thing happened. And ultimately story mein sab love stories ka happy ending hota heiand indeed the wedding takes place in the most perfect manner and Alice and Dubeyji ka bhi!!
<br /><br />One of my favourite movies and I can say ki even if i watch this movie once again, I won't feel bored. Hats off to Mira Nair for making such a nice movie and presenting all the plots in a very sensitive yet in a simple manner!! I got back my money's worth!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="277e8c078926ad3d1780b9f9f1703261" url=""><![CDATA[RIN SUPREME BAR ab bangaya hei SURL EXCEL BAR.....<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> Yeah, again came with another ad!! I had to, becoz these commercials pay me good money, to keep blogging, u see.
<br /><br />&quot;Mummy..... Mummyyyyyyyy...
<br />   Mummyy... Mummyyyyyyy......
<br /><br />Kya hua?
<br />  Ek burri khabar, ek achi khabar, kaun si khabar sunaayein?
<br /><br />Burri khabar?? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/ohmy.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/ohmy.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Rin supreme bar ab nahin milegaa.... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />  (tension on everyone's face...)
<br />  Aur achi khabar?
<br /><br />Rin supreme bar ab ban gaya hei Surf excel bar.....
<br />   (smile comes back on mummy's face and also on everyone's face.... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> )
<br /><br />Heyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy....
<br /><br />....
<br /><br />Aur aur Daam????? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Wahi daam, wahi daam..... HEYYYYYYYYYYYYYYYY........ (ALL bacheys start khushi manaaing... dancing, kudding...) <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />SURF EXCEL BAR!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bbcf393e0d9ffaa279649f64234ea19e" url=""><![CDATA[AMBUJA CEMENT -- Tumhaari pitaari mein.. Hei Duniya saari!!<br/><br/>I have always liked the ads, for being whacky, for their somewhat hatke style and the thoughts gone behind doing them, some are really very funny. Sometimes I wonder, where from they get such cool ideas?? 
<br /><br />But there are some ads as well, which make me emotional. I mean, make me go into my bachpan ke din...Like the Ambuja Cement ad that's shown now-a-days! -- that of a cute chotta sa bacha, running to his daadi for protection from his mom, after doing some badmashi. The whole ad has been so nicely done and picturised, seeing that ad, mujhe meri bachpan ke din yaad aa gaye, though I haven't been able to get, how the theme shown in the ad is related to Ambuja Cement!
<br /><br />Though I don't remember much about my Daadi ya Daada (grandpa ya grandma)-- they passed away when I was some 2 years old --- but us ad mein jaise woh bachey ko uski daadi maa kahani sunaake khilaa rahi hoti hei, (especially that chawal ko jaise chotte chotte gole banaake thali mein rakhti thi, that really reminded about my own experiences), My mummy used to do the same. Is ad mein aur meri story mein bas yehi difference hei ki, in my case I had my mummy doubling up as my daadi. I used to do a lot of nakhra while eating, then mummy would tell me a story, thik waise hi chotte chotte gole banaake rakh dethi hogi on the thalli. I would still say ki &quot;mein itna saara nahin khaaungaa&quot;, but ultimately end mein mummy kahani sunaa sunaa ke sab khilaa deti thi, and in my bachpan, I did have a nice healthy body (with those chubby cheeks...hehehhehehhehe <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />)!!
<br /><br />And just like the ad, I also had my share of lorries, being sung by mummy to me, though I never could listen them to the fullest,bcoz beech mein hi mujhe neend aajaati thi aur mein so jaata tha... phir mummy kutta billi, kya gaati hogi, mujhe nahin maaloom!! 
<br /><br />Just like the chotta sa bachaa in the ad, I also used to do badmashi, but badmashi ke baad, ultimately had to go to Mummy, mere liye to meri duniya wahin surru hoke wahin khatam hoti thi. Mummy jitna bhi ghussa kyun naa ho, jab mein udaash hoke, rone wali surat banaake jaake unko ek tight Bear Hug de deta tha aur bolta tha &quot;Mummy, aainda se nahin karungaa&quot;, woh sab bhul jaati thi... 
<br /><br />I still remember other than school, I would never go anywhere, if Mummy didn't accompanied me, not even if Papa escorted me, was more close to mummy..hehehhehehhe, I mean, still am. Jahaan bhi jaana ho, mummy ka honaa bahut jaruri tha. Just like the ad, mein bhi Mummy ke goddi mein so jaata tha.
<br /><br />Before leaving for the exams, just like this ad, Mummy would do the puja, and would apply sindoor ka tilak, would do aarti, give me , infact put one or two puja ke phool in my pocket and  would give me dahi. Exams se pehle Dahi khaane se dimaag achey se kaam kartaa hei, and memory bhi achi rehti hei -- My Mom used to say. Many may consider this a superstition, it might have been, but aaj jab unke baare mein sochtaa hun, I really feel very proud of my mom. Duniya chahe jo bhi kahe, I always have and always will love her simplicity. And she did has had a great role to play  in making me whatever I am today.
<br /><br />Another thing which comes to my mind is that she would never allow me or my bro to play during the exams, she would say, &quot;saraswati maata naarj ho jaati hei ,esse karne se&quot;. And those days I obeyed her every single word to the T. And whatever may be the reasons, results bhi waise hi aate the, the first rank. I still remember Mummy kitni khush hojaati thi, whenever the results were out. Hehehehhehehehhehe, I remember the first time I brought the result card to home, after the first term, the first exam, real exam of my life, I couldn't understand what that sheet of paper was, which My ma'am had given me. Ghar aaya to, bhaga ke Mummy ke paas gaya, aur deke kaha,&quot;Mummy, mummy, yeh kuch Nisha Miss ne diya hei&quot;, mujhe kuch bhi samajh nahin aaya tha, what that was. Nisha Miss ne bhi kuch nahin kaha tha, bas diya and said congratulations, apne parents se signature le aanaa. hehehhehheehe, I was truly a yedda those days, bas jitna samjhaya jaata tha, utna hi jaanta tha. 
<br /><br />And when the results of the final exams of ukg (my first year at school) were out, Papa had gone to bring the result sheet, and had brought a Cadbury's chocolate for me, for my results, I was , infact everyone in my family, were so happy that day. Those days we weren't financially so well-off, mere liye Dairy milk cadbury's chocolate was like a priceless gift. Mummy also that evening kept on pesterring Papa to buy a toy racing car, I had seen my neighbour's child Rintu playing. Mera bhi  us car ko dekhke bada jii kiya tha, but mein chup reh gaya tha, knowing our condition. But somehow Mummy ne bhi shayad yeh sab kuch dekhliya tha. I remember mujhe and bhai ko ghar mein Uppar Mummy(the aunty who used to stay upstairs, but who always treated me as her own child )
<br />ke paas chod ke gaye theyy Papa and mummy, and when they returned home with the racing car, I still remember mein kitna khush hua tha!!! I love u , Mom, I love u , Papa. Mere kuch naa bataa ne se bhi, woh meri feelings samajh jaate hein, infact thats what parents are . 
<br /><br />Just yesterday I had seen this ad, and aur dekhne ko jii kartaa hei, achaa lagtaa hei dekhne mein yeh ad. I think, again jab World cup ka final match khelaa jaayega, may be, tab dekhne ko milega yeh ad!!
<br /><br />Bas woh girlfriend wala kissa abhi tak hua nahin hei, hehhehhehehhehehehe, ( I don't think, in the near future kabhi hogaa), nor have I bought any car (naa,naa, not toy car, a real one ), jismein mein apni Mummy ko front seat mein bithaaun and Papa and Bhai ko bhi aur ghummaaun!! But I hope car khareedun ya naa khareedun, that never really matter to me, bas I hope ki for all the hardships my parents took for me,  in bringing me this far, in making me whatever I am today, I will be able to make them happy as well. And this also I know very well, not a car will do, just a BEAR HUG from me again can do the trick!!
<br /><br />Hey U all ad guys, keep creatings such touchy ads!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> All the very BEST!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>