<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="11">
		<document id="c6b88aad4e83a39274b4e8f7232935e6" url=""><![CDATA[‘Classified’ chapter of Dick Cheney book reveals pranks<br/><br/>Washington DC - The Bush Administration will go down in history as the “Prankster Presidency,” according to revelations made in a classified chapter of former Vice President Dick Cheney’s recently published memoirs.
<br /><br />The top-secret material, which shows George W. Bush and Cheney collaborating on a series of elaborate pranks, was made public today by NetSlips, the American version of WikiLeaks.
<br /><br />“The CIA had ordered Dick Cheney to burn this chapter of his memoirs,” said NetSlips founder and president Brice Villavich.  “Instead, he locked it in a safe deposit box and had his dog cremated so he would have ashes to hand over to the CIA. We learned how to get into the safe deposit box from an old Robert Redford movie.”...
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thespoof.com%2Fnews%2Fspoof.cfm%3Fheadline%3Ds2i100182"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thespoof.com/news/spoof.cfm?headline=s2i100182</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88ba2e26f6be6af7f397e449cdb8b27c" url=""><![CDATA[My links<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzcG9vZi5jb20vbmV3cy9zcG9vZi5jZm0/aGVhZGxpbmU9czJpMTAwODc1JmFtcDt1dG1fc291cmNlPW5ldGxvZyZhbXA7dXRtX21lZGl1bT1zb2NpYWwtbWVkaWEmYW1wO3V0bV9jYW1wYWlnbj1hZGR0b2FueQ__" target="_blank">Postal Service rescue plan would turn mail carriers into drug runners</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzcG9vZi5jb20vbmV3cy9zcG9vZi5jZm0/aGVhZGxpbmU9czZpMTAwNzcxJmFtcDt1dG1fc291cmNlPW5ldGxvZyZhbXA7dXRtX21lZGl1bT1zb2NpYWwtbWVkaWEmYW1wO3V0bV9jYW1wYWlnbj1hZGR0b2FueQ__" target="_blank">Steinbrenner Acquires the Tigers; Will Move Team to Yankee Stadium in Time for the World Series</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzcG9vZi5jb20vbmV3cy9tYWdhemluZS9jb2xsZWN0aW9uX2FnZW5jeV9nb2VzX2FmdGVyX2hvdXNlX3NwZWFrZXJfam9obl9ib2VobmVyXzk5NjIuaHRt" target="_blank">Collection agency goes after House Speaker John Boehner</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzcG9vZi5jb20vbmV3cy9zcG9vZi5jZm0/aGVhZGxpbmU9czJpMTAwNDk3JmFtcDt1dG1fc291cmNlPW5ldGxvZyZhbXA7dXRtX21lZGl1bT1zb2NpYWwtbWVkaWEmYW1wO3V0bV9jYW1wYWlnbj1hZGR0b2FueQ__" target="_blank">Michele Bachmann's economic fix: Change nation's name to 'Occupant'</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzcG9vZi5jb20vbmV3cy9zcG9vZi5jZm0/aGVhZGxpbmU9czJpMTAwMzk1JmFtcDt1dG1fc291cmNlPW5ldGxvZyZhbXA7dXRtX21lZGl1bT1zb2NpYWwtbWVkaWEmYW1wO3V0bV9jYW1wYWlnbj1hZGR0b2FueQ__" target="_blank">Wall Street raid is off target: cops arrest protesters instead of the perps</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzcG9vZi5jb20vbmV3cy9zcG9vZi5jZm0/aGVhZGxpbmU9czJpMTAwMzA4JmFtcDt1dG1fc291cmNlPW5ldGxvZyZhbXA7dXRtX21lZGl1bT1zb2NpYWwtbWVkaWEmYW1wO3V0bV9jYW1wYWlnbj1hZGR0b2FueQ__" target="_blank">Organized crime steps in to 'organize' the US government</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzcG9vZi5jb20vbmV3cy9zcG9vZi5jZm0/aGVhZGxpbmU9czJpMTAwMTgyJmFtcDt1dG1fc291cmNlPW5ldGxvZyZhbXA7dXRtX21lZGl1bT1zb2NpYWwtbWVkaWEmYW1wO3V0bV9jYW1wYWlnbj1hZGR0b2FueQ__" target="_blank">'Classified' chapter of Dick Cheney book reveals prankster secrets</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="83c435b2e9b73118de216ba53384e765" url=""><![CDATA[Obama Turns Back the Debt Clock to Save the World<br/><br/>Washington DC - With the stroke of a pen, President Barack Obama has rescued the world from a catastrophic economic meltdown. 
<br /><br />The president signed into law today The Quantitative Time Act, effectively freeing every man, woman and child on the planet from any debt that they might have signed-up for over the past three decades.
<br /><br />Better known as the Cover Your Assets Directive, the new law resets the fiscal calendar to 30 years ago so that all banking and investment transactions are back dated to 1981. That means any car loan, mortgage, home equity line or other debt less than 30 years old has already been paid in full in the real-time world of 2011.
<br /><br />“This is like daylight savings time on steroids,” Obama  explained. “The Quantitative Time Act means there are no more toxic loans out there, Greece can go back to being Greece, Trump and go back to being a douche, and the banking and investment gangs can move on to new scams and frauds.”
<br /><br />The wizards of Wall Street, who rarely pass up an opportunity to demonstrate their capacity for being long on greed and short on brains, agreed. 
<br /><br />“This is better than a ‘do over,’ ” said a spokesman for a major investment firm. “This is a ‘never happened.’ Now we’re free to go out and make the same expensive mistakes all over again, and get away with it all over again. I smell big bonuses for everyone on the street.”
<br /><br />And there will be no one to complain. The debt clock reversal essentially ends protests over the unfair distribution of wealth in America. “Most of those protesters hadn’t even been born yet in 1981,” Obama said. “So by turning back the clock, we are invalidating their birth certificates. Ironic, ain’t it?”
<br /><br />The president had no trouble getting the law past the Republican controlled House of Representatives. “The Republicans are always nostalgic about the Reagan era,” Obama said.  “Well, happy new year.  1981 is here again, only this time, I’m in charge.”
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca87236b9945f89114f0c70abaa243e4" url=""><![CDATA[Perry and Cain Check-In to the Ronald Reagan Memory Clinic<br/><br/>Texas governor Rick Perry is so prone to brain freeze that he has been advised to wear an insulated hat at all times. He almost sunk his campaign at the Republican presidential debate last week, when he couldn’t remember one of his own policy points.
<br /><br />His treatment at the Reagan Clinic will consist of prying his eyelids open so they can’t be closed and forcing him to watch every campaign speech he has ever made, over and over again.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thespoof.com%2Fnews%2Fspoof.cfm%3Fheadline%3Dwww.101818"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thespoof.com/news/spoof.cfm?headline=www.101818</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2e30cf98eef83e0bdc1b1262d43a960c" url=""><![CDATA[Bloomberg Cancels the Thanksgiving Day Parade<br/><br/>New York - Mayor Michael Bloomberg has called off the Thanksgiving Day Parade, charging that the event is a public health and safety hazard.
<br /><br />Following a strategy he developed in evicting Occupy Wall Street from the financial district, Bloomberg threatened that anyone marching in the parade or observing the event would be arrested by NYPD riot police.
<br /><br />“Those big balloons and huge floats are nothing but a threat to the physical and emotional well-being of New Yorkers,” the pint-size politician said. “A giant Underdog, a humongous Spiderman, a SpongeBob as big as a building. These are frightening to little people, and they scare the children too.”
<br /><br />NYPD Public Confiscation Units have already raided warehouses throughout metropolitan area, where Macy’s, the parade’s organizer, stores millions of dollars worth of parade paraphernalia. They brought it all to the Sanitation Department’s garages for “inventorying.”
<br /><br />A sanitation spokesman said that Macy’s could retrieve its property “on the day after Christmas, so we can be sure that no holiday celebration with these dangerous objects will be forthcoming.”
<br /><br />In a related incident that occurred during the raid, Max Baris, a 67-year-old retiree from Greenpoint, died in a hail of police gun fire. Baris was attempting to take a cell phone shot of a deflated Charlie Brown balloon as it was taken into custody.
<br /><br />“We developed a new, more effective policy toward unauthorized photography of our brave police officers in action,” Bloomberg said. “We call it: ‘If They See Something, Slay Something.‘ You’ll be seeing that slogan posted throughout the city, and you’ll heed its message if you know what’s good for you.”
<br /><br />As to the Thanksgiving Day Parade, Bloomberg took full responsibility for ordering an end to the 85 year holiday tradition, but he noted that the initial idea came from Wall Street. 
<br /><br />“The financial gurus pointed out that the parade costs the city millions and that we should be saving those dollars during these austere times,” the mayor said. “There’s going to be a little something extra in their bonus stockings this year for that gem.”
<br /><br />Citing similar health, financial and safety issues, Bloomberg said he is considering the termination by the city of such events as the St. Patrick’s Day parade, the Columbus Day parade, the Puerto Rican Day parade, and the Fourth of July fireworks.  “Someone could get an eye poked out by those things,” Bloomberg declared.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e04761d45e86e2edee098e28d3308b43" url=""><![CDATA[Iran Missile Blast Caused by Faulty Waffle Maker - Or Not<br/><br/>Tehran, Iran - A devastating explosion that leveled a missile firing range near Iran’s capital city was caused by a waffle iron, rather than by sabotage which had first been feared. 
<br /><br />The appliance short-circuited during a ballistics test, igniting the wrong end of a solid fuel rocket, according to an investigation by US intelligence operatives.
<br /><br />“The Iranians often use household items to activate their weapons systems because they have been shut out of the legitimate market for sophisticated electronic controls,” an unnamed CIA source said.  
<br /><br />“In this case, it looks like someone tried to pour syrup on the waffle before it was out of the appliance. The end must’ve come as quite a shock.”
<br /><br />Iranian officials are disputing the finding, charging that America is covering up “the true cause of the test base explosion -- a lucky shot by a US Air Force drone.”
<br /><br />“My people aren’t even allowed to eat waffles,” said Maj. Sundra Dee, an Iranian security commander. “Pancakes, yes. French toast, okay. Maybe even the occasional bagel. But waffles, no way.”
<br />MORE
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a0f1bca59171a1514ba9fe4abaf935bc" url=""><![CDATA[Jon Corzine Fingers Mr. Potter; Says Life’s Not So Wonderf<br/><br/>Washington DC - Failed hedge fund CEO Jon Corzine yesterday called on a House Subcommittee to arrest Henry F. Potter, a Bedford Falls banker and slumlord, for fraud and malfeasance in connection with the collapse of Corzine’s MF Global Hedge Fund and Building and Loan.
<br /><br />Speaking before the House Subcommittee for Farmland and Fertilizer, the former governor and United States Senator said he wasn’t sure how $1.2 billion in customer funds vanished from MF Global’s coffers. But he recalled that the last time he saw the money, Uncle Billy was counting it.
<br /><br />“Uncle Billy was supposed to deposit the $1.2 billion in Potter’s bank,” Corzine said. “But he was overexcited that day because my brother was coming back home after serving 10 years in Iraq. Somehow, Potter used uncle Billy’s confusion to get his hooks into that cash.”
<br />MORE 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thespoof.com%2Fnews%2Fspoof.cfm%3Fheadline%3Ds2i102574"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thespoof.com/news/spoof.cfm?headline=s2i102574</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3ba32dd96abea1f7987b9f814561dcb4" url=""><![CDATA[‘Christmas with the Candidates’ to Replace the Trump Deb<br/><br/>New York - Real estate developer Donald Trump has announced that his planned presidential debate has been canceled due to lack of interest and replaced by a holiday special. The program is scheduled to feature all of the remaining Republican candidates for president.
<br /><br />“It’s gonna be awesome,” Trump said in a recent news conference. “It’s gonna be like ‘Dancing with the Stars’ but without the dancing and without the stars. But we’re gonna pack plenty of Christmas magic into this very, very special special.”
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3053cd2a1a74aac4fa5fc4e14cf3d310" url=""><![CDATA[John Boehner Kills ‘Share Christmas With Your Senator’<br/><br/>A program that would have allowed United States Senators to join in the Christmas celebrations of their constituents has been voted down by the House of Representatives.
<br /><br />“We’re giving a big ‘bah humbug’ to that idea,” said House Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio).  “Sure the Senators need some place to go for Christmas dinner, but they forgot to include us Representatives. So they’ve ruined it for everyone, just like they always do.”
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="51849d2ab7b28b6c662b4a036bd9bd30" url=""><![CDATA[US Declares a World Record Victory in Iraq<br/><br/>The United States military today is celebrating a major win in Iraq. American troops are heading home after setting the world record for the longest and most expensive stop and frisk in the history of law enforcement.
<br /><br />“It seems like only yesterday that the United States pulled over Iraq on suspicion of possession of Weapons of Mass Destruction,” said President Obama. “Little did anyone realize that just 8 years and $1 trillion later we would be celebrating a world record together.”
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thespoof.com%2Fnews%2Fspoof.cfm%3Fheadline%3Ds2i102821"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thespoof.com/news/spoof.cfm?headline=s2i102821</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ab46158978d7c35ca7d4fad65d4d7579" url=""><![CDATA[Donald Trump Creates A New Political Party -- The Trumpets<br/><br/>New York -- Just days after turning in his Republican membership card and secret decoder ring, real estate developer Donald Trump has launched his own personal political party.
<br /><br />“It’s called the Trumpets, because I’m a guy who likes to toot his own horn,” Trump told a crowd of reporters at a hastily arranged press briefing. “Plus, Trumpets is a play on my name. So it shows how clever I am and that I have a sense of humor -- a man of the people. I think the voters will like that.” 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thespoof.com%2Fnews%2Fspoof.cfm%3Fheadline%3Ds2i102967%26amp%3Butm_source%3Dfacebook%26amp%3Butm_medium%3Dsocial-media%26amp%3Butm_campaign%3Daddtoany"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thespoof.com/news/spoof.cfm?headline=s2i102967&amp;utm_source=facebook&amp;utm_medium=social-media&amp;utm_campaign=addtoany</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>