<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="d513e3c5c4bd245c5897e0f946c2b4e9" url=""><![CDATA[Avoiding Foot Injuries When Playing Sport<br/><br/>Foot injuries are a very common sports injury that can occur from overtraining, the secret to avoiding an injury when you first start training is - don't do too much, build your training up over time.<br /><br />It is also very important to think of training in terms of hard and easy days and hard and easy weeks - make sure you give your body a chance to recover.<br /><br />If you are a runner then you should consider having 2 days off for every 5 days on, and build up your distance covered by an increase of 10% per week.<br /><br />Good quality running shoes are essential so old ones should be replaced with suitable shock absorbing shoes - ideally if you are running 20 miles + per week you should look to replace your shoes every 4 - 8 months.<br /><br />Stretching should also be carried out before and after running - this will help avoid tightness in the calf and hamstring.<br /><br />Stretching the calf muscles helps to reduce the area of concentrated force to your feet. It has been shown that you can reduce pressure at the heel and the ball of the foot by over half with simple stretching of the calf muscle. Other benefits to stretching include increased blood circulation to the foot<br /><br />Calf Stretch - The best stretch to the calf (achilles) is the wall stretch. I found that this blogger explained this smartly on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdebtask.com%2F2539%2Fdebt-consolidation-personal-bankruptcy%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://debtask.com/2539/debt-consolidation-personal-bankruptcy/</a>  webpage.<br /><br />You can also perform:<br /><br />Hamstring Stretch - To do this you need to straighten one leg with your knee locked in place on a foot stool. You then bend your body back and bring your head towards you leg.<br /><br />Foot Anatomy<br /><br />In order to understand how injuries to the foot can occur it is important to have a bit of knowledge of the anatomy of the foot.<br /><br />The foot essentially acts as the foundation to the whole body, they also act as shock absorbers and produce propulsion for the body.<br /><br />The foot and ankle contain:<br /><br />o	26 bones (One-quarter of the bones in the human body are in the feet.);<br />o	33 joints;<br />o	more than 100 muscles, tendons (fibrous tissues that connect muscles to bones), and ligaments (fibrous tissues that connect bones to other bones); and<br />o	a network of blood vessels, nerves, skin, and soft tissue.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b5895d56897b58a0cbc6d8febeb03430" url=""><![CDATA[Women's Sports Shoes - Care For Your Feet<br/><br/>Fancy worrying about the right kind of sports shoes to wear! We fuss about the right kind of clothes, the right kind of skin products, the perfect hair cut, then why not pay a little attention to our feet? After all, they are most important, because what's the point of taking all the trouble when you can't even walk around properly?<br /><br />Sports shoes as the names suggests, are specially designed for sports and physical exercise, but are nowadays more used as a comfort shoes for casual use. They are known by many names like trainers, joggers, sneakers, canvers, and tennis shoes and so on. These are used for running, or playing sports like basket ball, tennis and such lighter sports. I found that this webpage demonstrated this smartly on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwirelessspeakerssystems.net%2F305%2Fwireless-surround-sound-speakers-humbuzz-badly%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://wirelessspeakerssystems.net/305/wireless-surround-sound-speakers-humbuzz-badly/</a> post.<br /><br />So what should one look for while selecting the right kind of athletic shoes? One that has a flexible sole which can absorb impact and be made of flexible material to provide utmost comfort should be the right choice. They come in different shapes and sizes to suit different type of feet. They are usually divided into neutral, overpronation and underpronation running shoes to fit the foot strike of the runners. Since there are more details being paid attention to in these running shoes, amateur joggers as well as marathon runners, are paying more attention to purchase shoes based on their running style and foot arch.<br /><br />The reason this is done is in order to prevent injury, increase efficiency, support speed and increase comfort levels. There are shoes specially designed for racing, track shoes, skating, climbing etc. The wrong choice of shoes can lead to muscle pain, muscle stress and injury.<br /><br />Let's have a look at the considerations to be taken care of while making a choice of purchasing sports shoes. The walking style of a person is an important consideration. This in turn is related to the kind of feet people have. There are several sports stores which have all kinds of shoes in all shapes and sizes to cater to needs of different people. Also, keeping the fitness mantra of women in mind, there are companies that are coming up with sport shoes that help to keep the body fit and toned, which attracts customers to go for such shoes. Apart from showrooms, the internet is an open market which has shoes of all brands and with various attributes and at competitive prices to meet everyone's needs. So if sports shoes can bring so much comfort and added benefits, spending some time to select the right kind of shoe to suit your feet type is not a bad idea.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="99389fa37a112771901ebb1a44d388a5" url=""><![CDATA[Sports Supplements - How To Get Natural Strength And Boost P<br/><br/>When it comes to natural supplements, there are many different products on the market that you can choose from. For athletes, supplements that are created and geared towards sports can often give them the extra boost that they need to play better and last longer during their favorite activities.<br /><br />From high school athletes to professionals, sports supplements have been used for decades without any major issues whatsoever. Keep in mind that chemical supplements are not the topic of discussion here. This article is specifically focused on all-natural health supplements that can help with sports performance and strength. I found that this blog showed this incredibly on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmicrowavesreviews.net%2F994%2Fmicrowave-ovens-microwave-radiation-heat-food%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://microwavesreviews.net/994/microwave-ovens-microwave-radiation-heat-food/</a> website.<br /><br />When it comes to performing in sporting events, you have to have the right balance of fitness and vitamins in your routine. If you are working out too much, you will need more carbohydrates. To do this without eating terrible food, you can take supplements.<br /><br />If you need antioxidants because your body is stressed, you can take a supplement. There are a variety of naturally-occurring substances that athletes of all kinds rely on for their various health and performance needs. Sometimes, people use certain products regularly, while other times they may only use them here and there as needed.<br /><br />If it works, it doesn't matter. Sports supplements can offer increased strength, stamina, endurance, and more ability to accomplish the various sporting goals that people have. These are not offering any enhancements that would be considered cheating or unfair, but are simply helping to create better, healthier bodies so that sports can be played much more successfully.<br /><br />Like nutritional supplements, these are not a magical cure that is going to make everything better overnight. They can be very effective, but supplements will take time to work and will only do so much. Your body has to do the rest.<br /><br />It is very important that you get supplements from a brand that you know and trust. This is especially true with sports supplements because you could risk your entire game, season, or career on taking something that you aren't really sure about.<br /><br />These natural supplements aren't FDA regulated so it is up to you to find a credible resource for the supplements that you need so that you can get the products that work without spending a fortune or buying from the wrong company. Take the time to learn about sports supplements and your different options so that you can get the best products every single time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="743c5c97ce5e311fb402c515cef27660" url=""><![CDATA[Rugby Strength and Conditioning - Get Fit For a Bruising Spo<br/><br/>In rugby strength and conditioning is vital, more so than in many other sports. The relentless physical contact, the aggression and energy required make it pretty sapping. I found that this webmaster showed this intelligently on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Faskmarketers.com%2F779%2Fkind-engineering-demand-profession-highest-salary%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://askmarketers.com/779/kind-engineering-demand-profession-highest-salary/</a> weblog.<br /><br />Despite these facts, you might be surprised to know that many amateur players don't show up well in rugby strength and conditioning tests, according to research done for Sports Medicine journals. So even a once a week training programe is going to give you a good chance of doing well.<br /><br />When thinking about rugby strength and conditioning you need to bear in mind the following target areas - you need to think about speed AND power, plus quick recovery as who knows when the ball is heading your way next in the backs, or as a forward there is that need to get to the breakdown quickly. Power is also needed to make solid tackles, or even better, bone-crunching ones.<br /><br />Interval training is one way for a rugby strength and conditioning regime to produce results. It's pretty simple in that periods of exercise are followed by periods of rest. If you think about it it does simulate the game, when there are frantic spells followed by pauses. It also means that there is less lactic acid in the system. 400 metre laps followed by rest would be one example.<br /><br />Lower body exercises are also effective. They will help with power, whether it's for jumping to grab the ball in the line-out, to holding your own in the scrum, or to get motoring when you receive the ball in the back.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="92d695c7a50714a773f1b0c8a5b23044" url=""><![CDATA[Hand and Foot Card Game Rules<br/><br/>Do you know the Hand and Foot Card Game Rules? You will when you read this article to the fun and fast-paced four (or more) person game that's been very popular in the past and is experiencing a recent revival.<br /><br />If you enjoy card playing and would like to learn a new, exciting and fast moving game, this is the one. Take a few minutes to learn Hand and Foot card game rules and you're guaranteed a great many hours of fun for years to come.<br /><br />Hand and Foot is a type of Canasta, a card game that became popular starting back in the 1940s. It was originally played in South America where the word Canasta means 'basket'. Pronunciation originally had the accent on the first syllable, as in the word 'canister', but when the game came to America in 1949, this changed to the more common Ca-NAS-ta.<br /><br />There have come to be many variations of Canasta and learning the different Canasta card game rules can be confusing since they change from one version to another. Hand and Foot, also known as classic Canasta, is the most popular version played in the U.S. During the 1950s, the game became wildly popular and was played by millions. It even became more popular than Bridge for a few years and was actually the number one card game. I found that this site demonstrated this nicely on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fkitchenknivesreviews.net%2F480%2Fsister-dont-free-lawyer-brothers-case%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://kitchenknivesreviews.net/480/sister-dont-free-lawyer-brothers-case/</a>   webpage.<br /><br />According to accepted Hand and Foot card game rules, it's best played with four people in two teams, however, five and six person games are also possible. Regular decks of playing cards are used, including both jokers from each deck. The number of decks you'll need is equal to the number of players, plus one. For a four-person game five decks are used, making a total of 270 cards (including the 10 jokers). As an option, you can also buy specially made card decks that will also include Hand and Foot card game rules.<br /><br />Players sit across the table from their teammate and the object is to get rid of all your cards before the other team does. Points are awarded for different combinations of cards melded, much like in 500 Rummy. Jokers and twos are wild in this game, which is fast paced, challenging and, really, tons of fun.<br /><br />You can click on the links below to download a FREE copy of the complete Hand And Foot Rules If you want to learn some other fun games to play, you can also easily find Hearts card game rules and Spite and Malice card game rules online. Spite and Malice, also called Cat and Mouse, is a competitive form of Solitaire, suitable for two (or more) players.<br /><br />Hand and Foot card game rules may need to be studied several times, as this is a game that's rated as 'moderate' in difficulty. Once learned, though, it can give you hours of entertainment and is a great family game.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1686bd94ce8ff743256d49addbfefd09" url=""><![CDATA[Premier League Preview: Arsenal Vs Liverpool<br/><br/>Premier League match time returns to the Emirates with Arsenal set to host Liverpool in match week 33 on Sunday, April 17, in the second of a two-legged contest.<br /><br />The first, hosted by Liverpool on August 15, 2010, ended in a 1-1 stalemate. With neither side scoring in the first half, the stalemate was broken immediately after the interval, when Ngog gave Liverpool the lead. Arsenal had Reina in the Liverpool goal to thank for their equalizer when the Reds' keeper gloved an own goal in injury time. Earlier Liverpool were reduced to 10 men, when Cole was sent off, on the stroke of half-time. Arsenal midfielder Koscielny collected two bookings to reduce the Gunners to 10 men, themselves, in stoppage time.<br /><br />Their keeper Almunia was the weak link in the Arsenal armour, and for some time, arsene Wenger had been negotiating to wean Fulham's Schwarzer to take his place. Barring Cole's sending off, Liverpool gave a good account of themselves, and kept Arsenal's forwards at bay, for the best part of 90 minutes. I found that this blogger showed this well on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Felectronicdrumkitreview.com%2Feasy-good-drum-music-play-meaning-songs-produced-celebs%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://electronicdrumkitreview.com/easy-good-drum-music-play-meaning-songs-produced-celebs/</a>  blog post.<br /><br />Head to head, Arsenal have established an 8-4 lead over Liverpool in the last 20 league games played between the sides, with the remaining 8 matches drawn.<br /><br />In their last 10 league games, Arsenal have registered 5 wins and 5 draws, while Liverpool have won 6 of their last 10, while losing and drawing 4 each. Of their 16 home games this season, Arsenal have won 10, and lost and drawn 3 games each, while Liverpool have won 4 of their 16 games on the road, while losing 2 and drawing the remaining 10.<br /><br />In match week 32, Arsenal won 3-1 away at Blackpool, while Liverpool beat Manchester City 3-0 at home.<br /><br />Sunday's game assumes great significance for both teams. Arsenal would seek all of their remaining games, to keep their slender title hopes alive. Similarly, Liverpool, who are currently in 6th place, would want to use the remaining games to best advantage, and try to wrest a European qualification. Expect the Reds to fight hard in a game that will give Arsenal the considerable advantage of playing at home.<br /><br />Arsenal's starting eleven against Blackpool had the following players: Lehmann, Eboue, Squillaci, Koscielny, Clichy, Diaby, Fabregas, Wilshere, Nasri, van Persie and Arshavin. Ramsey, Gibbs and Walcott played as substitutes.<br /><br />Liverpool had the following men in their starting eleven against Manchester City: Reina, Flanagan, Carragher, Skrtel, Aurelio, Kuyt, Lucas, Spearing, Meireles, Suarez and Carroll. Ngog was used as a substitute.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3cf6a76b5df0223da9dbe2c4004a72cf" url=""><![CDATA[Cheap Hotels in Manchester and Sports<br/><br/>Cheap Hotels in Manchester and Football<br /><br />There are many luxury and cheap hotels in Manchester that put you within a short distance of some of the most famous football clubs in the world. Manchester is home to not one, but two premier league football teams, that of Manchester United and Manchester City. If you are a season ticket holder you may regularly visit the city and are always in need of hotels. You may just be looking to visit the stadiums for a one-off tour and need a hotel. The Manchester United Museum and Tour Centre lets visitors relive the clubs triumphs, tragedies and trophies and follow the clubs amazing history from 1878 to present. You can delve behind the scenes in the stadium tour by sitting in Sir Alex Ferguson's spot, see the home teams changing rooms and emerge from the players tunnel as you experience the famous turf the team plays on. Manchester City Football club stadium was originally built for Manchester's Commonwealth Games in 2002 and is now home to Manchester City. The football ground also offers a tour for fans and visitors where they can soak up the atmosphere and learn about the history of the club. Cheap hotels in Manchester are in large supply so after your game or tour you can relax in the Northern capital. I found that this person showed this smartly on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fhometheaterpad.com%2F292%2Fbuy-typical-5-1-surround-sound-speakers-plug-tv%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://hometheaterpad.com/292/buy-typical-5-1-surround-sound-speakers-plug-tv/</a>  post.<br /><br />Sport Activities and Cheap Hotels in Manchester <br /><br />Staying in cheap hotels in Manchester not only allows you to experience the city's fantastic football but also a number of other great sporting activities. Old Trafford International Cricket Venue is home to Lancashire County Cricket Club, known as Lancashire Lightening. The grounds host not only cricket matches throughout the year but large events like music concerts are popular. Marland Golf Club is situated within Springfield Park and offers an enjoyable yet challenging 18-hole course for golfers of all abilities. A great family day out can be at Manchester Aquatics Centre. Built for the 2002 Commonwealth games, the centre boasts two 50-metre swimming pools, a special diving pool, a fitness studio, health suite and a caf?? restaurant. If you fancy something a bit more exhilarating, Salford Quays is home to the UK Bungee Club where you can jump right at the water's edge! Of course these are just few of many sporting attractions in the city and staying in Manchester will guarantee you won't miss a single one!<br /><br />Sporting Events and Cheap hotels in Manchester<br /><br />When you are looking for cheap hotels in Manchester, be sure to look for those that are near to your sporting event. If it is a little out the way, this is not so much of an issue thanks to all the great public transport available. With the pressure building to London 2012 games, some of the best teams from around the world will be bringing their Taekwondo to Manchester this October for the British Open. As well as this the ROWE British Grand Prix Squash Championships are due to take place in September, the Great Britain Women's team for Water polo will be preparing and there are a number of cycling events being staged. There are also regular rugby fixtures throughout the year with Manchester's premier rugby team, the Sale Sharks taking on many opponents. Staying in  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.roomguide.co.uk%2Fcity%2Fmanchester"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.roomguide.co.uk/city/manchester</a>  opens up a number of sporting opportunities.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8664cb9403fb95d859377b0e32c71c4f" url=""><![CDATA[Ivory Simone Talks About Her Novel 'Havasu Means Blue Water<br/><br/>Author/Activist Ivory Simone has forged a gripping story that masters the importance of speech and dialogue relaying the emotions and strengths of the solid characters presented in the tale of Lyla Amir whose research for her master's thesis brings the past into the present.<br /><br />'Havasu Means Blue Water' examines the long ago lynching of a black farmer and his wife but while this is the main foundation of the story we are introduced to subplots linked to the contemporary story of Lyla, her research and her life.<br /><br />The story, past and present, of fictional Wilburn, AZ where the subjects of Lyla's research lived and died is both repellant and bittersweet. It is also where Lyla finds strength and an unexpected ally.<br /><br />Ivory talks with us about writing 'Havasu Means Blue Water'<br /><br />Lynnette Phillips - What inspired you to write Havasu Means Blue Water?<br /><br />Ivory Simone - My family history. I grew up listening to my grandfather who told me stories about his grandfather--a black Indian who came out of slavery as a boy. I found a 1780s census record with my great-great-grandfather's name and background information. The record confirms my grandfather's oral history was correct. This family history took on new meaning when I worked for a Native American Tribe years later. Both of these invents laid the foundation for Havasu Means Blue Water.<br /><br />LP - Does &quot;havasu&quot; mean blue water?<br /><br />IS - Yes, it does. In the Mojave language it means &quot;blue water&quot;. One of the characters in the story is a descendant of a Mojave tribe decimated by disease and other anti-Indian government policies.<br /><br />LP --Why should readers buy your book?<br /><br />IS -- It's a snapshot of the cultural wars we see in the Southwest--in places like my home state of Arizona. The inhabitants of the fictional town of Wilburn, Arizona are threatened by outsiders. They have a history of crushing groups who are different. However, the violence unleashed against outsiders is also used against the women and children of the town. Hate is a monster that's never satisfied. When it runs out of enemies to eat, it'll start devouring its own. Havasu Means Blue Water is a cautionary tale about the price a society pays for remaining passive in the face of racial and cultural intolerance.<br /><br />LP -- &quot;The legacy of injustice&quot; will be the topic in two author Facebook chats that'll be held on July 10th and July 16th at 3:00 p.m. (EST). Why is this an important issue?<br /><br />IS - I want people to think about what happens to a community when a grave injustice is allowed to fester. I want people to talk about what they can do to promote the healing of any festering wounds of injustice that divide and weaken their own communities. Justice is not optional--it's essential to the well-being of a community and its people.<br /><br />LP -- The love between the two murdered victims, Mary Alice and Nathaniel Venerable, is central to the novel, why?<br /><br />IS -- I believe love is the greatest force on earth. It's far greater than hate, far greater than the tyranny of violence. We first meet Mary Alice and Nathaniel as victims. However, I want readers to remember them for the deep love they shared. It's their love story that reaches out from the grave to influence the living, to propel events that bring about change.<br /><br />LP -- Mother-daughter relationships are also explored quite a bit in the novel. The relationship between Lyla Amir, the heroine of the story and her mother and the relationship between Amber Goody and Bonnie Good, a dysfunctional daughter and mother--are both important threads in the plot. Why?<br /><br />IS -- I'm a daughter and a mother of daughters. A daughter's relationship with her mother helps determine the type of women she'll grow-up to be. I wanted to show how certain acts and omissions mothers/women make in their lives shape the women their daughters become.<br /><br />LP -- Lyla Amir is an unusual heroine. She's an Arab-American of mixed parentage (her mother is African-American) investigating the murder of a black farmer and his wife. Her heritage is one of the story lines that adds tension to events that unfold in the novel. Why did you make her Arab-American.<br /><br />IS -- Lyla Amir's heritage is important because I believe Arab Americans now understand what Black Americans already know--what it feels like to be an undesireable &quot;other&quot;. Lyla self-identifies as black but she has racially ambiguous features. This presents problems for her when she goes to Wilburn. It's her Arab heritage that becomes the source of hatred and conflict for her.<br /><br />LP - The question of identity is also one of the issues Firestone Matise, the descendant of Mary Alice and Nathaniel Venerable, faces, too. Why?<br /><br />IS -- I think people are quick to label others based on appearance alone. I wanted to challenge the notion we can know a person's history based on his or her racial profile. Racial stereotypes get in the way of Americans' ability to form positive relationships with one another. The browning of America will make such thinking a liability in the future. I believe that's a good thing in the long run I found that this weblog showed this intelligently on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fhometheaterpad.com%2F996%2Fxbox-360-pc-monitor-logitech-speaker-questions%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://hometheaterpad.com/996/xbox-360-pc-monitor-logitech-speaker-questions/</a>   web page.<br /><br />LP -- What do you want readers to know about Ivory Simone?<br /><br />IS - I'm a writer and poet who dreams a lot. I have a vivid and active dream life that makes my journey in the world fascinating and sometimes strange.<br /><br />LP -- What's it like living in Bangkok, Thailand?<br /><br />IS -- There's never a dull moment. More importantly, I'm able to move about in relative safety and ease.<br /><br />Thank you, Ivory, for talking with us and for your wonderful novel 'Havasu Means Blue Water'
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6dd825df09e857b1f4d53cae11ccbcf9" url=""><![CDATA[What To Do When Your Pets Start Fighting?<br/><br/>When you have more than one pet living inside your home, you can possibly have problems with fighting pets. You can lose or have some of your properties damaged or your pets can get hurt. And so, it is important that you deal with this problem promptly and as effectively as possible.<br /><br />Keep calm. Once you witness your pets fighting each other, there are things that you need to do to stop them and ensure that they will not be hurt. First and foremost, remain calm and do not panic. Even if you have two big dogs fighting each other, you should not panic. There can be a good reason for you to fear for your welfare and the lives of your pets. But, it will do more good if you keep your cool.<br /><br />If you stay calm, you will be able to think clearly. You can either stop the fight or keep the damage at minimum. Your decisions will be sounder and it will be beneficial to you, your home, and your pets.<br /><br />Give up on screaming. Screaming at two hostile pets almost always never works. It will be very hard to get their attention this way. You will only waste your energy, lose your voice, and start feeling hopeless as your efforts at shouting at them doesn't seem to work. Even if you are afraid at coming close to two fighting animals, still refrain from shouting. You might just even aggravate the situation. I found that this blog demonstrated this nicely on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fkitchenknivesreviews.net%2F1543%2Ffrench-chefs-knife%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://kitchenknivesreviews.net/1543/french-chefs-knife/</a>   webpage.<br /><br />When they start fighting, sometimes shouting can be an instinctive response. But a little later, you will be able to control yourself and keep from doing such action.<br /><br />Break the fight. Since you cannot break the fight between your pets by just shouting at them from a corner, you will need to take some action. First, take out your pet's leashes. Even if they are still fighting, you just approach one pet and slowly try to place the leash on its neck.<br /><br />Find a place where you can tie the leash and keep one dog in place. Their fight might still be proceeding at this time. Just let them do so. You then take out another leash for your other pet. Do the same thing. But, make sure that you tie the other pet on a place that is far from the other one. As much as possible, keep one out of sight of the other. This will allow them to calm down and no longer feel aggressive.<br /><br />Do not attempt to pull them away from each other with your bare hands as you might get bitten or be included in their rumble. The use of leashes will be one of your best, if not your best, option.<br /><br />Place them in kennels. After you have separated them from each other, you can place them inside separate cages or kennels. This will further allow them to cool off by themselves. Aggressive behavior in dogs, cats, or any other pet can be lessened with proper training and disciplinary measures used on the pets.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="59a534e08ace670e5ded12e570a97c87" url=""><![CDATA[Facts About Lake Malawi<br/><br/>Lake Malawi, also known as Lake Nyasa amongst a host of other names, is a beautiful lake that is probably the main setting of some marine biologists' dreams every night. This lake is supposed to be the home of more fish species than that of any other body of freshwater on Earth, which isn't too surprising once you hear the fact that Lake Malawi is also the eighth largest lake in the world. Nestled in the Great Rift Valley system of East Africa, it is also Africa's third largest lake.<br /><br />People have depended for over a thousand years for food from the bountiful wildlife that resides in Lake Malawi, home of over a thousand species of cichlids, and provider of tasty fish such as kampango, a catfish. Many species of fish have evolved from the waters of Lake Malawi, most notably cichlids, and various other animals. Naturally, at least a few extremely exotic species of fish have evolved from these waters, such as the rare Mbuna fish, highly sought after by avid aquarists due to its brilliant coloring. As a result, the lake is not only a huge source of food, but also the source of work for thousands of Malawian fishermen, net and canoe manufacturers, and fish traders. Unfortunately, overfishing and water pollution threatens the potential future of the wildlife here.<br /><br />Lake Malawi is an attractive tourist location, with most of its tourists visiting during the dry season, which lasts from April to November. The wet season, on the other hand, lasts from December to March. Because the wet season is preceded by a very hot and humid period between November and December, the dry season is the most ideal season for visiting Lake Malawi. I found that this webpage described this intelligently on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdslrcamerareviewer.com%2Fcamera-nikon-d60-nikon-80-canon-eos-500d-550d%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dslrcamerareviewer.com/camera-nikon-d60-nikon-80-canon-eos-500d-550d/</a>  web site.<br /><br />The Malawian government has taken great strides in ensuring that the lake does not become too commercialized or overcrowded, and they have done a good job so far. The northern portion of the lake is largely untouched by tourists, and therefore lies in a pristine, unspoiled condition. The beaches are almost never crowded. One of the main forms of human activity you will see at Lake Malawi will probably be that of the fish traders, who vend thousands upon thousands of silver-colored fish that are dried, smoked, and sold in huts.<br /><br />Most of the permanent settlements, hotels, and campsites, however, can only be found on the southern portion of the lake. There, one can snorkel, dive, sail, and do pretty much any sort of fun recreational activity that can be done on any major beach. The lake itself possesses a beautifully warm temperature of 74 to 85 degrees Fahrenheit year-round. Before anyone actually visits Lake Malawi, they should know that malaria is a concern here, so tourists should try their best to minimize mosquito bites by using insect repellents, and trying to sleep in mosquito net-treated edifices. Never let your guard down against the mosquitoes.<br /><br />In conclusion, Lake Malawi has experienced a ton of historical legacies, ranging from being the host of a naval battle between the British and the Germans, to being the evolutionary site of an eclectic range of over 450 species of freshwater tropic fish. Its sheer size alone is enough to suggest that it still holds its fair share of untold mysteries that have yet to be discovered.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fb6bd4afb1ebcec36a6e0f9506ee9871" url=""><![CDATA[Siamese Fighting Fish Fact Sheet<br/><br/> There are several species in the genus Betta, but the best known and most spectacular is the Siamese Fighting Fish; Betta splendens; the splendid Betta. This fish comes from Thailand and the old name of Thailand was Siam. Other names for this fish are: Japanese Fighting Fish, Samarai Fighting Fish, Chinese Fighting Fish and Mexican fighting Fish. The Cambodian Fighting Fish is a colour variety of this fish. If you put two males together they will usually fight after going through a display. The display seems to be part of the fish's method of recognising the sex of the other fish. In a limited space like a small aquarium a fight would usually end with one fish dead. In Thailand fish fights are staged with betting on the outcome. This is a traditional sport which is now illegal in Thailand, although this does not mean that it never occurs.<br /><br />Females can be put together with each other and one male in a reasonable sized aquarium. Usually there is no serious trouble between them although a tank some hiding places is a good idea.<br /><br />The males are usually much more spectacular than the females, having longer fins and more intense colour.<br /><br />Temperature<br /><br />Fighting fish are a tropical fish; 24 degrees C is a suitable temperature. They can take at least 10 degrees higher than this, but will not be comfortable any lower than about 18 degrees C. In a climate like that of South Australia they need heating in the winter. The usual way of heating the tank is with an aquarium heater. A 50w heater is suitable for a small Aquarium. If you have a room that never gets cold then the Fighting Fish can be kept there without an aquarium heater. A room that is only heated by the sun will get cold when the sun is not shining. This is not suitable.<br /><br />Some very small tanks are sold for fighting fish. These are suitable for places with a warm climate. In temperate areas they are not suitable for fighting fish in winter unless they can be kept in a place which does not get cold. Many of these tanks are too small to put a normal aquarium heater in.<br /><br />Breathing<br /><br />Fighting fish are anabantids. They and their relatives can breathe air as well as water. This means that they can live in much smaller aquariums than most fish. In the wild they sometimes live and even breed in very small bodies of water including the water filled hoof prints of a water buffalo. They are often also found in rice fields. They need to be able to get to the surface or they can drown. Although they can be kept in very small containers this is not an ideal way. Like other fish they are affected by water quality. A small tank is harder to keep clean than a larger one, and usually you cannot put a filter in.<br /><br />Food<br /><br />The Fighting fish is sometimes described as a carnivore. In my observation, it is an omnivore with a preference for animal based food. In an aquarium, I recommend that a good quality Betta food be used as the basic diet, and this should be varied with the addition of the occasional feeding of live food like mosquito larvae of daphnia. frozen food like blood worms are also good.<br /><br />Water<br /><br />Rainwater<br /><br />Rainwater is often used. Some people use it successfully, but not all rainwater is safe for fish. Rain, as it falls from the sky in Rural areas is generally good water. When it comes into contact with the roof and gutters and then stays in the rainwater tank with any leaves etc which have washed in, it picks up contaminants. Some of these are harmless, but others can kill fish. If rainwater is the only type of water available then you will need to use it. Apart from the obvious things like keeping your gutters clear and avoiding spraying near the house or if the wind is towards the house you can add a rainwater conditioner. This will add the salts that rainwater does not have. It will also neutralise some (but not all) of the possible contaminants.<br /><br />Mains Water<br /><br />If you are in an area with Chlorinated water, a water conditioner will get rid of the Chlorine. In areras which use Chloramine, ther conditioner will still work, but needs to be used at up to five times the normal rate.<br /><br />If the Ph of the water is adjusted to be less than 7.2 the ammonia from the Chloramine should not be dangerous.<br /><br />There are also some water conditioners which remove ammonia as well as Chlorine. I recommend the use of one of these.<br /><br />Filtered Tapwater<br /><br />Some domestic water filters which have carbon cartridges will remove most of the Chlorine and Chloramine. The filter cartridge needs to be in good condition. If you have a filter it is a good idea to use this water for your fish. However, because the filter may not remove all the Chlorine or Chloramine from the water, it is still a good idea to use a conditioner to be on the safe side.<br /><br />Spring Water<br /><br />Many types of spring water are suitable for fighting fish without any conditioner or modification. If it is too far from neutral you will need to adjust it.<br /><br />Ph<br /><br />Ph is a measure of acidity or alkalinity. A ph of 7 is neutral. Below 7 is acid and above 7 is alkaline. The ideal Ph for fighters is about 7.1, but they can take moderate variations from this. The Ph of water can change, so it is a good idea to check it regularly.<br /><br />Foods and feeding<br /><br />Like most fish, fighting fish are omnivores, in the wild they will eat any animal or vegetable food they can find. They prefer animal foods such as mosquito larvae (wrigglers) daphnia, etc. In an aquarium they will eat all normal types of aquarium foods, but seem to do better on a food designed for them. As with almost any animal a variety of food is welcomed by fighting fish. Do not overfeed!<br /><br />Aquariums and Companions<br /><br />One fighting fish without any other fish can be kept in a quite small tank, provided that it can be kept warm. Fighting fish are usually not an aggressive fish and can be kept in an aquarium with other peaceful fish of a similar size or smaller.<br /><br />These are a few of the many sorts of fish suitable as companions for fighting fish in a reasonable sized aquarium.<br /><br />Like nearly all fish, fighting fish will eat another fish if the fish is small enough to fit in its mouth. Generally a fighting fish can be kept with fish as small as neon tetras without trouble. However, the occasional fighting fish may learn to catch neons. I would suggest that in a confined space fighting fish should be by themselve. I know of at least two cases of a fighting fish which has been put in a bag with neons and has learned to eat them. Having learned, the fish is likely to continue to eat neons in an aquarium. Fish have quite good memories.<br /><br />Fighting fish are slow and have long fins. They are very vulnerable to fish that nip fins.<br /><br />Some of the fish that can be fin nippers and which I would not recommend as companions for fighting fish are Tiger Barbs, Red Eye Tetras, Serpae Tetras, Some Galaxies and Rosy Barbs.<br /><br />Another way of keeping fighting fish is to use one of the Betta containers. These come under several names, but are similar and allow several male fighters to be kept in one aquarium.<br /><br />Another, similar, way of keeping fighters is to use a breeding tank which floats in an aquarium. Normally these are use for breeding fish such as Guppies, but they can also be used for keeping (but not breeding) Fighting Fish.<br /><br />There are several other options for keeping fighting fish. There are Duo and a Trio Fighting Fish tank, as well as many types of custom ones. The better ones are big enough to put a small heater into one of the compartments. There is often enough conduction of heat between compartments to keep them all warm enough.<br /><br />Transporting fighting fish<br /><br />Normally fighters are transported in a plastic bag. It is important that there be some air (or Oxygen) above the water in the bag. The bag should not be allowed to get very cold or very hot in transport. It is better that if you are transporting a male fighter that no other fish is in with it.<br /><br />Life Span<br /><br />Siamese Fighting Fish are not very long lived. Their normal life span is about two years. The Male fighters normally on sale in shops are typically about nine months old, so if you have had a male fighter for a year, it is already old and could die of old age.<br /><br />Female fighters are usually about five months old when sold.<br /><br />Breeding Fighting Fish<br /><br />The Siamese fighter is not one of the easiest fish to breed. It is considered to be a medium difficulty fish. Full instructions on breeding this fish would take up much more space than this fact sheet, but since I am frequently asked about breeding this fish, I will attempt to give a very brief description of breeding. Before the fish can breed they need to be in good condition; both the male and the female need to be well fed for sometime beforehand. An increase in temperature will sometimes induce the male to build his nest.<br /><br />After the male has built his nest, you can attempt to put a female in with him. Watch them! It is not unusual for one of them to attack and try to kill the other. It is not always the male that tries to kill the female.<br /><br />The fighting fish is a nest breeder. The male builds a nest of bubbles on the surface of the water.<br /><br />Then he entices a female to go under the nest with him. They wrap their bodies round each other, and the female releases her eggs while the male releases his sperm to fertilise them.<br /><br />After that the female sinks down in a sort of stupor while the male quickly picks up the eggs in his mouth and put them in the nest. If he has not finished before the female recovers, she starts eating the eggs. This process will be repeated until the female has no eggs left. The male then chases her away. She should be removed.<br /><br />If there is another female available, in some cases, a male will then induce her to go under the nest as well and he will raise a bunch of fry from the eggs of both females, but you are increasing the danger of problems by having two or more females in while breeding.<br /><br />The male guards the nest while the eggs hatch. He also guards the newly hatched babies until they are free swimming. After that he will eat them unless he is separated from them.<br /><br />Raising Young Fighters<br /><br />If you succeed in getting as far as having free swimming baby fighters, now you have the more difficult part. The babies are very small. You need reasonably good eyesight even to see them.<br /><br />They will need tiny food. In the wild they would be eating things like protozoans. These are single celled organisms usually too small to see without magnification, but much bigger than bacteria. In the aquarium hobby these are usually called infusoria. Some of these will be present in nearly all aquariums, but there will probably not be enough for the babies.<br /><br />There are ways of making cultures rich in infusoria, but this is a big subject in itself. There are also fry foods made by many companies. Fighting fish will need the finest ones at first.<br /><br />If you succeed in getting them growing at first, they will soon be big enough to eat larger fry food. At all stages, fighting fish benefit from some live food of suitable size. I found that this individual described this well on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbestwirelesssurroundsoundsystem.com%2F275%2Fsurround-sound-hdtv-ps3-1-hdmi%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://bestwirelesssurroundsoundsystem.com/275/surround-sound-hdtv-ps3-1-hdmi/</a>  article.<br /><br />At around six weeks old the baby's accessory breathing organ; the 'labyrinth' starts working. At this stage it will be necessary to have a small stream of air from an air stone to break up any surface film because the babies might not be strong enough to penetrate it to get air.<br /><br />The males and females are normally separated as soon as they can be distinguished, with the males going into containers by themselves.<br /><br />Types of fighting fish<br /><br />The wild fighting fish have much shorter fins than the aquarium ones. When they were bred in Thailand for fighting, colour varieties were developed, but fins were not selected for in the modem sense. The long and fancy fins of the present fighting fish are a comparatively recent development. Fighting fish are bred in many places. A lot of the fighting fish sold in Australia are bred in Singapore. Fighting fish come in many colours including blue, red, purple, white, yellow and black.<br /><br />Many different fin types have also been developed, including the crown tail, the half moon the double tail and the delta tail.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a210ec2ec2a00e65cedfb7c5e35e646d" url=""><![CDATA[Chess Software for Improving Your Skills<br/><br/>Most people who play chess find it to be somewhat addictive, so it's not a surprise that chess software for improving your skills is popular. Chess is a game of strategy and focus, and while some games are a game of luck where practice doesn't have the possibility of improving your game, practicing chess can really have some positive effects on your game, including your strategy and focus alike. There are a number of chess software programs for improving your skills available, and if you are considering using them, here are a few ways you can expect to benefit:<br /><br />Strategy<br /><br />Chess is absolutely a game of strategy. It involves developing a good plan of attack for taking your opponent's pieces, setting a trap for capture of the King, and more. It also involves developing a strategy for defending your own King and outlasting the other player. When you use chess software for improving your skills, you will find that you can more fully develop your own strategy for the game, which improves your likelihood of triumphing during game play. I found that this blog demonstrated this well on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbikereviewshack.com%2F436%2Fwethepeople-2010-rear-brake%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://bikereviewshack.com/436/wethepeople-2010-rear-brake/</a>  blog post.<br /><br />Thinking Ahead<br /><br />Another area where chess software for improving your skills can really help you is by developing your ability to think ahead. The game requires you to really think out your own moves, and the farther out you can plan your moves, the more successful you will be in the game. More than that, however, is the ability to try to think ahead and determine where your opponent will move. You will find that the better you get at anticipating your opponent's moves, the more likely you will be able to plan great moves of your own.<br /><br />Focus<br /><br />Adults and kids alike often have a difficult time focusing on anything for more than a few minutes. We all do live in a fast-paced world where the concept of multitasking and dividing your focus is honored and revered, but sometimes you really need to focus on one specific thing in life, and chess is a game that can help you learn how to do that. Through the use of software, you will get repetitive practice at focusing on the game without distractions, and this can help you to improve your own game as well as improve other areas of your life, too If you love to place chess, you should absolutely spend some extra time practicing the game.<br /><br />Opponents to play against are not always around, and when they are, they may not be ready to play whenever you are. There are some fabulous software programs available that can help you find a great partner to play with at any time, and this is a partner who can play at your level to give you the challenge you really want and need. You can play whenever you want and for however long you want without worry about dealing with someone else's schedule. What's more, chess software for improving your skills can help you to become a better player and can help you improve life skills outside of the game, too.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7ec853508285864703d81517b51d2747" url=""><![CDATA[How to Make Time For Family Fun Time<br/><br/>In the past, it was not uncommon for many American families to have one special night. This night might have been referred to as game night or movie night. For most American households, it appears as if these days are gone. With long work hours, lots of homework, and hectic sports schedules, more families are finding it difficult to sit down and spend some quality time together. If you know alto well what I am talking about, continue reading on for some helpful tips. It sounds silly, but these tips will help you make time for family time.<br /><br />Mark As Much As You Can on a Calendar: Of course, if your daughter comes home with a big book report that must be finished in 3-days, this may toss your calendar schedule off a bit. However, you want to write all business meetings, travels, sport schedules, and more on this calendar. At the beginning of a week, you may notice an evening or even a few hours that your family has free. This is your quality time. I found that this weblog demonstrated this well on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fhometheaterpad.com%2F162%2Fconnecting-sky-hd-box-home-cinema-normal-audio-cables-redwhite%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://hometheaterpad.com/162/connecting-sky-hd-box-home-cinema-normal-audio-cables-redwhite/</a>  post.<br /><br />Don't Have a Set Night: Now, lots of families like to pick a night and stick with it. But, things happen. Your husband may have to work later than normal, your teenager daughter may have a last minute soccer practice scheduled, and so forth. When something interrupts your weekly family fun night, you are less likely to reschedule it. You are just likely to cancel. Pretty soon, this may become a habit. Instead, use the above mentioned calendar approach. Choose a day at the beginning of the week that looks less hectic for your family.<br /><br />Make Family Fun Time Fun: When you have to work, you have to work. When your teenager son has football practice, he has football practice. However, there are some cases where family fun time gets put off because it doesn't seem like much fun. Someone in the family could think of something better to do so they create a reason to avoid this family bonding. This is more likely to happen with a teenager. However, when you actually make family fun time fun, watch as they enjoy themselves. This may be putting away the board games for the night and opting for the Wii console instead or letting your child pick the movie for movie night.<br /><br />In short, it may seem like so much trouble to go through just to schedule a family fun night. However, it is important. This is your chance to not only do something fun with the ones you love, but it is also a chance to talk and catch-up. Since life is hectic for individuals of all ages, you are sure to have lots of catching up to do.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="303948f096a3ee62cf4af2038b1e64f2" url=""><![CDATA[Successful Birthday Party Entertainment For Your Two Year Ol<br/><br/>So your baby is growing up and you face a birthday party with a child who is expert at tantrums and you have visions of all the guests ( being two years old or thereabouts ) having tantrums all at once! The vision has you filled with dread.<br /><br />It's probably too early to play traditional party games at your party. They take a certain degree of reason to be considered successful. Pass the Parcel at a two year old birthday party will probably result in a few tears as 'sharing' is probably not one of a two year old's best skills. They understand that in Pass the Parcel you get a prize if you have the parcel, so hold on to it and refuse to let it go, music or no music. It's all pretty understandable.<br /><br />If you are going to play musical bumps/statues, understand that this age group will not understand the concept of being 'OUT' so be prepared to act like the silly grown up and not be able to see who is out. Basically it's just an excuse to dance to some music. You will have to lead the statues quite visually, giving the children ideas of what an elephant, etc will look like when the music stops so expect to make some funny faces all in the name of fun.<br /><br />Soft play toys and/or a bouncy castle and/or ball pool is probably a better idea than party games at this age. If your budget doesn't stretch to hiring out this equipment, don't despair. A really nice alternative is to play some simple circle games where everyone is a winner and no one is out or gets a prize. ( Sometimes 'winning' a prize can be counterproductive and end in tears or with tantrums of 'don't want that, I want what Johnny has'.)<br /><br />CIRCLE GAMES: Fun where everyone is a winner.<br /><br />Ring a Ring o' Rosies is a lovely simple traditional game and is also a VERY useful way of getting the children into a circle for a picnic tea round a cloth or at any time when you require them to sit in a circle. Have you ever tried herding reluctant two year old's into a circle before? It sounds simple enough but can take a lot of time. Just say we're going to play 'Ring a Ring o' Rosies' and hold out your hands to invite children and mummies /daddies to play. Once everyone is holding hands, the parents can encourage the children to hold hands with each other once the confidence has grown, and then you can start to play:<br /><br />Ring a Ring O' Rosies <br /><br />The Farmer's in the Dell <br /><br />The Hokey Cokey<br /><br />By the time you have completed this, I can guarantee you will most probably collapse in a red faced satisfied heap on the floor. Who needs a gym subscription when you have children?<br /><br />Puppets are great for two years old parties. Toddlers are able to focus on a more formal puppet show by this stage. An hour's session should suffice, but do remember that sometimes young children require a little bit of 'get to know you' time before they get into their groove. If you would like support with your party, maybe a full two hour party with an entertainer wouldn't be a bad investment for peace of mind. Again, the secret is KEEP IT SIMPLE. Throwing too much at children of this age only serves to confuse them and stress them out. Let them focus on one thing at a time.<br /><br />For minimum tantrums, keep the present opening till the end of the party when the other guests have left. Too many times I've seen very upset party people crying because their friend played with their new toy. Remember sharing isn't easy. This is a social skill that takes practice and time. I like to impress on boys and girls that sharing is what 'big boys and girls' do. We all know how little children strive to become big boys and girls, a little impetus to learn to share never harmed anyone! So in conclusion, for a successful toddler party: I found that this person described this well on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsofasreviews.com%2Fsew-puff-sleeves-answers%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://sofasreviews.com/sew-puff-sleeves-answers/</a>  post.<br /><br />Understand that sharing isn't going to be easy. Pass the Parcel isn't an ideal game for this age group.<br />Keep things simple; have one form of entertainment at a time.<br />Stay away from competitive games, two year old's are simply too young to understand being 'out'.<br />Involve the parents, they are key to a great party.<br />Familiarity and repetition are your best friend; use songs and games they already know.<br />Keep present opening until the end after the guests have left.<br />Tidy away any favourite toys. Birthday child will not appreciate sharing their special toy with others.<br />If all else fails hire a professional. Check first though that they cater for under 3's, many don't.<br /><br />So that's it. Have a very happy birthday party, stress free and hopefully free of tantrums.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8bccc4c8c5d17a77d262c8a146da7b84" url=""><![CDATA[John Deere Birthday Party Theme Ideas<br/><br/>Grown-ups just love the John Deere tractors because they are stable, reliable and a well known brand. Children on the other-hand also happen to love the John Deere children's stories, many love Allie Gator, Danny Dozer and of course Johnny Tractor, they are tractors that go on many adventures and help people out. They put up buildings, plow through hay and even play around a little. It is a wonderful way to make kids learn about how the real tractors work and help people.<br /><br />Many children around the world love the books and they also love the characters. They are friendly and very easy to get along with and that is why children absolutely love them. If your child happens to love John Deere books they will adore you for throwing them a John Deere birthday party! They can drive around in toy tractors and pretend to be Danny Dozer or Johnny tractor. I found that this blogger showed this smartly on this  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frowingmachinesreviews.net%2Fgood-weight-lossmanagement-routine%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://rowingmachinesreviews.net/good-weight-lossmanagement-routine/</a>  web site.<br /><br />Planning the ultimate birthday party does not only involve getting the right birthday party supplies or should I say John Deere party supplies, it will start with planning. When planning for a John Deere party you have to first think about the venue, this is very important as this will be a good indicator of how many birthday party supplies you will be needing and how big the items should be. Next you have to think about the guest list as this will also be a good indicator of how many of your John Deere party supplies and party giveaways you should be preparing.<br /><br />After you have your list done, you should get on with ordering your party items and John Deer party supplies are specialty party items and can be found in specialty party shops usually. It is most advisable to purchase your birthday party supplies from one source as you might be able to work out a discount. Returns and repeat orders will also be more convenient this way and it make your life just a little bit easier when planning the party.<br /><br />Most importantly you would want to make sure that your child would like to have a party like this, you may try to ask his or her best friend to get an idea of what he or she really wants, especially if you are planning a surprise party. You also must be attentive to what your child needs and what makes them happy as this is what being a parent is all about.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e091e194886ed30b9ab5d8af8aeab348" url=""><![CDATA[PS3 Yellow Light Flashing - What Does It Mean And What Are M<br/><br/>If you have the yellow light flashing on the power button of your PS3 console then unfortunately it means that your console has overheated internally and you will need to get it repaired.<br /><br />Now when I tell most people this they say:<br /><br />&quot;Wait! My PS3 feels cool so how can it be overheating?&quot;<br /><br />Well it is all down to internal overheating as oppose to external so you will not normally feel the heat by placing your hand on the top of the console.<br /><br />The motherboard and in particular 2 important chips are important for the running and upkeep of your console and it is these parts that have suffered too much heat.<br /><br />You can have other parts of the motherboard overheat as well but if you get this you will not get the yellow light of death you will most likely get freezing up or your games not playing.<br /><br /><strong>So how do you fix it?</strong><br /><br />Well you have 2 choices and the first more standard way is to send it in and they will fix and perform the repair work for you. I found that this blogger showed this nicely on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Fza2RhdGluZ2V4cGVydHMuY29tLzE1MjUvY2hyaXN0aWFuLXRlZW5hZ2UtZGF0aW5nLXNjYW5kYWxvdXMv" target="_blank">Rudolph Mages</a> weblog.<br /><br />This can take about 4 weeks and then on top of that you will have a repair fee to pay of about $150.<br /><br />The only other way that you can get it fixed aside from using a third party company is to fix it yourself using one of these PS3 Repair guides that you may have seen.<br /><br />Now they can actually work for you but you need to make sure that you get one with a preview video, or at least so you can get some idea of how the repair guide will work.<br /><br />There are some good ones out there but of course you do not want to have to be a rocket scientist in order to use one.<br /><br />As long as you make sure that you get a guarantee and make contact before you go ahead with it you will be able to make a better decision.<br /><br />My advice is if you don't mind the wait just send it back in, however if you feel that you cannot wait to get your PS3 fixed then a guide might be the only choice left for you.<br /><br />I hope this article has told you a bit more about what causes the YLOD and given you a bit more info about how you can get back to gaming.<br /><br />Good Luck!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d8b41f7ea93e61168851dd97ca316e3" url=""><![CDATA[How to Fix PS3 Flashing Red Light - Repair Your PlayStation<br/><br/>Looking for a way on how to fix the ps3 flashing red light error? Did you just play your favorite game and in all of a sudden your PlayStation 3 gets a strange flashing red light? If you are looking for a way to fix this, than you're on the right address! Here you will find out what actions you have to take so you can play your favorite game on your PS3 again, today!<br /><br />In order to fix the RLOD error on your PS3, you should try to do these 3 things.<br /><br />1 - Restart your console.<br />&lt;br&gt;2 - Take out all cables, and plug them back in.<br />&lt;br&gt;3 - Take out the hard-drive, and place it back in your PS3 console.<br /><br />If these 3 tips didn't help you to fix your PS3 red light error, then it's high likely that you need to open up your console, and fix the problem from within. I really can't help you with that, because you'll need step by step instructions that's coming along with either videos or pictures. But, you've got 3 options to get your hardware problems solved. I found that this site demonstrated this simply on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RydW1raXRzcmV2aWV3cy5jb20vcGFpbnRpbmctcGljdHVyZS1yZXByZXNlbnRzLw__" target="_blank">Lacie Pembrook</a> weblog.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;There Are 3 Ways To Fix Your PS3 Red Light Problems.&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;1)&lt;/b&gt; If you don't have a clue of how to fix your PS3 flashing red light by yourself, you could send your PS3 back to Sony and let them figure out how to repair the problem. This is a pretty time taking way of fixing your ps3 because it could take up to 1 month before you will get your console back. And if your warranty has been expired, you have to pay $150,-<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;2)&lt;/b&gt; Take your PS3 to your local repair shop and let them fix it. Also, this might sounds like a good idea, but trust me, this only costs you a fortune and it takes up to 2 weeks. Another downside of this is that they can't guarantee that your PlayStation 3 will be fixed. The only one who can guarantee that it will be fixed, is you! The only thing you need to know, is how to fix ps3 flashing red light problem.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;3)&lt;/b&gt; Fix your PlayStation 3 by yourself. If you don't know how to fix ps3 flashing red light, than it's no problem. We will teach it to you! It's not hard, it's not expensive and it's not time consuming. In matter of fact, I know that you can fix your PS3 within this hour!<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;But, What's The Best Option To Fix Your Ps3 Red Flashing Light Error?&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Want to know how to fix PS3 flashing red light? Want to take the challenge to do it by yourself? First of all, why should you let Sony or a repair shop do it for you? They waste your time and money which you could better spend into gaming.. Right?!<br /><br />To fix your PlayStation 3 by yourself, I'd recommend that you take a PS3 red light repair guide. This guide will tell you step by step with detailed instructions and pictures how to fix your PS3 problems. It also contains bonuses for after your reparation.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="179fc41de12851689818eb32e47b6e03" url=""><![CDATA[How to Fix PS3 Flashing Red Light - Repair Your PlayStation<br/><br/>Looking for a way on how to fix the ps3 flashing red light error? Did you just play your favorite game and in all of a sudden your PlayStation 3 gets a strange flashing red light? If you are looking for a way to fix this, than you're on the right address! Here you will find out what actions you have to take so you can play your favorite game on your PS3 again, today!<br /><br />In order to fix the RLOD error on your PS3, you should try to do these 3 things.<br /><br />1 - Restart your console.<br />&lt;br&gt;2 - Take out all cables, and plug them back in.<br />&lt;br&gt;3 - Take out the hard-drive, and place it back in your PS3 console.<br /><br />If these 3 tips didn't help you to fix your PS3 red light error, then it's high likely that you need to open up your console, and fix the problem from within. I really can't help you with that, because you'll need step by step instructions that's coming along with either videos or pictures. But, you've got 3 options to get your hardware problems solved. I found that this person demonstrated this nicely on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2tpdGNoZW5rbml2ZXNyZXZpZXdzLm5ldC81NDAvcmVhZC1yZXN1bWUtd29udC1jYWxsLw__" target="_blank">Lyman Taualii</a> weblog.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;There Are 3 Ways To Fix Your PS3 Red Light Problems.&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;1)&lt;/b&gt; If you don't have a clue of how to fix your PS3 flashing red light by yourself, you could send your PS3 back to Sony and let them figure out how to repair the problem. This is a pretty time taking way of fixing your ps3 because it could take up to 1 month before you will get your console back. And if your warranty has been expired, you have to pay $150,-<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;2)&lt;/b&gt; Take your PS3 to your local repair shop and let them fix it. Also, this might sounds like a good idea, but trust me, this only costs you a fortune and it takes up to 2 weeks. Another downside of this is that they can't guarantee that your PlayStation 3 will be fixed. The only one who can guarantee that it will be fixed, is you! The only thing you need to know, is how to fix ps3 flashing red light problem.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;3)&lt;/b&gt; Fix your PlayStation 3 by yourself. If you don't know how to fix ps3 flashing red light, than it's no problem. We will teach it to you! It's not hard, it's not expensive and it's not time consuming. In matter of fact, I know that you can fix your PS3 within this hour!<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;But, What's The Best Option To Fix Your Ps3 Red Flashing Light Error?&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Want to know how to fix PS3 flashing red light? Want to take the challenge to do it by yourself? First of all, why should you let Sony or a repair shop do it for you? They waste your time and money which you could better spend into gaming.. Right?!<br /><br />To fix your PlayStation 3 by yourself, I'd recommend that you take a PS3 red light repair guide. This guide will tell you step by step with detailed instructions and pictures how to fix your PS3 problems. It also contains bonuses for after your reparation.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7c795f983e989c22edead09ae1ad2fa4" url=""><![CDATA[Leonardo Da Vinci, A Many-Sided Genius<br/><br/>Leonardo da Vinci, the genius of the Italian Renaissance was born in the town of Vinci; his birth is not known with accuracy but it is assumed he was born in 1452.<br /><br />Leonardo's achievements in so many different areas made him an outstanding human being: scientist, painter, philosopher, draughtsman, writer, botanist, inventor; there is hardly a branch of human learning to which he did not at one time or another give his eager attention. He was also interested in architecture, art-sculpture, mathematics, engineering and music; he was in fact a many-sided genius.<br /><br />Considered one of the greatest painters of all time and definitely the most talented person ever to have lived; in this article we will be mainly focus on two of his greatest masterpieces: &quot;The Last Supper&quot; and the &quot;Mona Lisa&quot;.<br /><br />&lt;u&gt;<strong>The Last Supper</strong>&lt;/u&gt;: Between 1496 and 1498 Leonardo painted this masterpiece, however it was originally executed in tempera on a badly prepared stucco ground and began to deteriorate a few years after its completion; it was restored on several occasions but it was not until 1908 that Professor Cavenaghi has, in opinion of experts, preserved it from further injury. I found that this website explained this incredibly on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BsZWFzZWFza2l0LmNvbS80MTkxL3BlcnNvbmFsLWJlbG9uZ2luZ3MtY3Jhc2gtcGVydGFpbmluZy1pbnN1cmFuY2Uv" target="_blank">Matt Chmelik</a> weblog.<br /><br />The Painting represents the last meal that Jesus had with the Apostles before he was betrayed, captured and killed. Leonardo successfully captured the betray effect in the painting and the gestures of the disciples reveal their temperaments, passions and shock by the realisation that there is a traitor in the group.<br /><br /><strong>&lt;u&gt;The Mona Lisa&lt;/u&gt;</strong>: Once back in Florence, Leonardo started working on the Portrait of &lt;em&gt;Mona Lisa&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;La&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Joconde &lt;/em&gt;by which the portrait is officially known in the Louvre Museum. It is assumed that he started working on the portrait in 1501 and it was finally completed in 1504; even when the completion of the most famous painting in the world took around four years, Leonardo did not paint it for Francesco and Lisa del Giocondo (They commissioned the painting); he painted it for the posterity; the enigmatic Mona Lisa looks like if she is alive and observing us from any angle you look at the painting.<br /><br />An extract of Vasari's eulogy of this portrait clearly reflects the admiration of this work: &quot;...The nose, with its beautiful and delicately roseate nostrils, might be easily believed to be alive; the mouth, admirable in its outline, the rose-tints of their colour with those of the face, in the utmost perfection, and the carnation of the cheek does not appear to be painted, but truly flesh and blood...&quot;<br /><br />A peck of pigment near the left elbow was damaged in 1956 when a young Bolivian named Ugo Unganza Villegas threw a rock at it.<br /><br />On the 22 May 1519, Leonardo da Vinci died, leaving us with an astonishing legacy of art and invention; he will leave forever as the &lt;em&gt;Universal genius &lt;/em&gt;of all time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24ba115ec6a3d982ec5d97c59769ec20" url=""><![CDATA[How to Draw Like Leonardo Da Vinci - The Bones and Muscles o<br/><br/>Renowned multitalented genius, Leonardo da Vinci was born in Italy in the year 1452. His wide-ranging interests spanned from various faculties of science to fine arts and literature. Throughout his career, he continued making his mark as an undisputed leader in drawing &amp; painting, while honing his skills in applied sciences. His love for pencil &amp; ink sketching and study of human body crystallized under his mentor, Andrea del Verrocchio in the form of a series of anatomical drawings.<br /><br />Over a span of about one year, between 1510 and 1511, Leonardo da Vinci created almost 200 works in collaboration with Dr. Marcantonio della Torre. Recreating these master works is indeed a challenge, where a lot of patience and diligence is required. The following guide will help you understand how to draw the anatomy of calf in his style:<br /><br />&amp;bull; Reference. Arranging for a reference picture may not be an easy task. However, the understanding that the significant calf muscle drawings were created in 1510 can help sort an appropriate picture. The internet has several images on the subject. Alternatively, specialized books or journals may be referred to.<br />&lt;br&gt;&amp;bull; Style. Apart from separate diagrams for bone structure and muscle placements, Leonardo da Vinci made coherent 'layered' structures highlighting both, bones &amp; muscles. He usually ventured in series, beginning skeletal figures, veins &amp; arteries, nerves &amp; membranes, ligaments &amp; tendons, and finally outer structures with skin. Some of the diagrams are drawn as a longitudinal section of the body parts, revealing the key bone &amp; muscles, alike. You may choose to draw a particular view of the calf or a series of sketches. I found that this individual explained this really well on this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NvZmFzcmV2aWV3cy5jb20vYW5zd2Vycy1sZWF2ZS1zZWFsZWQtaWtlYS1ib3gtZnVybml0dXJlLWdhcmFnZS1idWdzLWVhdC1jYXJib2FyZC1mdXJuaXR1cmUv" target="_blank">Alba Kawashima</a> post.<br />&lt;br&gt;&amp;bull; Bones. Creating a very well defined basic frame of bones may not be feasible. Nevertheless, you may use straight lines to mark the placement and structure of the bones. The calf consists of primarily the Tibia and Fibula bones, placed laterally. Fibula is the thinnest of the long bones of the human skeleton and is situated laterally besides Tibia. The latter is a visibly thicker and stronger calf bone, a key tool in the movement of the lower legs. Unlike Tibia, Fibula does not form a part of the knee joint. Give due consideration to the relative width and positioning of the two bones.<br />&lt;br&gt;&amp;bull; Muscles. Leonardo da Vinci was particularly fascinated by the compound muscles of the calf region. His drawings elaborately bring out the triceps of this portion and should be particularly significant from the drawing point of view. The powerful soleus and gastrocnemius (superficially placed) muscles form the triceps, known as the calf muscles. It is not possible to create the calf area without showing the termination of its bones and muscles at the back portion of the foot. The deeply situated muscles associated with the calf area are flexor hallucis longus, flexor digitorum longus (largest and strongest deep muscle), and tibialis posterior (principal stabilizing muscle).<br /><br />The placement of these bones, muscles, nerves, and tendons can be depicted in parts, like one of the complex layered diagrams of da Vinci or as a longitudinal section of the entire length of the calf.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c5d4702fbc451d6c92cf35d54eaffe36" url=""><![CDATA[Shake Weight Review - Does Shake Weight Work?<br/><br/>One fitness product that has become a center of media attention recently is the Shake Weight. This is a hand-held dumbbell like weight with a spring on either end that you can shake. The claim is that this can help women get that lean, toned, un-bulky look to their arms and shoulders.<br /><br />The Shake Weight became famous after being mentioned on several TV shows, most notably the Ellen Degeneress show. I believe that this site explained this smartly on the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGFpbGFuZG11YXljYW1wLmNvbS9tb3VudGFpbi1iaWtlLXJlbnRhbA__" target="_blank">muaythai thailand</a>  webpage.Most of the TV time this product got was slightly on the comic side due to the slightly suggestive infomercial, but this says nothing about the quality and effectiveness of the product itself, so I am going to disregard it for the purposes of this article.<br /><br />Here are the claims of the Shake Weight:<br />&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The Shake Weight works with a method called Dynamic Inertia in which you work your muscles by shaking the weight instead of lifting it.&lt;/li&gt;<br /> &lt;li&gt;That a scientific study showed that this product is more effective than regular weight training in many aspects. I tried to find reference to the study on their website but couldn't so I don't know who conducted this research and what the exact findings were.&lt;/li&gt;<br /> &lt;li&gt;That you can get terrific results in just 6 minutes a day.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;I don't know anything about Dynamic Inertia as this is a concept that I believe was born with the invention of the Shake Weight. Shaking an object certainly works the muscles, of that there is no doubt. Even shaking your arms in front of you without nothing in them does produce some stimulation.<br /><br />Whether this stimulation is more effective than traditional weight lifting is an open question. This is something that's very hard to measure as weight training can be done in so many fashions and variations that a simple comparison is just not accurate.<br /><br />There is one claim which I doubt is true and that refers to how the Shake Weight can help women get that long muscle growth instead of the bulky one which men prefer. The infomercial suggests that using traditional weight training machines and dumbbells is what causes bulky muscle growth.<br /><br />The real cause is genetics and the way you workout. Most women aren't built, genetically, to bulk up. They will have to train with very heavy weights and work extremely hard to get the bulky look. You can achieve a long, more feminine, muscle tone with dumbbells and machines. There is nothing wrong with them.<br /><br />So, the Shake Weight may be a fun product to use, and it certainly be used at home pretty easily, but it's not better than dumbbells in producing lean muscle growth. That being said, this product does look like a lot of fun and may prove to be a new way to workout.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="94545f7a95fce6239bca2b0d7a4bcb99" url=""><![CDATA[How To Camp<br/><br/><strong>Get Started</strong><br /><br />You are going to need some equipment. If you will not camp often, check with friends and see what you can borrow. Follow that by checking craigslist and eBay for items if time allows. Lastly purchase your items after doing a little research online. I see you are off to a good start there! You found this article. This article is written for the beginner headed to a campsite where the car will be nearby.<br /><br /><strong>Packing List</strong><br /><br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Tent&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Sleeping Bag&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Lighting&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Food&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Water&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Cooking Equipment&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;First Aid Kit&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Clothing&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Knife&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Rain gear&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br /><br /><strong>Breaking down gear</strong><br /><br /><strong>Tent</strong><br /><br />Tents are sized by how many sleeping bags will fit in them. Don't confuse this with double beds or cots. Add a couple sizes up to accommodate your gear. So if you are sharing a tent with someone, then I recommend a four person tent to accommodate your personal gear. This is by no means a hard and fast rule. Check the dimension advertised for the tent and use your own preferences. You definitely would not want to back an overly big tent if you are backpacking and have to carry it. Also make sure the seams are double stitched and the fly goes all the way to the ground for great rain protection.<br /><br /><strong>Sleeping Bag</strong><br /><br />Sleeping bags come in two styles; Mummy bags for cold weather and Rectangular for standard camping. Also they are rate in degrees A 10 degree bag should allow a person to not feel cold in 10 degree and warmer weather. You can increase this rating by wearing more clothes to bed or by using a bag liner like a fleece. This can increase the temperature rating by 10 degrees or more. So a 30 degree bag is good down to 20 degrees with a fleece liner. But, people are affected by the cold differently so you will need to fine tune this to suit your needs.<br /><br /><strong>Lighting</strong><br /><br />You should bring a lantern to light your campsite and a headlamp for hiking or working around camp. A lantern can be battery, gas or propane powered.<br /><br /><strong>Food and Water</strong><br /><br />Make sure you know if your campsite will have water nearby. Take a 5 gallon collapsable water container and a water bottle you can keep on you during warm months. For food check out some recipes online for ideas. Look into foil packs they are quick, easy and delicious. And don't forget the staple s'mores.<br /><br /><strong>Cooking Equipment</strong><br /><br />You can cook over the fire, use the pit at the campsite if available or bring a stove. I found that this blogger showed this simply on the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoYWlsYW5kbXVheWNhbXAuY29tL2ZpdG5lc3MtdHJhaW5pbmc_" target="_blank">thailand muay Camp</a> web post.Camping stoves can be propane or gas powered. Propane is easiest to operate. Consider bringing a dutch over to do a cobbler in. This will also require you bring some charcoal. Don't forget clean up! Bring some camp suds, two wash bins and a drying rack. Heat water on the stove for the two bins. One is for wash and the other for rinse. Never cook food near your tents and do not take food into your tents. Otherwise, prepare for visitors.<br /><br /><strong>First Aid Kit</strong><br /><br />Make sure you have a good stocked first aid kit with you. Have bandages, pain killers, neosporin, and mole skin for blisters. Add to it from there.<br /><br /><strong>Clothing</strong><br /><br />You won't change clothes at camp like you do at home so don't bring your dresser. Do bring some clean dry sleeping clothes to change into at night. Never go to bed with the socks you wore all day, it will make your feet cold at night and can lead to funky feet.<br /><br /><strong>Knife</strong><br /><br />Now that's a knife! Just a good sharp pocket knife will suffice. Sharp is key here. A dull knife is way more dangerous than a sharp one. Make sure it is a quality knife with a good strong locking blade that will not slip.<br /><br /><strong>Rain gear</strong><br /><br />Be prepared for inclement weather. A nice rain jacket or poncho can improve the experience of enduring some rain while working around camp. Consider a dining fly big enough to cover you eating area. the 10 x 10 popup shades work great.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d5317e8dd8a76d6bbfff1f9a9f8d7810" url=""><![CDATA[Flour Enrichment - What, When, Why<br/><br/>Two main goals in milling wheat flour are:<br />&lt;br&gt;&lt;ol&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Separating as much endosperm as possible from bran and germ in wheat berries<br /><br />&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Turning separating endosperm into fine flour<br />&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ol&gt;<br /><br />Unfortunately, this process also inadvertently removes many natural and valuable vitamins, minerals, dietary fibers.<br /><br />Lacking these essential nutrients in daily diets makes people very susceptible to diseases such as beriberi and pellagra.Many <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3JvYWRiaWtlcnJldmlld3MuY29tLw__" target="_blank">beats</a> irth defects are also linked to nutrient deficiency.<br /><br />In response to this problem, the Food and Drug Administration began, in 1941, to encourage millers to enrich freshly milled or &quot;green&quot; flour with iron, thiamin, riboflavin, niacin, and folic acid. The last four vitamins are also known as vitamin B. The recommended amount added to white flour should be equal to or exceed the amount in wheat flour.<br /><br />Adding back some of the lost nutrients is only one form of flour enrichment. Natural aging is another. The purpose of aging freshly milled or &quot;green&quot; flour is to improve dough handling and ultimately quality of baked goods.<br /><br />To many millers, this process is economically unfavorable and time consuming with inconsistent result. It depends on oxygen in air to perform two functions:<br />&lt;br&gt;&lt;ol&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Whitening flour by changing chemical structure of a flour pigment known as carotenoid<br /><br />&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Strengthening gluten forming proteins, glutenin and gliadin. This ultimately results in better volume and finer crumb in breads<br />&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ol&gt;<br /><br />Because natural aging does have its disadvantages, many millers instead like to add chemical or maturing additives such as potassium bromate or ascorbic acid to &quot;green&quot; flour.<br /><br />Types of baked goods also determine, to some extent, a preferred additive for flour. Since bread baking requires strong flour, potassium bromate is added to flour used for this purpose.<br /><br />On the other hand, cake flour does not need strong gluten formation, but its starch must be able to absorb moisture quickly. Therefore, chlorine is added to whiten flour and weaken gluten proteins.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="97bd34636cb83e2df1e46d38e1348620" url=""><![CDATA[680 FICO Scores Are Now Considered Just Okay<br/><br/>That is the new target score. Even though a 580 score may still barely qualify, over 680 is where the most favorable rates and terms are.<br /><br />Here is why:<br /><br />Conforming rates and/or fees have added on for scores under 680. These fees range from &amp;frac34; of a point to over 2% if the loan-to-value is over 70% of the purchase price. What does that mean? Well it means that buyers could pay as much as over $6,000.00 more in upfront fees on a 300,000 mortgage than a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvbWV0aGVhdGVycGFkLmNvbS8yMS9ob21lLXRoZWF0ZXItbGlnaHRpbmctcmVjb21tZW5kLw__" target="_blank">ok</a> with a credit score over 680. Think that could break a deal? Not to mention that the lower the score goes, the higher the rates get. So not only are they going to pay more upfront, they will also pay more per month. The difference between a 620 score and a 720 can be the difference between a $300,000 and a $335,000 home for the same payment.<br /><br />Also FHA has just initiated &quot;Risk based&quot; pricing as well. The upfront FHA fee will be substantially more for lower credit scores (under 680) and so will the monthly MI premiums. Once again, when the amount of money upfront necessary to fund the loan increases and the monthly payments increase the harder it is for the client to obtain favorable rates and terms, if a loan is possible at all.<br /><br />What is necessary in today's market place is mortgage professionals who can help clients obtain favorable rates and terms while educating them about how to understand and manage their credit scores effectively. There is no reason for anyone to be a &quot;credit score victim&quot;. A client's entire monthly budget is affected by their credit score. It has everything to do with the rates and terms they get on everything they finance from credit cards, auto and truck loans, lines of credit, any installment loan, insurance premiums and even possible employment. (75% of fortune 500 companies' check credit report prior to making a hiring decision and last year there was a 55% increase of employers checking). These can have a huge effect on the debt-to-income ratios when it comes time to obtain a mortgage. And the lenders have set that bar lower now than it has been in the past. Making few exceptions for DTI's that exceed 43% total expense ratio.<br /><br />So what does all of this mean? Well, the lenders have money to loan and for great borrowers, it means they will have little problem obtaining financing. But what about the other 80% that don't fall into the &quot;great&quot; category? Help them get there. Make sure you have mortgage professionals who can help educate clients about how to maintain credit scores so they can be &quot;great&quot;. Everyone wins!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>