<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="11">
		<document id="9a02007004c7c61a4f0cd60fb00c41d4" url=""><![CDATA[Kerala, the land of beauty and charm<br/><br/>Bliss was that dawn to be alive, to be young very heaven. I was born, bred in Kerala. I had my education in the sprawling Maharajas College which has seen very eminent politicians, historians, judges, cine actors, actresses, having had their education there. In those days, we had such a jolly good time. Education was a plesant experience. Our lecturers taught us the alphabets. Ernakulam was a dull city. Today bustling with the Vallarpadam terminals, and busy airlines landing and taking off, high flyovers, giant skyrappers, the beauty and charm of the town, the Queen of the Arabian Sea has fallen to the wayside.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1c5e5897e867368126112649cb5dcd09" url=""><![CDATA[New Year 2010<br/><br/>I think, most of us, would have waited for the new Year with baited breadth. 2009, like many many years before that, flew in its wings, leaving vivid memories of a Year which was tumultous, practically difficult year for the middle class and less priveleged.  The Institutions of which we were part and parcel tried their best to grapple, but with most consternation, held on. It is not remembered as the best of Years, even though, for the most, it would have been a Year that just whizzled Past. Many would have lost one or two kith and kin, one/two colleagues, and those memories may remember a haze.   
<br /><br />With us or without us, the World would go on, for nobody can claim immortality even the Gods who took birth in this beautiful World of Us. I remember the year 2009, as more a Year, when insipite of the best try, lot of things did not work the way we hoped. Yet, it was a bright year of Sunshine. The new Year, with its welcome smile is always welcome. It is not winter always.   If Summer comes, will it be winter always, mused the poet in a poetry which I heard from Kurup Sir when I was in my BA II Year at Maharajas. Yes; if today is bad, tomorrow will dazzle. Why worry.
<br /><br />Let us hope, 2010 will become one of the best Years in all our lives.Let us look ahead and not look behind.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b6c5e3874f35522efc262e83c35966be" url=""><![CDATA[In their old age, parents lead solitary life?<br/><br/>Today's fast-changing world needs the anchor of values and virtues that families can provide. Strong families instill responsibility and character in our children and teach them the ideals that make us a great nation. Through their love and sacrifice, parents, grandparents, aunts, uncles, siblings and other family members help prepare our young people to realize the bright future India offers for each child.
<br /><br />In India, the concept of Joint family system was prevalent.  Great grandfather, grand mother, grandpa, grandpa, father, mother, uncles, aunts, their children, nephews and nieces, were part of the great tharwads [ancestral house] and there was the Karanavar (Patriarch) who managed the whole family.  The entire tharawad was looked after by him and all the wealth were under his direct control.  He decided what should be done.   Children often went by his commands. But as the time changed, a new wave of family hierarchy came into being.  The Joint family system broke, nuclear families came into being, the children got separated, uncle and aunty went their own way, nephews and nieces went looking after greener pastures, the strict orthodoxy gave way to liberal thinking which saw inter-caste, inter-religion marriages becoming more and more frequent, the concept of joint family system and myths surrounding it has undergone a metamorphosis. 
<br /><br />Not-So-Nuclear Families explains the often painful choices that parents have to make for their children's--and their own--well-being.&quot;  In the United States public policy has focused on strengthening the nuclear family as a primary strategy for improving the lives of America's youth. It is often assumed that this normative type of family is an independent, self-sufficient unit adequate for raising children. But half of all households in the United States with young children have two employed parents. How do working parents provide care and mobilize the help that they need? In Not-So-Nuclear Families, An investigation into the lives of working parents and the informal networks they construct to help care for their children has been documented by sociologists. Each must navigate the ideology that mandates that parents, mothers in particular, rear their own children, in the face of an economic reality that requires that parents rely on the help of others. In vivid family stories, parents detail how they and their network of friends, paid caregivers, and extended kin collectively close the &quot;care gap&quot; for their school-aged children. Sociologists have debunked the myth that families in the United States are independent, isolated, and self-reliant units, by asserting that informal networks of care can potentially provide unique and valuable bonds that nuclear families cannot. 
<br /><br />The rise in the number of dual-earner couples in India may have led to an increase in the standard of living but it has also given rise to issues like how to balance home and work and how to devote enough time to children. There are many parents in India who depend on their children for their livelihood, having spent a fortune to rear their children. Some of them who had put their retirement doles into some form of activity benefiting their children have no source of independent income in their old age.  Pathetic is the mother’s case in case of bereavement of her husband. She has no body to care her, nor shelter her.  She .sometimes goes to one of the Old age homes to live the life of a destitute. 
<br /><br />The rise in the number of dual-earner couples in India may have led to an increase in the standard of living but it has also given rise to issues like how to balance home and work and how to devote enough time to children.
<br /><br />An international online poll conducted by a foreign based market research firm found that 74 percent of Indian respondents want a better home-work balance. Half said they want to spend more time with their families.  Couples are increasingly recognizing that any sort of balance can be achieved only if both partners chip in. For each couple, it's a matter of finding out what works best for them.
<br /><br />There are a number of techies who work from mid afternoon to midnight or who do night duties.   The responsibility of rearing the children falls on the spouse who has to adjust his job or reorient his schedule of work.  This suit greatly the people who work from Home Office. 
<br /><br />A journalist family friend of mine had to work the afternoon shift and she had to invariably work late into the night. Her husband was a photographer who had a studio in his residence itself.  This gave him cushion to look after their 5 year old kid and it was he who had played a large part in bringing up their daughter. He helped the child to go our for a stroll, taking her to the garden to play, helping her during mealtimes and taking her to the Doctor for check ups. Even though women feel that being in a career gives her a great deal of opportunity to be self reliant, and provide a more comfortable lifestyle for their family, they feel guilty that their spouse has to carry the duty of parenting the child alone.   Though his understanding nature helps, he has to sacrifice his job for the sake of his family.  It is not an easy ride.  
<br /><br />The husband has out-station jobs, and his unavoidable absence leave a vacuum in the household, as the child has to be left to the care of their neighbour who is busy with her two school going children and business-man husband. The Child also registers her protest by repeatedly crying when her mom leaves her house when the child’s father is away.  The journalist friend often feels very tired when she is unable to play with her daughter on weekend holidays. 
<br /><br />Although dual-earner couples are almost the norm now, it’s hard on the child.  All talks of quality time with kids are fine but it really just isn’t enough, which is why people prefer to have the support system like grandparents at home. .
<br /><br />That the family as a unit is in its transition stage is an understatement but that many facets of it are either understudied or has remained untouched by the researchers.  We need to understand the importance of relationship between the siblings apart from the numerous tensions between the husband and wife and parents and children that are confronted by the nuclear families in these times. 
<br /><br />The key to resolving work-life balance challenges, in fact, is flexibility. The way people negotiate working and parenting is an ongoing process and evolves continually.  There are many sociologists who believe it is futile to talk in terms of nuclear versus joint families, which is only an academic construction to understand Indian family. We must get out of this framework in order to grapple with the contemporary family composition. According to some others, this entire talk of nuclear versus joint family has an upper class urban approach, as the dichotomy does not lie in all strata of society in the country.
<br /><br />However, leaving old parents to live in their homes, when their children migrate to United States or far away Europe, with a Nurse, which is often the case in most of the families, has left the parents to muse over their past days of glory in solitariness. Some of the active ones, spent time visiting libraries, chatting with their friends of their age in the open lands attached to the temples, churches or mosques, while others whose mobility is restricted due to wear and tear, sit glued to the TV watching the modern mini screen stories.  Some of them feel orphaned, destitute and forlorn.  Their stories have no end or beginning.  Sending a few Dollars to them is considered to be a great favour done by the siblings to their parents.  What they want is Love, affection and see their grand children play. But to deprive them this pleasure, when they need most, in their old age, is itself pathos for the parents who struggled their life time to support their children!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1a7e810ab8972a713f923b0f964f87f6" url=""><![CDATA[India lives in her villages<br/><br/>India lives in her villages. It is the rural population who suffer the miseries of the socio-economic-political adventures of the urbanites.  The rural villages are beseeched by problems, the basic being illiteracy, lack of knowledge(ignorance) in upbringing children, unrestricted growth of the family, non availability of nutrious food, uncared expectant mothers, absence of protein, deficient food for pregnant woman, infant mortality growth, etc. 
<br /><br />They need good food, clothing and shelter. The Directive Principles of the State Policy envisage providing basic education, for which Anganvadi Schools can be used, lower primary schools be set up, adult education to the elders be provided through NGOs, vocational classes for womenfolk through volunteers, training for men be provided so that they can take up skill jobs according to their orientation and Hospitals for giving medical care. The villagers must be educated to maintain a clean environment. The Cultural department must organize talent finding camps so that the youth should be encouraged to bring out his latent talents.  Mobile dispensaries need to be opened wherein medicines and tablets must be made available to the poor, sick, needy and distressed. Encourage starting of tiny, mini industries to bolster their incomes. 
<br /><br />Mahatma Gandhi, whom we quote at the slightest pretext, advocated starting of village industries as a panacea to solve the problem of unemployment at the rural level. He, the fantast that he was, limnered his arguments that the spider web of our economy had its foundations in the grass root village economy. Most often, in spite of the hard work put in by the villagers, the villager is in a limbo because the so called rural employment programmes and dozens of Schemes chalked out by the KVIC and rural department of GoI seldom reach them; they are only in paper. He cannot, like the ‘limpet’ cry hoarse and crescendo for higher wages, in the guise of collective bargaining by the militant white collared comrades of the urban areas, who are never satisfied with their pay and demand more and more. His task of making both ends meet is gargantuan. Let us take perishable goods like vegetables.  The farmer sells tomato during seasons at Bellary (Karnataka) at Rs 1.60 per Kg. But the price for same commodity at a distance of 100 Kms is Rs 12/-. If a net work of marketing in the form of community service is available to him, the farmer could beget a higher price and the consumer for 50% of the existing rates.  The warehouses of Agricultural departments must ensure that they collect these produces at a fair value and transport it to the final market for disposal. These Marketing agencies should collect, pool all their collections at the manufacturing point and routed to various destinations where there is demand. Bellary (Karnataka) has a poultry cluster, where one egg costs 0.80 paise, while it sells at Rs 3.00 at Mangalore and Rs 4/- at Karwar (These figures were compiled by me in 1980 for the Government from central and coastal Karnataka). A little planning and coming together of a cluster of farmers could reap rich dividends for them. 
<br /><br />The Zilla parishads, and Village panchayats along with District Rural Development Societies, should bring together a group of people in every village, and create a voluntary group of people who could be trained to take up marketing so that they can pass on their expertise at the village.  A dedicated band of young men, who would help ligament the various sections, should be formed so that it will inure them to responsibilities from their wayward fanfaronade. 
<br /><br />The labour skills of the villagers have not been tapped properly.  A good artisan with deft fingers at Ankola (Kumta taluk) hardly gets Rs 60 per day; he is idle for the 6 months of the year; the same is the case with a diva, or a pastiche or a Conti writer. Their talents garnish the village and their lives syncopate leading them to misery. 
<br /><br />With a little amount of training, exposure and right fora experience, many of the rural folk, can put up commendable performance in art, craft, cultural programmes, sport etc. The Heggodu experiment (Magasasy award winner Heggde’s School of Drama) have shown how far the hidden rural talents can be brought about through the medium of dramas. Establishment of rural theaters, film criticism/appreciation courses, School of drama and dance, vocational guidance training camps for spotting talents in Sports, people with the gift of the gab chosen through elocution and essay competitions will boost the rural children’s appetitive to perform well in the Competitions enabling spotlighting talents. The Pople’s Action for Development (PADI), Ford Foundation, UNICEF and a hoard of Organizations have manifold Schemes aimed at providing training to the rural folk. 
<br /><br />The Anganvadi Schools can start as vehicles of thought and learning to the tiny tots. Good nutrious food can make them healthy. Cleanliness should be inculcated at this level itself. This will make them seek School education, so that literacy can be gradually increased.
<br /><br />For the elder village folk, recreation facilities should be provided. Community halls, parks, recreation centers must be part of the social milieu in the village.   The shyness of the rural folks can be overcome through exposure. They do not perform or show their talents in urban platforms for fear of inferiority. It has become modish to say that rural areas are backward yet a few fantasts come forward.
<br /><br />The Rural electrification programme, providing irrigation facilities to a wide command area, planting trees, growing vegetations, can be done in the rural areas with the support of the people. Pure drinking water can be made available by constructing storage tanks, at least one in a village. But poor villages continue to remain poor due to scanty facilities.  Basic facilities, how far they are provided is a hundred dollar question.  The artificial comforts of urban towns or Cities may be ditty in the rural.   The urbanite loathes rural areas, its settings and environment. But the natural rural environment and the rural demizes, would more than allegro compensate the shortfalls of rural conditions. Any takers?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a8d238125d3e85adb27205d224cbc14" url=""><![CDATA[Peon's vacany and Post Graduate applicants<br/><br/>In this era of macro development , fast communications through e-mails, swift  breakfast meetings at London, and evening meal at Chicago and night halt at Toronto, in the God’s Own Country, having the highest literacy including gender literacy, highly educated and the sophisticated prefer a local job in a Government office and that too, the Post of a ‘Peon’. 
<br /><br />In answer to an advertisement by the Kerala State Planning Commission seeking applications from candidates for the Post of Peons in the various Government offices and departments numbering 12,000 for the next five years, the Commission received over 12 lakh applications(12,31,499), the largest ever applications received by it.  It means, per one Peon’s post there are 100 applicants.   The minimum educational qualification fixed by the Commission for the Post was: the ability to read and write Malayalam, VII Pass.  But those who applied included a girl, who had an M.Phil (Zoology) with a BEd, MSc with Bed, doctoral researchers, college graduates, Post graduates, etc. 
<br /><br />The lure of Government Job, be it the job of a Peon or the lowliest in the Government hierarchy, which offers guaranteed security, light work, intermittent holidays due to strike, bundhs, fixed holidays, restricted holidays, Casual leave, medical leave, maternity leave(for woman), Child care leave for woman (2 years leave with pay).  If a staff lands into problems, the Unions will take care off, has attracted highly qualified unemployed to apply for the post of the lowly Peon’s position.
<br /><br />The 12.31 lakh applicants constitute roughly 4% of Kerala’s population of 3.18 Cr.  The fact that the applicant’s are in the 18-40 age group reveal that more than 10% of the young population have applied. 
<br /><br />The highest number of applications came from Thiruvanathapuram (1.75 lakhs) where job opportunities are less compared to Kochi, the Commercial capital which accounted for 1.11 lakhs, Kozhikode 1.25 lakhs,  and Kerala’s border districts like Wayanad (35,000) which had few opportunities and Kasargod(40,000) bordering Mangalore. 
<br /><br />The candidates who have applied for the peon’s post have joined coaching classes that prepares the last grade prospects for the Job test. 
<br /><br />One of the spin offs of the Post is that, whenever Government LDC vacancies would arise, 10% are earmarked for the last grade employees who just need to score just a pass mark to clear the clerical job test. 
<br /><br />Kerala has around 38 lakhs unemployed registered with the Employment Exchanges (9.1%) even though Goa has the highest employment rate (11.4%). In Kerala, there is more than 15% voluntary unemployment(a unique feature of Kerala) , as their kith and kin work in the Arabian Peninsula, Europe and America who send remittances back home regularly.   There are around 509.3 million employed in India. The labour force grew at a quicker rate of 2.84% than the workforce, unemployment has risen rapidly. The private sector accounted for a percentage growth from 0.44% to 0.92% while employment opportunities decreased in the Public sector from 1.53% to 0.54%.  There are ban on recruitment in most of the Government, autonomous, semi-autonomous bodies. Another factor which pushed up the growth of unemployment was the decrease in employment elasticity from 0.41% to 0.15% (from 1993-94 to 2000).  For the period 2004-5,t he aggregate elasticity has tripped from a low of 0.15 to 0.48 (that was the employment elasticity in 1993-94!). We talk about an economic growth of 8.4% for 2009-10. However, the labour force growth was 2.93%, which was more than the population growth rate. 
<br /><br />Globalization has seen that 26% of US technological firms founded by immigrants have more than 13% contributed by Indians and the rest combined contributed by UK, China, Taiwan, and Japan.  Kerala has immigrants in most parts of the globe which is more than 1 million. 
<br /><br />Human development or not, Kerala’s Gross State Domestic Product is heavily dependent on remittances from abroad which constitute 50% of India’s total remittance received from expatriates. Kerala’s exports constitute 2.4% of India’s total $ 185 billion. The Central sector public undertakings are a pie in the ocean of development. Kochi Port, heralded as the Queen of the Arabian Sea is worth a dozen Gold fields; its wealth is inexhaustible. Yet, the state which has the highest consumerism depends upon other states even for vegetables. This is because there is a need to study the structural unemployment scenario with special emphasis on the education scenario. Is it productive? Protective? Need-based? Meeting the challenges of the times?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e79625ddfb17ed99a9ff56ff415b2079" url=""><![CDATA[Is the pace of India that of a bullock cart?<br/><br/>In these days of fast moving technology, mind-boggling inventions, CCTVs, technology based security machines which would detect even a pin, India of the modern day does not care to use technology to detect fraud.   There is a saying in Malayalam which says, “Fearing a rat, one burns a house”. 
<br /><br />World over, scientific security measures are in place which will detect even a small thievery. There are other sophisticated equipments which will show the authenticity of a document. However, in India, we go for the primitive security rules.  The Government admits that the country has a large number of counterfeit notes printed abroad in circulation.  It further admits that the counterfeit looks more original than the original. It is said that hidden cameras will supervise actions of individuals; yet we see crackers hidden in the cargo space of a Plan, undetected for 24 hours!  We are yet to catch the culprits in so many crimes. Our Police is so ill equipped against modern day terrorists that the top most and the bravest fall prey to bullets just as it happened in the 26/11 Mumbai carnage. Marxists kill a platoon of soldiers well equipped. We shed tears for the dead but do not rectify our wrong doings based on introspection.
<br /><br />Reserve Bank of India, of all people, has circulated a note to all the Banks, 
<br />through a circular RBI Circular No.  – DPSS.CO.CHD.No. 1832/01.07.05/2009-10 dated 22nd February 2010 by virtue of which Banks are supposed to prohibit alterations/corrections in the cheque leaf during transit, lodging, clearing, or in any form of banking transaction. No changes/corrections should be carried out on the cheques (other than for dated of validation purpose, if required).  For any change in payees name, amount in figures (courtesy amount), amount in words (which in banking parlance called as legal amount) etc fresh cheques should be used by customers.   The reason disclosed by the Central Bank for issuing this notification is cited as this exercise would help banks to identity and control fraudulent alterations. Banks have been instructed to return cheques which have any alteration in the Payees name, amount in numbers, amount in words, etc.  Only the date can be altered and validated. This will come into force from 1st July 2010. 
<br /><br />We were told that Banks were computerized and Crores worth of security equipment to identity frauds were installed in the various Banks. Huge public money was spent on purchasing these.  Now, if the Banks cannot even detect forgery, alteration of the name of the payee, amount in figures/words then what type of vigilance mechanism the Banks are having.  A cheque is an instrument, and its payment is based on ‘Negotiable Instruments Act’.   For any legal document, for any inadvertent mistake, the law allows one to correct the wrong and put his full signature over it, so as to attest that he has corrected the wrong and he is personally responsible for what he has done.   If somebody erases the name using fraudulent methods, Banks should have equipments to detect the same.   We are living in the 21st century where automation has permeated to every single day chorus.  If this is the remedy RBI has found out to check fraudulent change of name, amount in figures or words, what about ATM Cards and other sophisticated instruments which can easily be manipulated.
<br /><br />Is the pace of India, the pace of a bullock cart?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="54b8e1a9283980f299a5f3ae7b90f586" url=""><![CDATA[G-20 Meeting and world recovery prospects<br/><br/>The US fiscal position is worse than that of major European triumvirates, Germany, France, and the United Kingdom. 
<br /><br />The G-20 Meeting for the Heads of Governments will be held at Toronto, preceded by a meeting of the Finance Ministers in Busan, South Korea. The G-20 members, discussed managing common challenges in 2009, and the spread of the budgetary stimulus to bring the economy back to shape, but now, the focus has shifted on sustainable public finances, and the need for measures to deliver fiscal sustainability, while the emphasis will be identifying steps which would strengthen the private sector recovery. Retrenchment is going to be a major plan which will phase the second leg of stimulus- phased exit strategies. Southern Europe is feeling the heat on the debt markets, its needs to soothe this vulnerable area. Britain is over cautious as it is anticipating ‘years of pain ahead’ while Germany is seized of the $ 100 billion retrenchment plan while the French followed it by outlining $ 80 billion retrenchment plan. 
<br />The developed countries face a homologous situation, 
<br /><br />with dismal budgetary deficit averaging 9% of GDP in 2009, while the prospect of public debt ratios rising from roughly 70% of GDP prior to the crisis to more than 100% of GDP in 2015.  The economists feel that to reach 60% debt ratio in 2030 would require a budgetary adjustment of almost 9% points of GDP on an average between 2010 to 2020. Though this is not impossible it is highly improbable and without precedent. 
<br /><br />How to make adjustments? To make it real, one has to have exhaustive economic brain. In the past, some countries have enjoyed tearless consolidation due to launch of retrenchment programme, and with the long-term interest rates dropped, causing a decline in private savings, and a surge in exports, exchange rate depreciation, or all of these at the same time.  
<br /><br />But conditions today are characterized by low interest rates and high private debt, so none of these may help, except possibly for exchange-rate effects. 
<br /><br />Indeed, depreciation has already started for Europe, and many consider the euro's fall, from $1.5 in late 2009 to $1.2 in recent days, sufficient to offset in the short term the retrenchment's negative impact on growth. In the Indian perspective, large sideways movement in the value of the Rupee against the euro has led to severe problems.  The evolving situation in the Euro zone does not inspire confidence.  There are indications of buyers in the EU region going slow in placing their orders. There are also cases where the Indian Companies have been asked to withhold consignments. All these indicate that the Second phase of global recovery will be slower as compared to the first phase having a bearing on the pace of expansion of global trade. 
<br /><br />But this can work only as long as the US does not follow suit and continues to serve as consumer of last resort. This may not happen. More importantly, increasingly nervous bond markets will at some point start questioning the sustainability of US public finances. 
<br /><br />The US fiscal position is no better than that of major European countries EU is fragmented, so markets started off by questioning the solvency of the weakest countries within it, and because Europe does not benefit from a safe-haven effect that it was the first to suffer the pressure.
<br /><br />Fortunately, the public-finance situation is entirely different in the developing world, which in some cases has been hit by capital flow reversals stemming from the collapse of world trade, but does not face an internal adjustment challenge. 
<br />The fiscal challenges for them are of much lower degree than in the advanced world.   So, what if Europe and the US both enter a phase of prolonged budgetary adjustment while the emerging world stays on course? What if the divergence between the North and South within the G-20 widens further?
<br /><br />Present state of world economy may cause spider web growth or a significant drag on world growth.  Even though emerging economies may sustain domestic markets and re-orient its export strategy by exporting more to developing countries other than EU, USA and Japan, the volume and content would be miniscule so as to have a base effect on world growth. Growth differential between emerging and advanced countries will widen intensifying flows of capital and labour to the developing world. But the developing world will not be able to sustain them on the medium to long term. Developed countries would need monetary support which would necessitate keeping low interest rates for years together, while the monetary needs of developing countries will be radically different. This will make fixed exchange rate links crack under pressure, as the same monetary policy cannot be appropriate for both the developing and developed regions. 
<br /><br />Double dip growth was savaged by the developed and developing countries through sound, stymied and theoretical economic monetary policies. But as the world slowly turned to ‘V’ shaped growth with short and sharp contradictions, while rapid and sustained recovery is no where on the cards. G-20 needs to face the challenges, divergence in the new context of different pictures of movement of economy in the developing and developed G-20 nations. This will be a major test of resilience at the same time to demonstrate effectiveness in the Catch 22 situation in the passing phase of global economy. The outcome of the Toronto conclave will determine the road the economy will take.
<br /><br />.
<br /><br />.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ef650b1a720f41b9a1ee493d9d2719f9" url=""><![CDATA[Judiciary requires speedy reforms<br/><br/>Indian judiciary, one of the pillars of the Indian Constitution, was venerated, respected and believed to be conscience keeper of the Country’s constitution. Certain land mark judgments, which recognized the right of the individual over absolute Power, independence of the IV estate and Executives invasion into the freedom of the Press had been considered sacred by the Courts, even Courts looked into certain legislative actions from the strict eyes of Law and juristic covenants, precedents and templates, have bee lauded and respected. It acted as an accountable body protecting the fundamental rights, the Courts struck acts and laws transgressing the limits of the Constitution, and kept up its supremacy.
<br /><br />However, when the Governments at the Centre and States started tinkering with Laws, and any arbitration between Centre and states, states and States, States Vs individuals were referred to the Courts for adjudication, the Executive wantonly transferred its responsibility to Courts.    When even administrative matters were not solved on the basis of Driot Administratef, Central Government and State Government Rules, but referred to Courts,. Examples of this are Ayodhya dispute, Cauveri Water dispute, etc were referred to Courts for its arbitration.  There are many issues which had been referred by the President of India to the Supreme Court for its clarification, Courts naturally became highly pro active, and took upon itself, cases which normally should not have been admitted. The Public Interest litigation was easy route for anybody to approach the highest Court of the land, whether the applicant had prima facie interest and affected by a particular order or action of the government, he surpassed the usual channels of law available to him, and knocked at the Supreme Court whether he was bona fide affected or not. This PIL later became a nuisance, and Supreme Court had warned the petitioners not to file vexatious PIL without sufficient reasons. 
<br /><br />The present judiciary is losing common man’s respect for obviously many reasons. Cases have been piled up in the lower Courts, higher Courts and Supreme Courts for ages, there are corruption charges against Judges of the higher Court, there are impeachment proceedings against some Judges, some judges involved in the PF case have brought shame to the judiciary. Criticism of one judge by another pusine judge through twitter or speeches have become common, there are parallel trails by the visual media 24x7 which prejudices the Case and one of the sad repercussions of these are loss of faith by the litigants on Courts which is supposed to dispense Fair Law. There have been past judgments which have been reversed 360 degrees by higher Courts. The recent incidents involving some of the sitting judicial officers for their Post Graduate legal examination  at Andhra Pradesh were caught red handed copying by a CCTV camera is a shame on the entire judicial system. If a judicial officer who should administer fair justice indulge in incorrect procedures, who will give justice to the litigants? Can litigants have faith in such judicial officers or the judicial system? 
<br /><br />There are also reports that appointments to the High Courts and Supreme Courts and transfer of High Court judges from one state to another are not fair. Good lawyers do not want to become Judges. Another factor in delay in delivering Justice is shortage of Judges. Even cases filed in the Fast Track Courts are unusually delayed. 
<br /><br />There is a need for overhauling reforms in Judiciary. The left over of the colonial past including Rules, regulations, acts, laws have been a stumbling block to deliver Law in these days when speed is a necessity. Globalization has changed global laws. World has changed. There are States or nations which indulge in Wars. There are non state actors who indulge in terrorism acts or take Law into their hands. Whether these acts are out of frustration, economic backwardness or political thinking is another matter. Judges are human, they can commit mistakes. But when some of the judicial officers think that they are conferred with infinite powers, they should be told that there are checks and balances in the judicial system. There are many acts of indiscipline within the Court rooms. The Judges are accountable to the system and Rule of Law. They are also accountable to the Constitution of India. They must be mild in their observations for the litigant who has obeyed the Law and stringent in their language against law breaker.  Government also should respect protocols and act impassionately. During the vote on account during the introduction of the Financial bill, CBI told the Supreme Court that enough evidence of financial irregularity against Mayawati is not there; but when to get the Nuclear Bill passed, where there was necessity to get the Left and BJP to support the Government, the CBI took a 360 degree turn and now says that evidences are there against Mayawati. This is the highest political misuse. 
<br /><br />Judicial Reforms is the need of the hour. Like the Fourth estate, Indian judiciary needs to exert self discipline.  The hallowed institution should command respect, reverence and worship! It must regain its lost legacy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="815634ebc525a57238014077b799a77c" url=""><![CDATA[Unbiased view on World-class institutions?<br/><br/>Union Environment Minister Jairam Ramesh's comment about the IITs and IIMs about the quality of Research or faculty needs introspection.   That there is a ready market for such students in the employment market with six digit salaries, but under what benchmark we have determined that these instructions are world class. Was there a comparison done with world class institutions or the basis on which they are classified as “world class”. The GoI can claim it as “world class” but let them the parameters analyzed to term these institutions as “world class”.   They may be the best institutions in our Country.  Who has given them the ‘world class tag?
<br /><br />Compared to the other institutions, where does the world class superiority of these institutions lay? It is true that the Indian middle class with affordability tag could easily get into one of the IITs or IIMs. Globalization brought in its wake a number of opportunities, and the biggest fall-out of its reach was on the middle class who made the maximum advantage out of it via these institutions which were the channels to get into big league. Bank and Government/Insurance jobs which were the aspirations of the upper middle class ; but come globalization, the spur of elite jobs in the Private sector which vied with one another to grab a prospective employee from one or the other IIT/IIM, made these young men/women troop to these institutions. An IIT or IIM became a status symbol. It was a platform for a good job with high pay. Now this demand for a seat in the IIT/IIM has necessitated competition for getting seats, not because these institutions are world class but  the preference the students get at the end of his curriculum for a posting in a Multi-national Company posited in India. .
<br /><br />Many people have obtained degrees and are talented, but fail to make an impression on these who are in the recruiting desk of the Private sector companies, because they do not take the glazed certificates of IIT/IIM. Is the “World class” status conferred, or was it arrived at against strict parameters of comparison with world class institutions
<br /><br />The world class tag comes into discussion, because we assume that these institutions are world class, and the best education is available in these institutes and no where else in our country. Other educational institutions pale into insignificance, when these IITs/IIMs are called “Centres of Excellence”.   But where is the excellence, except the students of IIT/IIM get preference for Private sector top jobs not because they had world class education but selected because the employers  assume IIT/IIM are world class. It is in this context that we have to take the status of our institutions, and try to make them unique. Vishwabharati University became something special because its founder was Rabindranatha Tagore. Similarly Indian Institute of Science owes its popularity due to Dr.CV Raman connection.  
<br /><br />The problems of these “world class” institutions like IIT/IIM are similar to the one faced by other educational institutions in the private/public sector. Quality of Research, availability of opportunity for research, faculty shortage, overload on teaching responsibilities, the strength of the batches which are unwieldy, government interference, etc.  World Class institutions need functional and financial autonomy to chart their course!
<br /><br />We need innovation, course-correction intechnological development, up-gradation of technology, slowly diminishing the obsolete technology, cheap technology, clean technology. What is India's contribution to Reserch and Development and Crores of Rupees spent on Reserch institutions. IIT/IIM's should produce students with scientific temper, and innovation centric. That is what growing India wants. Not speeches. Papers.
<br /><br />There have been good set of professors in the various instructions in India. They may have vast knowledge, and the field on which they teach. They may also be great teachers. They may be easily approachable. They may have analytical power. But where does Indian teaching stand in front of foreign educationalists who are well known, who have trained a number of illustrious people who have won world class credentials. There may be individual brilliance- one Kalpana Chawla, A R Rahaman, Sabeer Bhatia, Indra Nooyi, Amratya Sen, Mittal, Sam Pitroda, Dr Ramakrishnan, Nikki Randhawa Haley (Louisiana Governor) etc ( a sample and not exhaustive) that took them to surfeit of glory. Dirubhai Ambani did not study in any world class institutions.  Individual abilities transform them to greatness, which happens in every spheres of life.
<br /><br />In India, debates are made controversial so that discussions on some issues which needs wide ranging comments, and suggestions are nipped in the bud. Debates need to be non partisan, meaningful.  India had an institutional legacy left behind by Britishers. We had shut our doors for almost half-a century from the rest of the world.  We do not have any clue regarding what is world-class in the modern global context. We export goods calling them world-class when the goods are meant for the lowest retail shops. Compare our exports of US $ 245 billion with China’s $ 3.6 trillion. Higher education, specialized education, with world-class systems and environment flourished much before they did in India. In Indian context mastery in teaching is considered to be part and parcel of much achieved institutions while cutting- edge research, innovation is given growing importance for Schools of Excellence in the developed world.
<br /><br />We need to analyze the issue objectively, without prejudice, and analytically so as to make these institutions “world-class” , instead of criticizing those people who make a discussion point as being political and biased.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be27d6922568d636342f2398ccb7d30b" url=""><![CDATA[India, Corruption,greed, loot,wealth<br/><br/>Anna Hazare was not the only man  in India who thought that enough is enough about corruption, corrupt political class, greed, and an army of  political parties and regional parties, who have been in charge of country’s wealth, with nothing to show that there was actually a drop in the Below poverty line, and they had access to primary education, and employment in the Public education, affair and decent living, even after 65 years of people of India have given to themselves this Great constitution signed by the great, patriotic founding fathers. 
<br /><br />Anna Hazare’s resolve to elect honest people whose first mandate would be to revolutionize the Parliamentary system by enacting laws that strip them of their immune privileges, inordinate power to pander to bankers and their ability to hide behind their offices as if they are above every other Indian?
<br /><br />How about we hold them accountable for all their actions and make everything they do transparent? 
<br /><br />How about we the people get to vote on whether they have engaged in criminal behavior while in our employ? And, we the people get to determine their punishment by voting on the outcome of public trials of public officials!
<br /><br />And, while we're at it, how about we control the big banks once and for all so they don't caugh off money illegally to the big Corporates without equivalent guarantee   and the regulators who are supposed to be minding the public's interest but in practice supporting the political class. Many of their accounts fall in the domain of Non Performing Assets and in order to make it performing assets, the Loans are re-scheduled. 
<br /><br />What's at stake is whether gross criminal activity and reckless disregard for the public will continue to be whitewashed by regulators like the SEBI, TRAI, Insurance Ombudsmen and other quasi judicial bodies which are set up to be watch dogs but these bodies try to circumvent the crime by filing half-baked civil fraud charges with weak arguments so that the culprits go often scot free.  We have allowed the legislators who are having the power to pass stringent Laws to make meek laws so as to protect the dishonest who have means to prolong the criminal cases filed in the Court of Law through well paid Advocates who preach puberty in public life and argue for these corrupt businessman, politician, bureaucrat and save him from any punishment.  Honesty and transparency will be remembered on Oct 2nd of every year when the netas gather at Rajghat.  There is a section of Indians, who are greedy, who uproot every law, trample on every institution, in their pursuit to become richer! Courts after Courts will acquit them, because the prosecution case is decidedly made weak, records will be mutilated, witnesses will be intimidated, and the guilty parties will neither admit nor deny wrongdoing. In the face of weak evidence, distortion, the case will fall. They will be at their best after getting exonerated by the Court of Law. And the government, instead of making a post mortem of what went wrong, will find fault with the judiciary! While all these will go on, our respectable fourth estate through continuous breaking news broadcast will confuse the issue by bringing experts who will opine everything under the sun except the case in question. 
<br /><br />It's our God-given right, and we better exercise it before our ability to save ourselves from what we have become destroys the magnificent experiment our Founding Fathers and our heroic patriotic national leaders have fought for.
<br /><br />We are lying to ourselves if we do not believe that we are all part of this problem. It's not that most of us aren't honest. It's that we venerate money and wealth too much. 
<br /><br />Rather than being disgusted by dishonest manipulators, liars and cheats, we excuse the less-than-obvious perpetrators as if their example of cutting corners to get ahead, as far ahead as possible, might clear a path for some of our own pursuits.
<br /><br />What have we become? Are we a nation of people with liberty and justice for all, or just a bunch of money grabbers stepping on each other's liberties to pursue self-centered happiness by becoming filthy rich?
<br /><br />Nearly half of all members of Congress are millionaires. Most of them have gotten much richer in office over the past five/ten years while the country has become much poorer. They do not have to prove their worth when salaries and allowances are increased, they get service entitlement, constituency allowance, medical allowance, telephone allowance, free motor car, gadgets, house, telephone, etc etc. They are expected to travel on “fact finding” trips not only to different destinations in India but also overseas. 
<br /><br />We have been making Laws and breaking Laws by inserting inert dozen loopholes into whatever seemingly sensible laws exist presently. Politicians need money to fight the elections and their power comes from the office they hold. It is at this busy intersection that the Politicians collide with the Corporate by taking money to bequeath   opportunities when they get into power later. There are many examples of rags from riches story amongst the political and business class. 
<br /><br />We must ask ourselves whether we want an honest government or a government which obliges the Corporates through deliberate wrong acts. 
<br />Whether it is noble to pretend that we are an honest country or to put our arms around the nexus of money and power that has corrupted our integrity, our morals, and our future, and by opposing them, crush them, is what all Indians  should be actively debating.
<br /><br />We need to usher in a Government who are faithful to the ideologies of the Constitution created by our founding fathers, and sincere to the people who voted them to power. This change should happen in the nearest two election cycles, if we want to usher “Ram Rajya”
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d527a2d7ffe7f153f5da17df2e32219c" url=""><![CDATA[Can somebody suggest an industrial Policy for Kerala?<br/><br/>Kerala is a consumer state with manufacturing output and manufacturing industries in the micro, and small sectors doing very little  to increase industrial output. The states GDP vis-à-vis manufacturing sector may well be negative. Kerala entire income is derived from the service sector, hospitality sector, tourism, gold and jewellery, thriving liquor industry. 
<br /><br />Kerala came up with the Land Reforms Act. Though it was a brave attempt, fragmentation of land limited agriculture, coconut plantations which became homestead, and large scale farming became impossible and the cost: benefit analysis was not favourable to the farmer. 
<br /><br />The fisheries industry in India, on which the economy of most of the places were bound, caught up with modernization, and herd, which resulted in the traditional fishing industry non thriving. The mechanized boats, trawlers, saw the ruin of traditional fishermen. And the organized industry of speed boats and trawlers, were owned by people who were from outside the states. With the result, the fisheries economy, did not find change of hands in Kerala through goods and services.
<br /><br />Kerala is the home to many traditional industries like coir, coconut, rubber, etc. Though these industries are export centric, their capacity and production is so feeble that Kerala does not even contribute 3% of the total Indian exports of US $ 275 billion. Kerala’s exports include Spices, marine products, cashew, tea, coffee, rubber, coir, coconuts, etc.   The entire manufacturing sector include one or two big tyre companies, rubber chapels, light engineering, software, ship building unit (government owned), etc.  Kochi Port which was way back one of the finest natural all-weather Port, is mainly known for import of cargo, with lot of idle space. The Vallarpadam transshipment container will succeed, if the containers meant for various Ports with mother ships are received here. But it is a tall order.
<br /><br />There is a strong pillared private sector education institutes which provide specialized post-graduate education. It is the private sector investment in educational institutions, hospitals that had made Kerala a highly literate state with high medical facility. 
<br /><br />God’s Own Country brand has attracted tourists all over the world. It is the private investment again that has been able to attract low end and medium end tourists to the state of Kerala. Kerala is not the destination for high end tourist.
<br /><br />Kerala’s employment bastion is overseas. Malayalam speaking nurses are all over the World. There can hardly be a hospital in India where you do not have Kerala nurses. With a good demand across the world, Kerala nurses are in every hospital everywhere. The skiled workers are all over the place except in Kerala. Today, the vacant places have been filled by people from Bihar, Bengal, Orissa,, and other states with the least opposition from the militant Kerala labour. There are many Restaurants which bring the staff also from where the entrepreneur hails. 
<br /><br />There is a strong view by Economists that the money order economy is responsible for Kerala’s economic growth triggered by income growth and not due to equitable development. This is not hundred percent true, though correct to an extent. 
<br /><br />The state political leadership lacks a vision, a perspective industrial Policy imbued with export Policy to make the state an attractive preposition for industrialists.  We have the most sophisticated modern Cars on Kerala Roads which are full of holes and pits. We have the most primitive drainage and sewage system. We still depend upon the age old system of throwing wastes on the thoroughfares.  The civic amenities provided by the Corporations and Municipalities are of a low order.  We have craze for gold ornaments. High rise buildings. Fancy cars. The hot drinks are a favourite pastime of our households. Cinema is a passion. Construction activity is a wholesale industrial activity. 
<br /><br />We have 44 rivers with water to the brim, 41 flowing west draining water to the Arabian Sea. Three are east flowing. One upon a time, we sold electricity produced. Today we are borrowing electricity. We are in the 20th place in the per capita consumption of Water after Rajasthan. 
<br /><br />We have Kathakali. Many of our poets have been awarded the Jnanapeed Award. We have an intellectual population and a fair amount of newspaper circulation, having the highest density in terms of readership in the Country. We have ancient temples, mosques and churches. There is Sabarimala, Guruvayoor, and Sri Padmanabha Swami Temple. Adi Sankara is our own man. The architect of Green Revolution, Dr M S Swaminathan is from Kerala. 
<br /><br />But Kerala did not have a Sir Visheshwaryya , or a Naidu, or a CV Raman, who could trigger the resources to industrialization. It is a mind set. It is a ritual.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>