<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="19">
		<document id="9b740f4a21cf44d312fafcfa931d52aa" url=""><![CDATA[Life's Value<br/><br/>Everyone saw
<br />The whiff of fragrance
<br />Rise from the harp of the flower
<br />Into a thousand melodies;
<br />No one noticed
<br />The flower
<br />Had given away all it,s riches.
<br /><br />The fresh fragrance of my thoughts,
<br />My poems, my riches,
<br />Princes of my words,
<br />Bearers of my voice,
<br />Have emerged from the valley of my lips.
<br />Passing through the dread jungle of silence,
<br />They walk on sorrowful pathways,
<br />Burn in the hell-fires of the journey,
<br />Are led astray by the sound of footstep:
<br />All just to seek the pleasure of the journey,s end.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a42a61a82939133a44eb105384995875" url=""><![CDATA[YOU AND I<br/><br/>??? ? ???
<br />“You and I”
<br />???? ??????? ????? ???? ????
<br />Happy is the moment, when we sit together,
<br />?? ?????? ?????? ? ?? ??? ??? ??????
<br />With two forms, two faces, yet one soul,
<br />??? ? ???
<br />You and I...
<br />????? ??????? ??????
<br />The flowers will bloom forever,
<br />?????? ????? ??????? ??????????
<br />The bird will sing their eternal song,
<br />?????? ???? ????????
<br />The moment we enter the garden,
<br />??? ? ???
<br />You and I...
<br /> ???_ ???? ?????? ?????????
<br />The stars of heaven will come to watch us,
<br />? ????????
<br />And we will show them,
<br /> ????? ????
<br />The light of a full moon,
<br />??? ? ???
<br />You and I...
<br />?? ???? ?? ?????? ?? ? ???
<br />No more thought of you and me...
<br />???? ???? ?????????
<br />Just the bliss of union,
<br />???? ???? ???? ??????? ??? ? ???
<br />Joyous, alive, free of care, you and me...
<br />??? ?????? ??????? ??????? ??????
<br />All the bright-winged birds of heaven
<br />????? ?? ???? ?????? ?????-
<br />Will swoop down to drink of our sweet water-
<br /> ??? ?????? ??? ? ???
<br />The tears of our laughter, you and I
<br />?? ????? ???? ?????? ???.
<br />What a miracle of fate, us sitting here.
<br />???? ?? ?????? ????? ????????
<br />Even at the opposite ends of the earth
<br />?? ???? ?? ??? ???? ??? ? ???
<br />We would still be together, you and I
<br />?????? ???? ???? ??? ?????
<br />We have one form in this world,
<br />??? ?????? ???? ?????? ???????.
<br />Another in the next,
<br />????? ????? ???? ????????
<br />To us belongs an eternal heaven,
<br /> ????? ???????? ? ???
<br />The endless delight of you and I...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a2db7fe4dbbbdfb59e1d5566f240d0ca" url=""><![CDATA[A Dream within a Dream<br/><br/>A Dream within a Dream
<br />by: Edgar Allen Poe
<br /><br />Take this kiss upon the brow!
<br />And, in parting from you now,
<br />Thus much let me avow-
<br />You are not wrong, who deem
<br />That my days have been a dream;
<br />Yet if hope has flown away
<br />In a night, or in a day,
<br />In a vision, or in none,
<br />Is it therefore the less gone?
<br />All that we see or seem
<br />Is but a dream within a dream.
<br /><br />I stand amid the roar
<br />Of a surf-tormented shore,
<br />And I hold within my hand
<br />Grains of the golden sand-
<br />How few! yet how they creep
<br />Through my fingers to the deep,
<br />While I weep- while I weep!
<br />O God! can I not grasp
<br />Them with a tighter clasp?
<br />O God! can I not save
<br />One from the pitiless wave?
<br />Is all that we see or seem
<br />But a dream within a dream?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="33c3f59ef8d6759f3122343d2875d400" url=""><![CDATA[Alone<br/><br/>Alone
<br />by: Edgar Allen Poe
<br /><br />From childhood's hour I have not been
<br />As others were; I have not seen
<br />As others saw; I could not bring
<br />My passions from a common spring.
<br />From the same source I have not taken
<br />My sorrow; I could not awaken
<br />My heart to joy at the same tone;
<br />And all I loved, I loved alone.
<br />Then- in my childhood, in the dawn
<br />Of a most stormy life- was drawn
<br />From every depth of good and ill
<br />The mystery which binds me still:
<br />From the torrent, or the fountain,
<br />From the red cliff of the mountain,
<br />From the sun that round me rolled
<br />In its autumn tint of gold,
<br />From the lightning in the sky
<br />As it passed me flying by,
<br />From the thunder and the storm,
<br />And the cloud that took the form
<br />(When the rest of Heaven was blue)
<br />Of a demon in my view.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="623129981752efc503c216961135b5a9" url=""><![CDATA[Dreamland<br/><br/>Dreamland
<br />by: Edgar Allen Poe
<br /><br />By a route obscure and lonely,
<br />Haunted by ill angels only,
<br />Where an Eidolon, named NIGHT,
<br />On a black throne reigns upright,
<br />I have reached these lands but newly
<br />From an ultimate dim Thule-
<br />From a wild clime that lieth, sublime,
<br />Out of SPACE- out of TIME.
<br /><br />Bottomless vales and boundless floods,
<br />And chasms, and caves, and Titan woods,
<br />With forms that no man can discover
<br />For the tears that drip all over;
<br />Mountains toppling evermore
<br />Into seas without a shore;
<br />Seas that restlessly aspire,
<br />Surging, unto skies of fire;
<br />Lakes that endlessly outspread
<br />Their lone waters- lone and dead,-
<br />Their still waters- still and chilly
<br />With the snows of the lolling lily.
<br /><br />By the lakes that thus outspread
<br />Their lone waters, lone and dead,-
<br />Their sad waters, sad and chilly
<br />With the snows of the lolling lily,-
<br />By the mountains- near the river
<br />Murmuring lowly, murmuring ever,-
<br />By the grey woods,- by the swamp
<br />Where the toad and the newt encamp-
<br />By the dismal tarns and pools
<br />Where dwell the Ghouls,-
<br />By each spot the most unholy-
<br />In each nook most melancholy-
<br />There the traveller meets aghast
<br />Sheeted Memories of the Past-
<br />Shrouded forms that start and sigh
<br />As they pass the wanderer by-
<br />White-robed forms of friends long given,
<br />In agony, to the Earth- and Heaven.
<br /><br />For the heart whose woes are legion
<br />'Tis a peaceful, soothing region-
<br />For the spirit that walks in shadow
<br />'Tis- oh, 'tis an Eldorado!
<br />But the traveller, travelling through it,
<br />May not- dare not openly view it!
<br />Never its mysteries are exposed
<br />To the weak human eye unclosed;
<br />So wills its King, who hath forbid
<br />The uplifting of the fringed lid;
<br />And thus the sad Soul that here passes
<br />Beholds it but through darkened glasses.
<br /><br />By a route obscure and lonely,
<br />Haunted by ill angels only,
<br />Where an Eidolon, named NIGHT,
<br />On a black throne reigns upright,
<br />I have wandered home but newly
<br />From this ultimate dim Thule.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8e5eba7f63368447873a8602c58ece2c" url=""><![CDATA[A Dream<br/><br/>A Dream
<br />by: Edgar Allen Poe
<br /><br />In visions of the dark night
<br />I have dreamed of joy departed-
<br />But a waking dream of life and light
<br />Hath left me broken-hearted.
<br /><br />Ah! what is not a dream by day
<br />To him whose eyes are cast
<br />On things around him with a ray
<br />Turned back upon the past?
<br /><br />That holy dream- that holy dream,
<br />While all the world were chiding,
<br />Hath cheered me as a lovely beam
<br />A lonely spirit guiding.
<br /><br />What though that light, thro' storm and night,
<br />So trembled from afar-
<br />What could there be more purely bright
<br />In Truth's day-star?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a7d4d0f53a57363ef8ee852fce65e24" url=""><![CDATA[Dreams<br/><br/>Dreams
<br />by: Edgar Allen Poe
<br /><br />Oh! that my young life were a lasting dream!
<br />My spirit not awak'ning till the beam
<br />Of an Eternity should bring the morrow.
<br />Yes! tho' that long dream were of hopeless sorrow,
<br />'T were better than the cold reality
<br />Of waking life, to him whose heart must be,
<br />And hath been still, upon the lovely earth,
<br />A chaos of deep passion, from his birth.
<br />But should it be - that dream eternally
<br />Continuing - as dreams have been to me
<br />In my young boyhood - should it thus be giv'n,
<br />'T were folly still to hope for higher Heav'n.
<br />For I have revell'd, when the sun was bright
<br />I' the summer sky, in dreams of living light
<br />And loveliness, - have left my very heart
<br />In climes of mine imagining, apart
<br />From mine own home, with beings that have been
<br />Of mine own thought - what more could I have seen?
<br />'T was once - and only once - and the wild hour
<br />From my remembrance shall not pass - some pow'r
<br />Or spell had bound me - 't was the chilly wind
<br />Cam o'er me in the night, and left behind
<br />Its image on my spirit - or the moon
<br />Shone on my slumbers in her lofty noon
<br />Too coldly - or the stars - howe'er it was,
<br />That dream was as that night-wind - let it pass.
<br /><br />I have been happy, tho' [but] in a dream.
<br />I have been happy - and I love the theme:
<br />Dreams! in their vivid coloring of life,
<br />As in that fleeting, shadowy, misty strife
<br />Of semblance with reality which brings
<br />To the delirious eye, more lovely things
<br />Of Paradise and Love - and all our own!
<br />Than young Hope in his sunniest hour hath known.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89504eedae84bda289879891c41d131d" url=""><![CDATA[Beauty<br/><br/>And a poet said, 'Speak to us of Beauty.'
<br /><br />Where shall you seek beauty, and how shall you find her unless she herself be your way and your guide?
<br /><br />And how shall you speak of her except she be the weaver of your speech?
<br /><br />The aggrieved and the injured say, 'Beauty is kind and gentle.
<br /><br />Like a young mother half-shy of her own glory she walks among us.'
<br /><br />And the passionate say, 'Nay, beauty is a thing of might and dread.
<br /><br />Like the tempest she shakes the earth beneath us and the sky above us.'
<br /><br />The tired and the weary say, 'beauty is of soft whisperings. She speaks in our spirit.
<br /><br />Her voice yields to our silences like a faint light that quivers in fear of the shadow.'
<br /><br />But the restless say, 'We have heard her shouting among the mountains,
<br /><br />And with her cries came the sound of hoofs, and the beating of wings and the roaring of lions.'
<br /><br />At night the watchmen of the city say, 'Beauty shall rise with the dawn from the east.'
<br /><br />And at noontide the toilers and the wayfarers say, 'we have seen her leaning over the earth from the windows of the sunset.'
<br /><br />In winter say the snow-bound, 'She shall come with the spring leaping upon the hills.'
<br /><br />And in the summer heat the reapers say, 'We have seen her dancing with the autumn leaves, and we saw a drift of snow in her hair.'
<br /><br />All these things have you said of beauty.
<br /><br />Yet in truth you spoke not of her but of needs unsatisfied,
<br /><br />And beauty is not a need but an ecstasy.
<br /><br />It is not a mouth thirsting nor an empty hand stretched forth,
<br /><br />But rather a heart enflamed and a soul enchanted.
<br /><br />It is not the image you would see nor the song you would hear,
<br /><br />But rather an image you see though you close your eyes and a song you hear though you shut your ears.
<br /><br />It is not the sap within the furrowed bark, nor a wing attached to a claw,
<br /><br />But rather a garden forever in bloom and a flock of angels for ever in flight.
<br /><br />People of Orphalese, beauty is life when life unveils her holy face.
<br /><br />But you are life and you are the veil.
<br /><br />Beauty is eternity gazing at itself in a mirror.
<br /><br />But you are eternity and you are the mirror.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bcb6044cad188f8ae4bd5ff4f06d3b83" url=""><![CDATA[Freedom<br/><br/>And an orator said, 'Speak to us of Freedom.'
<br /><br />And he answered:
<br /><br />At the city gate and by your fireside I have seen you prostrate yourself and worship your own freedom,
<br /><br />Even as slaves humble themselves before a tyrant and praise him though he slays them.
<br /><br />Ay, in the grove of the temple and in the shadow of the citadel I have seen the freest among you wear their freedom as a yoke and a handcuff.
<br /><br />And my heart bled within me; for you can only be free when even the desire of seeking freedom becomes a harness to you, and when you cease to speak of freedom as a goal and a fulfillment.
<br /><br />You shall be free indeed when your days are not without a care nor your nights without a want and a grief,
<br /><br />But rather when these things girdle your life and yet you rise above them naked and unbound.
<br /><br />And how shall you rise beyond your days and nights unless you break the chains which you at the dawn of your understanding have fastened around your noon hour?
<br /><br />In truth that which you call freedom is the strongest of these chains, though its links glitter in the sun and dazzle the eyes.
<br /><br />And what is it but fragments of your own self you would discard that you may become free?
<br /><br />If it is an unjust law you would abolish, that law was written with your own hand upon your own forehead.
<br /><br />You cannot erase it by burning your law books nor by washing the foreheads of your judges, though you pour the sea upon them.
<br /><br />And if it is a despot you would dethrone, see first that his throne erected within you is destroyed.
<br /><br />For how can a tyrant rule the free and the proud, but for a tyranny in their own freedom and a shame in their won pride?
<br /><br />And if it is a care you would cast off, that care has been chosen by you rather than imposed upon you.
<br /><br />And if it is a fear you would dispel, the seat of that fear is in your heart and not in the hand of the feared.
<br /><br />Verily all things move within your being in constant half embrace, the desired and the dreaded, the repugnant and the cherished, the pursued and that which you would escape.
<br /><br />These things move within you as lights and shadows in pairs that cling.
<br /><br />And when the shadow fades and is no more, the light that lingers becomes a shadow to another light.
<br /><br />And thus your freedom when it loses its fetters becomes itself the fetter of a greater freedom.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="657755d7f2c3d40ab839f915f44a08ef" url=""><![CDATA[Joy & Sorrow<br/><br/>Then a woman said, 'Speak to us of Joy and Sorrow.'
<br /><br />And he answered:
<br /><br />Your joy is your sorrow unmasked.
<br /><br />And the selfsame well from which your laughter rises was oftentimes filled with your tears.
<br /><br />And how else can it be?
<br /><br />The deeper that sorrow carves into your being, the more joy you can contain.
<br /><br />Is not the cup that hold your wine the very cup that was burned in the potter's oven?
<br /><br />And is not the lute that soothes your spirit, the very wood that was hollowed with knives?
<br /><br />When you are joyous, look deep into your heart and you shall find it is only that which has given you sorrow that is giving you joy.
<br /><br />When you are sorrowful look again in your heart, and you shall see that in truth you are weeping for that which has been your delight.
<br /><br />Some of you say, 'Joy is greater than sorrow,' and others say, 'Nay, sorrow is the greater.'
<br /><br />But I say unto you, they are inseparable.
<br /><br />Together they come, and when one sits alone with you at your board, remember that the other is asleep upon your bed.
<br /><br />Verily you are suspended like scales between your sorrow and your joy.
<br /><br />Only when you are empty are you at standstill and balanced.
<br /><br />When the treasure-keeper lifts you to weigh his gold and his silver, needs must your joy or your sorrow rise or fall.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ded3e04334610b4e99aac70d68f8aa12" url=""><![CDATA[Love<br/><br/>Then said Almitra, 'Speak to us of Love.'
<br /><br />And he raised his head and looked upon the people, and there fell a stillness upon them.
<br /><br />And with a great voice he said:
<br /><br />When love beckons to you follow him,
<br /><br />Though his ways are hard and steep.
<br /><br />And when his wings enfold you yield to him,
<br /><br />Though the sword hidden among his pinions may wound you.
<br /><br />And when he speaks to you believe in him,
<br /><br />Though his voice may shatter your dreams as the north wind lays waste the garden.
<br /><br />For even as love crowns you so shall he crucify you. Even as he is for your growth so is he for your pruning.
<br /><br />Even as he ascends to your height and caresses your tenderest branches that quiver in the sun,
<br /><br />So shall he descend to your roots and shake them in their clinging to the earth.
<br /><br />Like sheaves of corn he gathers you unto himself.
<br /><br />He threshes you to make you naked.
<br /><br />He sifts you to free you from your husks.
<br /><br />He grinds you to whiteness.
<br /><br />He kneads you until you are pliant;
<br /><br />And then he assigns you to his sacred fire, that you may become sacred bread for God's sacred feast.
<br /><br />All these things shall love do unto you that you may know the secrets of your heart, and in that knowledge become a fragment of Life's heart.
<br /><br />But if in your fear you would seek only love's peace and love's pleasure,
<br /><br />Then it is better for you that you cover your nakedness and pass out of love's threshing-floor,
<br /><br />Into the seasonless world where you shall laugh, but not all of your laughter, and weep, but not all of your tears.
<br /><br />Love gives naught but itself and takes naught but from itself.
<br /><br />Love possesses not nor would it be possessed;
<br /><br />For love is sufficient unto love.
<br /><br />When you love you should not say, 'God is in my heart,' but rather, I am in the heart of God.'
<br /><br />And think not you can direct the course of love, if it finds you worthy, directs your course.
<br /><br />Love has no other desire but to fulfil itself.
<br /><br />But if you love and must needs have desires, let these be your desires:
<br /><br />To melt and be like a running brook that sings its melody to the night.
<br /><br />To know the pain of too much tenderness.
<br /><br />To be wounded by your own understanding of love;
<br /><br />And to bleed willingly and joyfully.
<br /><br />To wake at dawn with a winged heart and give thanks for another day of loving;
<br /><br />To rest at the noon hour and meditate love's ecstasy;
<br /><br />To return home at eventide with gratitude;
<br /><br />And then to sleep with a prayer for the beloved in your heart and a song of praise upon your lips.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e010bb3a62c95a2f87288917adab799f" url=""><![CDATA[Pain<br/><br/>And a woman spoke, saying, 'Tell us of Pain.'
<br /><br />And he said:
<br /><br />Your pain is the breaking of the shell that encloses your understanding.
<br /><br />Even as the stone of the fruit must break, that its heart may stand in the sun, so must you know pain.
<br /><br />And could you keep your heart in wonder at the daily miracles of your life, your pain would not seem less wondrous than your joy;
<br /><br />And you would accept the seasons of your heart, even as you have always accepted the seasons that pass over your fields.
<br /><br />And you would watch with serenity through the winters of your grief.
<br /><br />Much of your pain is self-chosen.
<br /><br />It is the bitter potion by which the physician within you heals your sick self.
<br /><br />Therefore trust the physician, and drink his remedy in silence and tranquillity:
<br /><br />For his hand, though heavy and hard, is guided by the tender hand of the Unseen,
<br /><br />And the cup he brings, though it burn your lips, has been fashioned of the clay which the Potter has moistened with His own sacred tears.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="67dd0565810a72393445132d3af18ca9" url=""><![CDATA[Pleasure<br/><br/>Then a hermit, who visited the city once a year, came forth and said, 'Speak to us of Pleasure.'
<br /><br />And he answered, saying:
<br /><br />Pleasure is a freedom song,
<br /><br />But it is not freedom.
<br /><br />It is the blossoming of your desires,
<br /><br />But it is not their fruit.
<br /><br />It is a depth calling unto a height,
<br /><br />But it is not the deep nor the high.
<br /><br />It is the caged taking wing,
<br /><br />But it is not space encompassed.
<br /><br />Ay, in very truth, pleasure is a freedom-song.
<br /><br />And I fain would have you sing it with fullness of heart; yet I would not have you lose your hearts in the singing.
<br /><br />Some of your youth seek pleasure as if it were all, and they are judged and rebuked.
<br /><br />I would not judge nor rebuke them. I would have them seek.
<br /><br />For they shall find pleasure, but not her alone:
<br /><br />Seven are her sisters, and the least of them is more beautiful than pleasure.
<br /><br />Have you not heard of the man who was digging in the earth for roots and found a treasure?
<br /><br />And some of your elders remember pleasures with regret like wrongs committed in drunkenness.
<br /><br />But regret is the beclouding of the mind and not its chastisement.
<br /><br />They should remember their pleasures with gratitude, as they would the harvest of a summer.
<br /><br />Yet if it comforts them to regret, let them be comforted.
<br /><br />And there are among you those who are neither young to seek nor old to remember;
<br /><br />And in their fear of seeking and remembering they shun all pleasures, lest they neglect the spirit or offend against it.
<br /><br />But even in their foregoing is their pleasure.
<br /><br />And thus they too find a treasure though they dig for roots with quivering hands.
<br /><br />But tell me, who is he that can offend the spirit?
<br /><br />Shall the nightingale offend the stillness of the night, or the firefly the stars?
<br /><br />And shall your flame or your smoke burden the wind?
<br /><br />Think you the spirit is a still pool which you can trouble with a staff?
<br /><br />Oftentimes in denying yourself pleasure you do but store the desire in the recesses of your being.
<br /><br />Who knows but that which seems omitted today, waits for tomorrow?
<br /><br />Even your body knows its heritage and its rightful need and will not be deceived.
<br /><br />And your body is the harp of your soul,
<br /><br />And it is yours to bring forth sweet music from it or confused sounds.
<br /><br />And now you ask in your heart, 'How shall we distinguish that which is good in pleasure from that which is not good?'
<br /><br />Go to your fields and your gardens, and you shall learn that it is the pleasure of the bee to gather honey of the flower,
<br /><br />But it is also the pleasure of the flower to yield its honey to the bee.
<br /><br />For to the bee a flower is a fountain of life,
<br /><br />And to the flower a bee is a messenger of love,
<br /><br />And to both, bee and flower, the giving and the receiving of pleasure is a need and an ecstasy.
<br /><br />People of Orphalese, be in your pleasures like the flowers and the bees.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b4c29167a871937c8af790b476844696" url=""><![CDATA[The Meaning of the Remembrance<br/><br/>The Meaning of the Remembrance
<br /><br />This is the music of the soul. When he lives in the garden, he sings. God makes this music and he lives in a garden different from any garden he has lived in before. He lives inside the garden of the soul. He has left his body because his body is not important in this religion. From the beginning, his body must be left outside and must be kept clean. Each follower lives with his God at the height of politeness. He knows the meaning of politeness and his heart is very beautiful. When he begins to sin, his soul begins to speak and he knows the meaning of every word he sings. When he beings to remember the unity, he sees only the face of God. He sees light coming from the letters of the name, and each letter becomes bigger and bigger. He is empty of all but God, and lives in the heart of his God, facing Him soul to soul. This is the life, the only life. When he leaves everything outside and loses himself in the heart of God, he feels beauty and peace. He has left his heart and his soul. He has left everything and lives only for God. He returns to the first world, the world of pre-eternity (al-azal), before creation.
<br /><br />If anyone wants to remember the name, he must first wash, wash with the holy water of truth. This is the way of courtesy. He returns to the source of this courtesy each time he washes. He must open his heart and his ear to be washed in it water, which takes him from this earth to the world of the soul, to the light. He is cleaned of all unnecessary qualities and is reborn every minute. In each remembrance of the name, he cleans his heart and soul. Everyone needs this cleaning. He wants his soul to live free in the world of al-azal, to return to his origin. This is the true place of his birth before he came into this world. He lives with his soul because he has the knowledge of the name, and lives only with his God in each remembrance. The remembrance of the name needs to be done by a special person, in a special place, and at a special time. This remembrance is very holy. It is like the peace; it is not for everyone. If any of these three are not present then the remembrance is forbidden. They all must be joined together to make the dhikr complete. When the student makes the dhikr, he lives in the garden of the soul, in a high station. As he says the name, he speaks with his God, soul to soul. It is necessary for him to be with God all the time, not just when making adh-dhikr, but to be facing his God at any time, at any place, and to be in constant dhikr. Everyone needs to be in remembrance of the name continually, all his life, and to be with God always, not just at a certain time. In this way he reaches God Who is his Master. Each time he remembers, he remembers himself because he has returned to the source and there is no difference between him and his God. God does not need this remembrance. He is very rich, but each time he remembers His name, he cleans his soul to be one with his Beloved.
<br /><br />When he reaches this high station, it is of the highest courtesy to remember His name in a low voice. If He is inside you, and you live with Him all your time, why do you speak loudly to Him? He listens inside you. If you speak in a loud voice, you are not being polite with Him. You need the highest politeness when you sit with your Lord. In the beginning the student can remember in a loud voice because he does not have the knowledge, but when he reaches, he needs to be very quiet and to remember in his hear and softly on his lips. Be silent and very polite when you remember His name.
<br /><br />When a person does not know, he does not say anything. Then when he wants to know, he begins to remember the name all the time. This remembering is necessary for him to become complete. When he is complete, he remembers himself and no other. Because he has become one with the name, when he remembers the name of God, he also remembers himself. He is the mirror of God, for Him to see Himself reflected. Each remembrance cleans this mirror to reflect only the qualities of God.
<br /><br />He needs to change his body from station to station, not stopping with the body. Leave the world (ad-dunya) and begin to live inside, but know that there is no outside and no inside. All is one when he remembers the name. This is the meaning of adh-dhikr, the remembrance. You are the remembrance. There is no difference between you and Him. When a student reaches and is complete, there is no difference between him and his Lord - he is His mirror. But in the beginning he must follow every word God has given him and every order. He must pray and send love and mercy to everyone and know the meaning of this mercy. Begin with yourself. Help yourself first. Send love and mercy to yourself. After you have helped yourself, then you can send mercy and love to another. You cannot send mercy if you do not see the mercy in every face. Love everything because everything in this world is the picture of God. Without love, you cannot reach. And without giving mercy and being courteous with everyone, you can not reach.
<br /><br />Listen to every word and search for its meaning to know Who speaks with you. There is nothing and no one, only He. If you see another, then you are still not witnessing the complete truth because every picture fades into one picture, after a time. When the remembrance becomes complete in your being, you will see only one picture and know there is nothing, only He. Know that you are the question and you are the answer, and you are everything. When you stop making differences between the outside and the inside, you can touch the secret inside you because the outside and the inside are the same.
<br /><br />This is the meaning of the remembrance. When you remember the name of God, you live in the garden. There are many gardens when you reach God, but He wants you to live in the garden of the soul, now, not tomorrow! Not after you die, but now. You can feel happiness and peace and you can touch Him in your hand. Do not stop or go slowly, if you want Him. I have said enough! Allah!Allah
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="49f00bca81dc8a9af3eb2b68000ae4c9" url=""><![CDATA[The Love<br/><br/>The Love
<br /><br />When you find the love, you find yourself. The secret is in the love. You are the love, not another. Everything is in the love, and everyone needs the love. If you find this, what more could you want? When you know, what could you want? When you have the knowledge of the love, you feel peace in your heart. The jewels are inside you. This is the holy meaning. When you understand, then you are the meaning, the holy meaning. But look and reach so that you find every meaning and do not hesitate because inside every meaning is the quality of the love. The love has seven qualities and this love knows no differences. If the Muslims, Jews, Christians, and the people of any other religion, knew their religion well, there would only be one religion, the religion of love and peace and mercy.
<br /><br />Leave everything outside that is not useful and give everything to God to live inside His garden of love. Remember then name of God at every waking moment, and you will find Him beside you, to help you to walk in the way. Be courteous with everyone you meet. Give the mercy to help them to know the meaning of this love. Give and listen to everyone who speaks to you. Listen with the ear of your heart because this is the voice of God speaking to you, trying to help you to know Him. If you hear another voice, it is wrong. Open your heart to God and He will give you everything. Then your heart will fell quiet and you will only see the love, on the love.
<br /><br />You are the reflection of God. There is nothing, only He. Where is another? Give everything to God and you will begin to know yourself. When God made you, He made beauty. Live with the people on the outside, but hear only your God. Those who live in the outside world are like jewels that need cleaning. They need the fire to burn away all their imperfections so that the jewel may reflect its inner beauty. If you are not clean, how can you find the love? The Sufi way is the straight way - walking a straight path to God, letting nothing on either side block the vision of the straight way. I will ask God to send mercy and peace to everyone because He is the Peace.
<br /><br />If you want God, remember that He gives you what you want. Don’t be afraid. God will not give to you anything that is not good. We must see God in the face of every human being. When you walk and when you sleep, remember the name of God because He knows no time. When you pray to God, pray only to love Him. Do not pray for Him to put you in the garden. God throws out a net, and when He catches you in this net, then you are in the garden. Every student needs God.
<br /><br />When He helps you to find Him, then pray, and when you look into another’s eyes, see the reflection of God looking at you. Understand that inside every word is a message or a sign from God. See the picture of God in every person that you meet.
<br /><br />All the troubles in the world are necessary. If there was no darkness, how could there be light? If you did not see sadness, how could you see happiness? Be courteous to everyone and see the face of God in every person, but know that the people on the outside carry two faces. On the inside they carry the face of God, but on the outside, the face of the shaitan. Be polite with both faces, and when you see someone angry or shouting, know Who speaks to you. Everyone has put himself in his place and this is the station for that person. Be polite with him and give him mercy. Be with God all the time and do not speak with anyone from the outside unless it is necessary.
<br /><br />Give your time for God and he will change you from station to station, cleaning your heart of everything that is not good. This is the message of the prophets. It is a difficult way and at the same time a very easy way. When anyone wants to know God, He will help anyone to walk the straight way.
<br /><br />Follow one guide to take you by the hand, to guide you from the darkness to the light. He will make the walking easy for you and then you can rest. If you go from here to there, you lose time. The student of the family of God rests because he lives in the garden. When anyone knows why he lives and walks in this created world, then he begins to know himself. We are here only to know Him. Live all the time in the garden of love. When your heart feels love, then everything around you is quiet and at peace. This is from the message, but not all the message. Live to love and to know God.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8c69475bb7de72354c932a87c9e2a8a0" url=""><![CDATA[DifferenceBetween The Shaitan and the Nafs<br/><br/>I have been wondering about the difference between the shaitan and the nafs. There is also a shaitan spirit that I have read about. How do you know when something is from the shaitan or the nafs or does it matter?
<br /><br />Surely, my beloved, when the person, the student, is the beloved of Allah, if he is the beloved of Allah, Allah does not give him to the devil. He does not leave him to the devil, but He is always with him, and helping him. The shaitan tries to conquer him and speaks to the nafs. If the person is not careful and he listens to the voice of the devil through the nafs, if he follows God, this means that it is important for him to return back to God, and to remember, and to look to see if this is from the Order of Allah or not.
<br /><br />For example: A voice comes to your mind saying, “Do not pray. Why do you pray so much? Why do you help? Why do you send peace to that person? This is not right because that person does not need your mercy.” You must look to Allah to see where this voice is from. Does the Word of Allah forbid you to help or to pray? No, this is from the shaitan. It is important to stop and to cut this voice, to remember the Name and to not listen to this voice. Then you help yourself and you conquer the shaitan. This is a very deep and very subtle thing. For this reason it is very important for every beloved to be very careful about what he does, and it is important to know that Allah does not leave you. He is always with you; He helps you. Try to say the Name of Allah when you see that something happens to your heart and you are weak, then you will see that He helps you. The shaitan is very weak and the believer is very strong; he conquers the devil so that the devil can not make anything with him.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3392ef026db2b2a5e0f168eaa83cdd29" url=""><![CDATA[How can I find Allah?<br/><br/>How can I find Allah?
<br /><br />If you want to come to Allah, you will find Him beside you. If you want Allah, you must be polite because Allah is not outside of you. First look inside. Many people read about the truth (al-haqq) because they want to know, but Allah is not with a person if he does not want to know Allah from his heart. Allah will not give you this truth unless you are sincere. If you are not sincere with everything, you will not reach. This is your message.
<br /><br />You cannot know the truth if you do not weep for the time you have lost. If you truly wan to know Allah, He will give you everything. But your must be clean. How else can he give you what you want? Allah puts everything in it place.
<br /><br />Allah is very rich. He can give anyone what He ants. If a person wants money, He can give him money, or love, or mercy. All this is easy for Him. If you want Him, this is difficult, but you can reach if He helps you. If you walk straight, you will find Allah; but if you do not walk straight, how will you find Allah?
<br /><br />Allah can bring you from America or Europe or anywhere and put you in this place. If anyone wants Allah he can come to this house and Allah will lead him to find Him. Then you can pray and reach what you want. You can reach Allah because He has given you the time to thank Him.
<br /><br />The truth is very expensive. The price of truth is everything. But if you can give everything to Allah, Allah will give you everything. You are everything and He gives you Himself. You are His picture, so keep this picture for Him; not everyone has this chance. You must be in prayer all your time, and no one can contain you except the family of Allah.
<br /><br />You need to remember the Name of Allah. You need the time to pray and to remember the Name of Allah to walk in the way. To know the meaning of the way it is important to pray, so do not leave the prayer. If you leave this prayer and remembrance, you leave the meaning of the family of Allah. When you reach, you need to remember everything, and understand what you have reached to know everything. Pray in your tongue but also in the eye of your heart Allah
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c028cd6e6d0e14b104ce88df3be8ff4c" url=""><![CDATA[Man Ant: Who Are You?<br/><br/>Man Ant: Who Are You?
<br /><br />If you know why God made you in this world, then you begin to know everything. When you know why God made you and why He put you in this place, then you will know the secret of yourself. He has made everyone to know why He has made them - not to eat, not to sleep, but only to know Him. When you have this knowledge, then you can go and give it to anyone who wants to become complete. But you cannot know if you do not walk in the way, God’s special way.
<br /><br />First you must begin to know yourself because everything that matters is inside you, not outside. All the secrets are inside you and you are the holy secret. If you know yourself, then you can touch the secret with your hand, but with a new hand. God has changed everything in you because He is the Mercy. Why do you search outside? God put the mercy inside you. When you know the secret of the mercy and understand its meaning, then you begin to know Him. Many people feel the mercy and want it but can neither take it nor give it because the mercy is not inside them. If you want to know, then you must open your heart and remember the name of God. Listen to what He says, and do not refuse any order at any time. He send the orders, not only to the prophets, but to everyone. He has sent and taught the order to all the prophets. Then He took the qualities from the prophets and put them in the guides because there are no more prophets now, only guides. God teaches the guide, soul to soul.
<br /><br />When you were born the first time, I do not mean in this world, but in pre-eternity, God said, “I made the human being from one soul and then I put in the numbers.” He put the numbers on the outside because on the inside there are no numbers. He also said, “I made the sides (places), but really there are no sides, and I have made many people, but really there is only One - Me.”
<br /><br />You are Adam, the same Adam as when God made the first picture. You are the beginning, but then the picture goes. God put all the qualities in Adam, but where is Adam? There is no Adam, only God. Yet what He put in Adam, He also put in you. You see many pictures, but really there is only one picture. It is like a mirror. You look and you see your face, but whose reflection is this? The qualities are the same. For example, Allah has put the quality of hearing in your ear, but for what ? Only to hear His voice. Return this quality to Him. He has given the human being all His ninety-nine qualities and He speaks through all of them. When He wants any of these qualities, He takes them. One of the qualities is al-Hayy, the Living. This is a special quality from which all of the other   qualities flow. When the order comes to die, where do you go? There is no place. He wants you to return to your origin in the first world (al-azal). He wants you to    return to Him.
<br /><br />You see all the qualities in every person, but really they are only a veil for Him. If you see a quality and it is different from the name, then you are not looking from the truth. Every quality is the same as the name. If you say, “This is my quality,” you are wrong. No quality is yours. But if you find the real meaning of this quality and you know where it is from, then I say that when you leave this world, you do not die. This quality remains because it is from God and God does not go. You are the mirror of God. He wants to see Himself inside your reflection. That is why He put these qualities in you. But you cannot keep any quality for yourself. You are the holy name and the secret, but know the meaning of the secret. If you return all the qualities right now, then you can understand the secret. You are the name and you are very holy, but know the name. Know Who walks, and know Who speaks, and know Who makes everything!
<br /><br />Every material thing you see in this world, like radio and television, for example, would be entirely different if you came here in a thousand years. This is by His hand because He wants to speak through these things, so when you use these things, know Who is speaking with you. This is the voice of God Who speaks on the radio or television. Where is the voice that inspires people to make these things? One may think, this is from my mind, I made it. Yet God put the secret in everything and He wants everyone to see it. When you listen and understand what this voice is, then you know that it is the voice of God. So when you ask, “Who made it,” you know that God put the secret inside this person who made it, to speak with you. God says, “I am here in everything. You can hear me.”
<br /><br />God put His light in every picture. When you erase this picture and look with the eye of your soul, and you look from the inside to the inside, you will find the answer. But you need to break your tomb. You need to break your body and to break your soul. If you do not break your tomb, you have wasted your time. If you do not break your tomb, you cannot wake up. When I say break, what I mean is clean. Make all the qualities in your body pure. Be the slave of God. Be the mercy and be courteous with everyone. Help everyone because they are all the reflections of God, but they do not understand what they are. This is your chance to know who you are.
<br /><br />He has helped you; why not help another who needs help? All the people in this world need the peace. They search now to find the peace. If you want to find peace, you must first break your tomb. You cannot feel quiet if you do not leave your body because you feel trouble where you are now. God wants everyone to wake up from his sleep. He wants everyone to be special for Him. Clean and clean and clean your heart! You need to change and to clean everything, beginning with your body. After that you need to clean your heart because the heart is the ruler of your body. If the ruler is not clean, then how can the body be clean? If a ruler sits among the people and he is not good, how do the people live? Your body has a special government and this government is very holy. You must change your heart to be the house of God. God will not some to sit in a house if that house is not clean.
<br /><br />How do you clean your body? From the beginning, you must believe in every order that God sent through His prophets. Do not make differences between any of them of any of the holy books because every word has a deep meaning, but not everyone understands. He has sealed every word in the last book and in the last Prophet. Muhammad, may the blessings and peace of Allah be upon him, is the Prophet of love. If you walk, you must listen and not refuse any order that He has given. Do not harm anyone. Send mercy to everyone. Do not steal. Do not sleep with anyone unless you are married. Be righteous. Pray to Him, and also pray for yourself. God does not need this praying, but He want to clean you when you pray, to clean all the unnecessary qualities. When you pray, you pray for the quality of the guide.
<br /><br />How do you pray? Who is speaking with your tongue when you pray? God speaks with your tongue. This is the secret. When you begin to walk in the way, you need to remember the name all the time, when you are awake and when you are asleep. Only your body sleeps, but the qualities within you do not sleep. For example, when you dream, you see many things and you feel many things, some good and some bad. Another sleeping beside you does not feel the same thing you do. When you dream, sometimes you live in the garden and sometimes you live in the fire. But do you? Not really. This is what it is like in this life. Why does the person sleeping beside you not feel what you feel? Because your soul is not in your body. Your soul is free and travels fast and far. What is the meaning of this? This is the secret, but He wants to show you some of the secret. Sometimes you sit here, and in one moment your soul travels to Holland or to somewhere else. When you give everything and you are beginning to know, then He can give you everything in one moment. So give. But what do you have to give? You have nothing, yet He says, “Give to Me.” What He really wants from you is for your to be special for Him, to be clean and to be a slave. This is the real life and there is no life like this life, if you reach.
<br /><br />This is my life. I want all the family and anyone who lives in this world to be feeling what I feel. This is your message. Everyone needs to live in peace, to live with the peace and the mercy, and to live in the garden. Everyone! God made all the people to live in the garden, but for those who refuse what He wants, what can he make for those people? Nothing. If you refuse, how can you take? But He helps everyone because He is the Mercy and He is the Love. If you do not love, you cannot have what you want because everything is in the love.
<br /><br />Love everything. When you love everything, you love God. Then you know the real meaning of the love. If a person who lives outside loves a woman, he loves like everyone would love. But when he reaches and he understands the deep love and he is complete, living only for his beloved God, then he really loves. Then he knows the deep love, and this love is different from the love of those who live outside. This is the true love. Be loved, be loved, beloved. This is a special message and a holy one. What are you? (man ant).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e46d759cbf3554b0a3b55e2818e04a9b" url=""><![CDATA[What does it mean to have the real love?<br/><br/>What does it mean to have the real love?
<br /><br />The real love is when you give the love to a person you do not love and who does not love you, to give him the chance to open his heart. If you are not thirsty, you do not need water but the person who is thirsty needs water. If you are not sick, you do not need medicine but the person who is sick needs medicine. Those who do not have love are sick. It is important for you to open your heart, and for you to give. This is the real love. Believe me, I could send one word to those kind of people and in one moment they would leave, but this is not the way because God asks me about the reasons he made me the guide for the love. See what Allah makes everywhere. There is a difference, my beloved, inside the heart of the real Muslim, deep inside.
<br /><br />The Prophet Muhammad may peace and blessings are upon him, told his people not to kill women, not to cut down trees, not to kill animals or any birds. This is what he said to his soldiers. You want to give medicine to the person who needs the medicine. If anyone refuses your religion, still you keep him. If he wants to be Christian, you let him. Show him the message if he wants, and if he refuses, give him the chance that he wants. Allah says, “If anyone touches anyone or kills anyone, it is like he kills me.” This is the real message about the peace.
<br /><br />This is the real Islam, but the Muslims do not understand Islam. They say, “Why?” This is not from the Islam. But the real Islam…look deep and you will see. And this is a picture of what I have spoken about happening now. You can see the separation. If something happens there are people who are killed, and this is not my message. My message is the Message of Allah, and I am very careful. I say care. If anyone is wounded, help him, and give to him, and take him to his home without why or what. Follow the Teachings of your Government. Be Jesus of your time for everyone. Allah makes what He makes. 
<br /><br />Excuse me…Allah Hu Allah
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>