<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="13">
		<document id="64a2441bfa08f0cd47a55bc860efc933" url=""><![CDATA[Things<br/><br/>Starting to be very good friends again with the assistant manager at work. She and I have worked together for a few years now and our friendship has always been on/off/on/off to say the least lol. Pretty soon she is going to be promoted and will be my new boss .. I've been asked if I would like to take her place and be her assistant. I don't know. That is something that I would have to really think about.
<br /><br />Somehow, word has gotten out that I no longer have any interest in dating anymore. I'm getting a lot of grief over it with a few people going as far as to say that I must be gay for making such a choice. I assure you that I am not. I simply have no interest whatsoever. Perhaps in the future? I doubt it but who knows? I see dating and relationships as being just a game to people in today's world. Nobody cares about loyalty, commitment, trust, or even respect for someone other than themselves. Yes, I am a little jaded but this is my choice to make. I'm very happy being with the only person I can trust and count on no matter the circumstances ... Myself. 
<br /><br />I will admit that it hasn't always been all bad. In fact the last woman I dated was able to win my trust quite easily. In many ways I suppose you can say she still holds it even now. But that is a different story and one that I don't wish to think about at the moment.
<br /><br />You wouldn't believe the e-mails I have been getting over the &quot;death wish&quot; posting of mine. Please everyone... let it be ok? Once again it is my choice to live my life how I choose and there is nothing that you can say that will change it. I respectfully do not want your help, sympathy, or your pity least of all. That is not why I said what I did. I write whatever comes to mind at the time regardless of consequences. 
<br />Let me go .. <em>please</em>?
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="54778cff3e2a3733029e564dbd256eca" url=""><![CDATA[I need to shut up<br/><br/>Ever hear that voice inside your head tell you that you really need to shut up? One of these days I will decide to heed it's advice.... Hopefully before I'm unemployeed!
<br /><br />Things are still steadily going downhill at work. At best I have two, perhaps three months, left before we are &quot;reorganized&quot;. Oh goody goody what joy. The cause of all of the strife is two very arrogant manager individuals who couldn't managed their way out of a paper sack. I'm referring of course to our ton of joy market manager and whatevertitlehegiveshimselfthisweek food service corporate manager. Our business has such potential to turn a huge profit. We have it all.... 
<br />Great location, friendly service, loyal customer base, access to the best quality merchandise from the top supplier, and an established good name within the community..... (not to mention the fact that our overall location earned second place in the ENTIRE southeast division for the SECOND year in a row!!!)
<br />So why is my little bitty section not booming? We are these people not taking advantage of this and creating an empire? Who freaking knows.. Maybe they were dropped as children? Didn't have enough milk in their fruit loops growing up? Or perhaps the truth is more simply because they can and choose not to. So stupid, so very stupid.
<br /><br />Or .. maybe, just maybe ... it's because I told them both that they are arrogant incompetent p*$&amp;*# that would screw up even a toilet cleaning job if left alone? (a little more colourful spoken but you get the point)
<br /><br />I think I should learn to listen to that voice in my head and shut up from time to time.
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3bcec69610de045838b1d8d8e209ee98" url=""><![CDATA[Bonny Portmore<br/><br/>O Bonny Portmore, I am sorry to see
<br />Such a woeful destruction of your ornament tree
<br />For it stood on your shore for many's the long day
<br />Till the long boats from Antrim came to float it away.
<br /><br />O Bonny Portmore, you shine where you stand
<br />And the more I think on you the more I think long
<br />If I had you now as I had once before
<br />All the Lords in Old England would not purchase Portmore.
<br /><br />All the birds in the forest they bitterly weep
<br />Saying, &quot;Where shall we shelter or where shall we sleep?&quot;
<br />For the Oak and the Ash, they are all cutten down
<br />And the walls of Bonny Portmore are all down to the ground.
<br /><br />O Bonny Portmore, you shine where you stand
<br />And the more I think on you the more I think long
<br />If I had you now as I had once before
<br />All the Lords of Old England would not purchase Portmore.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d41229a1525f12b9cf19e8c7cbf92291" url=""><![CDATA[Stuff<br/><br/>Nothing much to write about. Still tutoring my friend as often as I can. Having a bit of trouble though as her instructor went from basic html to advanced in one lesson. What a nice guy .. just confuse the hell out of all your students. 
<br /><br />Went chasing last week but couldn't find anything good as I had a very late start getting out. Just lots and lots of rain. Maybe next time I'll get lucky.
<br /><br />BTW, I have still yet to find the &quot;person&quot; who killed my little sis. But don't worry ... I won't give up.
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ac49dff7df2a7c86af7406f08a42b51f" url=""><![CDATA[Work<br/><br/>Sorry been so late in posting, having a lot to do in a short amount of time. Trying like hell to save my job while at the same time irritate the one responsible as much as possible. I met with our former Regional Director and another person from the new regional corporate office in Florida, but not sure what they can do to help. The RD is a friend of mine and one the finest individuals I have ever worked for. I wish he was still in charge as the &quot;crap&quot; that has been going on would never be tolerated.
<br />As it stands I have a choice to make. I can be promoted (again) to a QSR Manager and take over the activities of our Millington store or.... become an assistant manager at my current store. It's not really a choice though since the district manager is pushing me to accept her offer of being a QSR Manager (again ugh) so I would be her little puppet and jump nicely through her hoops. For anyone that knows me you'll have already guessed that I don't respond well to the whole being somebody's slave. I don't see myself becoming an assistant manager because that would mean I've rejected her orders (thought it was a choice<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> and there is no way in hell she would ever permit me to change areas. 
<br /><br />so....
<br />I have a meeting with her and a few reps tomorrow so this should be quite interesting! I have a feeling that by this time next week I'll be unemployed. 
<br />BTW, the assistant manager job was supposed to be given to another friend of mine, Jess but she is being screwed out of it. Don't you love how a simple little job can quickly turn into a soap opera? Drama baby drama!!
<br /><br />Oh yeah almost forgot... My friend that I have been tutoring passed her course with flying colours! Man I'm good hee hee
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5c568b0404aed72448b1d165599b6fc5" url=""><![CDATA[Was Fun<br/><br/>Well, it was fun while it lasted. My job officially ends this afternoon. I decided to take my two week vacation starting Friday and to be honest I don't believe I will come back. Not that there is a job to come back to anyway. The district manager is angry with me for not taking her &quot;offer&quot; of a promotion but you know what? Being a slave to somebody just isn't me.
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9a705bc158e0095eb717a4b304246c6e" url=""><![CDATA[?<br/><br/>Still no clue as to what is going on at work. It's interesting how a company can be run when it's management can't seem to get together on anything. We are a classic example of how NOT to run a business.
<br /><br />I'm getting my vacation starting this saturday. I basically told them either give me my two weeks off or I'll give you a two week notice. Just being away from there for only a few days would do a world of difference for me. 
<br /><br />Jess came by for a few minutes today. It was very nice to get to see her. She looked beautiful. I only wish we could have talked for a bit but we both had other matters to attend to. 
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="494d8b8828b6ee984f147218f26e60d7" url=""><![CDATA[Vacation<br/><br/>Bonjour!
<br /><br />Leaving for Paris this evening for my vacation.
<br />Be back sometime someday.
<br /><br />À la prochaine, au revoir!
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b63c3e12a1e104bd3dc0870f03965069" url=""><![CDATA[Back<br/><br/>Well... I'm back. I really really didn't want to! I already miss being in Paris.
<br /><br />I finally went and visited my father's grave site. I hadn't gone to see him since the funeral back in 2000. Also, while researching about my little sis I made a huge discovery. My fiancee, who I was told was buried in Michigan with our twins, is actually buried just outside of Paris. I was shocked and speechless to say the least. All this time they have been so close and I never knew it. Of course I shouldn't have been surprised at the deceit since her family hates me. One of those &quot;you don't have enough money and influence, you are below us, you are working class trash&quot; deals. Don't you love those?  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/confused2.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="86ae4c5d7c629991439daeecea598d0c" url=""><![CDATA[wow<br/><br/>Found out today that our District Manager just died of a massive heart attack. Although I did not personally like the woman one bit I still did not wish to see this happen to her and her family. She was only 42 years old! Nine years older than I! 
<br />Really gets you to thinking.
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f8f56c0b20a37c0396160978f46e43af" url=""><![CDATA[Hi<br/><br/>Hi there! Long time no write!
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5dd74dc83ad191d3a6e6596a64d1b272" url=""><![CDATA[Hi<br/><br/>Hi there again.
<br /><br />Adding some more pictures.
<br /><br />~B
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b4a40a0471f2db10b3e74efcf4456ee6" url=""><![CDATA[new<br/><br/>You can find me here:
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2FTepengaPK"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.facebook.com/TepengaPK</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>