<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="870eef48995e2aab57a484becc12b073" url=""><![CDATA[drums<br/><br/>got my new travis barker drumsticks lol paid 20 pound for them lol
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="859670561b16b26833d50921be588289" url=""><![CDATA[all<br/><br/>hey gals pm if u wanna chat thankees <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b82a004652b0a82edd746a17f4164c5d" url=""><![CDATA[HELLO ALL<br/><br/>hey guys and gals add me as a friend im bored and need someone to talk to 
<br />thanks<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />james
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="27da930822438da51c2fe3f205f2eeee" url=""><![CDATA[Lucky 100<br/><br/>hey all i need one more friend to make the lucky one hundred <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />leave me a motivation note when trying to become my friend and ill pick the person with the best comment 
<br /><br />its like a Prize draw lmao
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="558aa34ec2d6e33119da0bb334242ac1" url=""><![CDATA[ONLY 55 PEOPLE CAN READ THIS<br/><br/>ONLY 55 PEOPLE CAN READ THIS...CAN YOU? Body: Cdnuolt blveiee taht I cluod aulaclty uesdnatnrd waht I was rdanieg. The phaonmneal pweor of the hmuan mnid, aoccdrnig to a rscheearch at Cmabrigde Uinervtisy, it dseno't mtaetr in waht oerdr the ltteres in a wrod are, the olny iproamtnt tihng is taht the frsit and lsat ltteer be in the rghit pclae. The rset can be a taotl mses and you can sitll raed it whotuit a pboerlm. Tihs is bcuseae the huamn mnid deos not raed ervey lteter by istlef, but the wrod as a wlohe. Azanmig huh? yaeh and I awlyas tghuhot slpeling was ipmorantt! if you can raed tihs rpsoet it. Strange..isn't it? ONLY REPOST IF YOU CAN READ THIS. CHANGE THE NUMBER AT TOP THOUGH, &quot;ONLY __ PEOPLE CAN READ THIS...CAN YOU?&quot; go up a number if you can read it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f77aa21beacad3d88bfe8a4a0141a4a5" url=""><![CDATA[Kissing Language<br/><br/>People with crooked teeth usually Kiss BETTER than people with straight teeth...
<br /><br />-- When you chew gum before you kiss, it actually makes your breath SMELL WORSE than before because of your salivary glands...
<br /><br />// Mints work MUCH better. &lt;3 &lt;3 &lt;3
<br /><br />`*GUYS; It is much more ROMANTiC to kiss girls in a fancy restaurant or UNDER THE STARS than to kiss in your disgusting bedroom or in the movie theaters
<br /><br />`*GiRLS; Just because a guy kisses you every 10 minutes doesn't mean he’s using you ...he's just a little horny &amp;&amp; there`s no problem with that !!!
<br /><br />-- It has been PR0VEN that when people with the SAME Hair C0L0R kiss, it is more R0MANTiC than that of a different hair color!!!
<br /><br />[(WE D0NT KNOW WHY)]
<br /><br />-- your First Kiss isn’t always your BEST Kiss
<br /><br />-- If you can tie a KN0T in a CHERRY with your tongue, it doesn't mean you are a good kisser .. it just means your TOUNGE MUSCLE is strong
<br /><br />-- ALL GiRLS are NOT hoes, and ALL GUYS are NOT PLAYERS .. EVERYONE gets a LiTTLE H0RNY sometimes
<br /><br />BE A GREAT KiSSER W/ THESE TiPS
<br /><br />-- T0UCH HiS/HER FACE
<br /><br />-- RUN Y0UR FiNGERS THR0UGH HiS/HER HAiR
<br /><br />-- KiSS S0FTLY AT FiRST, THEN APPLY M0RE PRESSURE
<br /><br />-- H0LD Y0UR KiSSiNG PARTNER
<br /><br />Kissing Language (yup, it's a language)
<br />if a kiss is the Language of Love,
<br />then we have a lot to talk about it...
<br /><br />methods of Love....
<br /><br />+kiss on the ear--------------------&quot;i'm horny&quot;
<br />+kiss on the cheek-----------------&quot;we're friends&quot;
<br />+kiss on the hand------------------&quot;i adore you&quot;
<br />+kiss on the neck-------------------&quot;we belong together&quot;
<br />+kiss on the shoulder--------------&quot;i want you now&quot;
<br />+kiss on the lips---------------------&quot;i love you&quot; or &quot;i want you&quot;
<br />+holding hands-----------------------&quot;we can learn to love each other&quot;
<br />+a wink---------------------------------&quot;Let's get it on&quot;
<br />+slap on the butt---------------------&quot;thats mine&quot;
<br />+playing with the ear----------------&quot;i can't live without you&quot;
<br />+holding on tight---------------------&quot;don't let go&quot;
<br />+looking into each other's eyes---&quot;let's get romantic&quot;
<br />+playing with hair on head---------------&quot;tell me you love me&quot;
<br />+arms around the waist -----------&quot;i love you too much to let go&quot;
<br />+laughing while kissing-----------&quot;i am completley comfortable w/you&quot;
<br /><br />=advice=
<br />***if you're kissing someone, close your eyes. it's not nice to stare...
<br /><br />=requirements=
<br />post this again after reading!!...or you'll have a bad year of relationship
<br /><br />If you REALLY LIKE (or LOVE) SOMEONE right now AND MISS THEM and can't get them out of your head or ur crushin on someone then re-post this within 1 minute and whoever you are missing will surprise you tomorrow
<br /><br />Repost this as KISSING LANGUAGE
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="230f595b42126d1780c24418fac7003d" url=""><![CDATA[Ask me<br/><br/>You can ask me one question + one question only, + i have to answer it, HONESTLY.
<br /><br />Stick this on your blog, you'll be surprised at some of the things you get asked!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6a35341b40e280b512add719f41422c8" url=""><![CDATA[sex poems<br/><br/>roses are red
<br />Lemons are sour
<br />Open ur legs and give me an hour
<br /><br />Kissing Is A Habit
<br />Fucking Is A Game
<br />Guys Get All The Pleasure
<br />Girls Get All The Pain
<br />10 Minutes Of Pleasure
<br />9 Months Of Pain
<br />3 Days In The Hospital
<br />A Baby Without A Name
<br />The Baby Is A Bastard
<br />The Mother Is A Whore
<br />This Woulda Never Happend If The Rubber Hadn't Tore!!
<br /><br />Sex is like math
<br />You subtract the clothes
<br />Add the bed
<br />Divide the legs
<br />And Pray to god
<br />You dont multiply
<br /><br />Roses are red
<br />Grass is green
<br />Open your legs
<br />And I'll fill you with cream
<br /><br />Hickory dickory dock
<br />This bitch was suckin my cock
<br />The clock struck two
<br />I dumped my goo
<br />And dumped her to the end of the block
<br /><br />Sex is good
<br />Sex is fine
<br />Doggy Style &amp; 69
<br />Just for fun
<br />Or gettin paid
<br />Everyone likes gettin laid
<br /><br />Sex is evil
<br />Sex is a sin
<br />Sins are forgiven
<br />So stick it in!!!
<br /><br />u opened it so u r cursed for 5 yrs. u need to read it ENTIRELY!!
<br /><br />roses are nice
<br />violets are fine.
<br />ill be the six
<br />if you be the nine.
<br /><br />Repost this as ''sex poems''
<br /><br />if u repost this in 1 min: the guy /girl that you like will tell u that he/she loves u and that he/she wants to go out with u.
<br /><br />if u repost this in 2 min: the guy/girl that you like will give you a hug and a kiss on the cheek
<br /><br />if u repost this in 3 min: you'll find $20 while your out shopping
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c51096c02fc6a48ec4de6de75302e366" url=""><![CDATA[90z KIDZ<br/><br/>ANYBODY UNDER THE AGE OF 13 SHOULD NOT RE-POST THIS. JUST CAUSE YOU
<br />WERE BORN IN '93' OR '94' DOES NOT MEAN YOU ARE A 90s KID. IT'S NOT LIKE YOU COULD REMEMBER SOME OF THE ORIGINAL SIMPSONS.
<br /><br />YOU KNOW YOU'RE A 90s KID IF...
<br /><br />YOU CAN SING THE RAP TO &quot;THE FRESH PRINCE OF BELL AIR&quot;
<br /><br />YOU'VE WORN LEGGINGS AND FELT COOL.
<br /><br />YOU USED TO LOVE PLAYING WITH YOUR &quot;PUPPY IN MY POCKETS&quot;
<br /><br />YOU REMEMBER WHEN IT WAS ACTUALLY WORTH GETTING UP ON A SATURDAY MORNING TO WATCH LIVE &amp; KICKING OR SM:TV.
<br /><br />YOU HAD A HUGE FRINGE AT SOME POINT IN YOUR CHILDHOOD.
<br /><br />YOU REMEMBER READING AND WATCHING &quot;GOOSEBUMPS&quot;
<br /><br />YOU TOOK PLASTIC CARTOON LUNCH BOXES TO
<br /><br />SCHOOL.
<br /><br />YOU KNOW THE WORDS FROM THE SHAKEY JAKE MILKSHAKE ADVERTS
<br /><br />YOU REMEMBER THE CRAZE OF YO-YOS AND TAMAGOTCHI'S
<br /><br />YOU STILL GET THE URGE TO SAY &quot;NOT&quot; AFTER EVERY SENTENCE. NOT.
<br /><br />YOU KNEW THAT KIMBERLY, THE PINK RANGER, AND TOMMY, THE GREEN RANGER WERE MEANT TO BE.
<br /><br />YOU COLLECTED POKEMON CARDS.
<br /><br />YOU PLAYED AND/OR COLLECTED POGS.
<br /><br />YOU HAD A WEIRD ALIEN THAT LIVED IN GOOEY STUFF IN A PLASTIC 'POD' AND THOUGHT IF YOU STUCK 2 BACK TO BACK THEY WOULD HAVE A BABY!
<br /><br />YOU WATCHED THE ORIGINAL POSTMAN PAT, FIREMAN SAM AND NINJA TURTLES.
<br /><br />YIKES PENCILS WERE THE BEST!-WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM?
<br /><br />YOU REMEMBER WHEN THE NEW BEANIE BABIES WERE ALWAYS SOLD OUT
<br /><br />YOU GOT YOUR MUM TO BUY 'BN' BISCUITS
<br /><br />YOU USED TO WEAR THOSE
<br /><br />STICK ON EARRINGS, NOT ONLY ON YOUR EARS BUT
<br />AT THE CORNERS OF YOUR EYES.
<br /><br />YOU KNOW THE MACERENA BY HEART.
<br /><br />&quot;TALK TO THE HAND&quot; ENOUGH SAID.
<br /><br />YOU REMEMBER THE TIME BEFORE LITERACY AND NUMERACY HOUR EXISTED.
<br /><br />YOU THOUGHT BRAIN FROM &quot;PINKEY AND THE BRAIN&quot; WOULD FINALLY TAKE OVER THE WORLD.
<br /><br />YOU REMEMBER BUM BAGS.
<br /><br />YOU ALWAYS WANTED TO BE ON FUN HOUSE
<br /><br />YOU COLLECTED TAZOS.
<br /><br />2 WORDS, SPICE GIRLS.
<br /><br />RE-POST THIS IF YOU ARE A 90s KID AND CAN RELATE TO ANY OF THESE
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12457f5285a3a32f9c12cbef42aef646" url=""><![CDATA[hallo<br/><br/>hey all u gorgeous girlies add me please i need more of you to be my friends <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />thanks
<br /><br />james 
<br />x
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ae083851b18664b2eefe4e2266f751fd" url=""><![CDATA[blue/green eyes<br/><br/>BLUE EYES
<br /><br />People with blue eyes last the longest in relationships. They are kind, pretty or handsome,very good kissers and are really hot. They always fall in love with their closest friends and never understand why. They are very funny, outgoing and don't care what people think or say. They are very satisfying and love to please. Are best in bed. Are straight up WARRIORS when necessary. If you repost this and you have blue eyes you will have the best kiss sometime in the next 5 days.
<br /><br />GREEN EYES
<br />Sex Addicts!!! People with green eyes have the most passion put into relationships,honest and trust worthy, they have long lasting relationships. People with green eyes are also the horniest and most beautiful. are fun and outgoing, love to make people laugh, random as hell, love to pleasure their guy/girl. They long for the touch of another. People with green eyes are very sexy and very attracted towards the opposite sex. tend to cover up true feelings, get scared over relationships.You will meet/stay with the person you're going to spend the rest of your life with if you repost this.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="44dac46963d76fa3e563652f35e7dffb" url=""><![CDATA[cheating hurts<br/><br/>cheating hurts
<br />Girl is on the couch making out with a hot guy, her cellphone rings...
<br /><br />Girl:Hey babe, I'll be right back. I need to take this call.
<br /><br />Boy: Yeah okay. Sure.
<br /><br />She walks into the next room.
<br /><br />Girl: Hey! What's up?
<br /><br />Guy [on her cellphone]: Nothing, hey hun, do you think we could go do something later tonight? What are the chances my boss let me get out early.
<br /><br />Girl: Yeah, sounds great!
<br /><br />Guy [on her cellphone]: Okay. I'm right by your house, I'll come to get you now.
<br /><br />Girl: That's not such a good idea...
<br /><br />Guy [on her cellphone]: Why not?
<br /><br />Girl: I'm busy right now... sorry.
<br /><br />Guy [on her cellphone]: With what? It's our anniversary! You didn't make any other plans did you...?
<br />In her head she yells, CRAP! Throws clothes back on quickly.
<br /><br />Girl: No No... I was just eating... with the family.
<br /><br />Guy [on her cellphone]: But I thought you said your family was away this weekend, up at your resort?
<br /><br />The guy walks into her house, turns the corner into the hallway. Goes downstairs, and finds his best friend on her couch, half un-dressed, trying to pull his pants back on and his girlfriend pulling her shirt over her head.
<br /><br />Guy: What the heck is going on?!
<br /><br />Girl: I can explain! Please listen to me!
<br /><br />Guy: Benny? How could you do this to me! Rachel! I thought you loved me! And yet, your sleeping with MY BEST FRIEND!!!!
<br /><br />Girl: John...!
<br /><br />John with tears in his eyes, he rushes out of room, and slams the door.
<br /><br />Benny climbs out of the window, starts his car, and drives off down the street.
<br /><br />Girl runs after her boyfriend. Yelling....
<br /><br />Girl: NOOOO! Please!! Come back John!! Pleeeeeasssse????!! She falls down and cries.
<br /><br />John turns around, looks straight at his girlfriend in tears.
<br /><br />John: Why? Rachel, why? I loved you! Oh my God, I'm in love with a whore. Does this mean I have to pay you now?!
<br />Here take this as the cash. He drops a ring box on her lap.
<br /><br />She opens the ring box. Her jaw drops... Before her eyes is a diamond wedding ring.
<br /><br />Girl: You were going to propose?
<br /><br />Guy: Yeah... how dumb was I? And as he slowly walked back to his car, his headlights faded... And she was in despair.
<br /><br />Later that night, the girl got a phone call from the police saying he had died of an overdose of drugs and when they found him he had a picture of him and her in his hands
<br /><br />If you love/like someone, and you want them in your life forever. Repost in 380 seconds as &quot;cheating hurts.&quot; Or your true love will walk away from you
<br /><br />Did you no that every night b4 u go to sleep there is 1 person of the opposite sex thinking of you. they want 2 kiss u, they want 2 b with u, they r always thinking about u, this is all true and not fake. if u repost this in 5 min the person that is longing to b with u will approach u within 1 month and ask u out or grab you and kiss u. but if u break this chain no 1 will like u or ask u out again for 5 years
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9f80692d67855927ffbe780b3491b6b6" url=""><![CDATA[gals and guys read!<br/><br/>When you catch a girl
<br />glancing at you,
<br />she wants you to look
<br />back and smile
<br /><br />When a girl bumps into your arm
<br />while walking with you
<br />she wants
<br />you to hold her hand
<br /><br />When she wants a hug
<br />she will just stand there
<br /><br />When u break a girls heart
<br />she still feels it when
<br />you run into each other 3 years later
<br /><br />When a girl is quiet,
<br />millions of things are running through her
<br />mind
<br /><br />When a girl is not arguing,
<br />she is thinking deeply
<br /><br />When a girl looks at you with eyes full of
<br />questions,
<br />she is wondering how long you will be
<br />around
<br /><br />When a girl answers, &quot;I'm fine,&quot; after a
<br />few seconds,
<br />she is not at all fine
<br /><br />When a girl stares at you,
<br />she is wondering why you are playing games
<br /><br />When a girl lays her head on your chest,
<br />she is wishing for you to be hers forever
<br /><br />When a girl says she can't live
<br />without you,
<br />she has made up her mind that you are
<br />her future
<br /><br />When a girl says, &quot;I miss you,&quot;
<br />no one in this world can miss you more
<br />than that
<br /><br />When a girl is mean to you after a break-up
<br />she wants you back, but shes
<br />scared she'll get hurt and knows
<br />you're gone forever
<br /><br />--------GUYS--------------
<br /><br />Guy Facts:
<br /><br />When a guy calls you,
<br />he wants to be with you
<br /><br />When a guy is quiet,
<br />He's listening to you...
<br /><br />When a guy is not arguing,
<br />He realizes he's wrong
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I'm fine.&quot; after a few
<br />minutes
<br />he means it
<br /><br />When a guy stares at you,
<br />he wishes you would care about him and
<br />wonders if you do
<br /><br />When your laying your head on a guy's
<br />chest,
<br />he has the world
<br /><br />When a guy calls/texts/comments you everyday,
<br />he is in love
<br /><br />When a (good) guy tells you he loves you,
<br />he means it
<br /><br />When a guy says he can't live without you,
<br />he's with you til your done
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I miss you,&quot;
<br />he misses you more than you could have
<br />ever missed him or anything else
<br /><br />repost this in 10 minutes and your true
<br />love will
<br />call you
<br /><br />someone was in your mind as you read this
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8a4ecf6acf15ed77e73c0dc0dbaae29b" url=""><![CDATA[what you think<br/><br/>if you could choose any 3 words 2 describe me what would they be? be honest, but be nice. copy and paste this to your blog!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a3992cb234505ca0d37a353ae62afc4" url=""><![CDATA[Favourites<br/><br/>Favourite album: Riot! by paramore
<br /><br />Favourite song: Into oblivion by Funeral For A Friend
<br /><br />Favourite artist: Avenged Sevenfold
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="af565ac9911c272ec7c28970a175959a" url=""><![CDATA[ello all<br/><br/>hey all can you add me pwease people comments welcome and all returned<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9b143c5518495123741aa855acbc8e35" url=""><![CDATA[Heya all<br/><br/>hey all you peeps out there can you add me as a friend please and if u wanna chat pm me 
<br />thanks
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b201532d29c70c68c3594f59293bd0d2" url=""><![CDATA[Girls would you?<br/><br/>ANSWER THE QUESTIONS AS:
<br />Y=Yes N = No M = Maybe
<br /><br />WOULD U???
<br />[ ] Push me into a wall and kiss?
<br />[] Come To My House To Do Nothing But Hangout?
<br />[ ] Slap Me?
<br />[ ] Slap me if i asked you to?
<br />[ ] Kiss Me?
<br />[ ] Let Me Kiss You?
<br />[ ] Watch A Movie With Me?
<br />[ ] Take Me Out To Dinner?
<br />[ ] Take A Shower With Me?
<br />[ ] Take Me Home For The Night?
<br />[ ] Let Me Sleep In Your Bed?
<br />[ ] Take Me Anywhere With You
<br />[ ] Repost This For Me To Answer Your Questions?
<br />[ ] Lock Me In Your room And Take Advantage Of Me?
<br />[] Let me lock you in your room and Take Advantage of you?
<br />[] Let Me Make You Breakfast?
<br />[ ] Make me breakfast?
<br />[ ] Tickle Me?
<br />[ ] Let Me Tickle You?
<br />[ ] Stick Up For Me Uf I Was Being Put Down?
<br />[ ] Instant Message Me?
<br />[ ] Greet Me In Public?
<br />[ ] Hang Out With Me?
<br />[ ] Hold my waist from behind while we are out?
<br />[ ] Bring Me Around Your Friends?
<br /><br />Do You...
<br />[ ] Miss Me?
<br />[ ] Think I'm Sexy?
<br />[] Think I'm Cute?
<br />[ ] Think I'm Hot?
<br />[] Think I'm Ok?
<br />[ ] Think I'm Ugly?
<br />[ ] Want To Kiss Me?
<br />[ ] Want To Cuddle With Me?
<br />[ ] Want To Date Me?
<br /><br />Am I...
<br />[ ] Smart?
<br />[ ] Funny?
<br />[ ] Cool?
<br />[ ] Loveable?
<br />[] Adorable?
<br />[ ] Great To Be With?
<br />[ ] Attractive?
<br />[ ] Mean?
<br />[ ]ugly?
<br /><br />Have You Ever...
<br />[ ] Thought About Hooking Up With Me?
<br />[ ] Found Yourself Wanting To Kiss Me Non Stop?
<br />[ ] Wished I Were There?
<br />[ ] Had A Crush On Me?
<br />[ ] Wanted My Number?
<br />[ ] Had A Dream About Me?
<br />[ ] Been Distracted By Me?
<br /><br />Are You...
<br />[ ] Happy You Know Me?
<br />[ ] Thinking About Me
<br />[ ] my friend
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="79b8237f71e590bece2563137ba8ca86" url=""><![CDATA[ello<br/><br/>hey all give me some comments and sign ma g book all returned 
<br />if u want to chat then pm me or add me as a friend.
<br /><br />thanks
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8000e66391020c90a8760b53c2ea8cb5" url=""><![CDATA[fill in<br/><br/>Bet you won't give it to me.
<br />Name:___________________Number:___________________- - - - - - - - - - Best time to call:__________________I dare you to copy and paste this and see how many numbers you get.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4404bf2b6099d170b79a4c35c594851c" url=""><![CDATA[everyone<br/><br/>hey all add me as a friend please
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c805cae561df4ccf1790288eb9d2a7ee" url=""><![CDATA[hey<br/><br/>hey can all you lovely ladies out there add me as a friend please xxx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f38fbcf61243f6768b18ad3cc9166dea" url=""><![CDATA[all people :)<br/><br/>heya all leave me some comments please as im sat at home with a severely broken arm need some cheerin up thank=s all xx <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/thumbsup.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88f415d061a179e99c3b004bc9f334f8" url=""><![CDATA[please do peeps x<br/><br/>Come on girls 
<br />You can ask me 5 questions 
<br />They can be as rude, clean or wierd as u like 
<br /><br />1. 
<br /><br />2. 
<br /><br />3. 
<br /><br />4. 
<br /><br />5.
<br /><br />answers returned through mail <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>