<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="15">
		<document id="7e4575b44d415d1b0058d19999210aaa" url=""><![CDATA[Why is YouTube Slow? Learn How to Fix If Your YouTube is Run<br/><br/>Nothing is also said about what will be done with the information that is shared (Clifford, 1999).<br /><br />Another issue with managed care companies is the large volume of data processed and the carelessness in handling medical information. A salient example deals with lost records as noted in a 1993 survey sample of San Francisco Bay Area psychologists. In this survey, 59% of reports were mailed or faxed to wrong persons, charts accidentally switched, or proper authorization not obtained (Clifford, 1999).<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Maintaining and Protecting Electronic Private Medical Information&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />In order to maintain and protect valued private medical information, we must always be vigilant and proactive. Basic steps can be taken prior to using electronic information sharing. For example, when signing a &quot;Release of Information&quot; form, read everything carefully. If not clearly understood, ask questions. Also, remember that HIPAA grants you the right to request that your healthcare provider restrict the use or disclosure of your medical information. Make sure those who ask for information are properly identified and authorized to collect this information. Finally, make sure that the person collecting information uses at least two &quot;identifiers&quot; to ensure proper identification of patient (e.g. name, last four of social security number, address, telephone, number, birth date etc.<br /><br />When dealing with electronic and computerized medical information, the situation gets more tenuous and much more complex. Secure networks and websites, passwords, firewalls, and anti-virus software, are unquestionably the first steps in a plan of protection. Then there is always the ever present fear of hackers and pranksters retrieving your personal information. There are still so many questions unanswered (Consumer Reports.org, 2006).<br /><br />In conclusion, we are now stuck with a &quot;Cyberspace Monster&quot; and all of its advantages and shortcomings. When we use cyberspace, we can have no expectations of privacy and we must accept a level of risk. Therefore, when transmitting and sharing private medical information, we must be always aware to take precautions in safeguarding our privacy as much as possible by using secure networks, P3P architecture, passwords, firewalls, encryption, message codes, digital signatures, and devices like smart cards and &quot;VeriChips.&quot; Medical records are among the most personal forms of information about an individual, but we are challenged to find a balance between society's interest in protecting medical confidentiality and the legitimate need for timely access to critical medical information especially with fears of influenza pandemics and bioterrorism. When this information is transferred into electronic format, we have heightened concerns about maintaining and protecting this private data. With managed care, there is a demand for an unprecedented depth and breath of personal medical information by an increasing number of players. While the HIPAA provisions are a welcomed start in protecting our private medical information, we must remain vigilant of the ever increasing need to protect this special information.<br /><br />References:<br /><br />Cagliostro, C. (1999) Smart card primer.<br /><br />Clifford, R. (1999) Confidentiality of records and managed care legal and ethical issues.<br /><br />Consumer Reports.org (2006). The new threat to your medical privacy.<br /><br />Diversified Radiology of Colorado (2002) History: HIPAA general information.<br /><br />Mehlman, M. J. (1999) Emerging issues: the privacy of medical records.<br /><br />MSNBC (2004) FDA approves computer chip for humans.<br /><br />Parmet, W. E. (2002) Public health protection and privacy of medical records.<br /><br />Privacy Rights Clearinghouse (2006) Internet privacy resources.<br /><br />Spinello, R. A. (2003) CyberEthics: Morality and law in cyberspace. Jones and Bartlett Publishers, Sudbury, MA<br /><br />Standler, R. B. (1997) Privacy law in the USA.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">reseller vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1142c5b380431534de195c412c1d9b18" url=""><![CDATA[Ethical Considerations of Privacy and Cyber-Medical Informat<br/><br/>This is common in all forms of managed care, but most evident in closed-panel HMOs. This sharing of information increases the fear that the insurer may use the data to limit benefits or terminate insurance coverage (Mehlman, 1999).<br /><br />Some managed care companies are reporting private medical information to an extreme in requiring providers to report to case managers within twenty-four hours any case that is considered a high risk potential for the client, a second party, the employer, or the managed care company. Even with laudatory goals of saving money, making medical care more efficient, and decreasing drug reactions and interactions, there are still inherent dangers to this national plan. There are valid concerns that pharmaceutical companies may attempt to market a new drug or device for your specific medical condition. There are also strong worries of exploitation and abuse of personal data. Who will monitor access to the information? There are also concerns that lenders or employers may rely on private medical information to make business decisions. Then there is always the ever present fear of hackers and pranksters retrieving your personal information. There are still so many questions unanswered (Consumer Reports.org, 2006).<br /><br />In conclusion, we are now stuck with a &quot;Cyberspace Monster&quot; and all of its advantages and shortcomings. When we use cyberspace, we can have no expectations of privacy and we must accept a level of risk. Therefore, when transmitting and sharing private medical information, we must be always aware to take precautions in safeguarding our privacy as much as possible by using secure networks, P3P architecture, passwords, firewalls, encryption, message codes, digital signatures, and devices like smart cards and &quot;VeriChips.&quot; Medical records are among the most personal forms of information about an individual, but we are challenged to find a balance between society's interest in protecting medical confidentiality and the legitimate need for timely access to critical medical information especially with fears of influenza pandemics and bioterrorism. When this information is transferred into electronic format, we have heightened concerns about maintaining and protecting this private data. With managed care, there is a demand for an unprecedented depth and breath of personal medical information by an increasing number of players. While the HIPAA provisions are a welcomed start in protecting our private medical information, we must remain vigilant of the ever increasing need to protect this special information.<br /><br />References:<br /><br />Cagliostro, C. (1999) Smart card primer.<br /><br />Clifford, R. (1999) Confidentiality of records and managed care legal and ethical issues.<br /><br />Consumer Reports.org (2006). The new threat to your medical privacy.<br /><br />Diversified Radiology of Colorado (2002) History: HIPAA general information.<br /><br />Mehlman, M. J. (1999) Emerging issues: the privacy of medical records.<br /><br />MSNBC (2004) FDA approves computer chip for humans.<br /><br />Parmet, W. E. (2002) Public health protection and privacy of medical records.<br /><br />Privacy Rights Clearinghouse (2006) Internet privacy resources.<br /><br />Spinello, R. A. (2003) CyberEthics: Morality and law in cyberspace. Jones and Bartlett Publishers, Sudbury, MA<br /><br />Standler, R. B. &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">buy online vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1b90eba67334ef2125aca25dbd3ac744" url=""><![CDATA[How Can I Access My Email From Another Computer? Remotely Ac<br/><br/>Although the sudden slowdown of the giant video site occurs occasionally at the user side, people are clueless what could be the cause of this problem. It is understood no body wants to wait long for videos to load and then watch them especially if the videos are longer and are in several parts. Faster streaming is the need of every internet user. If YouTube runs slow sometimes then there are surely some reasons behind that. Most people are not sure what to do in such a situation and make the videos load faster in YouTube.<br /><br />Before I share the guidelines to deal with this speed slowdown I would invite you to think of the reasons which result in YouTube errors such as sluggish streaming, flash crashing in YouTube and other YouTube videos errors. There are two major reasons which result in these annoyances. One is the problem at the user end that includes PC speed, Internet speed, PC Windows errors, PC programs conflict such as Flash issues, while the second reason may be caused by the server or external internet traffic load. Although the web site is very effectively maintained there appear some troubles sometimes. This, however, is not a big issue as we all trust the services provided by such a user friendly web site. The issue becomes serious when video errors and slow speed becomes a routine. This has to be something to do with the personal computer one is using.<br /><br />Here I am outlining some tips that will help you to make YouTube faster for you:<br /><br />* Start from repairing your Windows registry and fixing your Windows errors that become the cause of many browser and applications errors causing a conflict situation. &lt;br&gt;* Test your computer for viruses and spyware. &lt;br&gt;* Run SpeedTest to test whether you have sufficient bandwidth available to smoothly play YouTube videos without causing the site to run slower. &lt;br&gt;* Disconnect your internet and then reconnect it to know why is YouTube slow and whether it is because of the poor internet at your side. &lt;br&gt;* Disable ads through some of the browser plug in that will allow you to run fewer background services while you are playing videos online. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your flash player version. Although the YouTube has started to stream videos through a new technology there is still a large number of web sites using the flash platform. So it is a nice idea to try to change the flash player version to play videos without crashes and error messages. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your browser. One good browser to play YouTube videos is Chrome. If you have not tried that go for it. Also contact your ISP provider if they are limiting your bandwidth at specific durations of the day. &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br />Do you need to access your email account from work, school or another location? Many people will inevitably find themselves away from their home or office PC and need to access their emails, programs or transfer files from their host computer for some reason. Most Remote access tools offer a free download and they are very easy to install, the better tools will even allow you to access your emails and transfer files from a Mobile Phone or PDA, how's that for mobility!<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">uk vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">purchase vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9902155cabc50a5cbf63cde366ab0027" url=""><![CDATA[Ethical Considerations of Privacy and Cyber-Medical Informat<br/><br/>The procedure cost is about $150-200 (MSNBC, 2004).<br /><br />Another more commonly used medical information tool is the &quot;smart card,&quot; a credit card sized device with a small-embedded computer chip. This &quot;computer in a card&quot; can be programmed to perform tasks and store important information. During an emergency, paramedics and emergency rooms equipped with smart card readers can rapidly access potentially life-saving information about a patient, such as allergies to medication, and chronic medical conditions. There are different types of smart cards: memory cards, processor cards, electronic purse cards, security cards, and JavaCards. These cards are tamper-resistant, can be PIN protected or read-write protected, can be encrypted, and can be easily updated. These unique features make smart cards advantageous for storing personal medical information and are popular throughout the world. In Germany and Austria, 80 million people have the capability of using these smart cards when they visit their doctor (Cagliostro, 1999).<br /><br />There is also a recent proposed government plan to create a national system of electronic health records (EHRs). Details include the building of a National Health Information Network that will electronically connect all patients' medical records to providers, insures, pharmacies, labs, and claim processors. The sharing of vital information could improve patient care, include more accurate and timely substantiation of claims, and be an asset to public health in emergencies. The goal is to have it operational by 2009. Even with laudatory goals of saving money, making medical care more efficient, and decreasing drug reactions and interactions, there are still inherent dangers to this national plan. There are valid concerns that pharmaceutical companies may attempt to market a new drug or device for your specific medical condition. There are also strong worries of exploitation and abuse of personal data. Who will monitor access to the information? There are also concerns that lenders or employers may rely on private medical information to make business decisions. Then there is always the ever present fear of hackers and pranksters retrieving your personal information. There are still so many questions unanswered (Consumer Reports.org, 2006).<br /><br />In conclusion, we are now stuck with a &quot;Cyberspace Monster&quot; and all of its advantages and shortcomings. When we use cyberspace, we can have no expectations of privacy and we must accept a level of risk. Therefore, when transmitting and sharing private medical information, we must be always aware to take precautions in safeguarding our privacy as much as possible by using secure networks, P3P architecture, passwords, firewalls, encryption, message codes, digital signatures, and devices like smart cards and &quot;VeriChips.&quot; Medical records are among the most personal forms of information about an individual, but we are challenged to find a balance between society's interest in protecting medical confidentiality and the legitimate need for timely access to critical medical information especially with fears of influenza pandemics and bioterrorism. When this information is transferred into electronic format, we have heightened concerns about maintaining and protecting this private data. With managed care, there is a demand for an unprecedented depth and breath of personal medical information by an increasing number of players. While the HIPAA provisions are a welcomed start in protecting our private medical information, we must remain vigilant of the ever increasing need to protect this special information.<br /><br />References:<br /><br />Cagliostro, C. (1999) Smart card primer.<br /><br />Clifford, R. (1997) Privacy law in the USA.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">Top vpn provider</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">Best vpn provider</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="328301eb71fde404cb19fac159138c57" url=""><![CDATA[Ethical Considerations of Privacy and Cyber-Medical Informat<br/><br/>This code is then used to download encrypted medical information. The procedure cost is about $150-200 (MSNBC, 2004).<br /><br />Another more commonly used medical information tool is the &quot;smart card,&quot; a credit card sized device with a small-embedded computer chip. This &quot;computer in a card&quot; can be programmed to perform tasks and store important information. During an emergency, paramedics and emergency rooms equipped with smart card readers can rapidly access potentially life-saving information about a patient, such as allergies to medication, and chronic medical conditions. There are different types of smart cards: memory cards, processor cards, electronic purse cards, security cards, and JavaCards. These cards are tamper-resistant, can be PIN protected or read-write protected, can be encrypted, and can be easily updated. These unique features make smart cards advantageous for storing personal medical information and are popular throughout the world. In Germany and Austria, 80 million people have the capability of using these smart cards when they visit their doctor (Cagliostro, 1999).<br /><br />There is also a recent proposed government plan to create a national system of electronic health records (EHRs). Details include the building of a National Health Information Network that will electronically connect all patients' medical records to providers, insures, pharmacies, labs, and claim processors. The sharing of vital information could improve patient care, include more accurate and timely substantiation of claims, and be an asset to public health in emergencies. The goal is to have it operational by 2009. Even with laudatory goals of saving money, making medical care more efficient, and decreasing drug reactions and interactions, there are still inherent dangers to this national plan. There are valid concerns that pharmaceutical companies may attempt to market a new drug or device for your specific medical condition. There are also strong worries of exploitation and abuse of personal data. Who will monitor access to the information? There are also concerns that lenders or employers may rely on private medical information to make business decisions. Then there is always the ever present fear of hackers and pranksters retrieving your personal information. There are still so many questions unanswered (Consumer Reports.org, 2006).<br /><br />In conclusion, we are now stuck with a &quot;Cyberspace Monster&quot; and all of its advantages and shortcomings. When we use cyberspace, we can have no expectations of privacy and we must accept a level of risk. Therefore, when transmitting and sharing private medical information, we must be always aware to take precautions in safeguarding our privacy as much as possible by using secure networks, P3P architecture, passwords, firewalls, encryption, message codes, digital signatures, and devices like smart cards and &quot;VeriChips.&quot; Medical records are among the most personal forms of information about an individual, but we are challenged to find a balance between society's interest in protecting medical confidentiality and the legitimate need for timely access to critical medical information especially with fears of influenza pandemics and bioterrorism. &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">Top vpn provider</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">Best vpn provider</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9519a78e65730b734cc63664fccce1c8" url=""><![CDATA[Why is YouTube Slow? Learn How to Fix If Your YouTube is Run<br/><br/>Most people are not sure what to do in such a situation and make the videos load faster in YouTube.<br /><br />Before I share the guidelines to deal with this speed slowdown I would invite you to think of the reasons which result in YouTube errors such as sluggish streaming, flash crashing in YouTube and other YouTube videos errors. There are two major reasons which result in these annoyances. One is the problem at the user end that includes PC speed, Internet speed, PC Windows errors, PC programs conflict such as Flash issues, while the second reason may be caused by the server or external internet traffic load. Although the web site is very effectively maintained there appear some troubles sometimes. This, however, is not a big issue as we all trust the services provided by such a user friendly web site. The issue becomes serious when video errors and slow speed becomes a routine. This has to be something to do with the personal computer one is using.<br /><br />Here I am outlining some tips that will help you to make YouTube faster for you:<br /><br />* Start from repairing your Windows registry and fixing your Windows errors that become the cause of many browser and applications errors causing a conflict situation. &lt;br&gt;* Test your computer for viruses and spyware. &lt;br&gt;* Run SpeedTest to test whether you have sufficient bandwidth available to smoothly play YouTube videos without causing the site to run slower. &lt;br&gt;* Disconnect your internet and then reconnect it to know why is YouTube slow and whether it is because of the poor internet at your side. &lt;br&gt;* Disable ads through some of the browser plug in that will allow you to run fewer background services while you are playing videos online. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your flash player version. Although the YouTube has started to stream videos through a new technology there is still a large number of web sites using the flash platform. So it is a nice idea to try to change the flash player version to play videos without crashes and error messages. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your browser. One good browser to play YouTube videos is Chrome. If you have not tried that go for it. Also contact your ISP provider if they are limiting your bandwidth at specific durations of the day. If you decide to use software, you will have to install the software on both the host computer and the remote computer and then you will have full control over the host PC. On the other hand if you use Web based remote access, all you need is an internet connection and you can access your host computer from any location in the world. All you need to do is log on to the service provider's website and you're good to go.<br /><br />So if you were wondering How Can I Access My Email from another Computer, then wonder no more as all you need to do is grab some remote access tools and you should be able to check out your emails from anywhere in the world. Most Remote access tools offer a free download and they are very easy to install, the better tools will even allow you to access your emails and transfer files from a Mobile Phone or PDA, how's that for mobility!<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">Best vpn provider</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">Best vpn provider</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ab40f4e5d7614d6163d2c1ad4487bd5e" url=""><![CDATA[Why is YouTube Slow? Learn How to Fix If Your YouTube is Run<br/><br/>This P3P architecture helps define and improve cyberethics, improves accessibility, improves consistency, and increases the overall trust in using cyberspace. MACs utilize a common key that generates and verifies a message whereas digital signatures generally use two complementary algorithms - one for signing and the other for verification.<br /><br />There has also some creative technology proposed for maintaining and protecting private medical information. In October 2004, the &quot;VeriChip&quot; was approved by the FDA for implantation into the triceps of patients. The chip is about the size of a grain of rice and is inserted under the skin during a 20-minute procedure. This invisible chip stores a code that can scanned to further release a patient's private medical information. This code is then used to download encrypted medical information. The procedure cost is about $150-200 (MSNBC, 2004).<br /><br />Another more commonly used medical information tool is the &quot;smart card,&quot; a credit card sized device with a small-embedded computer chip. This &quot;computer in a card&quot; can be programmed to perform tasks and store important information. During an emergency, paramedics and emergency rooms equipped with smart card readers can rapidly access potentially life-saving information about a patient, such as allergies to medication, and chronic medical conditions. There are different types of smart cards: memory cards, processor cards, electronic purse cards, security cards, and JavaCards. These cards are tamper-resistant, can be PIN protected or read-write protected, can be encrypted, and can be easily updated. These unique features make smart cards advantageous for storing personal medical information and are popular throughout the world. In Germany and Austria, 80 million people have the capability of using these smart cards when they visit their doctor (Cagliostro, 1999).<br /><br />There is also a recent proposed government plan to create a national system of electronic health records (EHRs). Details include the building of a National Health Information Network that will electronically connect all patients' medical records to providers, insures, pharmacies, labs, and claim processors. The sharing of vital information could improve patient care, include more accurate and timely substantiation of claims, and be an asset to public health in emergencies. The goal is to have it operational by 2009. Even with laudatory goals of saving money, making medical care more efficient, and decreasing drug reactions and interactions, there are still inherent dangers to this national plan. There are valid concerns that pharmaceutical companies may attempt to market a new drug or device for your specific medical condition. There are also strong worries of exploitation and abuse of personal data. Who will monitor access to the information? There are also concerns that lenders or employers may rely on private medical information to make business decisions. Then there is always the ever present fear of hackers and pranksters retrieving your personal information. There are still so many questions unanswered (Consumer Reports.org, 2006).<br /><br />In conclusion, we are now stuck with a &quot;Cyberspace Monster&quot; and all of its advantages and shortcomings. When we use cyberspace, we can have no expectations of privacy and we must accept a level of risk. Therefore, when transmitting and sharing private medical information, we must be always aware to take precautions in safeguarding our privacy as much as possible by using secure networks, P3P architecture, passwords, firewalls, encryption, message codes, digital signatures, and devices like smart cards and &quot;VeriChips.&quot; Medical records are among the most personal forms of information about an individual, but we are challenged to find a balance between society's interest in protecting medical confidentiality and the legitimate need for timely access to critical medical information especially with fears of influenza pandemics and bioterrorism. (1997) Privacy law in the USA.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">Top vpn provider</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">Top vpn provider</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="334b02ead204b0c0bc8baf54056eade9" url=""><![CDATA[Why is YouTube Slow? Learn How to Fix If Your YouTube is Run<br/><br/>Technical Security Mechanisms refers to PHI transmitted over a communication network such as the Internet, frame relay, VPN, private line, or other network. PHI transmitted over a communication network must be encrypted.<br /><br />There are also some noticeable shortcomings to HIPAA. The act did little to actually make health insurance more &quot;portable&quot; when an employee changes employers. Also, the Act did not significantly increase the health insurers' accountability for wrongdoing with provisions that are often difficult to monitor and enforce. There is also much confusion for patients, as well as healthcare providers, in regard to the interpretation of the act (Diversified Radiology of Colorado, 2002).<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Other Laws, Regulations, and Decisions Regarding Private Medical Information&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Besides HIPAA, there are important state regulations and laws, and federal laws and legal decisions, concerning the privacy and confidentiality of medical information (Clifford, 1999):<br /><br />The Privacy Act of 1974 limits governmental agencies from sharing medical information from one agency to another. Congress declared hat &quot;the privacy of an individual is directly affected by the collection, maintenance, use and dissemination of personal information ...,&quot; and that &quot;the right to privacy is a personal and fundamental right protected by the Constitution of the United States ...&quot; (Parmet, 2002).<br /><br />The Alcohol and Drug Abuse Act, passed in 1988, establishes confidentiality for records of patients treated for alcohol or drug abuse (only if they are treated in institutions that receive federal funding).<br /><br />The Americans with Disabilities Act, passed in 1990, prohibits employers from making employment-related decisions based on a real or perceived disability, including mental disabilities. Employers may still have access to identifiable health information about employees for reasonable business needs including determining reasonable accommodations for disabled workers and for addressing workers compensation claims.<br /><br />Supreme Court decision in Jaffee v. Redmond: On June 13, 1996, the Court ruled that there is a broad federal privilege protecting the confidentiality of communication between psychotherapists and their clients. The ruling applies to psychiatrists, psychologists and social workers.<br /><br />Freedom and Privacy Restoration Act of 1999: Designed to prohibit the creation of government unique medical ID numbers.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Managed Care and Cyber Threats to Private Medical Information&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />The introduction of the Internet and the advances in telecommunications technology over the last two decades allows us to access vast amounts of medical information, regardless of time, distance, or remoteness, with relative ease. This cyber access to medical information has profoundly changed how healthcare providers treat patients and offer advice. No longer are there barriers to the efficient exchange of health information and critical life-saving medical information. In addition to the many benefits of cyber access to medical information, there are also serious threats to our personal privacy and our medical information.<br /><br />The intense interest for the protection and privacy of medical information is driven by two major developments. The first is the growth of electronic medical record keeping that has replaced paper records. &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">Best vpn provider</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">Best vpn provider</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3f5b018c97b6f70c49cc29bcab514d14" url=""><![CDATA[Why is YouTube Slow? Learn How to Fix If Your YouTube is Run<br/><br/>There are two major reasons which result in these annoyances. One is the problem at the user end that includes PC speed, Internet speed, PC Windows errors, PC programs conflict such as Flash issues, while the second reason may be caused by the server or external internet traffic load. Although the web site is very effectively maintained there appear some troubles sometimes. This, however, is not a big issue as we all trust the services provided by such a user friendly web site. The issue becomes serious when video errors and slow speed becomes a routine. This has to be something to do with the personal computer one is using.<br /><br />Here I am outlining some tips that will help you to make YouTube faster for you:<br /><br />* Start from repairing your Windows registry and fixing your Windows errors that become the cause of many browser and applications errors causing a conflict situation. &lt;br&gt;* Test your computer for viruses and spyware. &lt;br&gt;* Run SpeedTest to test whether you have sufficient bandwidth available to smoothly play YouTube videos without causing the site to run slower. &lt;br&gt;* Disconnect your internet and then reconnect it to know why is YouTube slow and whether it is because of the poor internet at your side. &lt;br&gt;* Disable ads through some of the browser plug in that will allow you to run fewer background services while you are playing videos online. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your flash player version. Although the YouTube has started to stream videos through a new technology there is still a large number of web sites using the flash platform. So it is a nice idea to try to change the flash player version to play videos without crashes and error messages. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your browser. One good browser to play YouTube videos is Chrome. If you have not tried that go for it. Also contact your ISP provider if they are limiting your bandwidth at specific durations of the day. &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br />Do you need to access your email account from work, school or another location? Many people will inevitably find themselves away from their home or office PC and need to access their emails, programs or transfer files from their host computer for some reason. Well in this article I am going to answer the question, can I access my email from another computer, and also show you how you can not only access your emails on your work or home PC from a remote location, but also transfer files and run your programs as if your sitting their right in front it.<br /><br />Now the way you're going to able to access your emails from another computer is by using remote access technology. Most Remote access tools offer a free download and they are very easy to install, the better tools will even allow you to access your emails and transfer files from a Mobile Phone or PDA, how's that for mobility!<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">Top vpn provider</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">Top vpn provider</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f01a4710d241a90aa82d8a5356e22b49" url=""><![CDATA[How Setup An Easy VPN? Look No More!<br/><br/>This cyber access to medical information has profoundly changed how healthcare providers treat patients and offer advice. No longer are there barriers to the efficient exchange of health information and critical life-saving medical information. In addition to the many benefits of cyber access to medical information, there are also serious threats to our personal privacy and our medical information.<br /><br />The intense interest for the protection and privacy of medical information is driven by two major developments. The first is the growth of electronic medical record keeping that has replaced paper records. A report from the National Academy of Sciences states that the healthcare industry spent between $10 and $15 billion on information technology in 1996 (Mehlman, 1999). This was the year that the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act was passed with most of the expenditure attributed to converting hard-copy information to electronic formats.Electronic medical records (EMRs) present a significant threat to maintaining the privacy of patient-identifiable medical information. This medical information can be retrieved instantaneously by anyone with access and passwords. Although hard-copy medical information can be easily copied, electronic records are much more easily copied and transmitted without boundaries.<br /><br />The second major development that concerns the privacy of patient information is the overall growth of managed care organizations. There is a demand for an unprecedented depth and breath of personal medical information by an increasing number of players. In contrast to traditional fee-for-service healthcare, the provider of care and the insurer can be the same entity. In this situation, any medical information in the possession of the provider is also known to the insurer. This is common in all forms of managed care, but most evident in closed-panel HMOs. This sharing of information increases the fear that the insurer may use the data to limit benefits or terminate insurance coverage (Mehlman, 1999).<br /><br />Some managed care companies are reporting private medical information to an extreme in requiring providers to report to case managers within twenty-four hours any case that is considered a high risk potential for the client, a second party, the employer, or the managed care company. Examples include such things as possible danger to self or others, suspected child abuse, potential threats to national security or the client organization, client's request for records, complaint about Employee Assistance Program services or threat of a lawsuit, and potential involvement in litigation including confession or knowledge of criminal activity. No mention is made concerning client privacy or rights regarding the release of this information. Nothing is also said about what will be done with the information that is shared (Clifford, 1999).<br /><br />Another issue with managed care companies is the large volume of data processed and the carelessness in handling medical information. A salient example deals with lost records as noted in a 1993 survey sample of San Francisco Bay Area psychologists. In this survey, 59% of reports were mailed or faxed to wrong persons, charts accidentally switched, or proper authorization not obtained (Clifford, 1999).<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Maintaining and Protecting Electronic Private Medical Information&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />In order to maintain and protect valued private medical information, we must always be vigilant and proactive. Basic steps can be taken prior to using electronic information sharing. (1997) Privacy law in the USA.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWVpZ2h0dnBu" target="_blank">online vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVr" target="_blank">vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXJlc2VsbGVy" target="_blank">strong vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWZpdmU_" target="_blank">usa vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVz" target="_blank">buy vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWVpZ2h0dXNh" target="_blank">perfect vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWF1cw__" target="_blank">uk vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXNldmVyYWw_" target="_blank">strong vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">online vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">europe vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="845f84c1f0c3dccbaa10ca147908a2f8" url=""><![CDATA[How Setup An Easy VPN? Look No More!<br/><br/>Regardless of our definition, the right of privacy usually concerns individuals who are in a place reasonably expected to be private. Information that is public record, or voluntarily disclosed in a public place, is not protected.<br /><br />The open architecture of the modern phenomenon that we call the Internet raises very unique ethical concerns regarding privacy. Information is sent effortlessly over this vast global network without boundaries. Personal information may pass through many different servers on the way to a final destination. There are virtually no online activities or services that guarantee absolute privacy. It is quite easy to be lulled into thinking your activity is private when actually many of these computer systems can capture and store this personal information and actually monitor your online activity (Privacy Rights Clearinghouse, 2006). The Net's underlying architecture is designed to share information and not to conceal or protect it. Even though it is possible to develop an adequate level of security, with an acceptable risk level, it is at enormous cost and considerable time.<br /><br />Medical records are among the most personal forms of information about an individual and may contain medical history, lifestyle details (such as smoking or participation in high-risk sports), test results, medications, allergies, operations and procedures, genetic testing, and participation in research projects.The protection of this private medical information falls under the area of medical ethics. The realm of medical ethics is to analyze and resolve ethical dilemmas that arise in medical practice and biomedical research. Medical ethics is guided by strict principles or standards that address: Autonomy, Beneficence, Nonmaleficence, Fidelity, and Justice (Spinello, 2003). The principle of Autonomy includes a person's right to be fully informed of all pertinent information related to his/her healthcare. A discussion of medical ethical principles and patient rights leads us to further discuss legislation designed to maintain and protect these cherished rights.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Access to Private Medical Information and the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996<br /><br />&lt;/b&gt;Since 400 B.C. and the creation of the Hippocratic Oath, protecting the privacy of patient medical information has been an important part of the physician' code of conduct. Unfortunately, many organizations and individuals not subject to this strict code of conduct are increasingly requesting this private information.Every time a patient sees a doctor, is admitted to a hospital, goes to a pharmacist, or sends a claim to a healthcare plan, a record is made of their confidential health information. In the past, all healthcare providers protected the confidentiality of medical records by locking them away in file cabinets and refusing to reveal them to anyone else. Today, we rely on &quot;protected&quot; electronic records and a complicated series of laws to maintain our confidential and private medical records.<br /><br />Congress duly recognized the need for national patient record privacy standards in 1996 when they enacted the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act HIPAA). &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVr" target="_blank">online vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWZpdmU_" target="_blank">cheap vpn service</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXJlc2VsbGVy" target="_blank">uk vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">uk vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">best vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWVpZ2h0dXNh" target="_blank">strong vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWVpZ2h0dnBu" target="_blank">online vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWF1cw__" target="_blank">cheapest vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWR5bmFtaWM_" target="_blank">fast vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXNldmVyYWw_" target="_blank">vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5160d0a1a826659bc4e7d525266e13c" url=""><![CDATA[Why is YouTube Slow? Learn How to Fix If Your YouTube is Run<br/><br/>This, however, is not a big issue as we all trust the services provided by such a user friendly web site. The issue becomes serious when video errors and slow speed becomes a routine. This has to be something to do with the personal computer one is using.<br /><br />Here I am outlining some tips that will help you to make YouTube faster for you:<br /><br />* Start from repairing your Windows registry and fixing your Windows errors that become the cause of many browser and applications errors causing a conflict situation. &lt;br&gt;* Test your computer for viruses and spyware. &lt;br&gt;* Run SpeedTest to test whether you have sufficient bandwidth available to smoothly play YouTube videos without causing the site to run slower. &lt;br&gt;* Disconnect your internet and then reconnect it to know why is YouTube slow and whether it is because of the poor internet at your side. &lt;br&gt;* Disable ads through some of the browser plug in that will allow you to run fewer background services while you are playing videos online. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your flash player version. Although the YouTube has started to stream videos through a new technology there is still a large number of web sites using the flash platform. So it is a nice idea to try to change the flash player version to play videos without crashes and error messages. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your browser. One good browser to play YouTube videos is Chrome. If you have not tried that go for it. Also contact your ISP provider if they are limiting your bandwidth at specific durations of the day. &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br />Do you need to access your email account from work, school or another location? Many people will inevitably find themselves away from their home or office PC and need to access their emails, programs or transfer files from their host computer for some reason. Well in this article I am going to answer the question, can I access my email from another computer, and also show you how you can not only access your emails on your work or home PC from a remote location, but also transfer files and run your programs as if your sitting their right in front it.<br /><br />Now the way you're going to able to access your emails from another computer is by using remote access technology. Remote Computer Access refers to the concept of accessing your work, office, home or company network from a remote location. It is really simple to setup and once you have the proper tools in play you can remotely access your host computer from any location in the world.<br /><br />Remote PC access is possible by using special software or Web-based/Web Interface Remote Access. Most Remote access tools offer a free download and they are very easy to install, the better tools will even allow you to access your emails and transfer files from a Mobile Phone or PDA, how's that for mobility!<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVr" target="_blank">cheap vpn service</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWNh" target="_blank">europe vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWF1cw__" target="_blank">vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXJlc2VsbGVy" target="_blank">online vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWZpdmU_" target="_blank">uk vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXNldmVyYWw_" target="_blank">perfect vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWVpZ2h0dXNh" target="_blank">usa vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">online vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVz" target="_blank">purchase vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWR5bmFtaWM_" target="_blank">online vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="92db3d1d64368168b77e83baf627876c" url=""><![CDATA[Ethical Considerations of Privacy and Cyber-Medical Informat<br/><br/>According to these new standards, a code set is any set of codes used for encoding data elements, such as tables of terms, medical diagnosis codes, procedure codes, etc.<br /><br />SECURITY:<br /><br />The security section is divided into four major parts:<br /><br />1. Administrative, which requires documented formal practices, the execution of security measures to protect data, policies and procedures regulating conduct of personnel in protecting data, security training, incident procedures, and termination policies.<br /><br />2. Physical Safeguards relate to the protection of physical computer systems, network safeguards, environmental hazards, and physical intrusion. One must consider computer screen placement, pass code protection, and computer locks to control access to medical information.<br /><br />3. Technical Security Services refers to PHI stored on the computer network and how it is securely stored and accessed. Those using the PHI must be logged on and authenticated. An audit trail of authenticated access will be maintained for 6 years.<br /><br />4. Technical Security Mechanisms refers to PHI transmitted over a communication network such as the Internet, frame relay, VPN, private line, or other network. PHI transmitted over a communication network must be encrypted.<br /><br />There are also some noticeable shortcomings to HIPAA. The act did little to actually make health insurance more &quot;portable&quot; when an employee changes employers. Also, the Act did not significantly increase the health insurers' accountability for wrongdoing with provisions that are often difficult to monitor and enforce. There is also much confusion for patients, as well as healthcare providers, in regard to the interpretation of the act (Diversified Radiology of Colorado, 2002).<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Other Laws, Regulations, and Decisions Regarding Private Medical Information&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Besides HIPAA, there are important state regulations and laws, and federal laws and legal decisions, concerning the privacy and confidentiality of medical information (Clifford, 1999):<br /><br />The Privacy Act of 1974 limits governmental agencies from sharing medical information from one agency to another. Congress declared hat &quot;the privacy of an individual is directly affected by the collection, maintenance, use and dissemination of personal information ...,&quot; and that &quot;the right to privacy is a personal and fundamental right protected by the Constitution of the United States ...&quot; (Parmet, 2002).<br /><br />The Alcohol and Drug Abuse Act, passed in 1988, establishes confidentiality for records of patients treated for alcohol or drug abuse (only if they are treated in institutions that receive federal funding).<br /><br />The Americans with Disabilities Act, passed in 1990, prohibits employers from making employment-related decisions based on a real or perceived disability, including mental disabilities. Employers may still have access to identifiable health information about employees for reasonable business needs including determining reasonable accommodations for disabled workers and for addressing workers compensation claims.<br /><br />Supreme Court decision in Jaffee v. Redmond: On June 13, 1996, the Court ruled that there is a broad federal privilege protecting the confidentiality of communication between psychotherapists and their clients. The ruling applies to psychiatrists, psychologists and social workers.<br /><br />Freedom and Privacy Restoration Act of 1999: Designed to prohibit the creation of government unique medical ID numbers.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Managed Care and Cyber Threats to Private Medical Information&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />The introduction of the Internet and the advances in telecommunications technology over the last two decades allows us to access vast amounts of medical information, regardless of time, distance, or remoteness, with relative ease. This cyber access to medical information has profoundly changed how healthcare providers treat patients and offer advice. (1997) Privacy law in the USA.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">secure vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">best vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8ac281c1c34f549b0f194acdf0ddd2e" url=""><![CDATA[How Setup An Easy VPN? Look No More!<br/><br/>The new threat to your medical privacy.<br /><br />Diversified Radiology of Colorado (2002) History: HIPAA general information.<br /><br />Mehlman, M. J. (1999) Emerging issues: the privacy of medical records.<br /><br />MSNBC (2004) FDA approves computer chip for humans.<br /><br />Parmet, W. E. (2002) Public health protection and privacy of medical records.<br /><br />Privacy Rights Clearinghouse (2006) Internet privacy resources.<br /><br />Spinello, R. A. (2003) CyberEthics: Morality and law in cyberspace. Jones and Bartlett Publishers, Sudbury, MA<br /><br />Standler, R. B. (1997) Privacy law in the USA.<br /><br />Many frustrated users addicted to video streaming ask this question. Although the sudden slowdown of the giant video site occurs occasionally at the user side, people are clueless what could be the cause of this problem. It is understood no body wants to wait long for videos to load and then watch them especially if the videos are longer and are in several parts. Faster streaming is the need of every internet user. If YouTube runs slow sometimes then there are surely some reasons behind that. Most people are not sure what to do in such a situation and make the videos load faster in YouTube.<br /><br />Before I share the guidelines to deal with this speed slowdown I would invite you to think of the reasons which result in YouTube errors such as sluggish streaming, flash crashing in YouTube and other YouTube videos errors. There are two major reasons which result in these annoyances. One is the problem at the user end that includes PC speed, Internet speed, PC Windows errors, PC programs conflict such as Flash issues, while the second reason may be caused by the server or external internet traffic load. Although the web site is very effectively maintained there appear some troubles sometimes. This, however, is not a big issue as we all trust the services provided by such a user friendly web site. The issue becomes serious when video errors and slow speed becomes a routine. This has to be something to do with the personal computer one is using.<br /><br />Here I am outlining some tips that will help you to make YouTube faster for you:<br /><br />* Start from repairing your Windows registry and fixing your Windows errors that become the cause of many browser and applications errors causing a conflict situation. &lt;br&gt;* Test your computer for viruses and spyware. &lt;br&gt;* Run SpeedTest to test whether you have sufficient bandwidth available to smoothly play YouTube videos without causing the site to run slower. &lt;br&gt;* Disconnect your internet and then reconnect it to know why is YouTube slow and whether it is because of the poor internet at your side. &lt;br&gt;* Disable ads through some of the browser plug in that will allow you to run fewer background services while you are playing videos online. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your flash player version. Although the YouTube has started to stream videos through a new technology there is still a large number of web sites using the flash platform. &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">usa vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">fast vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d4ea8a6199d0e5fb0ef6cb0d4d6cc492" url=""><![CDATA[How Can I Access My Email From Another Computer? Remotely Ac<br/><br/>One is the problem at the user end that includes PC speed, Internet speed, PC Windows errors, PC programs conflict such as Flash issues, while the second reason may be caused by the server or external internet traffic load. Although the web site is very effectively maintained there appear some troubles sometimes. This, however, is not a big issue as we all trust the services provided by such a user friendly web site. The issue becomes serious when video errors and slow speed becomes a routine. This has to be something to do with the personal computer one is using.<br /><br />Here I am outlining some tips that will help you to make YouTube faster for you:<br /><br />* Start from repairing your Windows registry and fixing your Windows errors that become the cause of many browser and applications errors causing a conflict situation. &lt;br&gt;* Test your computer for viruses and spyware. &lt;br&gt;* Run SpeedTest to test whether you have sufficient bandwidth available to smoothly play YouTube videos without causing the site to run slower. &lt;br&gt;* Disconnect your internet and then reconnect it to know why is YouTube slow and whether it is because of the poor internet at your side. &lt;br&gt;* Disable ads through some of the browser plug in that will allow you to run fewer background services while you are playing videos online. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your flash player version. Although the YouTube has started to stream videos through a new technology there is still a large number of web sites using the flash platform. So it is a nice idea to try to change the flash player version to play videos without crashes and error messages. &lt;br&gt;* Try to change your browser. One good browser to play YouTube videos is Chrome. If you have not tried that go for it. Also contact your ISP provider if they are limiting your bandwidth at specific durations of the day. &lt;br&gt;* Also recommended that you do the following steps if the YouTube is slow due to DNS related settings:<br /><br />Click start &gt; settings &gt; control panel &gt; network connections &gt; Local Area Connection/ Your default internet connection &gt; properties &gt; Internet Protocol TCP/IP &gt; properties &gt; check the option &quot;use the following DNS server address&quot; and use this address: Preferred DNS Server: 208.67.222.222 Alternate DNS Server: 208.67.222.220<br /><br />Do you need to access your email account from work, school or another location? Many people will inevitably find themselves away from their home or office PC and need to access their emails, programs or transfer files from their host computer for some reason. Well in this article I am going to answer the question, can I access my email from another computer, and also show you how you can not only access your emails on your work or home PC from a remote location, but also transfer files and run your programs as if your sitting their right in front it.<br /><br />Now the way you're going to able to access your emails from another computer is by using remote access technology. Most Remote access tools offer a free download and they are very easy to install, the better tools will even allow you to access your emails and transfer files from a Mobile Phone or PDA, how's that for mobility!<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank">vpn</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank">buy vpn</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>