<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="aebc08e1179bbc65d3747988c2252e5b" url=""><![CDATA[Ahmedabad to Bangalore – How to Reach<br/><br/>Situated on the banks of the river Sabarmati, Ahmedabad, known as the Manchester of the East is one of the largest and fastest growing cities in the state of Gujarat.
<br /><br />Bangalore, the capital of Karnataka, is the hub of the IT sector and is India’s third most populous city. Bangalore was found by Kempegowda and was ruled by a number of rulers and dynasties, including the rulers of the Vijayanagara Empire and Tipu Sultan.
<br /><br />Due to its high elevation, Bangalore enjoys a moderate climate throughout the year and has an extensive cover of greenery making the place a ‘pensioner’s paradise’ and the ‘Green City’.
<br /><br />The main attractions in and around Bangalore are the Bangalore Palace, Vidhana Soudha, Bangalore’s Secretariat and State Legislature building, Bull temple, ISKON temple, Tipu’s palace, Bannarghetta  Biological Park and Nandi hills.
<br /><br />The distance from Ahmedabad to Bangalore is 1500 km.
<br /><br />The best and cheap way to reach Bangalore from Ahmedabad is by train. Though no daily trains, there are altogether 9 trains from Ahmedabad to Bangalore running on different days. Trains from Ahmedabad arrive in Bangalore at three stations, namely Yesvantpur Junction (YPR), Bangalore City Junction (SBC) and Krishnarajapurm (KJM)
<br /><br />The fastest trains from <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL0hvdy1Uby1SZWFjaC9Gcm9tLUFobWVkYWJhZC1Uby1CYW5nYWxvcmUtMjU2LTI5Mw__" target="_blank">Ahmedabad to Bangalore</a> are the Okha-Madurai Vivek Express and the Rajkot-Coimbatore Express that takes around 30 hours to reach Bangalore. The approximate charges for sleeper are Rs 420, AC 3-tier is 1160 and AC 2-tier is Rs. 1850. Another convenient train is the Ahmedabad-Yesvantpur Weekly Express. All the bogies in this train are air-conditioned.
<br /><br />The other trains that run between Ahmedabad and Bangalore are Gandhidham-Bangalore Express, Ajmer-Mysore Express, Jodhpur-Bangalore Express, Garib Nawaz Express, Jodhpur-Yesvantpur Express, and Ahmedabad-Bangalore Express.
<br /><br />Get More on Bangalore to Vijayawada
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a2178ee1e07ac7e530681a60a3529b2" url=""><![CDATA[Jaipur Packages - A taste of royalty<br/><br/>The Pink City of Rajasthan, Jaipur is a city soaked in royalty. Built and planned by the ruler Sawai Jai Singh II, the city has also been named in his honour. This beautiful city is also credited for being one of the first planned cities in India.
<br /><br />The city of Jaipur owes its sobriquet to the pink buildings that dominate the city’s landscape. Most of the older buildings and the city’s layout has been done following the ancient art and science of Vaastu Shastra. It was under the architectural guidance of scholar Vidyadhar Bhattacharya that the city was built, taking into account many Indian classical treatise such as Shilpa Shastra and Vaastu Shastra among many others. It is believed that the nine rectangular sectors of the city symbolizes the nine divisions of the universe. Another interesting aspect in the making of the city was the use of uniform colour pink in its many structures and buildings. This is believed to have been used since the colour pink is said to represent the Rajput royalty.
<br /><br />This exotic city lined with majestic palaces and lofty havelis, prominent among them being the City Palace, Hawa Mahal, Jai Mahal, Nahargarh Fort. It is also a land of numerous temples and other places of worship such as Govind Dev Ji Temple, Galtaji, Shri Kali Temple, Sanganeri Gate, Lakshmi Narayan Mandir commonly known as Birla Temple, Garh Ganesh Temple, Shila Devi Temple in Amber, Tadkeshwara Mahadev, Panchayati Hall, Radha Govind Ji Temple and All Saint’s Church.
<br /><br />To experience Jaipur in its entirety, one can choose between the numerous Jaipur Packages on offer that include choice of accommodation along with trips around the city and also even rich Rajasthani food. Many of these Jaipur Packages also include guided tours of the magnificent palaces and forts around the city which gives one a brief glimpse into the luxurious lifestyles of the erstwhile kings here. Keeping in mind the religious tastes of the elderly, a variety of Jaipur Packages include exclusive trips to the many sacred temples here.
<br /><br />A very important aspect of Jaipur is its fame as a shopper’s paradise. Catering to the shopping needs of many tourists, some Jaipur Packages also include one full day just to indulge in a shopping spree. Exquisite handicrafts, delicate artifacts, furniture, jewellery and carpets give Jaipur the title of ‘Craft Capital of India’. Popular items that are a must buy here are the five coloured bandhej on textiles, traditional meenakari jewellery, hand knotted carpets, camel leather bags and sandals.
<br /><br />Jaipur is well connected to the rest of the country by a network of air, rails and roads and so is very easily accessible from any corner of the country.
<br /><br />For more information on Jaipur Resorts and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItSmFpcHVyLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMzgzLTYteWVzLWRlc3RpbmF0aW9uLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Hotels in Jaipur</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="28dac60aa40f202753604791b3b47c2" url=""><![CDATA[Agra Packages - Revisit a marvellous era gone by<br/><br/>The city of Agra famous all over the world for being home to one of the Seven Wonders of the World, the Taj Mahal, is situated by the river Yamuna. One of the most famous cities in Uttar Pradesh, Agra is renowned for its many forts, palaces and ancient streets and markets that have an old world charm to them that lure tourists from all across the world. The beautiful city of Agra is bordered by the district of Mathura in the north, Dhaulpur in the south Firozabad in the east and Bharatpur in the west.
<br /><br />Famed for its many architectural marvels, the city owes most of its spectacular structures to Mughal rulers like Babur, Akbar, Jahangir and Shahjahan. These rulers played a huge role in adorning this city with its many magnificent structures and also lending Agra its unique blend of flavour. As part of the Agra Packages, trips to the magnificent monuments that line the city of Agra like the Fatehpur Sikri, Agra Fort, Sikandra, Itmad ud Daula, Sur Sarovar Bird Sanctuary, Jama Masjid, Diwan-i-Am, Buland Darwaza are some of the marvelous monuments in the city. Among one of the most prominent structures erected in Agra, the Agra Red Fort is most popular and is a UNESCO World Heritage Site that includes the Anguri Bagh Gardens, Diwan-i-Khas, Jahangir’s Palace, Ladies’ Bazaar, Moti Masjid, Nagina Masjid and Shish Mahal all inside its premises.
<br /><br />Taj Mahal, the magnificent pure white marble mausoleum erected by Shah Jahan in memory of his beloved wife Mumtaz Mahal is however, the star attraction of the Agra Packages. Agra is also home to other structures like Itmad-end of ud-Daulah Tomb, often referred to as ‘Baby Taj’, owing to the similarity in architecture between the two. Fatehpur Sikri is another notable attraction included in Agra Packages that was built during the 16th century by the Mughal Emperor Akbar. Among the famous monuments in Fatehpur Sikri are the Jama Masjid, Mariam-uz-Zamani’s Palace, Buland Darwaza, Tomb of Salim Chisti and Panch Mahal. Few other popular monuments in Agra are the Chini Ka Rauza, Soami Bagh Samadh and Tomb of Akbar the Great which are all included in most of the Agra Packages.
<br /><br />Aside from its architectural marvels, the city of Agra is also very famous for its rich Mughal cuisine like the creamy korma, pasandas in almond sauce, nargisi kofta, dalmoth and petha.
<br /><br />Agra is situated just 30 minutes from the national capital city of Delhi and is easily accessible from there by road and rail. Agra has a major railway station that is well connected to most major cities in the country. The nearest airport is located in the neighbouring city of Delhi.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2FncmEtcmVzb3J0cy0xLTI1NS0xMy5odG1s" target="_blank">Agra Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL0FncmEtUGFja2FnZXMtMjU1LTEteWVzLTAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Hotels in Agra</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e7a03838fbbedbc5992f7a5d88aa4d1d" url=""><![CDATA[Agra – Homage to Love<br/><br/>Agra is by far one of the most popular tourist destinations of India, widely renowned for being home to the eternal symbol of love the Taj Mahal. Everyday thousands of tourists from all parts of the world flock to the region to adore the spectacular architecture and the craftsmanship of the early craftsmen seen in almost every inch of this great monument. Many tourist couple flocks to the city either to renew their love for each other or to make the stand testimony to the couple’s undying love for each other. Such is the charm and appeal of the city that it forms one of the components of the ‘Golden Triangle’ of the Indian tourism industry, the other two being Delhi and Jaipur.
<br /><br />Sitting along the banks of the River,Agrais one of the most popular cities of Uttar Pradesh. However, the city having seen its golden days as the capital of Hindustan under the Mughal Empire is a distant cry from its original beauty and grandeur. Overt commercialization and poorly planned growth of the city has robbed the city of its original charm and glamour. Nevertheless, the city still manages to charm tourists and distantly resembles its yesteryear beauty on a moonlit night, with its reflection falling onto the River Yamuna.
<br /><br />Agra has layers of character and mysticism to it waiting to be explored by curious travelers. The prominent tourist attractions of Agra are the three UNESCO World Heritage Sites – Taj Mahal,Agra Fortand Fatehpur Sikri. Some of the other attractions of Agra include Swami Bagh, Ram Bagh, Mehtab Bagh, balkeshwar Temple, Kailash Temple, Sikandra, Itmad - Ud - Daulah’s Tomb, Jama Masjid, Chini Ka Roza and much more.
<br /><br />Along with sightseeing tourists can also opt to explore the bustling markets of Agra famous for its leather goods, perfumes, bangles and other such goodies, gorge on the local food fare from the mouth watering chats, pethas to the delicious veg and non-veg cuisines.
<br /><br />Agra is heavily visited by tourists throughout the year and as such there is no best time to visit this charming city. There are also plenty of hotels and resorts in Agra catering to the lodging needs of the multitude of travelers visiting the region. The Agra Hotels found at nearly every corner of the city are present across all budget segments, ranging from the luxury hotels and resorts to the economy and budget hotels thus, catering to every travel need.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2FncmEtcmVzb3J0cy0xLTI1NS0xMy5odG1s" target="_blank">Agra Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQWdyYS1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTI1NS0xLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Agra</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="86ca662dfcffa7e8eae7ef4bcd18f6d0" url=""><![CDATA[Bangalore – The Party Destination<br/><br/>Bangalore is a name that needs no introduction. Capital of the state of Karnataka, it is one of the leading factors behind India’s stupendous growth story. Home to numerous IT hubs, MNC’s and various educational Institutions, the region serves as a dream destination for the millions of youths of the city. The city is home to a large majority of youth population from different ethical backgrounds, who together give the region a very hip, lively and vibrant look, which attracts a large number of tourists looking to explore and learn about the nerve center of India.
<br /><br />Bangalore is one of the few cities, which has been bestowed with numerous epithets reflecting the various facets of the city for instance, , the garden city, Silicon Valley of India, Pub city, IT city. However, rapid growth and development has robbed the city much of its greenery and as such several epithets like, ‘pensioner’s paradise’, ‘garden city’ no longer applies to the region.
<br /><br />The city running on youth energy acts as a live wire and is worth visiting at least once in a life time. Bangalore offers plenty of things to see and do, from exploring the various tourist attractions to pub hopping and indulging in various sorts of adventure sports activities. Some of the popular tourist attractions of Bangalore include, Vidhana Soudha, Vikasa Soudha, Seshadari Iyer Memorial, Bangalore Palace, Tipu Sultan’s Palace, The Bull Temple, Maha Bodhi Society Temple, ISCKON Temple, St. Mary’s Basilica and various other attractions.
<br /><br />The city is home to numerous pubs and lounges which offer a youthful place to relax and de-stress, along with that there are plenty of adventure companies offering a variety of sports to the interest of tourists. Alternatively tourist can also explore the local markets like, Brigade road, MG road, Commercial Street and others offering everything from international brands to desi goods and handicrafts.
<br /><br />Bangalore enjoys a temperate weather and as such can be visited throughout the year. There various Resorts in Bangalore and hotels together also very well cater to the lodging needs of the multitude of leisure and business travelers visiting the region. Needless to say the hotels and resorts in Bangalore are found across all budget segments so as to cater to varied tastes and preferences of the myriad of travelers visiting the region.
<br /><br />Bangalore is also well connected to the rest of the country and also various corners of the world by an efficient International airport, several railway stations and fleets of buses.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2JhbmdhbG9yZS1yZXNvcnRzLTEzLTI5My0xMy5odG1s" target="_blank">Bangalore Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQmFuZ2Fsb3JlLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMjkzLTEzLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Bangalore</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9cd07117362814ac80f462d7ced9a7b" url=""><![CDATA[Jaipur – Retreat to the Royal Land<br/><br/>Jaipur is a magical destination adorned with magnificent palaces, spectacular forts and various other grand royal monuments, all adding to the beauty of this desert queen. Jaipur enjoys great popularity among the tourist circle attracting travelers from far off places with its royal grandeur and elegance. This royal city holds great importance in the Indian tourism industry and is one of the three components of the ‘golden triangle’ of the tourism industry, the other two being Delhi and Agra.
<br /><br />Jaipur is also fondly referred to as the ‘Pink City’ owing to the distinctive color of the city walls, which were colored so as to resemble the red sandstone, Mughal architecture to welcome its royal guest King Edward VII. The city is the largest city in Rajasthan and is also the capital of the state. Jaipur also offers the perfect base to tourists willing to explore other desert cities like Udaipur, Jodhpur, Jaisalmer, etc.
<br /><br />Jaipur has a rich historical background, which contributes significantly to the mysticism and depth of the city. Jaipur served as the bastion of Rajput Empire and was founded in 1727 by Maharaja Sawai Jai Singh II, ruler of Amber. It was India’s first planned city and boasted of rich architecture. Today, Jaipur represents an intriguing blend of the old architectures standing tall amidst the modern marvels and various commercial establishments.
<br /><br />Jaipur acts as a treasure trove for travelers offering plenty of things to see, explore and engage in. Some of the prominent sightseeing attractions of Jaipur include include the Hawa Mahal, Amber Fort, Jaigarh Fort, Nahargarh Fort, City Palace, Jantar Mantar. Gaitore, Ram Niwas Gardens, Vidyadhar Garden, Sisodia Rani Palace and Garden, Galtaji, Lakshmi Narayan Temple and much more.
<br /><br />Things that every traveler must try out in Jaipur include elephant and camel rides, watching a puppet show and various other cultural performances, gorging on the delicious local food fare, exploring the colorful markets famous for its colorful rajais, jewels and various other handicrafts and local trinkets, last but, not the least indulging in the various adventure sports activities like desert safari and various other such activities.
<br /><br />There are plenty of accommodation options offered in the region, ranging from the luxury hotels and Resorts in Jaipur to the budget hotels. Jaipur also offers some fine heritage hotels, which takes guests back to the golden days of the yesteryears without missing on modern luxuries along with pampering them like royalty.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2phaXB1ci1yZXNvcnRzLTYtMzgzLTEzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Jaipur Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItSmFpcHVyLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMzgzLTYteWVzLWRlc3RpbmF0aW9uLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Hotels in Jaipur</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="663c49b89970a239be17e4d66ad6b106" url=""><![CDATA[Wayanad – Walk through the paddy fields<br/><br/>Wayanad is a popular tourist destination in the state of Kerala situated amidst the mighty Western Ghats. This picturesque hill station, famously known as green paradise is situated in the Wayanad district and is also part of the Nilgiri Biosphere.
<br /><br />The hill station of Wayanad is located in close proximity to many popular tourist destinations such as Ooty, Kannur, Bangalore, Mysore and Coorg. This dream locale is fringed by high mountain ranges, green plantations and dense forests, which house several aboriginal tribes, exotic wildlife and a variety of flora. Wayanad is a haven for those seeking some hardcore action that involves trekking through the undulating terrains of the region. Muthanga and Tholpetty are two wildlife reserves here that are home to a wide variety of flora and fauna.
<br /><br />Chembra Peak, Edakkal Caves, Kuruva Islands and the highest point in Wayanad, Lakkidi are some of the most popular tourist destinations here. Few other popular places of interest are Pakshipathalam, Pazhassi Raja Tomb, Pookot Lake, Sentinel Rock Waterfalls, Kanthanpara Waterfalls, Soochippara Waterfalls and the Banasura Sagar Dam. Wayanad also has some beautiful temples like the Sulthan Bathery Jain Temple, Thirunelli Temple, Valliyoorkavu Temple, Sita Luva-Kusha Temple and the Thrissilery Shiva Temple.
<br /><br />Wayanad Hotels include a wide variety of packages that comprise of accommodations ranging from luxury, B &amp; BS to the budget kinds. The Jungle Park Resort is the only four-star resort in Wayanad located in the scenic Fintser Hills of Vythiri. This luxury resort offers several amenities like free room service, laundry facility, gift store, florist, front desk, safe vault, travel desk, state-of-the-art health spa, restaurant, conference facilities, games room and hot/cold running water among several other facilities.
<br /><br />There are several three-star resorts, too, that include, Green Gates Resort, Meenmutty Heights, Vythiri Resort, Harithagiri Ayurvedic Village and Resort, Banasura Hill Resort and several others. These resorts are set in the most picturesque of places and since every inch of Wayanad is covered in a carpet of green vegetation, the view from these resorts is also breathtaking. Most of these three star hotels include facilities like 24 hour restaurant, coffee parlour, cycling, jacuzzi tub, badminton, bonfire, jungle trekking, airport pick/drop, railway station transfer, jogging track, travel desk service.
<br /><br />Greeshmam Resort, Isaac’s Royal Palm Residency and Royal Palm are some of the budget accommodations part of Wayanad Hotels. There are also many homestays in Wayanad like Aranyakam, Ente Veed, Fringe Ford, Glenora Homestay, Green Mount Resort, Hiliya Resort, Hill View Homestay, Pranavam Homestay, Sweet Home and several others.
<br /><br />The closest city to Wayanad with an airport and railway station is Kozhikode and is situated around 98 km away. A network of roads connects Wayanad to major cities within the state and in the neighbouring states too.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL3dheWFuYWQtcmVzb3J0cy0xNS01OTUtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Wayanad Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItV2F5YW5hZC1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTU5NS0xNS15ZXMtZGVzdGluYXRpb24uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Hotels in Wayanad</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5703c762e019cb45558f6c61f917e0c" url=""><![CDATA[Agra – The Beloved Beauty<br/><br/>Agra is a fascinating and extremely popular tourist destination of India. The city based along the banks of River Yamuna is widely renowned for its grand monument dedicated to love, the Taj Mahal, which is also a UNESCO enlisted World Heritage Site. Tourists from all corners of the country and also from various parts of the world flock to the region in large numbers to witness the grandeur and the elegance of this magnificent monument. Along with Taj Mahal, Agra is also home two other UNESCO enlisted World Heritage Sites namely, the Agra Fort and Fatehpur Sikri.
<br /><br />The monument, Taj Mahal renders the city a very romantic ambiance and as such the region is also a popular honeymoon destination of India for the various Indian newlyweds. Couples from all quarters and from all walks of life visit the region to mark a new beginning of their love life, celebrate their love for each other and much more.
<br /><br />Agra also has a rich historical background, which contributes significantly to the character and mysticism of the region. The city used to be the capital of Hindusthan during the Mughal era. Reflections of the region’s past is still clearly visible among the rich architecture of the Mughal’s seen in the various buildings adorning the various crowded lanes of the city along with other monuments.
<br /><br />There is plenty to see and explore in the vibrant city of Agra, from the various historical sites, architecture to the various modern marvels. Some of the prominent attractions of Agra include the Agra Fort, Swami Bagh, Ram Bagh, Mehtab Bagh, Balkeshwar Temple, Kailash Temple, Sikandra, Itmad – Ud – Daulah’s Tomb, Jama Masjid, Chini Ka Roza and Fatehpur Sikri among others.
<br /><br />Along with sightseeing tourists can also explore the local markets famous for its leather goods, perfumes, bangles, etc. A must do in Agra is to feast on the local delights like the varied varieties of Indian Chats, the pethas (sweet) and various other local street eat.
<br /><br />There are ample choices available when it comes to accommodation in Agra. The various hotels and resorts can be found across various budget segments ranging from the high-end luxury hotels to the economy and budget hotels thus, catering to all preferences and needs of the myriad of travelers visiting the region. Tour operators also effectively take care of Agra hotel booking along with the entire tour package, for the complete ease and comfort of the travelers.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2FncmEtcmVzb3J0cy0xLTI1NS0xMy5odG1s" target="_blank">Agra Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQWdyYS1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTI1NS0xLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Agra</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="48b4104c65c0a6a168ce08237f9301fa" url=""><![CDATA[Bangalore - The Nerve Centre of Karnataka<br/><br/>Bangalore is the capital of the south Indian state Karnataka. The city is a popular tourist destination and is also a leading IT hub of India. The city is one of the few regions of the country which is known by several epithets like the Garden City, IT Hub of India, Pub City, Pensioner’s Paradise and the Silicon Valley of India; However, a number of these epithets like the Garden City and Pensioner’s Paradise no longer apply to Bangalore, owing to large scale development in the region.
<br /><br />Bangalore witnessing large scale immigration from various corners of India, owing to brighter career and educational prospective, wears a very youthful look owing to the presence of large majority of youths. The glistening appeal of Bangalore as a major IT hub also attracts large number of emigrants from various parts of the world, who together with the local immigrants give the city a very colorful and vibrant look, transforming the region in to a true metropolis. Besides, the business travelers, Bangalore also attract a large number of leisure travelers flocking in from all parts of the country and rest of the world to witness the leading factor behind India’s spectacular growth story.
<br /><br />Bangalore is a pretty exciting place offering tourists plenty of things to see and do. Some of the prominent tourist attractions of Bangalore include Vidhana Soudha, Vikasa Soudha, Seshadari Iyer Memorial, Bangalore Palace, Tipu Sultan’s Palace, The Bull Temple, Maha Bodhi Society Temple, ISCKON Temple, St. Mary’s Basilica and much more.
<br /><br />Along with sightseeing tourists can go pub hopping in the Pub Capital of India or explore the local markets wherein one can shop anything from branded goods to local products. There are also plenty of adventure clubs present in the city offering various outdoor sports activities.
<br /><br />There is absolutely no dearth of good Hotels in Bangalore catering to the lodging needs of the myriad of business and leisure travelers visiting the region. The hotels and resorts needless to say are found across all budget segments ranging from the luxury hotels to the budget and economy hotels thus, catering to all tastes and preferences.
<br /><br />There are plenty of tour and travel operators offering exciting and lucrative Bangalore packages, inclusive of transportation, accommodation, sightseeing, etc. A benefit of opting for these Bangalore packages is that tourists needn’t have to worry about various travel arrangements and just sit back and enjoy a relaxing holiday in India’s Silicon Valley.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL0JhbmdhbG9yZS1QYWNrYWdlcy0yOTMtMTMteWVzLTAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Bangalore Packages</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2JhbmdhbG9yZS1yZXNvcnRzLTEzLTI5My0xMy5odG1s" target="_blank">Bangalore Resorts</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e677d5738ee342db410ab31901d86d14" url=""><![CDATA[Jaipur – A Treasure Trove<br/><br/>Jaipur is a picturesque holiday destination widely renowned for its royal connect and the various monuments and architectures standing witness to it. The region having a rich and intriguing historical background is a treasure trove travelers looking to explore and learn about Indian royalty, the traditions and culture of India along with having a truly memorable time. The city enjoys great popularity among the tourist circle and is visited by large number of tourists coming in from all parts of the country and also rest of the world. In fact Jaipur forms an integral part of the ‘Golden Triangle’ of the Indian tourism industry along with Delhi and Agra.
<br /><br />Jaipur was founded as India’s first planned city by his highness Maharaja Sawai Jai Singh II in the year 1727 and was consequently named after the founder. The city also has an interesting story behind its famous epithet the ‘pink city’; the city was so colored to resemble the red sandstone architecture of the Mughals so as to welcome the royal guest, Prince of Wales.
<br /><br />Jaipur has several layers to it, revealed slowly to tourists. There are plenty of things to see and explore in the city. Some of the prominent attractions of Jaipur include the Hawa Mahal, Amber Fort, Jaigarh Fort, Nahargarh Fort, City Palace, Jantar Mantar. Gaitore, Ram Niwas Gardens, Vidyadhar Garden, Sisodia Rani Palace and Garden, Galtaji, Lakshmi Narayan Temple and much more.
<br /><br />Along with sightseeing tourists can also enjoy various cultural performances held on regular successions from the folk songs and dance to the puppet shows. A must do in Jaipur is to take a camel or elephant ride. Tourists can also explore the local markets famous for its colorful rajais, jewels and various other handicrafts and local trinkets among others, also not to forget gorging on the delicious food of the region.
<br /><br />Hotels and Resorts are aplenty in Jaipur, offering tourists a plethora of options. The hotels and resorts are found across all budget segments, from the heritage hotels, luxury hotels to the budget and economy hotels thus, catering to all tastes and preferences of the myriad of travelers visiting the region.
<br /><br />Tour operators easily take care of Jaipur hotel booking along with other travel needs and services, ensuring complete ease and comfort on the part of travelers.  Jaipur being a prominent holiday destination of India is needless to say one well connected region; however, one very stylish way of touring he region is by the super luxury train ‘Palace on Wheels’.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2phaXB1ci1yZXNvcnRzLTYtMzgzLTEzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Jaipur Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItSmFpcHVyLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMzgzLTYteWVzLWRlc3RpbmF0aW9uLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Hotels in Jaipur</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1755ffe02fcce8ee180d439f214d575" url=""><![CDATA[Wayanad - A Relaxing Vacation<br/><br/>Wayanad is a pleasing holiday destination sitting in north-east of Kerala. The hill station kind of takes its tourists back to those golden days when things weren’t so complicated and life was still simple and easy. Wayanad is like a retro destination which fascinates tourists with the simplicity of life offered and the relaxed pace of life thus, offering the perfect destination wherein one can sit back, catch their breath and adorn the beauty of nature along with enjoying the simple pleasures of life. Tourists from all corners of the country and various regions of the world throng to this rare retreat to experience true bliss.
<br /><br />Wayanad has an interesting background to the naming of the region. It is believed that the region was earlier referred to as ‘Mayakshetra’ (maya’s land) which was later transformed to Mayanad and finally to Wayanad which literally translates into ‘land of paddy fields’ pointing to the presence of several paddy fields. Wayanad boasts of a naturally endowed region complete with plantations, forests and wildlife.
<br /><br />Wayanad offers to its tourists various interesting tourist destinations, from the natural sites to various man-made attractions. Some of the prominent tourist attractions located in and around Wayanad include the Chembra Peak,Neelimala, Meenmutty Falls, Chethalayam Falls, Pakshipathalam, Banasura Sagar Dam, Wayanad Wildlife Sanctuary, Muthanga Wayanad Wildlife Sanctuary, Tholpetty, Jain Temple, Edakkal Caves, Pazhassi Raja’s Tomb, Pookote Lake, sentinel Rock Falls, Kanthanpara Falls, Sunrise Valley and much more.
<br /><br />Tourists can also explore the local markets or indulge in various sorts of adventure sports activities offered in the region.  There are also plenty of accommodation options for tourists to choose from. The hotels and resorts in Wayanad are present across various budget segments ranging from the luxury hotels to the economy and budget hotels thus, catering to varied tastes and preferences of the myriad of travelers visiting the region.
<br /><br />Tour operators also offer Wayanad hotel booking inclusive in the entire tour package for the complete ease and comfort of travelers.
<br /><br />Wayanad enjoying a salubrious can be visited throughout the year; however, the region does offer the much needed relief from the scorching summers experienced in the country. The hill station is also pretty well connected by the Kozhikode airport located approx. 66 km and the Kozhikode railway station located approx. 110 km away. In addition to that regular state and private buses can easily availed from various regions of the state and neighboring areas for Wayanad.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL3dheWFuYWQtcmVzb3J0cy0xNS01OTUtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Wayanad Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItV2F5YW5hZC1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTU5NS0xNS15ZXMtZGVzdGluYXRpb24uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Hotels in Wayanad</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a01d2729cf76bce277d570006bef8563" url=""><![CDATA[Agra Hotels - Hand in Hand with Heritage<br/><br/>Agra, the famous city where one of the seven wonders of the world, Taj Mahal is situated, is in the state of Uttar Pradesh, about two hundred kilometers from the capital of India, Delhi. Known for heritage tourism, Agra has three main tourist attractions namely Taj Mahal, Agra Fort and Fatehpur Sikri. The great Mughal emperors, who were also architecture connoisseurs, have built many buildings in Agra that made it a favorite heritage tourism site in the later years.
<br /><br />Emperor Babur built the famous Aram Bagh or the garden of relaxation, his son Akbar built the Agra Fort and the Fatehpur Sikr,i and the world famous Taj Mahal was built by his grandson Shah Jahan, the latter in the loving memory of his wife Mumtaz Mahal. Taj Mahal, the fame of Agra, is the most famous site here. Taj Mahal is a tomb built out of white marble and is one of the most well preserved architectural masterpieces in the world. There is an entry fee to enter this beautiful monument which is open from 6 am to 7.30 pm.
<br /><br />Fatehpur Sikri was the capital of the Mughal Empire for about 10 years. It has inside it the famous Jama Masjid of Agra along with well preserved palaces and courtyards. It was built in the 16th century and it is a UNESCO World Heritage Site.
<br /><br />Swami Bagh, Ram Bagh and the Mehtab Bagh are the famous gardens in Agra frequented by tourists. Some of the main temples in Agra also attract a lot of tourists like Balkeshwar temple, Kailash temple, Mankameshwar temple, Prithvinath temple, Rajeshwar temple, Shyam Ji Maharaj temple, Mahakal and Mahakali temple and Rowli Maharaj temple. There are also a number of tombs built in reverence of many great personalities of the Mughal times which have now turned into tourist spots.
<br /><br />ITC Mughal, Trident Hilton and the Oberoi Amarvilas are the five star Agra hotels. The star Hotels in Agra have pretty good value for money compared to the star hotels in other cities. Considered among the top hotels in Asia, these hotels provide a good view of the Taj from the pavilions on top.
<br /><br />Among the mid-range Agra Hotels, Hotel Priya, Hotel Mandakini Vilas, Laurie’s Hotel, Hotel Raj, Rajmahal Hotel and Hotel Taj Resorts are favored by many. The budget hotels in Agra are available on a daily rent of Rs. 700 to 900 per day. Hotel Sheetla, Hotel Amba Inn, Hotel Kamal, Hotel Neelkanth, Saniya Palace and Shanthi Lodge are the well known budget Agra Hotels.
<br /><br />About 20 trains connect Agra to Delhi everyday which is also easily accessible from Jaipur. Well connected with roads, rails and aeroplanes, Agra is a tourist’s paradise.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL0FncmEtUGFja2FnZXMtMjU1LTEteWVzLTAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Agra Packages</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQWdyYS1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTI1NS0xLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Agra</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="90bccb187c4d86190c1ca1b4fb8e51c7" url=""><![CDATA[Bangalore Hotels - Experience the Garden City<br/><br/>Bangalore is beautiful city in the state of Karnataka known for its salubrious climate all year round. Known by various sobriquets like the Garden City, Pensioners Paradise, Silicon Valley of India and few others, the city of Bangalore is a tourists’ delight.
<br /><br />Bangalore is dotted with many interesting tourist attractions like palaces, gardens, churches, temples, museums and historical monuments. Shopping and clubbing are two other favourite pass times for those who visit this city. The city has its fair share of luxury malls and street shopping options that is sure to entice all kinds of shoppers. The city is also famous for its many pubs and clubs that play hosts to world renowned DJs and are a favourite haunt among the youngsters of the city. Bangalore’s many renowned theatres and art and culture centres cater to the more refined arts too. Bangalore is also the venue for many renowned touring theatre groups, dancers and classical musicians.
<br /><br />Among the parks in Bangalore, Lal Bagh and Cubbon Park are most famous, while the Tippu Sultan Summer Palace, Bangalore Palace and Mayo Hall are the most prominent among the historical structures. Bangalore Museum and Vishweshwaraiah Museum are a favourite among children while Iskcon Temple, Bull Temple, St Mary’s Basilica, St Patrick’s Church and the Masjid-e-Khadria are some of the popular places of worship here in Bangalore.
<br /><br />Bangalore is a metropolis that is famous for its hotels that range from luxury to budget and even several boutique hotels. The Leela Palace, the Oberoi, Le Meridien, Taj Westend, ITC Windsor, Lalit Ashok, the Chancery Pavilion etc are some of the five star Bangalore Hotels which offer tourists a taste of luxury. With lavish suites, some of which can set you back by a lakh or so for a single night, these luxury hotels cater to every need of the occupants.
<br /><br />For those who do not wish to spend a fortune on a single hotel room can go for the more pocket friendly hotels that apart from providing good accommodation also offer various other facilities like swimming pool, lounge area, 24 hours front desk and many more such amenities. Ramada Bangalore, Monarch Luxur, Fortune Park JP Celestial, St Marks Hotel, Lemon Tree Premier, Svenska Design Hotel, Park Plaza, The Zuri, Savannah Sarovar etc are some of the mid range hotels that combine luxury and budget.
<br /><br />For the backpackers seeking low budget accommodation, there are many hotels in the city that despite not providing too many amenities, offer basic room with or without a/c, baths with hot water, in room television and intercom phone. Bangalore hotels in this range include the TAP Gold Crest, Infantry hotel, Baron’s Inn, Hotel Nandhini, Koramangala Residency and several others.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2JhbmdhbG9yZS1yZXNvcnRzLTEzLTI5My0zNC5odG1s" target="_blank">Bangalore Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQmFuZ2Fsb3JlLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMjkzLTEzLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Bangalore</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="605b73b0ab95ee520a60336fc4d88bb4" url=""><![CDATA[Wayanad – Eco Tourism Hub<br/><br/>Nestled in the lush green valleys of the Western Ghats, Wayanad is one of the later formed districts of Kerala. Wayanad district came into existence in 1980 with the headquarters at Kalpetta, carving out areas from Kozhikode and Kannur districts.
<br /><br />Wayanad with its forest covered mountains and valleys, extensive jungle cover, flora and fauna, pristine waterfalls, crystal clear lakes and historic monuments is a tourist hot spot and one of the most visited districts in Kerala.
<br /><br />Wayanad’s strategic location has also been a boon for the tourism development in Wayanad. Wayanad lies on the border of the neighboring states of Tamil Nadu and Karnataka, making it advantageously located near other tourist locations like Ooty, Mysore and Coorg. Its proximity to Bangalore also attracts a lot of tourists on the weekends.
<br /><br />At a height of about 2100 metres, Chembra Peak is the highest peak in Wayanad and considered to be a trekkers’ paradise. There is a lake at the summit which promises spectacular views from the top.
<br /><br />Pakshipaathalam is also another favoured trekking destination. There is a natural rock cave in the Brahmagiri Hills that is also a favoured trekking destination. The 6 km trek from Tirunelli takes you through thick jungle. A lot of resorts and hotels can organise the treks.
<br /><br />Sultan Bathery, a small town in Wayanad derives its name from the Nizam of Hyderabad, Tipu Sultan, who built a fort here that was known as Sultan’s Battery, as he used this place to store ammunition.
<br /><br />Pazhassi Raja, considered the ‘Lion of Kerala’, was the first to fight a guerrilla war against the British. In the memory of Pazhassi Raja a tomb has been built near Mananthavady in Wayanad.
<br /><br />Muthanga and Tholpetty are two wildlife reserves in Wayanad that are home to a wide variety of flora and fauna, which even include some endangered species.
<br /><br />Believed to be in existence from the New Stone Age, Wayanad is full of archaeological sites as well. Edakkal caves, an ancient rock shelter, 4000 feet up the mountain, are famous for the rock art depicting human and animal carvings.
<br />Some of the most popular religious centers in Wayanad are Ananthanatha Swamy Temple, popularly referred to as the Jain Temple, the Tirunelli Temple, Papanasini, Valliyoorkavu Temple, Sita Lava Kusha Temple, Thrissilery Shiva Temple and the Pallikkunnu Church and is a must for the religiously fervent.
<br />Kuruva Island on the Kabini River is a relatively untouched mass of tropical forests that houses many exquisite varieties of flora and avifauna.
<br /><br />Another popular attraction here is the Banasura Sagar Dam which is famous as the largest earth dam in India.
<br /><br />The nearest airport is Karipur international airport in Kozhikode and the nearest railway station is the Kozhikode railway station.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL3dheWFuYWQtcmVzb3J0cy0xNS01OTUtMzQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Wayanad Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItV2F5YW5hZC1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTU5NS0xNS15ZXMtZGVzdGluYXRpb24uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Hotels in Wayanad</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dba6e89bb1d159b2ad729ce102cfa36a" url=""><![CDATA[Agra – The Cradle of Mughal Empire<br/><br/>Agra, the erstwhile capital of the Mughal Emperors, is situated on the banks of the River Yamuna in the North Indian state of Uttar Pradesh. Located at an approximate distance of 363 kilometres to the west of state capital Lucknow and around 200 kilometres to the south of national capital New Delhi, Agra is popularly known as the city of Taj. It is one of the most populous as well as polluted city of the state.
<br /><br />One of the earliest mentions of Agra can be found in the great Epic, The Mahabharata. Agra was known as Agreva?a (which literally means border of the forest). Folklores credit Raja Badal Singh, a Sikarwar Rajput king, as the founder of the city of Agra, in the year 1475. It is also said that the Fort Badalgarh had stood on or near the location of the present Agra Fort.
<br /><br />On the other hand, the 11th century Persian poet Masood Sa’d Salman wrote about a frantic attack on the fortress of Agra (which was under the control of the Shahi King Jayapala at that time), by Sultan Mahmud of Ghazni. Sultan Sikandar Lodi of the Delhi Sultante was the first one to move his capital from Delhi to Agra in the year 1506. When he died in 1517, his son Ibrahim Lodi continued to be in power at Agra for around nine more years, before finally being defeated at the Battle of Panipat in 1526.
<br /><br />Agra reached its pinnacle of fame as the capital of the Mughal emperors from the year 1526 to 1658. Agra is today one of the major tourist destination, mainly because of its numerous Mughal-era buildings. Among them, the most notable are the Taj Mahal, Agra Fort and Fatehpur Sikri. All these three sites of Agra have been listed under the UNESCO World Heritage Sites’ list.
<br /><br />The major sightseeing attractions of Agra are the Taj Mahal, Agra Fort, Fatehpur Sikri, Itimad-Ud-Daulah, Akbar’s Tomb (named Sikandra), Swami Bagh Samadhi, Mankameshwar Temple, Ankit ka Tal, Jama Masjid, Chini ka Rauza, Ram Bagh, Mariam’s Tomb, Mehtab Bagh, Keetham Lake, Mughal Heritage Walk and The Cathedral of the Immaculate Conception, to name a few.
<br /><br />Agra experiences a semiarid climate with characteristic features like mild winters, hot and dry summers and a monsoon season. Hence, the best time to visit Agra would be during the winter months extending from November to March.
<br /><br />Agra is well-connected and easily accessible from all parts of the world. Agra has an airport located just at the outskirts of the city. Agra is a major railhead that is connected to all parts of the country as well. Buses also ply from the nearby cities to Agra on a regular basis.
<br /><br />For more information on <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL0FncmEtUGFja2FnZXMtMjU1LTEteWVzLTAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Agra Packages</a></strong> and popular <strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQWdyYS1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTI1NS0xLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Agra</a></strong> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9edf30bbf4b4b48e82c76bad84061a2e" url=""><![CDATA[Bangalore – The Cosmopolitan Metropolis of India<br/><br/>According to some legends, King Veeraballa of the Vijayanagara dynasty once lost his way in forest. Starved and exhausted, he chanced upon lonely shack in the dense forest wherein he came across an old woman. When he asked for food, she gave him boiled beans (called ‘Benda Kalu’ in Kannada). The King was surprised to discover that this modest meal tasted better than the most sumptuous menu of his palace. To mark this incident, he titled the place as “Benda Kalu Ooru” (meaning ‘the Place of Baked Beans). Over the years, the words Benda Kalu Ooru slowly got transformed into the name Bangalore.
<br /><br />The Capital City of the South Indian state of Karnataka, Bangalore is one of the fastest growing cosmopolitan cities of Asia. It is home to some of the most sophisticated industries of the country. The Information Technology industry especially views Bangalore as the ‘Silicon Valley’ of India. Bangalore is also home to some of India’s premier scientific organizations. Endowed a healthy climate, gardens &amp; parks, natural lakes, architectural landmarks, business opportunities, shopping malls, multi cuisine restaurants and pubs in this part of the world, currently Bangalore is considered as the ideal gateway to India and beyond. Bangalore has something to offer for everyone – music and dance concerts (Western and Indian), dramas, exhibitions, carnivals, conferences and other cultural activities are all a part of the life in Bangalore.
<br /><br />The ideal place for disco-hopping, social drinking, shopping till the feet gives away, eating in the most fashionable restaurants, watching one’s favourite movie in comfortable movie hall or simply teeing off to fame, everything is easily possible in Bangalore.
<br /><br />The major sightseeing attractions in and around Bangalore include the Bangalore Palace, Lalbagh, Iskcon Temple, Ashoka Pillar (near Lal Bagh), Dargah Hazarath Tawakkal Mastan, Juma Masjid (oldest mosque of the city), Ravindra Kalakshetra (built to commemorate the centenary of Rabindranath Tagore), St. Mary’s Church (established in 1811), Indian Institute Of Science (IISc or Tata Institute) Gandhi Bhavan, Innovative Film City, Jawaharlal Nehru Planetarium, Ulsoor lake, Hebbal Lake, Visvesvaraya Museum, Vidhana Soudha, Cubbon park, The Bangalore Race Course, Muddenahalli (birthplace of Sir M Visvesvaraya), Devenahalli (birthplace of Tipu Sultan) and Chikkajala (a vassal fort), to name a few.
<br /><br />Bangalore is easily accessible as it is well connected by air, rail and road to all the major cities of the country. Bangalore Airport is used for both domestic and international flights. Bangalore is directly connected to cities such as Delhi, Chennai, Mumbai, Kolkata and Hyderabad, as well as almost all other important cities and towns of Karnataka and neighbouring states.
<br /><br />Bangalore also enjoys regular train and bus services to and from Chennai, Mysore, Kolkata, New Delhi, Mangalore and Kochi among others.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2Rlc3RpbmF0aW9ucy9CYW5nYWxvcmUtT3ZlcnZpZXcuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Bangalore Holiday Packages</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQmFuZ2Fsb3JlLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMjkzLTEzLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Bangalore Hotel Booking</a> Visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d859a0fb1a3401deb799f52fe190d3d8" url=""><![CDATA[Jaipur – Shoppers’ Paradise<br/><br/>Jaipur, famous for its forts and monuments, is situated in the state of Rajasthan. The city is also called the ‘Pink City’ because pink stones are used for the construction of the buildings and the walls of the city. The city of Jaipur was founded in the year 1727 by Sawai Jaisingh II.  Jaipur, the capital of Rajasthan, is also called the ‘Walled City’.
<br /><br />Jaipur houses many attractive forts, some of them are Amber Fort, Jaigarh Fort, Jal Mahal, Nahargarh Fort and the City Palace.  Nahargarh Fort was the residence of the Maharaja. The Maharaja Jaisingh was well known for his vast knowledge in astronomy and he himself had taken initiative for the design and the construction of the city of Jaipur.
<br /><br />The architectural beauty of the city of Jaipur is very unique. The construction of the various forts and monuments showcases the culture of the Mughals and the Rajputs. The construction of the city was well planned as the City Palace is in the centre and the markets, residents and the public buildings are placed around the City Palace. The huge gates of the palaces and the walls attract the travelers.
<br /><br />Jaipur Literature Festival is the largest and the most prestigious meeting of literature lovers, for which a lot of people from India and abroad gather every year. The site of the Literature festival is the Diggi Palace in Jaipur.
<br /><br />Jaipur  attracts  tourists of varied interests. Jaipur is a shoppers’ paradise as bed sheets with traditional Jaipuri print, cloths with mirror work and other curios are a familiar sight in the markets. Jaipur is a haven for arts and crafts. The famous tie and die fabric making, block printing, painting and sculpture making are some of the arts in Jaipur. The popular Kundan style jewelry is a much demanded item. Stone carving, sandalwood carving and brass items are also very popular. The adorable jewelry and fantastic handicrafts are a treasure to the tourists.
<br /><br />Some of the festivals celebrated in Jaipur are Gangaur, Elephant Festival, Teej, Makar Sankranti, Shitla Asthami and Donkey Fair. The Elephant Festival is celebrated in the month of March-April on the day of Holi. The elephants are decorated with colorful clothes and a procession is also arranged to attract the tourists. Elephant Polo match, Elephant races and performance by the folk dancers of Rajasthan are mind blowing.  The festival Teej is celebrated in the month of July-August to welcome the monsoon rain. Makara Sankranti is celebrated on the 14th of January and a kite flying festival is also organized in Jaipur. Camel Festival, Beneswar Fair, Nagaur Fair, Desert Festival, Mewar Festival,  Pushkar Fair, Gangaur Fair are some of the other fairs and festivals celebrated with much enthusiasm.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2phaXB1ci1yZXNvcnRzLTYtMzgzLTM0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Jaipur Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItSmFpcHVyLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMzgzLTYteWVzLWRlc3RpbmF0aW9uLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Hotels in Jaipur</a>, Visit- HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="75cf82317ca1e1efd898e87e5085151e" url=""><![CDATA[Wayanad - All round experience<br/><br/>Wayanad is a popular tourist destination set snugly amidst the Western Ghats in the state of Kerala. Situated in the Wayanad district, the hill station of Wayanad is part of the Nilgiri Biosphere.
<br /><br />This green paradise lies at the border of the greener portion of Kerala and is part of the Nilgiri Biosphere. Spread over an area of 2132 square km, it comprises of three taluks Mananthavady, Sulthan Bathery and Vythiri. Wayanad is set in close proximity to many other popular tourist destinations like Ooty, Kannur, Bangalore, Mysore and Coorg.
<br /><br />Fringed by high mountain ranges, bathed in green plantations and dense forests that house several aboriginal tribes, exotic wildlife and a variety of flora, Wayanad is truly a dream destination. In fact there are parts of Wayanad that are even now unexplored owing to the intense forest covers and in these parts are preserved a unique and and as of yet untouched ecosystem. The adventurous kinds are also rewarded with many outback trails and trekking routes due to the undulating terrains of the region. Muthanga and Tholpetty are two wildlife reserves in Wayanad that are home to a wide variety of flora and fauna, which even include some endangered species.
<br /><br />Chembra Peak, Edakkal Caves, Kuruva Islands and the highest point in Wayanad, Lakkidi are some of the most popular tourist destinations here. Few other popular places of interest are Pakshipathalam, Pazhassi Raja Tomb, Pookot Lake, Sentinel Rock Waterfalls, Kanthanpara Waterfalls, Soochippara Waterfalls and the Banasura Sagar Dam. Wayanad also has some beautiful temples like the Sulthan Bathery Jain Temple, Thirunelli Temple, Valliyoorkavu Temple, Seetha Luva-Kusha Temple and the Thrissilery Shiva Temple.
<br /><br />Pookote lake is perhaps one of the most visited attractions here. This natural freshwater lake is surrounded by dense evergreen forests and hills. Another popular attraction here is the Banasura Sagar Dam which is famous as the largest earth dam in India. Many Hindu pilgrims take a trip to Thirunelli and bathe in the holy waters of the stream Papanasini, since it is believed to wash off all sins. A lovely island on the Kabini river, Kuruva Island is a relatively untouched mass of tropical forests that houses many exquisite varieties of flora and avifauna. Meenmutty waterfalls is an ideal trekking experience and so is Pakshipathalam in the Brahmagiri hills comprising of a 17 km trek through the wild forests. Edakkal Caves are ancient caves on the Ambukutty Mountains with famous rock carvings on the inner walls.
<br /><br />Kozhikode is the closest city with an airport and a railway station and is situated around 98 km from Wayanad. A network of roads connects Wayanad to Kozhikode and few other major cities within the state and in the neighbouring states too.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL3dheWFuYWQtcmVzb3J0cy0xNS01OTUtMzQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Wayanad Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItV2F5YW5hZC1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTU5NS0xNS15ZXMtZGVzdGluYXRpb24uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Hotels in Wayanad</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="732ae53543e743e0d6e6f1f30755fcfc" url=""><![CDATA[Agra Hotels – Accommodation in the Land of the Taj<br/><br/>Agra, popular around the world due the presence of the Taj Mahal, lies in the north Indian state of Uttar Pradesh. Situated close to the national capital of Delhi, Agra is a premier destination of the world that prominently figures in the list of UNESCO World Heritage Site. Often called as Poetry in Marble, the Taj Mahal of Agra is one of the most visited places of India by both national and international tourists.
<br /><br />Agra is an ancient city which finds mentions in ancient texts like the Mahabharata. Known as Agravana in the earlier days, Agra owes its present fame to the reign of the Mughal Emperors who had patronized the city like no other rulers. Though it was Sikandar Lodi of the Lodi dynasty who had first made Agra his capital, it was under the Mughal rule that the city flourished.
<br /><br />Though Agra is famous for Taj Mahal, which is said to be a mausoleum constructed by the Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan in memory of his wife Mumtaz Mahal, it is also known for other historic sites like Agra fort and Fatehpur Sikri. Both of these edifices also feature in the list of UNESCO World Heritage Site.  Some other popular attractions of Agra are the Chini Ka rauza, Itimad-ud-Daula (Baby Taj) and which was constructed by Nurjahan, the Queen of Emperor Jehangir in memory of her father, Mariyam’s tomb, Jama Masjid, Boudmath, numerous Gurudwara, Jain Temples, Churches and Mosques, among others.
<br /><br />Since it is a city visited by tourists throughout the year, there are many Agra Hotels that have come up to accommodate the lodging and boarding needs of Agra’s visitors. Given that it is a global tourist destination, Agra Hotels are well-prepared to meet the varying needs of their guests. Agra Hotels can be broadly classified into budget hotels, medium range and luxury hotels as well as resorts. It can be concluded that whatever the budget of the guest, there are numerous Agra Hotels that are lined up in various parts of the city to cater to the needs of the visitors.
<br /><br />Some of the most popular Agra Hotels are the Jaypee Palace Hotel, Welcome Hotel Mughal Sheraton, Holiday Inn, Amar Hotel, The Gateway Hotel, Clarks Shiraz Hotel, Howard Park Plaza, Taj Heritage Hotel, Agra Ashok Hotel, Trident Agra, Agra Mahal Hotel, Taj Resorts Hotel, Hilltop Hotel, Welcome Heritage Grand Imperial (all five star rated hotels) and Amar Yatri Niwas, Grand Hotel, Mansingh Palace, Siddhartha Hotel, Taj Khema, Ajay International Hotel, Taj Plaza Hotel (all four star rated hotels). There are plenty of other budget hotels also available easily in Agra. Moreover, Homestays, B &amp; B Inns and Deluxe hotels also are aplenty in Agra.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL0FncmEtUGFja2FnZXMtMjU1LTEteWVzLTAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Agra Holiday Packages</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQWdyYS1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTI1NS0xLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Agra</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b28a2bd5470664e12efa4adf132b23b9" url=""><![CDATA[Bangalore Hotels – Lodging in the Garden City<br/><br/>Popularly called the ‘Garden City’ of India in the olden days, Bangalore, the state capital of Karnataka, is now more or less known as the Silicon Valley of India. This is mainly due to the presence of numerous Information Technology companies and technological parks situated along the length and breadth of this beautiful city. Bangalore was also considered as a Pensioner’s Paradise in the early days as it enjoyed moderate climate conditions as well as peaceful surroundings.
<br /><br />Bangalore today is an ultra modern city characterized by high rise buildings, ever growing infrastructures (like roads, metro rail, malls and other modern facilities) and IT Parks among others. Ever since the IT industry was established in Bangalore, it underwent huge changes – both physically and demographically. What used to be a greener city with numerous gardens now has turned into a metro city full of modern buildings; the pensioners paradise has turned into a job seeker’s paradise as Bangalore has a host of industries like IT, Bio-technology, Mechanics and Electronics, to name a few. Apart from these, people from all over the country throng the place in search of good education avenues, thus turning it into a major education hub.
<br /><br />The major tourist attractions of Bangalore include its famous gardens like Lal bagh, Cubbon Park, and Lumbini Garden among others; Bangalore Palace, Iskcon Temple, Ashoka Pillar (near Lal Bagh), Dargah Hazarath Tawakkal Mastan, Juma Masjid (oldest mosque of the city), Ravindra Kalakshetra (built to commemorate the centenary of Rabindranath Tagore), St. Mary’s Church (founded in 1811), Indian Institute Of Science (IISc or Tata Institute) Gandhi Bhavan, Innovative Film City, Jawaharlal Nehru Planetarium, Ulsoor lake, Hebbal Lake, Visvesvaraya Museum, Vidhana Soudha, The Bangalore Race Course, Muddenahalli (birthplace of Sir M Visvesvaraya), Devenahalli (birthplace of Tipu Sultan) and Chikkajala (a vassal fort), to name a few.
<br /><br />Bangalore plays host to several people who visit the city for numerous purposes like education, career, business and sightseeing among others. Bangalore Hotels are well equipped to meet this constant influx of visitors to the city. As a city that welcomes its guests with open hearts and minds, Bangalore Hotels cater to the needs of a traveller on a shoe string budget as well as a business tycoon in search of the most luxurious amenities.
<br /><br />Bangalore Hotels are conveniently located all over the city, and a visitor can easily access them according to his budgetary preferences. Some of the Bangalore Hotels that fall under the luxury category are Taj West End, ITC Windsor, The Lalit Ashok, Le Meridian and Oberoi among others. Bangalore Hotels like Mapple residency, Algate Hotel, Basil Hotel, Hotel Shalimar and Mayura among others provide budgetary accommodation to its guests at comparatively cheaper rates.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2JhbmdhbG9yZS1yZXNvcnRzLTEzLTI5My0zNC5odG1s" target="_blank">Bangalore Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQmFuZ2Fsb3JlLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMjkzLTEzLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Bangalore</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="da7e7195eb4f5edf131883d0cb205f11" url=""><![CDATA[Jaipur Packages – The Desert Land<br/><br/>Jaipur, a heritage city, is situated in the state of Rajasthan. The city is also called the ‘Pink City’ because pink stones are used for the construction of the buildings and the walls of the city. The city of Jaipur was founded in the year 1727 by Sawai Jaisingh II.  Jaipur, the capital of Rajasthan, is also called the ‘Walled City’. The city is famous for its forts and monuments and enthralls its visitors by its planned architecture.
<br /><br />By availing Jaipur Packages one can enjoy sightseeing and the luxurious accommodation. Jaipur houses many attractive forts and some of them are Amber Fort, Jaigarh Fort, Jal Mahal, Nahargarh Fort, Hawa Mahal and the City Palace.  Nahargarh Fort was the residence of the Maharaja. Janthar Manthar is a collection of instruments constructed by Sawai Jaising II and is used for astronomical calculations. Hawa Mahal is a five-storied monument with overhanging windows. Amber fort is a huge fort which contains marvelous chambers like Diwan-i-Aam, Sheesh Mahal, Sukh Niwas and Jai Mahal.
<br /><br />The construction of the various forts and monuments showcases the culture of the Mughals and the Rajputs. The construction of the city was well planned as the City Palace is in the centre and the markets, residents and the public buildings are placed around the City Palace. Jaipur Havelis are very famous with arched gates, big courtyards and beautifully carved balconies. Some of the famous Havelis in Jaipur are Nattani ki Haveli, Rajputana Haveli and Nawab Sahib ki Haveli. The huge gates of the palaces and the long walls mesmerize the tourists.
<br /><br />Jaipur Packages attract the tourists of varied interests. Jaipur is a shoppers’ paradise as bed sheets with traditional Jaipuri print, cloths with mirror work and other curios are a familiar sight in the markets. Sireh Deori Bazar is a famous market that sells clothes, puppets and other items. Jaipur is a haven for arts and crafts. The famous tie and die fabric making, block printing, painting and sculpture making are some of the arts in Jaipur. You can get all the bandhani and block printed textiles from Johari Bazar. The popular Kundan style jewelry is a much demanded item.  Stone carving, sandalwood carving and brass items are also very popular.
<br /><br />Some of the festivals celebrated in Jaipur are Gangaur, Elephant Festival, Teej, Makar Sankranti, Deepawali, Holi and Shitla Asthami. Camel Festival, Beneswar Fair, Nagaur Fair, Desert Festival, Mewar Festival,  Pushkar Fair, Gangaur Fair are some of the other fairs and festivals celebrated here.
<br /><br />The temperature in Jaipur in the summer is comparatively high as it is a desert land. It rises up to 46 degrees Celsius during daytime. The winter season is the ideal time to visit the city of Jaipur.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2phaXB1ci1yZXNvcnRzLTYtMzgzLTM0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Jaipur Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItSmFpcHVyLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMzgzLTYteWVzLWRlc3RpbmF0aW9uLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Hotels in Jaipur</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="433a662084a6f01fec3b819c50a5bbaa" url=""><![CDATA[Wayanad Hotels – Living In the Jungle<br/><br/>Wayanad, a district in Kerala, is located in the lush green valleys of the Western Ghats. Wayanad is one of the later formed districts of Kerala, formed by carving out areas from Kozhikode and Kannur districts.
<br /><br />Wayanad is a tourist hot spot and one of the most visited districts in Kerala. With its forest covered mountains and valleys, extensive jungle cover, flora and fauna, pristine waterfalls, crystal clear lakes and historic monuments, Wayanad’s strategic location has also been a boon for the tourism development.
<br /><br />Some of the tourist spots are Chembra Peak, Edakkal Caves, Kuruva Islands, Pakshipathalam, Pazhassi Raja Tomb, Pookot Lake, Sentinel Rock Waterfalls, Kanthanpara Waterfalls, Soochippara Waterfalls and the Banasura Sagar Dam. Wayanad also has temples like the Jain Temple, Thirunelli Temple, Valliyoorkavu Temple, Sita-Luva-Kusha Temple and Thrissilery Shiva Temple.
<br /><br />Being essentially a forest area, the forest department has numerous tourist lodges and inspection bungalows located near the numerous wild life sanctuaries situated around Wayanad.
<br /><br />These Wayanad Hotels have only the basic amenities and it is always better to book well in advance and carry your own provisions. The Forest Bungalow in Thirunelli offers two double rooms and a dormitory. The rooms cost Rs 500 a night and the dormitories Rs. 100 a bed. But be prepared, there are no phones or TV connection.
<br /><br />A popular mid-range Wayanad Hotel is Panchathirtha Rest House which has about 60 double bedded rooms.
<br /><br />A lot of camps and home stays are also available in Wayanad. Green Gales Hotel has set up a camp near the Kabini River near Kuruva islands and organises all sorts of adventurous activities like rafting, trekking and fishing.
<br /><br />You can also try out the beautiful home stays in Wayanad and enjoy the hospitality and homely food in these Wayanad Hotels. Home stays may cost from Rs. 2000 upwards depending on the facilities provided.
<br />One of the leading Wayanad Hotels is the ones run by DTPC.
<br />Another popular Wayanad Hotels are the tree houses and eco-lodges in Vythiri. One has to reach the tree house using an ingenious self-propelling elevator made out of cane and counter balanced by the weight of water.
<br /><br />Some of the five star luxurious Wayanad Hotels are Rain Country Resorts, Meenmutty Heights, Vythiri Resort, Harithagiri Ayurvedic Village and Resort, Edakkal Hermitage, Banasura Hill Resort and several others. These resorts are set in the most picturesque of places and the view from these resorts is also breathtaking. Most of these star hotels include facilities like 24 hour restaurant, coffee parlour, cycling, jacuzzi tub, badminton, bonfire, jungle trekking, airport pick/drop, railway station transfer, jogging track, travel desk service.
<br /><br />The nearest airport is Karipur international airport in Kozhikode and the nearest railway station is the Kozhikode railway station.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL3dheWFuYWQtcmVzb3J0cy0xNS01OTUtMzQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Wayanad Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItV2F5YW5hZC1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTU5NS0xNS15ZXMtZGVzdGluYXRpb24uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Hotels in Wayanad</a> visit HolidayIQ.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7cc6c308cf6f4abbbb441d9c0224a91e" url=""><![CDATA[Bangalore Packages – In the Garden City<br/><br/>Bangalore, the capital of Karnataka, is often referred to as the Garden City. Strategically located at an altitude of 1000 metres above sea level, Bangalore, also known as Bengaluru, has a very pleasant climate throughout the year. This cool climate has attracted a lot of retired people to make Bangalore their home giving the city another nickname “The Pensioner’s Paradise”.
<br /><br />Bangalore is also called the core for India’s information technology sector with numerous soft ware companies opening offices here.
<br /><br />Bangalore got its name from the word “Bendha Kaalu” (which means boiled beans in Kannada). The story is that once King Veera Ballala of the Vijayanagara Kingdom was lost in a forest and he came across a hut where an old woman lived. The lady offered the King the boiled beans, and thus the place came to be known as “Bendha kaalu ooru” (the land of boiled beans). Bendha kaalu ooru later came to be known as Bengaluru.
<br /><br />Bangalore was found by Kempe Gowda. Bangalore was also ruled by a number of rulers and dynasties, including the rulers of the Vijayanagara Empire and Tipu Sultan.
<br /><br />A lot of travel agents and tour operators offer tailor made Bangalore Packages to the numerous visitors coming to Bangalore.
<br /><br />If you are a nature lover choose a Bangalore Package which would include a visit to the numerous parks and gardens in around the city. The main gardens in Bangalore are Cubbon Park, Lumbini Gardens, Bugle Rock Park, and Lal Bagh Gardens. Flower shows and exhibitions are organised in these gardens.
<br /><br />A visit to the Bannerghatta Biological Park will be an ideal option for the kids. Here visitors are taken around the park in caged vans and can enjoy the wildlife.
<br /><br />Most of the Bangalore Packages would include the other main attractions in and around Bangalore that are the Bangalore Palace, Vidhana Soudha, Visvesvaraya Museum, Gavi Gangadeshwara Cave Temple, HAL Aerospace Museum, Bull Temple, Bangalore’s Secretariat and State Legislature building, Bull temple, ISKON temple, Tipu’s palace, and Nandi hills.
<br /><br />One can also take one day trips to nearby places like Bandipur, Nagarhole, Srirangapatna, Coorg, Mysore, Chikmagalur, Ooty and Wayanad.
<br /><br />Bangalore has an efficient public transport system, Bangalore Metropolitan Transport Corporation (BMTC), that have a fleet of air conditioned buses for the convenience of the tourists.
<br /><br />The Karnataka State Road Transport Corporation (KSRTC) and private buses connects Bangalore to all the major cities in Karnataka and other states.  Bangalore City Railway station and Yesvantpur Junction are the main railway stations in Bangalore. The mass rapid transit system in Bangalore is called the Namma Metro and has currently started operation.
<br /><br />Bangalore, being a cosmopolitan city, has all the modern amenities and facilities at a world class level.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL2JhbmdhbG9yZS1yZXNvcnRzLTEzLTI5My0zNC5odG1s" target="_blank">Bangalore Resorts</a> and popular <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQmFuZ2Fsb3JlLUhvdGVscy1SZXNvcnRzLVJldmlld3MtUmF0aW5ncy1UYXJpZmYtUmF0ZXMtMjkzLTEzLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Hotels in Bangalore</a>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="62f8bf4a8a97f5e00eba799e76ebad21" url=""><![CDATA[Agra Hotels – Lodgings in the Land of Taj Mahal<br/><br/>Agra is known all over the world for being the abode of Taj Mahal, which is also a featured world heritage attraction. Taj Mahal is said to have been built by the Mughal Emperor Shah Jehan in memory of his wife Mumtaz. Agra, situated in the North Indian state of Uttar Pradesh is also known for two other monuments featured in the UNESCO World Heritage Sites’ list – The Agra Fort and Fathehpur Sikri – over and above many other edifices from the past.
<br /><br />Some of the popular attractions of Agra are Chini Ka Rauza (a mausoleum built in 1635), Sikandra, Samadh of Soamji Maharaj, Itimad-ud-Daulas, (also called Baby Taj), Mariyam’s tomb the red sandstone building, Jama Masjid, Boudmath, Gurudwara, Jain Temples, Churches and Mosques, to name a few.
<br /><br />Agra is an ancient city, which finds mention in the epics like Mahabharata. Agra was known as Agravana in the early days and it means ‘End of the Forest’, as Mathura had a huge forest cover extending up to Agra.  Founded by Badal Singh in 1475, Agra was made the capital city of the Delhi Sultante by Sikandar Lodi. After Mughal Emperor Babur defeated Lodis, Agra becoming the haven of Mughal kings, under whom the city flourished.
<br /><br />As an internationally acclaimed tourist destination, there is no dearth in accommodation options in Agra. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQWdyYS1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTI1NS0xLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Agra Hotels</a> can be found across all categories like budget, deluxe, premium, Luxury and resort, to name a few. There are close to 200 well- equipped Agra Hotels, which offer world class facilities for the guests of this quaint town.
<br /><br />Of the five star rated Agra Hotels, the Jaypee Palace Hotel, Welcome Hotel Mughal Sheraton, Holiday Inn Agra, Amar Hotel, The Gateway Hotel, Clarks Shiraz Hotel, Howard Park Plaza, Taj Heritage Hotel, Agra Ashok Hotel, Trident Agra, Agra Mahal Hotel, Taj Resorts Hotel, Hilltop Hotel and Welcome Heritage Grand Imperial among others, offer first class accommodation options coupled with the most luxurious settings.
<br /><br />The 4 star rated Agra Hotels like Amar Yatri Niwas, Grand Hotel, Mansingh Palace, Siddhartha Hotel, Taj Khema, Ajay International Hotel and Taj Plaza Hotel also offer first rate accommodation and amenities to their guests.
<br /><br />A plethora of Agra Hotels belonging to one, two and three star rating are spread all over the city. Most of the Agra Hotels are conveniently located and easily accessible. A few of the Hotels in Agra also fall into the category of Homestay arrangements, B &amp; B Inns and guest houses that offer basic accommodation facilities.
<br /><br />Many of the Agra Hotels, especially in the high end category, often offer special packages and discounts to their customers. Whichever category they belong to, Agra Hotels are well equipped to meet the constant influx of visitors.
<br /><br />For more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL0FncmEtUGFja2FnZXMtMjU1LTEteWVzLTAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Agra Holiday Packages</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob2xpZGF5aXEuY29tL1BvcHVsYXItQWdyYS1Ib3RlbHMtUmVzb3J0cy1SZXZpZXdzLVJhdGluZ3MtVGFyaWZmLVJhdGVzLTI1NS0xLXllcy1kZXN0aW5hdGlvbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Agra Hotel Booking</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>