<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="20">
		<document id="622e33a5a8c3b361602635db87c67925" url=""><![CDATA[WordPress Development – Ideal for CMS Websites<br/><br/>WordPress open source technology used to build highly collaborative &amp; user friendly website. The technology has become increasingly popular and reliable users since its launch in 2003. WordPress has become important for the development of your business development.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a25cfd3c052479b095d3105675b2b605" url=""><![CDATA[7 Free Life Changing iPhone Apps<br/><br/>Today, Mobile device have become a significant part of our daily life. When it comes to smart-phones, the leading among them would be the iPhone.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d5153d40a8e05bfd151abf37599dbbc3" url=""><![CDATA[Hire Iphone Application Developer to Make Best Iphone App<br/><br/>Day-by-day, the demand of iPhone is being increased by designed in functions as well as add on programs available on the apple shop. The need of iPhone programs is going on improving.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bb55becddd73586c660edfe694870e45" url=""><![CDATA[WordPress Extension Development and the Need to Hire WordPre<br/><br/>Blog is an internal part of most of the websites today and WordPress is an excellent open source blogging platform. When you visit a blog, often you will see features on the sides, top and bottom of the blog.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="52d08162b532721108c113b92691dc1" url=""><![CDATA[Benefits of HTML5 Ecommerce Development and Its Popularity<br/><br/>From the time internet exists HTML has been the language of interaction between man and machine. Over the years it has emerged, enhanced and expanded into various versions with better features as time went by resulting in various versions of the platform, the most recent being HTML5.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.perceptionsystem.com%2F2012%2F08%2Fbenefits-of-html5-ecommerce-development-and-its-popularity%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blogs.perceptionsystem.com/2012/08/benefits-of-html5-ecommerce-development-and-its-popularity/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6b23c1c1c7d9080ab3f22018f8ce57da" url=""><![CDATA[Web Development Company - Necessary for Successful Online Bu<br/><br/>In today Internet world, having a website is necessary for small &amp; big businesses. Creating a website is not a difficult job for anyone, you just need to have a domain name and find a template to build your own website.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmFwcGxpY2F0aW9uZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnRpbmRpYTEuYmxvZ3Nwb3QuaW4vMjAxMi8wOC93ZWItZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQtY29tcGFueS1uZWNlc3NhcnktZm9yLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">web development company</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="30f3f6e666ad5d252968d13aff950073" url=""><![CDATA[Build Your Strong Online Impression with Ecommerce Solutions<br/><br/>To Develop a website, needs plan, focus &amp; money, whether you develop an ecommerce shop or multiple shop. The online merchant needs to gather the detail of targeted areas (country, state, city or worldwide), attractive schemes, Goals, etc,
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2ee266a9ac88bc72dbb8379f5db6f691" url=""><![CDATA[The Role of Software Development Company in Your Business<br/><br/>Today, IT Industry is become a most famous and ensuring sectors all over the world. Software development company play the important part in this field for rapid development. 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwebapplicationdevelopmentindia1.blogspot.in%2F2012%2F08%2Fthe-role-of-software-development.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://webapplicationdevelopmentindia1.blogspot.in/2012/08/the-role-of-software-development.html</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b11a05c86fe20eb21aa30ad4ed6470c" url=""><![CDATA[Iphone Application Development – Best Field to Build Your<br/><br/>Day-by-day, the demand of iphone application development is growing rapidly. Its not just a perception of iphone developers or iphone users, the trend is indicating a rising graph in mobile world.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gl%2FicCR3"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://goo.gl/icCR3</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fadb01a1d9c9ca199b3ede5c5b707cc5" url=""><![CDATA[Web Development – All Time Demanding Field<br/><br/>In Today's online completive world, companies have to come up with the innovative concepts of creating their website in a more eye-catching way. Therefore, they are seeking the services of web development companies to fulfill their development needs. A professional and unique design builds trustworthiness of your website, which increase your online sale.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgoo.gl%2F0Epcn"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://goo.gl/0Epcn</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="29416b44320f164a155f6a4ff2b27be6" url=""><![CDATA[Things to Ponder While Choosing the Right Ecommerce Developm<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wZXJjZXB0aW9uc3lzdGVtLmNvbS9lLWNvbW1lcmNlLWFwcGxpY2F0aW9uLWRldmVsb3BtZW50Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ecommerce development,ecommerce solution</a>Ecommerce platforms have simplified it for businesses to mark their presence on the web. The availability of new and advanced versions of ecommerce software’s with ample amount of benefits often makes it difficult for the business owners to select the best ecommerce solution.
<br /><object width="336" height="295"><param name="movie" value="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4717563"></param><param name="wmode" value="window"></param><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"></param><embed src="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4717563" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowFullScreen="true" wmode="window" width="336" height="295"></embed></object><object width="336" height="295"><param name="movie" value="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4717564"></param><param name="wmode" value="window"></param><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"></param><embed src="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4717564" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowFullScreen="true" wmode="window" width="336" height="295"></embed></object>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="47bb6e0bf54f1c3ad4660178928e4ecd" url=""><![CDATA[Importance of Ecommerce Solutions from Business And Consumer<br/><br/>Today time is money and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wZXJjZXB0aW9uc3lzdGVtLmNvbS9lLWNvbW1lcmNlLXNvbHV0aW9ucy1zZXJ2aWNlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">ecommerce solution</a> is what make the balls rolling. Ecommerce is the buzz word for business’s looking to grow and flourish. They have been successful in grabbing the attention from both the vendors and consumers world wide. One of the chief reasons being, successful running of online business’s that increase your ROI manifolds.
<br /><br />From vendors point of view, less time is spent processing the transaction, as such thousands of transactions can be carried through out the day and from customers perspective less time is consumed during the purchase and checkout, creating a win-win situation for both vendors and customers.
<br /><br />Ecommerce solutions help you create a professional, functional and cost-effective online store, enabling you to sell anything you want, anytime you want. It acts as a virtual store that is always up and running, be it day or night. One can place an order even at midnight and can buy the products with the help of few mouse clicks via the internet with ease.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wZXJjZXB0aW9uc3lzdGVtLmNvbS9lLWNvbW1lcmNlLXNvbHV0aW9ucy1zZXJ2aWNlcy5odG1s" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/181270278_8166172_50361400.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />From business’s perspective, ecommerce is far more cost effective then the traditional methods and has redefined the way business’s are carried out. For consumers, online purchasing has become far more convenient and a lucrative option as they can acquire branded goods at discounted rates.
<br /><br />From business point of view, ecommerce provides better connectivity for potential buyers and your respective website. This way, helps you reach out to a broad spectrum of customers, eliminating the limits of geographical location. From customers view point it enables them to browse through different categories, search products, compare items and buy from the best brands, without moving a single inch from your chair or even stepping out of the house.
<br /><br />Ecommerce development have opened up new doors of opportunities for plethora of industries. It is one of those online marketing strategies that offers you guaranteed results. So if you are looking to hike up your sales by targeting new audience, consider E-Commerce as your solution.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb61ba2a9000ec7fef77bbd29b96c4c1" url=""><![CDATA[Software Development – Its Need and How to Proceed with It<br/><br/>Yes, software development for a company will bring in more preciseness, reduce cost, fasten its operations and bring in many other benefits. However the next question coming would be, how does a non-technological company proceed with the entire process of application development. There can be many options, however the most feasible and cost effective way would be to outsource the entire project to a dedicated web development company.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Jsb2dzLnBlcmNlcHRpb25zeXN0ZW0uY29tLzIwMTIvMDkvc29mdHdhcmUtZGV2ZWxvcG1lbnQtJUUyJTgwJTkzLWl0cy1uZWVkLWFuZC1ob3ctdG8tcHJvY2VlZC13aXRoLWl0Lw__" target="_blank">Read More</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a363d15a5738db5ebe527e4f8c6ba920" url=""><![CDATA[Key Benefits of Offshore Web Development Services<br/><br/>With the IT industry witnessing rapid advancement the offshore web development is turning out to be the most imperative management practice nowadays.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogs.perceptionsystem.com%2F2012%2F09%2Fkey-benefits-of-offshore-web-development-services%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blogs.perceptionsystem.com/2012/09/key-benefits-of-offshore-web-development-services/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="40c4bd1be86b2b4af9581bd33146ad2d" url=""><![CDATA[Continuous Ecommerce Development – A Must for an Updated <br/><br/>Do you own an ecommerce store? How long it has been since you looked at it critically? Does it still display your friendship day offers? When did you add your last blog post? Is your web store’s navigation perfect? Ask all these questions to yourself, and if there has been long time gaps since you did all this, then the time has come for you to change. Ecommerce changes every now and then, you need to make ecommerce development a continuous process for your business and change accordingly to fit in here.
<br /><br />On this you might agree that you need to consider ecommerce development on a regular bases to ensure that your site remains updated, but the question might be how much or what are the few most important things to look for? Here are the five things you must do to ensure your ecommerce store remains updated:
<br /><br />Refresh Content: Latest Google updates have made content the super king of SEO, you need to focus on it even more, your content should now appeal to both the search engine and your visitors. And this does not necessarily mean the text on your site but everything that is there, including images and videos. Update your blog regularly and socialize more often this should be an easy way to ensure you have fresh content on your site.
<br /><br />Focus on Website Design: If it has been quite some time since you updated the look of your website, then do it once again. Ecommerce design trends have changed rapidly, things that were good for your site previously have now become common and new things have become known to bring in more traffic to your site. Most of the ecommerce development companies offer designing services as well and are sure to include all those things in your site that will bring in more business to you.
<br /><br />Competition Analyzes: You need to do it as often as possible, this will not only help you keep ahead of your competitors but will also upgrade you about the latest happenings in the ecommerce development world. If there are new things that are helping your competitor, get them to work for you also. This can be done by hiring ecommerce solution services, as they will work together to deliver that what you need for your store.
<br /><br />Inventory Management: At the end of the process, no buyer likes to find that the product they want to buy is out of stock. Consider this seriously, ecomme rce development has solution for inventory management, look for it and work it out for your site. With this feature, product in stock or out of stock status will be displayed on the product page, giving your consumers a clear idea as to whether the product is available or not.
<br /><br />Consider Navigation: This is important, often people will follow different navigation path to the product they are interested in. Analyze this and you should be able to know how to make navigation easier for them. When they are able to find products easily they will surely give you more sales.
<br /><br />All these and many more things need to be taken care of when you plan to consider ecommerce development to help you keep your online store updated.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7c90123e194dc74b7e86c8348bac5a4c" url=""><![CDATA[Ecommerce Development – To Comprehend the Changes Here<br/><br/>Info: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.perceptionsystem.com%2Fe-commerce-application-development.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.perceptionsystem.com/e-commerce-application-development.html</a> 
<br /><br />When you own an ecommerce website, you need to remember that time changes rapidly, and you need to change even faster to cope with it. Seasons change, festivals change and so the buying patterns change. Similarly promotions and special offers come with a lifetime, change them as they expire. To survive here it is thus important to change as things change and to keep updated you will have to consider ecommerce development as part of your store operations.
<br /><br />Though this sounds logical, there are many who seldom consider updating their online store regularly. If you plan to do it regularly then here are a few things you should consider:
<br /><br />Site Cleanup: Get someone to go through your site atleast once in a week to go through categories, product pages, shopping cart, checking checkout page etc. This will give you status of all the changeable details on your site. At this stage clear old or expired offers as well as add or remove images as needed.
<br /><br />New Products First: Continuously add new products to your site, consumers like that. Make efforts to inform them about the product launch. For this you can either create separate tab for “New’ products, move the products at the top of the page or write a blog post. While you will need to opt for ecommerce customization to add the “New” tab, writing a blog post should be easier for you.
<br /><br />Manage Promotions: If you at all run them, then make sure to change them regularly or atleast rotate them. This way consumers will notice them easily. Most of the ecommerce sites benefit from this, have some promotions and rotate them regularly to benefit from them.
<br /><br />Navigation: How soon, how easily customers are able to find the products they are looking for affects their buying decision to a large extent. Analyze a little on this, and you would be able to find why people on your site leave unhappy. Use ecommerce solution, make the required changes and you will surely see an increase in your sales and happy customers.
<br /><br />Check your Competitor: Whether it is ecommerce or any other business, competitors teach you lot many things and so you need to consider them first. Check what your competitors are doing from time to time and think of something similar for your site. Ecommerce customization would be an easy way to get those things on your site.
<br /><br />Many more ways can help you keep your ecommerce store updated, consider them, use the best ecommerce development services, and strive to be updated to improve your online business.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9ccc1d7b007015856cb83c10bbbab0f2" url=""><![CDATA[Offshore Web Development Service – The Ultimate Solution W<br/><br/>Day-by-day, the demand of professional website is rising rapidly, because of the online shopping and dealing is increasing. Therefore, the organizations are working hard and deeply involved in the procedure of improving their website as per the suitable requirement of client. This improvement is incredibly necessary for the organizations as well as for their customers, who are the most essential individuals, who need the end item of these web-enabled solutions for the advantages of the international leads.
<br /><br />If you have a bravery of getting a longer period tracks in the worldwide industry and if you are seriously planning to sign-up your existence with the worldwide best then you require the support of the professional web development service provider for fulfill all your requirement. These organizations are the most reliable resources of getting the best solutions for all web development solutions.
<br />There is no question that the competitors among the various organizations is becoming clearer and clearer with the passing of your energy, but the best organization has its own paths of doing work and these organizations never spend your valuable time to energy in making themselves well-known only by dint of terms. The professional software development company is aware of the fact that sites are business identification of the organizations and individuals who are preparing to make a worldwide existence with their products and services.
<br /><br />The organization is devoted towards assisting the sites with the best programs which the organizations are looking for. These organizations are wonderfully backed by the group of best web developers and designers. The group works in nearer synchronization of each other and the result is certainly spectacular. The professionals in the area of web developing and design are legendary and they know and understand their responsibilities and obligations well.
<br /><br />The potency of the services improves numerous by the fact that the best development company makes use of the newest program and software to design and create the most flexible websites. These software and language like PHP, CSS, Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Display, etc. The best user-friendly websites are also designed with the help of Wordpress, Magento and Joomla. But, the choice of the most appropriate program relies on the characteristics of the websites and their programs.
<br /><br />The demand of the e-commerce and Cms is also due to the features designed for the websites with the help of the best and appropriate program. if you looking for professional web development company? contact “Perception System” to fulfill your web development needs.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.perceptionsystem.com%2Fweb-development-services.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.perceptionsystem.com/web-development-services.html</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9e3a097fa42d65c3458b0779c6393726" url=""><![CDATA[Magento Development – Increase Your Ecommerce Website Inco<br/><br/>Now-a-days, e-commerce stores have to be in queue with advanced individual designs. Online shops should be able to pay attention to preferences with the capability to generate the important modifications.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2e5637e92699b62ac2c77ebdf4659eed" url=""><![CDATA[Joomla Development – The Best Open Source CMS for Website<br/><br/>Today, majority of people know about Joomla open source content management system technology. It is a very uncomplicated to get started with Joomla technology. Joomla development solutions provide a vast prospective to work in.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="58d9584ab6475210cc6bc00f44de2a43" url=""><![CDATA[Ecommerce Development Is Boom for Ecommerce Website Merchant<br/><br/>E-commerce is a great way to distribute goods or services, and buy online. These proposals are made to the site through the communication network.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>