<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="11">
		<document id="7b2f3cc298803a5ce7a4d4e84853b839" url=""><![CDATA[move to open<br/><br/> Chapter 15 carelessly
<br />Time of renewal 2010-11-148:19:41 word number:3389
<br /><br />Get into the day after tomorrow one heavy state, Zhao4 Zhuo2's real strenght have already equal bitterness practice the practice of fighting skill of decade a son, and this decade bitterness achievement but stand in no fear of wind and frost cold and hot, day after day, year by year of accumulation, inside arrive spirit blood blood vessels, outside arrive muscle skeleton, physical stature already with ordinary people big difference.
<br />  But this, calculate a view iron a tiger to get martial arts a superior instruction, also impossible at like this the age attain this kind of state, both of margin it obvious.
<br />  The view iron tiger is the cousin of view precious jade, so Zhao4 Zhuo2 also not absorb his spiritual influence, then simply avoid its sharp point.
<br />  Hence, allow a view iron how tiger is fierce of take the offensive, but connect Zhao4 Zhuo2's side<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape power leveling</a>  to all could not be stained with, two people of fight also from the garage transfer outside of yard, the air often spread to&quot;shout&quot; of ball stick voice.
<br />  Quarter past, view iron tiger already tired get pant noisily, support ground with the ball stick, stare at spirit to stop and think carefree, connect a little Zhao4 Zhuo2 whom the sweat all has no, a face of unimaginable, very in a short while just startled way:&quot;How possibility, you be more severe than my teacher!&quot;
<br />  &quot;How, the now spirit eliminated point?&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 Dan4 say with smile.
<br />  &quot;Hum!More severe than me how again, more severe than me isn't a lier?Calculated you to once practice martial arts, also not the representative isn't a lier!&quot;View iron tiger again is defy spirit and is not believe of way.
<br />  &quot;See to quick temper larger, &quot; Zhao4 Zhuo2 Yi face wry smile, regrets way:&quot;Your elder sister seek world famous doctor and also feel helpless to your daddy's disease.Helplessly looking at a close relatives to suffer hardship, but can't save to cure, have already made her mental exertion distressed, can say that have already got close to despair.&quot;
<br />  Make reference to here, the view iron tiger air be dreary, the but again be obstinate of a grind teeth a way:&quot;This you have no relation!&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 is light to say:&quot;Have relation with I to fasten, if you now kick out me, equaled to give° the rice straw of Help of your elder sister to throw away, be subjected to stroke most of is your elder sister just rightness!&quot;
<br />  The view iron tiger facial expression is one Jiang and the fist hold tightly a way:&quot; Calculate so ……I also would never let you cheat my elder sister!&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 is light on smile, hands 1:&quot;Cheat the doesn't matter cheat a wealth to cheat a color, you can ask your elder sister, I didn't seek any guerdon, as for cheat a color, your thinking your elder sister would see top I so common of person?&quot;
<br />  The facial expression of the view iron tiger was gradual to mollify, but again doubt way:&quot;That do you have no the least bit an advantage?&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 say with smile:&quot;Your elder sister and our company have an advertisement want cooperation, if I pain point, can let your elder sister have peace of mind to clap a drama, was the biggest advantage to me.&quot;
<br />  View iron the tiger was cold to hum 1 and keep start son way:&quot;You are indeed as expected a lier, however, I let you go in, but you if think to be irregular to my elder sister, I will not pass you!&quot;
<br />  &quot;The younger brother of the view can at any time surveillance I.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 Wei2 a smile.
<br />  Inside 2, ever since that time yesterday in hand elbow top experiment to have inside result, Zhao4 Zhuo2 decision after all want assurance whether he can wake up or not to the pure spiritual influence in the view poised brain first, the brain be most key of one wreath.
<br />  Make use of the spirit drill to resolve pure spiritual influence, oneself be an affair which waste mentality very, but in the meantime, this also invisibly similar in fix Lian, the spiritual influence in Zhao4 Zhuo2 Ti3 continuously of drive hammer Lian, enhance, change and influence imperceptibly toward more pure state.
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 is of one heart and mind a view poised treatment, very quick of getting into and forget my state in, all time, the space don't reply existence, unique clear of, be flow at the spiritual influence of body, with pure spiritual influence that need to be resolve.
<br />  But have yesterday of experience, Zhao4 Zhuo2 already ability list hand stability of drill to move, by so doing, once having the fragment of pure spiritual influence to be drill to fly, left hand then ability quick of stick up, fragment inhale inside body.
<br />  Imperceptibly, the sun have been already descended mountain, Xian month rise sharply, wait until Zhao4 Zhuo2 exhaustion mentality, depend on time of open the view poised brain, already close 1:00 A.M..
<br />  Although utterly exhausted, but Zhao4 Zhuo2 some unclear of excitement feeling, original he is calculate also want at least very much 12 month of time then can finish resolve one regiment pure spirit, after last night promotion the day after tomorrow a heavy drill speed and strength of spread the pure spiritual influence obvious ratio want to enhance a lot, although now absorb of just that huge rock sort spiritual influence in very small of a part, so keep on bottom go to, time should advance arrive the half month is or so.
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 Yi stand up, then and immediately felling arrive the belly rise severe, from go off work to now has been sit, now just think of didn't°yet top lead a health.
<br />  He is hurriedly blunt to the bathroom of the first floor, push away a door to uncover toilet cover, draw back to pull to practice to take out a younger brother younger brother, the urine idea of immediately a Han Chang comply with the surrounding but.
<br />  But he just think of at this time, enter bathroom previous here the noodles is bright light, and now obvious felling arrive inside have light fog spirit, obviously someone just once used hot water here.
<br />  Not only such, the sharp sense of hearing have already caught the breath voice of inside, he twist overdo on see, bathroom most inside of bathtub, through the translucent curtain, ambiguously ability see an engaging body Zi.
<br />  And this damn of evolution of eyes, once concentrate, then the ability delineate this figure the elephant delicate strokes make uniform a sort, the lines be clear good separated 1 F paper.
<br />  &quot;Murmur-&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 difficulties of swallowing and swallow saliva, one blank in the brain, just flection of the younger brother younger brother stretch tight a while keep pretty stand of, direct urine arrive toilet cover up.
<br />  At this time, a jade hand with delicate white explore a curtain and the view precious jade come out a head to say:&quot;Show Yi, my bathrobe ……&quot;
<br />  This words just make reference to half, view precious jade then again say not bottom go to, a pair of the United States eyes Zheng get consumedly of, the inside of the health many man don't say, return positive Tao wear does the trick urinate.
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 again where know view precious jade incredibly at this time take a shower between the health, and even the door all have no a pass.
<br />  At that time two people was all foolish to live, only urinate of&quot;Hua Hua Hua&quot; voice return at continuously of ring out, younger brother the younger brother be dominant and uncommon straight, seem to because this embarrassed condition but satisfied not already.
<br />  At this time, the footstep voice of outside rang to get up and spread show Yi in the meantime of voice:&quot;Young lady, I went fetch a bathrobe.&quot;
<br />  View precious jade the reaction come over a while, the low voice be nasty call way:&quot;Quick hide!&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 also whole body dozen arouse to work properly, also ignore have urine to finish, everywhere on see, then blunt arrive door empress hid to get up.
<br />  The show Yi push door to come in and Be hanging a bathrobe in washing noodles basin side of hanging up son and willing turn round to pull to come.
<br />  &quot;Show Yi, need not close the door, I will go out right away.&quot;The view precious jade hurriedly say.
<br />  &quot;But, Mr. Zhao4 is still in the home.&quot;Show Yi dynasty outside hope to watch from a distance, remind a way.
<br />  &quot;Didn't ……have no matter.&quot;View precious jade 1 have the bitterness the unspeakable facial expression, Zhao4 Zhuo2 be also that the face all stick at wall up, the in the mind whisper a way, now just say this, also a little bit too late.
<br />  After show Yi close a door, the inside of the health then leave two people, but at this time two people again in the meantime detection, view precious jade station of the position basically could not take a bathrobe.
<br />  Very in a short while, the view precious jade just small voice call way:&quot;Bother you to bring over here a bathrobe for me.&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 quickly should 1, part will pull to practice to pull good, part once carried on the back a body to walk to wash noodles basin there, took down the anti- hand to the bathrobe to pass past.
<br />  &quot;You are still not quick to go out!&quot;The view precious jade see Zhao4 Zhuo2 Hai2 at the inside station, lightly Duo descend feet, again abashed again the way of Nu.
<br />  &quot;.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 this just return to absolute being, hurriedly the door of health, on closing a door, heart then the elephant was full of electricity similar, plop plop plop of crazy spring up, a spirit blood fiercely toward nose blunt, good elephant not the Wu live and then will have two nosebleed jet to come general.
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2's at heart complain of hard lot repeatedly, although oneself all right color, at most also is to turn over an adult small book, watch adult small movie, what younger sister Wu3 Teng2, little Ze younger sister, younger sister Gao Shu4, that but 1 be also incognizant.
<br />  But with Han2 Duo Er2 accident of embrace each other, was held shake hands by the view precious jade outside, with woman basically have no intimate contact, don't even lift to peep the affair that the woman take a shower.
<br />  This bottom can good, I this is pure feeling small place the innocent fame of the male because of water give ruin, absolutely be an intolerable injustice.
<br />  Positive Chui chest the foot wear and the door of health open and come out to view precious jade of bind the whole body pale blue color bathrobe.
<br />  The night light which open a light blue of inside in the living room, shine upon the inside of the hall good ocean general, just once took a shower of the view precious jade be long hair shawl, the skin powder be delicate like infant, the whole body send forth delightfully fresh mint flavor, bathrobe inside can easy see peep out of the half put on milk ditch and that high fair beautiful legs.
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 hurriedly don't be overdo go to, the one breath absorb top of head from the feet bottom and all say a color word a head top a pair of knife, beauty kill people need not knife, is really go to thou famous saying, world the truth, again see so bottom go to, tonight definitely is spray blood but Wu.
<br />  &quot;Small Zhuo, you have no matter?&quot;The view precious jade close lightly lips to call a way.
<br />  &quot;I, I have no matter.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 hurriedly echo a way.
<br />  View precious jade a face of way of apology:&quot;Execuse me all is me carelessly, close the door.&quot;
<br />  &quot;Don't don't be me carelessly, I see a light and should knock on door to ask once, however just true suppress too nasty ……&quot; Zhao4 Zhuo2 Lian2 voice apology, in the meantime secretly took aim view precious jade is one eye, that Qiao blush with shame red of, elephant powder the apple of the powder, blowing to play can break.Indeed as expected is a big star, that each and every move once one Pin smile, lovely get let person become mad, and this kind of affair thought of first of is also oneself of wrong, if change into <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape accounts</a> Han2 Duo Er2, don't tore into a few pieces oneself be.
<br />  At this time, but listen to view precious jade say:&quot;However, I be very happy ……&quot;
<br />  Happy?Happy is peep by me, still happy see my younger brother a younger brother ……Zhao4 Zhuo2 whole body dozen arouse to work properly, small precious jade small precious jade, you be too true brave.
<br />  &quot;……See because of me, for the sake of treatment the uncle's disease, you really work hard.&quot;
<br />  &quot;Ha, should ……should of.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 this just know oneself would wrong idea, repeatedly jilt a head, lay aside the crazy idea that shouldn't have.
<br />  The view precious jade say:&quot;So you also the breakfast return a rest, tomorrow still need to go to work.&quot;
<br />  &quot;BE BE, small precious jade you also breakfast rest.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 Da4 the courage interjectioned small precious jade, see her facial expression nothing important variety, in the mind not from secretly pleased, feel this name to more read aloud more easy to read, part dynasty outside walk, part return small voice of call, more call more feel easy to read.
<br /><br />Chapter 16 change spirit
<br />Time of renewal 2010-11-148:19:53 word number:3123
<br /><br />On the other hand, in a certain bar reserved box, the leopard be relating the news which listen to there from the street bludger in the very happy:&quot;Young master, they say of that looks so-so Wu3 Lin2's superior's being certain be that poor boy!&quot;
<br />  The Zou a life time hero start to raise a cross-legged derision a way:&quot;Wu3 Lin2's superior absorb the star big method?Leopard you take me for idiot, do this kind of words speak someone letter?&quot;
<br />  Say of leopard but oath solemnly pledged:&quot;Young master, fighting skill this kind of thing be true certain, my having the elder brothers teacher be the NO3 that the whole country spread dozen and hear he childhood top little effort of Lin2 Si4 Xue2 go to, descend mountain after 20 years, that one punch can give° the bone of tiger dozen to spread.&quot;
<br />  The tiger attach in the part with way:&quot;To the rightness, I past way top mix of the time once saw 1 as well**eldest brother, what to practice is skill open stone tablet Zhang, that is really a Zhang can one Chinese foot thick stone tablet dozen smash.&quot;
<br />  See two people speak the Mo be horizontal to fly, the Zou a life time hero don't sway of sneer at 1:&quot;Scold your 2 had no culture to all encourage you, this boy was true and have to have this skill, return use wear be does 1 break salesman?&quot;
<br />  Leopard Leng scart a head to hesitate a way all of a sudden:&quot;Probably he more low key ……&quot;
<br />  The Zou a life time hero take out to fold a document from the inside of the document pack, throw on the tea side-table, sneer at way:&quot;The low key arrive in the free partment?You think I don't know detention in room occurrence what, the police officer have already told me.However, the words of those bludgers also ability really, sow all ability top tree.&quot;
<br />  &quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2, 22 years old, all of parents are a state-owners enterprise officers and workers, house have 1 set two room one hall of housing, insufficient fund 50,000, be salesman at the brilliancy advertising agency business section currently, try out wages inside the period 800.Boy in&quot;tiger one word be a to finish read, Cui way, &quot; how so poor?If I be Wu3 Lin2's superior, have already robbed bank to go.&quot;
<br />  The leopard be carelessly also a full face of to touch a head, if Zhao4 Zhuo2 is really Wu3 Lin2's superior, that his parents should be also an out of this world Gao talented person rightness, how be the financial situation so poor?
<br />  The Zou a life time what hero disdain swept two people's 1:&quot;Good, the head which want to break you also can not figure out a good way and still let young master I tell you, deal with this kind of poor boy, will on inviting a life write clearly white on this data white, his biggest weakness be clear!&quot;
<br />  &quot;Poor.&quot; Leopard reaction come over.
<br />  Zou a life time the hero be hazy of a say with smile:&quot;Rightness, poor.Last time do not eat this boy to the suffering, he today incredibly again dare to run a home to the view precious jade, that I tomorrow will send him a big gift!&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 drive to return to apartment down stairs, Lin2 Bao3 also soon rest, this public security of work is last daytime class, evening root need not tube, this haunt apartment, is a person all get back to give up three inside.
<br />  See Zhao4 Zhuo2 Kai's car come back, Lin2 Bao3 ha ha say with smile:&quot;Small, appeared in public for two days, all started to open a car to come.&quot;
<br />  &quot;Whole is look after by Lee's eldest brother.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 Xiao4 should voice, suddenly remind of a piece an affair, he got off to walk into public security room and then stared at Lin2 Bao3's leg to look get up.
<br />  Yin and yang at present, the spiritual influence that is on the leg flow very clear, at the its thigh seamy side neighborhood, have a wound of circular, this wound not refuse stubbornly slantingly and at the right moment cut off two spiritual influence, make two spiritual influence become 4, and contrary but line, resulted in the spiritual influence jam.Spiritual influence after jam, direct influence arrive blood circulation and nervous system, end cause leg of disable and sick.
<br />  See the leg of Zhao4 Zhuo2 Ding oneself see, Lin2 Bao3 also not angry, open-mindedly say with smile:&quot;I this leg, is a true war of the time be harm by the person's mistake of, a bullet beat in go to, almost artery in dozen.Although the bullet took to come out,this leg discarded.&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 part listen to, part deliberation the method for solve, the spiritual influence is a Human body of origin, as long as can freedom control spiritual influence, want to save a person still harm person however all arise from one wrong idea.
<br />  This wound although he have no a way to heal for it, if can work°out the problem that the spiritual influence jam, the so other problem solve problems with the greatest ease for the meeting.
<br />  He is careful observation wound, detection want to want let spiritual influence no longer the treacherous acts jam and so only use to make use of outside the dint let them cut through wound conjunction just line.
<br />  At have no outside the function of the dint, the spiritual influence in the human body is along blood vessels but line, but at Zhao4 Zhuo2 Kan4, spiritual influence be invisible of place, so in the body wear wound deeply but flow also have no impossible, want to think with Lin2 Bao3 Shuo oneself to he press several descend a leg ability cure good his disable and sick is see not as the joke?
<br />  &quot;Wood's eldest brother, I today just academic association a set of new of massage skill, you try felling for me how?&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 part say, part hand press at his leg up, two hand slowly crumple to knead medium, the spiritual influence be gradual vomit, contrary flow of spiritual influence toward wound crowded.
<br />  &quot;Ha ha, younger brother you had heart, however I this leg early have lost consciousness ……Yi, how does the felling have a little to rise?&quot;Lin2 Bao3 Chi a surprised.
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 say nothing but smile, slowly try the push to the spiritual influence, although the spiritual influence be invisible, with blood muscle the body be vitally related, if hastily spiritual influence connect with each other, may cause the blood vessels be damaged, so use light and soft of massage method, let the spiritual influence slowly promote, make location of injury orientation it existence.
<br />  Because Zhao4 Zhuo2's spiritual influence already pure go to the day after tomorrow a heavy, to common spiritual influence in the human body manipulate nature easy matchless, but spiritual influence of circulate also stimulate nervous system, let Lin2 Bao3's leg have few consciousness.
<br />  Lin2 Bao3 is very comfortable of depend enjoy on the chair, Zhao4 Zhuo2's but again thought of severity of problem, past have no a promotion the day after tomorrow a heavy, Han2 Duo Er2 have no detection oneself fix for of make progress, now oneself also calculate fix true, that she certain ability see out.
<br />  To want to conceal an identity in her in front so have to hide pure spiritual influence inside the body line just, but, how do a line just?
<br />  See Lin2 Bao3 comfortable asleep, also the dozen have light Han, Zhao4 Zhuo2 then touch a water dragon mirror and got into a treasure to work properly space.
<br />  Suddenly haven't stand firm on go in, then see a treasure work properly 100 meters to sprint of fly, in the meantime in small mouth return loudly yell:&quot;The elder brother of the eldest brother is true good, worked properly son to just feel to feel hungry!&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 Yi's face is deelpy ashamed, hurriedly toward empress crazy back, yell 1 in the meantime:&quot;Stop!&quot;
<br />  The treasure work properly slanting cerebellum bag, a face of way for don't understand:&quot;The elder brother of the eldest brother, how?&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 explain and convince a way:&quot;Work properly son, I once said a lot of time, my coming in not a representative will feed your spiritual influence of, and you yesterday eat so satisfied.&quot;
<br />  &quot;But the somebody else digest quick.D in&quot;the treasure work properly to stick out index finger, smilingly rounded a turn a way, &quot; point spiritual influence, in a moment son I can will they all Lian change into pure spiritual influence to pull.&quot;
<br />  The each and every move that the treasure work properly all deeply wear lovely strength, Zhao4 Zhuo2 say with smile:&quot;How do I hide the spiritual influence of the body inside to get up?&quot;
<br />  The treasure worked properly to want to think a way:&quot;General fix true will fix a Lian method door, the method door be more profound, more can hide spiritual influence.But eldest brother the elder brother didn't fix a Lian method door, but pass spiritual influence with my share promote to fix for.&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 say:&quot;I am to think since us is share spiritual influence, that one heavy spiritual influence in my body, should can also share arrive you of go inside body.&quot;
<br />  The treasure work properly to smile a way:&quot;I understand the eldest brother elder brother's meaning, the eldest brother elder brother be think and use you of one heavy spiritual influence to exchange some spiritual influence of the common run of people, so can't front the quilt host detection you is fix true of identity!&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 cachinnation way:&quot;Work properly son true cleverness, can that this method is all right?&quot;
<br />  &quot;There is a very great problem.&quot;The treasure work properly Jue since the small mouth way, &quot; so can't be close close.&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2's at heart big sweat, connect to coax to take to cheat of way:&quot;Next time close close I certain give you a lot of spiritual influence, so, you help of darling I solve at present of hard nut to crack.&quot;
<br />  Will there is a lot of spiritual influence eat while hear, the treasure worked properly face top to smile to open flower and open mouth on vomit, then see a big the spiritual influence of the common run of people fly from and dance in the wind in the hole hall.
<br />  The treasure work properly to say:&quot;Eldest brother elder brother demand oneself of spiritual influence vomit, again this spiritual influence inhale then good.&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2 Shen take a suck at spirit, whole body spiritual influence come together get up, then slowly of vomit, the spiritual influence be a body, then feel whole body weak have no dint, the treasure work properly finger lightly 1:00, the spiritual influence of the common run of people then led to go into inside his body.
<br />  Is outstanding to engrave since the treasure work properly to withdraw in space, indeed as expected detection body be full of the spiritual influence of the common run of people, this bottom was an insurance on the whole.
<br />  The home didn't turn on a light, but had moonlight to spread to drop down, also be unlikely to can't see thing, Zhao4 Zhuo2 He saliva, walk to a health to wash pair of face, the preparation just entered room, but heard the door of guest room open, inside spread Han2 Duo Er2 of voice:&quot;You come in bottom.&quot;
<br />  Zhao4 Zhuo2's at heart an earthquake, Han2 Duo Er2 how suddenly call oneself past, might it not be is oneself hide not good, was discover by her oneself of identity?
<br />  Wrong, she should detection not.
<br />  Although in the mind doubt, Zhao4 Zhuo2 still unbearable curious aboutly drill into guest room, Han2 Duo Er2 sit wood chair in bedside, facial expression equanimity of see come over, although the look in the eyes there is no past so sharp-edged, still the elephant take the sword of sheath, a carelessly will be stabbed very cool.
<br />  This woman after come, seem to half step all have no traveler's building, fully lead several days, the rice don't drink water not to drink also just, complexion ratio ordinary people O.K., that the small face be smooth rosy and red, with view precious jade that blow to play can break of the Qiao face really have a put together.
<br />  There are also her clothes, everyday seem to be to all want to throw 1 set, although don't know that she had never taken advantage o own absence to take a shower, calculate separate so far, also ability smell the light jasmine fragrance of flower of her body.
<br />  See Zhao4 Zhuo2 recklessly conjecture himself/herself, Han2 Duo Er2 just a little Cu descend eyebrows, the openings ask a way:&quot;What name do you call?&quot;
<br />  &quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 hurriedly move to open eyes<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape gold</a> absolute being, caution dirty bang bang crazy jump, at present this woman be a the day after tomorrow six heavy superior, although don't know the day after tomorrow six heavy actually is what state, Zhao4 Zhuo2 know it in heart, an ask for her not happy, that oneself have to drive kill people kill, ruin corpse to put out a vestige, still caution the point be good, later eyes all don't dynasty her body hello, otherwise the small life don't protect have to the Chang lose.
<br />  &quot;Are you the person of Shih-cheng City?&quot;A tone for interrogate in Han2 Duo Er2.
<br />  &quot;BE not, however I read here four year university.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 Hui2's way.
<br />  &quot;That, do you acquaint with to Shih-cheng City?&quot;Han2 Duo Er2 continue to ask a way.
<br />  &quot;The Hey isn't me brag, this university four year, I in addition to foolish in the library, be swim mountain to play water together with native classmate, is suburban in city that is to everything master in, whether young lady Han2 want to move out or not?You literally say a ground, I shut to fix attention on all an ability to send you.&quot;Zhao4 Zhuo2 cover up not to live an excitement of way.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e71a40b7163d3cf10e2d899937bcc498" url=""><![CDATA[research center<br/><br/> &quot;Ming younger brother of river, the hope your ability caution this is evil female, she dare to stay alone, affirmation have it the purpose.&quot;DO not realize shell Ti the irony of the friendship, way Xin suddenly know to remind a way toward river Ming through an absolute being.
<br /><br />In fact need not way Xin remind, river Ming also know shell Ti a friendship to presume to leave alone, nature is have already rely on with scheme, as for is what, now who also don't know, but believe, lead not how long, she nature would expose come out.
<br /><br />Now most let what river Ming worry be the affair that the black and evil boundary invade, the moxa<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape power leveling</a>  Li son spread of the information be brief and unclear not pure, let him the slightest can not distinguish now of Chu to fix true the condition of boundary, more let what he worry BE, how return to fix true boundary, although don't know a Xin and Luan evil spirit son whether two people have a way or not, river Ming still oneself of worry in detail told two people.
<br /><br />According to reason, river Ming conduct and actions conceal the host of boundary, complete can pass oneself of conceal boundary to return to fix true boundary, but he just tasted to take a shot immediately surprise of detection, this front in the demon true the passage listen to demon the affair that boundary boundary say when work properly look complete is true.Whole demon boundary and maneuver boundary this fix absolute being a fasten definite drive fairyland and mentally dense boundary of numerous fairy and Buddha consociation close get up, oneself now the slightest can't with conceal boundary exchanges, see to pass to conceal boundary to return to fix true boundary of hope at last fell through.
<br /><br />Unique of method can be a treacherous acts to cross Lian fairy passage, but do so to also have a problem, that is to know can success cross treacherous acts passage, calculate success words, demon the condition of boundary now say for river Ming is also fan, particularly before pass by this strong line go to Gu after, now of demon boundary perhaps have already become one to spread all over cosmos of dust, although possibility still existence a few star of, hastily return of words, not only connect the entrance of way to all can not find, even may return would enchant cosmos in Hao Miao in.
<br /><br />Seem to see a river Ming of perplex, after drive way Xin plot secretly against, always a face of cut up rough of station at he after death of shell Ti friendship suddenly Zhang Kou3 Dao4:&quot;I can help you, not equal to we do trade, I can for you return to fix true boundary, return can tell you me to stay at you nearby of true purpose, even also can tell your black and evil boundary take the offensive to fix true the affair of boundary, however you have to promise my[one] condition.&quot;Looking at anxious and fretful river Ming, the shell Ti friendship have ready plans to meet a situation of say.
<br /><br />&quot;What condition!!&quot;After hearing shell Ti the request of the friendship, way Xin and Luan evil spirit son almost in the meantime Zhang Kou3 Wen4's way.
<br /><br />&quot;Now didn't°yet think good, waiting me to think good words me will tell you.&quot;Obviously and early knowing two people will ask so and the shell Ti friendship immediately and satisfiedly say.
<br /><br />&quot;Do you know not to know?If you sneak in the Fo pity Jing of your body can at any time attackstone you of spirit, if need, it release of the spirit swim silk complete can become an idiocy to you.&quot;Hear shell Ti the words of the friendship, the way Xin be suddenly bad mercilessly threat way.
<br /><br />&quot;Ha ha, certainly, I pour true want to see me ability persistence many long time, see exactly is me persistence of time long, still my husband of those friends persistence of time long, perhaps wait the time that I finally accept defeat, fix true boundary of have those people already vanquished a devil king Zang Jue!&quot;Hear a threat of Xin, the shell Ti friendship immediately use a pair the very and innocent appearance say her.
<br /><br />In public certainly understand her words meaning for represent, so after she say finish, immediately in succession silent come down.
<br /><br />&quot;All right, I promise, however if want me to do those an evil head a sort person not the affair of disgrace, I will not do.&quot;Contemplated a short while, river Ming resolutely raised head to promise a way.
<br /><br />&quot;Did you really promise?If that I want to be you of wife wish would not like to?&quot;Hear river Ming promise down, shell Ti friendship immediately the Xi smile to make fun of a way.
<br /><br />&quot;You assurance is this request?&quot;Hear his words, river Ming immediately and coolly counter-question a way, however see him like the ice frost general facial expression, term who can't thought of river Ming, either will have to her what affection.
<br /><br />&quot;Of course not BE, which meeting so cheapness you?Etc. I will let you beg me to marry mine when the time comes.&quot;The shell Ti friendship make reference to here, to river Ming nearby of Luan evil spirit the son mercilessly saw one eye and frighten of Luan evil spirit son immediately body a Suo hid river Ming after death.
<br /><br />&quot;Good, everyone maneuver an old demon, I be walk, pair of your house lane of so ragged, true embarrassed!!&quot;Seem to be the importance make fun of enough, shell Ti friendship part to other looking at oneself Yai Zi desire crack of maneuver boundary fairy demon Ao however of dozen hello, part again evocable the boundary evil Mao.
<br /><br />Set off in the boundary evil Mao on the her white delicate and small hand at the moment cleverly at center of palm of hand dozen turn, after the shell Ti friendship slightly a signal hint, the boundary evil Mao immediately and again Gao Kong of the Cuan, public of at present, also in the meantime again the flash across be a green lightning flash.
<br /><br />Different from last time of BE, this time the boundary evil Mao obviously haven't made selection to break through knot boundary of position, at green light of cover with bottom, continuously of the in mid air round a turn, however very quick of, the boundary evil Mao imitated Fo to smell bloody the fly of flavor general, quick of solidify in the sky 1:00 motionless, and gradual concealed went a body form here.
<br /><br />Neighborhood of the sky beginning gradual from clear of blue become a dark yellowish green color, and the color more become more deep, be end become a bushy black after, public suddenly feel a biggest of Gang breeze quick whence blow, Gang breeze mixture 1 if have if have no of energy moment will public surround among them, but in the sky that black of space, a way star light let the person feel more like a pair of pair dulcify of eyes general over there faintly discernable of flicker.
<br /><br />&quot;There be fix true boundary, you want hurry, passage very quick meeting knot the boundary strongly recover ego under the ability close of.&quot;See passage gradual to take shape, shell Ti friendship immediately strain of say.
<br /><br />&quot;Close, you just not is say can formation permanence of passage?&quot;Hear shell Ti the words of the friendship, she nearby of way Xin immediately oddness of ask a way.
<br /><br />&quot;If another part is a mentally dense space of words, that passage will become permanence of, but this is of two boundaries, both parties of knot the boundary all have strong ego repair ability, is can't formation permanence passage.&quot;Helplessly seeing a way Xin is helplesslyone eye, shell Ti the friendship be fast of explanation way, again press in the meantime public.
<br /><br />See this scene, river Ming no longer hesitant, although way a time of Xin look in the eyes which use vigilance signal hint toward him,river Ming still keep resolutely rushing at passage, the Luan evil spirit son also close on the heels of afterward heel go up, but shell Ti friendship under the look in the eyes convoy that public anger hate dive into the in a flash of passage, the whole passage indeed as expected such as it say, beginning continuously of contract, and end disappear disappear.
<br /><br />Hope like what didn't also occurrence lead general of the sky, the way eyebrows with handsome Xin <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape accounts</a> can not help tight lock together.
<br /><br />*****
<br /><br />At present scene quickly be bright and be river Ming to cross that oddness of knot boundary after, impressively detection, oneself really already arrive fix true boundary, seeing to the evil boundary can up to now stand erect not to pour under the lay siege to of numerous fairy absolute being Fo way, obviously from have it the exquisite place, only the marvellous strength of this boundary evil Mao obviously river Ming know, other public middleman is can't mimicry.
<br /><br />However river Ming don't know, in fact the boundary evil Mao of say for the evil boundary, also very rarely seen of, Wang2 Zang Jue2 of the conduct and actions black and evil boundary in fact this front have never heard as well.
<br /><br />However have some river Ming guessed a rightness, the this kind of boundary evil Mao be actually not a kind of living creature, more of the elephant be a kind of magic weapon, however this kind of fix of magic weapon Lian way be special and unusual, demand of the material isn't only sparse to lack, and fix the way of Lian morely what to depend on is control breath, rather than technical skill, so even if gather the strength of the evil boundary one boundary, aeon, also refining several limited.
<br /><br />But compare at the boundary evil Mao, river Ming is in five the line the door the token of promise learn of cut a day nine types but want exquisite of many, at the beginning occasionally it power for emerge, can expand brand-new of one boundary, this compared with the boundary evil Mao power for emerge, root be ocean and small river, the sun and Ying fire general, root can't mention in the same breath.
<br /><br />The prospects of at present cosmos seem to be special acquaint with, river Ming tour once on all sides after, immediately surprise of detection, oneself unexpectedly appear a double in green Xia place sub- stars an area.
<br /><br />The double seen acquaint with son star, suddenly have 1 kind in the river Ming heart can't repress of the viewpoint living from the brain, at process brief of thinking after, he immediately take a Luan evil spirit son two people to fly toward the double son star.
<br /><br />The double son star that is at this time has been thoroughly everything is completely changed in the river's Ming eyes, original and the rise and little subsist on the star of some original ecosystem plant by now complete is replace by the huge metals, the whole star have already thoroughly become a metals star in outward appearance's eyes and see come at oneself after leave, green Xia this science and technology madman thoroughly carry on to the double son star significant of reformation.
<br /><br />When river Ming just the preparation land star surface of time, suddenly from on all sides of dark place the interstellar battleship which fly to an innumerable be in advance and unexpectedly round and round he to surround, but have no omen.
<br /><br />The choice of chapter 2 green Xia
<br /><br />Such the mishap immediately let the river's Ming vigilance get up, but proper he prepare to do time for respond, the leader of a battleship suddenly open a warship head of porthole, a huge stereoscopic cast shadow the prospects immediately appear before river Ming's eyes, but the prospects middleman be unexpectedly an impressively green Xia.
<br /><br />&quot;Eldest brother, you how can arrive me here come of?&quot;A consciousness flow suddenly from the battleship in the brain stream into river Ming, but at river Ming wait for someone return future of and answer of time, a the soft light beam have already bathed in three people among them and very quick of three people is inhaled battleship.
<br /><br />Battleship of conductor inside tower, the green Xia looking at a river Ming gape of appearance, satisfied of smile, but river Ming root have never thought, only separate very short this time inside, the science and technology star of green Xia unexpectedly already development arrive at present this astonish situation.
<br /><br />&quot;I have already comprehended mankind to fix true fasten of some basic laws, this be the battleship which pass those laws creation.&quot;Seem to be understand river Ming of doubt, the green Xia be proud of of explanation way, but her topic be also matching river Ming's idea, river Ming be this time to come to want oneself at demon some viewpoint of the boundary Wu tell green Xia.
<br /><br />Hear river Ming's suggestion, the green Xia imitated Fo to eat a want most eat but again has been having no opportunity to eat of good dinner general, immediately excitement of dance and stamp.At simple of order battleship land star after, she immediately pull of no time for waiting river Ming to oneself of research the center walk.
<br /><br />The whole son star by now became out and out a modern civilization star, take to have synthesize of metals texture the material to spread full whole ground, auto run about of street each region conjunction of star together, on the street, some looks beautiful of the handsome's beauty be leisurely and carefreely buming on the street at the moment.
<br /><br />&quot;They have plenty of mankind and have of then the gram of my creation Long person.&quot;The green Xia is simple of explanation, immediately let river Ming's Luan evil spirit son and shell Ti the friendship be shocked not small.At present of everything have already outrun it can comprehension of scope, particularly green Xia just that sentence let two people feel more extreme of shocked, can manufacturing life say for two people, already not the Di is at the absolute being general of means.Although river Ming also achieved green Xia to mean surprise, after all the all these haven't outrun his comprehension category.
<br /><br />Very quick, the green Xia be so-called of research the center have already appear at at present, say for the green Xia, science and technology development to now this situation, in fact have already arrived some medium extreme limit and top of science, at the moment she most demand of is not what technique and energy, but for cosmos the most basic of understanding and rule, only these see opposite simple of the thing just can let science and technology achievement have leap of quality, but fix true exactly want understanding in this aspect of many.
<br /><br />Long-term of travel over and ratio mere mister many of many of experience let river Ming this is from the Earth come of fix true gradual of in mind for energy of usage and dispensation have some oneself of understanding, but this kind of understanding under the a certain condition but is with some oneself practice moral teachings of method door mutually Miu, so this is also river Ming to seek green Xia of reason, Be science and technology of enthusiast, green Xia should from another angle come oneself of doubt untie.
<br /><br />&quot;I detection, in fact for long time fix true of practice moral teachings a way, in fact and all depend on some basic energy rules to carry on, generally speaking, cosmos be from energy constitute of, order about of the energy be more strong, so the strength have by him also more strong of, but regardless life of an energy be still a cosmos the energy of the origin, actually and all would not° until under the premise that respect some rules usage, once treachery this rule of words, will encounter gobble up of energy, this come up to say in a certain meaning, should with fix true of from explode with Du day rob likeness.&quot;Arrive at research center, the green Xia open a topic way first.
<br /><br />But when hear from explode to rob with Du day, the Luan evil spirit son and shell Ti friendship immediately peep out attention of facial expression, after all this two matter regardless for fix true still fix demon fix evil all is most concern.
<br /><br />Finish listen to green Xia of introduction, river Ming oneself also deep have feeling together, oneself regardless fix Lian of achievement the method exactly has how much abstruse with strong, but in the process of fixing Lian he total felling arrive have 1 kind to puzzlingly limit sex, particularly arrive demon boundary with after maneuvering boundary, see fairy there demon the energy of Lian that etc. fix and usage of way absolutely complete and oneself of fix a Lian way contrary, if say fix true is the one who fix absolute being with fix a Fo even what to emphasize be an energy of pure and unique of words, so fix demon exactly the opposite, they only emphasize pure of the energy be strong, contrary for the mixed problem of energy but inattentive, and more let the person feel oddness of BE, inside their body existence of swim and leave energy and river Ming past fix Lian of five line door achievement method, complete mutually scold.
<br /><br />River Ming will these doubt put forward to the green Xia of in the meantime again take out some oneself spare time time at demon boundary record of some jade Chien handed over to her, here noodles integrity of record some at demon the boundary be very common of thing, however say for the green Xia, then very precious with rare research object.
<br /><br />Research the center still keep is the angel's heart which depend on Han Si work, however in the green Xia in this time in addition to afresh reformation the angel's heart outside, again usage gram Long technique creation several complete homology of the angel's heart, but all machine also is all take into control by these angel's hearts, this let research center of operation and manufacturing speed complete come to an an ordinary people can't comprehension of degree.
<br /><br />River Ming's jade Chien very quick drive sent to a research center of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape gold</a>  calculation inside, at process brief of calculation after, research result is sent back a green Xia hand again up, but when see research result after, the facial expression of green Xia immediately from equanimity change of concussion matchless.
<br /><br />&quot;Energy rules, complete make whole, at least basic energy rules already drive complement integrity!!!&quot;Looking at a research result, green Xia concussion of embrace a river Ming excitement of call way, however when she see public consternation of facial expression after, immediately smile explanation.
<br /><br />&quot;The Earth has a common saying to call different roads lead to the same goal, in fact this sentence can also describe to fix really and technological of relate to, although fix aspect really of some and strange behavior can't explanation, the level that can explain science and technology strength to haven't attained to correspond.But among them the biggest obstacle be concerning basic energ
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f749822a80b41d0fed8895b3addf7a2" url=""><![CDATA[and have<br/><br/> &quot;That you write, a short while give out me!&quot;Happiness small bird answer.
<br />    &amp;quot;Okay, that you wait a little while first, I conceive outline once and wait me to write good,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape power leveling</a> give you hair past&quot;the good luck gather good luck to spread response way.
<br />    &amp;quot;Okay!&quot;Very quick ability arrive happiness small bird of response.
<br />     He sank into a bitterness to think contemplation in ……?embarrassed, I had a meal first and have already urged some times, a short while wife should become angry, day the earth big, the wife be the biggest!A short while had a meal to continue again ……?
<br />     A glow-in-the-dark is once rowed by the brain, &quot;have, alas!Not line?&quot;He hour but stand up, hour but sit down, hour but soliloquize, hour but still peep out some silly smile.Lead to many curious about vision at this time, everyone is stop hand inside of work, see a bedlamite at there hand painting feet, public all stare big frightened of eyes look at him.
<br />     &quot;How, why the voice had no a knock keyboard??&quot;He become overdo to see on all sides and a vision with hot fire be stare at him to see.&quot;What do you all stare at me to see do?&quot;Because everyone be an old acquaintance, and oneself was also overbearing to spoil, and no one realize him, however still have incognizant of the girl be down below whispers and steal to smile ……
<br />     An any realized again and continue to sink into a thinking ……    
<br />     &quot;Good&quot; good luck gathered good luck to spread to give a happiness the small bird to send out news, &amp;quot;You see, &amp;quot;
<br />       &quot;Okay!&quot;Very quick got the happiness small bird of reply, her no time for waiting get openned news, saw write a way in the text:
<br />     &quot;The light breeze, the very thick feeling, see my 1 not a line.
<br />      The night of Meng Meng, very soft cloud, is the soul that you hang up me.
<br />      Very green grass, very greenly, love I 1:00 ok or not.
<br />      Carefully rain, the idea that is deeply, you I meet and destine later of continue.&quot;
<br />      Spirit happiness small bird fly into a rage, &quot;this bad boy, dare to share me cheapness?I have to teach teach well he!&quot;Suit the action to the word, quick return to an information:This be the prose that you write, I be true to think ……&amp;quot;Later on hair a the marking which&quot;vomit&quot;.
<br />      &amp;quot;Not is pregnancy, we 2 just understanding ……&quot;the good luck gathered good luck to spread ill-wisher to smile to come out, &quot;too habit, see her how answer my problem&quot; and have a kind of pleasant sensation for make reprisals.
<br />      &amp;quot;You, you this person how so, ignore you&quot;happiness the small bird suppress red double face answer, is really a noodles peach blossom, gorgeous Lee, saw make the person infatuate with.
<br />      &quot;Do not so, I just open a fun.Don't be angry is that I is wrong!&quot;The good luck gather good luck to spread worried of station get up, wonder:Not good, play trick overdo, she didn't be really angry&quot;the heart bottom have an in fine threads and sorry and ashamed.
<br />       Lead very a burst of, also do not get a happiness the echo of the small bird, different meeting, the QQ head was like manifestation to
<br /><br />Chapter 3 meet
<br />    An any return to in home to lie on the bed, once in a very long while can't fallen asleep, don't know how of, the shadow of the happiness small bird always hover around in his brain.She exactly is what kind of girl's son, today I whether make out some excessively ……
<br />   If tomorrow again meet her, I is certain to her apology, claim her forgive.For meaning my sincerity, let her accept my apology, I want to write 1 for her afresh, Be compensate.He turn over to Fu to go to of think, write what good?The self-respect of &quot;having to there is sincerity, returning can't be without reserve&quot; man, make him some to put not to open a face, body of twist and moving to make the sheet all transformed, he a time of deliberation ……drive distort of the letter paper lie on the ground, pathetically hope him and imitate Fo complaint host to oneself the ground trample upon, but can't speech, also have to silently bear with …
<br />   &quot;Alas, how exactly write.&quot;A any sighed tone, put out strength to grasp to grasp hair, &quot; is annoyed!&quot;He loudly call way, without extra trouble fling out a pillow from afar.
<br />  &quot;What is stem?Still sleeping?Not the sleeping roll out go to, big evening of, hair what nerve?&quot;1 scathingly the voice spread, frighten one any Suo once neck, &quot; nothing important, this sleep!&quot;The words sound just fell and another voice rang out in the ear:&quot;So night, return to turn on a light, many fee electricity, this month electricity charges you hand over!&quot;What a guy, come to men and women mixture the double scold, true can not stand!
<br />  &quot;Alas, I how so hard luck?&quot;Complaining to return complain is still a sleeping, this 2 of home can not to be taunted:1 are an old daddy and 1 be old mama.Asked for hair them, the former was light 1 scold mercilessly, heavy meeting flesh bloom;And then?The ability whet Ji you a night, as if read tight the hoop curse general, than kill oneself still want terrible ……
<br />   Unconsciously, led pillow Ling, found a week Mr. to play chess ……
<br />   The second day in early morning, an any go straight to a net cafe but go to ……
<br />   Quiet quiet by the side of the computer wait for of an any, one blank in brain, hope happiness small bird breakfast appear.Suddenly spread a burst of&quot;Du Du&quot; voice, his heart be like to be clenched once, hurriedly openned to see one eye, and fast of return to an information&quot;do not reason I, vexed?&quot;&quot;Alas!She how still not come&quot;the mood drop into to°from the highest point a low valley a while, the excitement feeling that is just a sweep but go to, any further lift not fascination and others chat.Time so a little past, an any silently bear with to endure long hardship ……
<br />   Until the cope of night condescend to come, again spread a burst of good friend top line of the voice of Du Du, already lose an any idlely raise a hand, slightly Piao one eye.Make him at present immediately for this eye a bright:Was her to come, she finally come!!!An any cover up don't live heart of excitement, quickly hair a few information past, but hair lead of information all such as the mire sink an ocean sort, boundless have no news.
<br />  &quot;I am wrong, I sincerely of hope your ability forgive I!&quot;Hair from an any the apology of the heart, he has already abandonned at this time oneself of principle.
<br />  &quot;Line, I forgive you, see you of sincerity, you have to re- write a prose for me!&quot;A good half-day just spread a happiness small bird a letter in reply, her You You of take in the look in the eyes one silk melancholy.
<br />   Dark medium clear have a light, illuminated the road of front, also in the meantime warmth his mind;Be like to hold tight 1 to help rice straw in the as in, although once saw both sides just on the net, he have already moved genuine feeling to the happiness small bird, be just he haven't realize just, perhaps is a predestination suddenly approach to let him have no reaction to come over!Positive should medium that old words:Authorities fan!Note:In view of the fact on the net, writer will instauration an any of identity, &quot;the good luck gather good luck to spread&quot;, later will not do again much explanation, call in the reality the life male leading role is an any, we call in the network world he&quot;the good luck gather good luck to spread&quot;!
<br />Chapter 4 tasty's happiness small bird top
<br />  &quot;Okay, as long as your ability forgive me, don't say that is 1, be 10 all right&quot; his facial expression serious.With that peacetime hippies smiling face, day not afraid, ground not afraid of that is small to mix son and seem to be some different, &quot;as long as ability get you of forgive, let me do what all line!&quot;The good luck gather good luck to spread quick of return to way.
<br />  &quot;I ain't greed, only 1 line&quot; happiness small bird as if on smile, &quot;can not tell, this is pretty silly boy still lovely, see him letter Dan Shi the appearance of a life time, be unlike is to say false words, I this is how, it is no longer to believe a man?How to show leniency to this boy?Not line, if this continues can't ……&quot;the heart read aloud such, the favour ask a way: you exactly still write not to write, I didn't so several times and your wave take a lot of work, write quick write!&quot;Face top instauration frosty in bearing facial expression.
<br /> &quot;I write, I now write&quot; good luck gather good luck to spread a pair truly Huang truly and perhaps of appearance, very not easy get her forgive, so once in a lifetime of the opportunity how could it be pass it reason and he write a way:Light drizzle dim moonlight night, the feeling think an idea much sorrow;Huang2 Liang2 Yu2 's dream round and a long distance find understanding friend.Quick hair past.
<br />  &quot;Quite good, however be what I want a prose, not a thou poem, say this again to be what you <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape accounts</a> write?&quot; The happiness small bird one doubt of appearance, erupt a dozen the QQ picture of question mark.
<br />  &quot;Wrong, really is what I write, I be in honor of we acquaint with of yesterday, but temporary make of&quot; good luck gather good luck to spread loudly of protest.Certainly, this be the breathed protest and the words that are otherwise still don't let the person take him to be bedlamite to treat.
<br />  The happiness small bird of&quot;if let me believe, unless, you promise the prose which write to me, write out&quot; resolutely say.Although mouth top say so, but the heart is soft half.At this time, a wisp of red and dizzy silently climb up the face, &quot;I today is how, why meeting so, don't , resolute don't believe a man!&quot;Rational make she very quick calm down.
<br />  &quot;Okay, you wait me a small meeting son, very quick, I will give you hair past!&quot;Perhaps is the happiness tone of the small bird make him feel unprecedented of challenge, injury he be the man's sense of pride, &quot; wait for, I will let you admire sincerely to take orally of&amp;quot;The good luck gather to silently think in the good luck relax by taking stroll.
<br />  Make reference to not equal to attain, put into action right away, led for several minutes, an information hair past, write a way in the text:The memory of cover with dust has already fallen to settle dust, look for a true love in the boundless huge, open the front door of mind, you of figure already drive keep, things of the past of various have already spread with the breeze, again the perfect love also unavoidably will have regret, float in the sky of state of mind as if the bird is in the hover, heart and heart of collision is a fish is sing …… a burst of roma set of the body be since then you of figure in all aspects brain in continuously of go back and forth, imagination you of good, you of bad, is that my this present life be the biggest of expectation ……
<br />  The happiness small bird of&quot;quite good, have a little a literary talent&quot; saw a short while answer.
<br />  &quot;General, drink to much also vomit, ride a toad also top tree, see you so of the beauty also can not walk anymore road, &quot; good luck gather good luck to spread ocean ocean to satisfiedly say&quot;this time you total should believe!&quot;See!The chronic ailment made again, just the Kua be 2, tail raise a God.
<br />  &quot;Be regarded as you to write of, ha ha&quot; happiness small bird hair past a smiling face, and unbearable break into laughter voice come, wish, this person talk pretty interesting, talk stand stir!
<br />  For a long time have no so happy, ever since that time with male the friend break up later have no real happy lead, originally want to smile, is such simple, happy of felling true good!Want to receive to advise those ever disappointed friends here at the writer, open happy nature spend every day, the laughter is a God for us creation of the most beautiful and wonderful note ……?good, today first write here, now is already 2:00 A.M., tomorrow still need to go to work of, wife adult provision at least finish write 2 then can sleeping, otherwise I also be unlikely favour arrive so night, oneself a time compose novel, some what language sentence confidence isn't very good, I hope everyone ability support once, thanks!?
<br /> &quot;You call what name?Haven't you told me?If&quot;the good luck gather good luck to spread some say of no time for waiting, &quot; I never force to do of, if you would like to, please say?&quot;The hair sit to anxiously wait for over there after the over information.
<br />  The oneself peacetime seldom ask other people's name on the net, think a network too vain.Even the other people would like to tell you and use of the most be also an assumed name.
<br />  &quot;Today I this was how&quot; he felling oneself this two days some oddness.That is 1 kind to want understanding true facts and want understanding this riddle similar chemisette oddness mind, be like childhood looking at grape for grow in the next door house, want to secretly take off to taste, but again afraid is sour that kind of felling, want understanding, again afraid know of result and oneself of conceive different ……
<br />  Led a good half-day, from there and finally spread echo:Okay, I tell you, I call to fly son!
<br />  The happiness small bird seemed bottom very great decision, hesitate of vision in obviously was a consideration very long time, not long since, male friend also ever honeyed words, think a to the utmost the whole way to coax oneself happy, but now, everything all already past, no longer reply existence.
<br />  &quot;Now of this boy, be the value unworthy to believe?Temporary believe him once, anyway I can't have with him, either what relation of, tell him again no harm?&quot;She sighed an one breath.
<br />  &amp;quot;Very good to listen name, I call an any&quot;didn't°yet etc. the other party ask, he said first oneself of name, and didn't forget compliment the other party once.
<br />  However, he tell the name of the other party but true, because he feel, regardless is to reality the friend in the life be still on the network, all should the open heart mutually treat.So you then can win more friend and this is also his to deal with affairs a principle.Although in the network, the meeting have certain of vain, in the reality the world, difficult way nonexistent the business of your deceit my Zha?He would like to even face everything with the vision of reasonableness ……so regardless is really false, all didn't necessity pursue.
<br />  &quot;That you is where of person?Does &quot;he continue to ask a way, &quot; ability tell me?&quot;Writer explanation once:That time of network, return be unlike now so, there is software of check the IP address, perhaps return meeting someone ask:All chat so long time, hair video frequency not line, even appearance all ability see.Because video frequency equipments in that age be still extravagant solid of outcome, big city City equipment shoot to be like a head to still be regarded as minority of, the small net cafe of still less village, oneself ? Suo!<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
<br />  &quot;Stupid!Can't you see personal data?&quot;Happiness small bird occasionally also very naughty once, &quot; see him type of the speed also be unlike a time get to the Internet, how connect so simple of matter, all surprisingly?&quot;Thought of here, not from of smiled to smile.
<br />  &quot;True is embarrassed, I forgot, I this see, you hold on a moment&quot; say that finish, the good luck gathered good luck to spread then personal data of open the other party to look get up ……
<br />  The happiness small bird helplessly shake, feel some in distress situation ……
<br /><br />Personal data:The pet name happiness small bird, sex:female;Age:22, reside ground now:Shenzhen City;Chinese Zodiac Sign<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />og;……
<br />  &quot;Are you a Shenzhen???When&quot;after finishing see data, the good luck gather the question mark that the good luck spread one brain, &quot; just added her, how not very good-looking see?Also too far!&quot;Although just a little have a little in the heart regret, turn to read on think, &quot; so falsely is me want of?A little bit far better, also province meet!Province not a few bother&quot;
<br />  He never see a net friend and the network be after all a network, the reality be a reality, and he would not like to lump together arbitrarily both.
<br /> &quot;Strength yes and what's wrong?Isn't a suspicion I leave of far, if is so, don't with I chatted&quot;because of advance once saw the other party of data, although gather good luck to spread one silk good will to the good luck, in regard to her character:Would rather don't have, also not the wish let the other party have one silk reluctant attitude, this is also mightiness of the sense of pride be play tricks.Turn a moment, appeared an icy facial expression again on the face.
<br />  &quot;Not yes, I ain't that meaning!&quot;The good luck gather good luck to spread quickly explanation way, &quot; you don't misunderstand, I really have no that meaning!&quot;Say that finish, hate not of two ability living a rightness wing, fly to the other party in front an explanation clear, in order to prevent drive misunderstand.
<br />  The happiness small bird of&quot;good, forgive you first this time&quot; lightly say that wish&quot;I get to the Internet is not look for happy come?BE not because of in a bad humor, just come of?Have a lot of matter me can't with nearby of friend say, but on the net, he and I say what all line, leave far, on the contrary is a good matter&quot;so understanding the other party.
<br />  &quot;I wasn't with you to once say, do I also like prose?I wrote 1 and you helped a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape gold</a> my evaluation once!&quot;The happiness small bird was once very quick and then transfered a topic.
<br />  &quot;Okay, your hair come over, I wait for&quot; good luck gather good luck to spread to say.
<br />  Different meeting, happiness small bird hair the information come over and see come is advance write okay, see headline be to don't cry, contents as follows:
<br />  Don't cry
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="100f15b3fa2549c54d30b308d56a83b3" url=""><![CDATA[the pole saw<br/><br/> Person at halfway of his detection the blood stain of ground, along step 1.1 drops of extension arrive front.He agreeable ground top drippy blood stain, didn't toward anyone find out to with ease arrive at first aid<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape power leveling</a>  room door outside.
<br /><br />&quot;Lung-chuan, you come.&quot;Fat Dun hello is over Lung-chuan then again speak up.
<br /><br />&quot;Who the ability tell me to be what is the row ……BE who bottom so of malicious hand?!&quot;Hemp the pole saw there is also no answer in an eye Lung-chuan.
<br /><br />&quot;You are all silly!Or the ear be deaf?!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Lung-chuan, you no longer need to ask him.All is me not good ……my penitence dead!&quot;Lung-chuan look for voice to seek go to, the square see Dong3 Nuo2 be turn the Cape low Qi!Her whole body splash full blood stain, a pair of slender and high finger also have blood stain have already condense whole piece.
<br /><br />&quot;All blame me to excite too much!All blame me too muddle-headed!……I lost reasonableness at that time ……&quot;she voice the tears accompany start put one sad cry!……He flowed a lot of blood ……I how by hand also don't live even wound ……the blood without intermission and outwardly gush!&quot;She cry about to suddenly hold tight Lung-chuan.&quot;I very love he ……you know!You are the clear!……You tell them ……you tell them.Rightness, you still need to let even know!&quot;She slowly the Quan Suo is on the ground.&quot;You know that my love he ……more ……excel ……love I ……oneself!He will not forgive me!&quot;
<br /><br />Chen2 Huai2 Yang2 doesn't want to say again what, he have already known occurrence how a matter, although still incompletely understanding this affairs of havings process, very obvious of elucidation is for the sake of a damn of&quot;love&quot; word.The state of mind that this kind of band together make Lung-chuan a burst of to deplore greatly!This kind of taste elephant that didn't°yet be complete mature of green skin plum, drive lead early of take off to eat from the tree branch into mouth inside, end realize to leave is bitter and astringent!Flick in the memory it don't go ……
<br /><br />Dong3 Nuo2 of at present present lately- take place everything ……
<br /><br />Ma3 Zhan3 Ping2, you frankly speaking.Are you to is it the old feeling that reply Ran?Don't think I don't know you with her past of matter!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Dong3 Nuo2 , do you when then can be understand?Never once had with other women after I with you explicit be in love relation ambiguity of matter!Include to say a joke all very caution!……Why?Because your vinegar strength be too big ……I be off-balance!……I be afraid you!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;You are afraid I!……Afraid I yesterday still accompany her a whole afternoon?Who knew you to all do what good matter!Such as not afraid!Difficult way the noodles which still want to be me with she warm and affectionate!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Her man go toward the dead to her inside beat ……she plea for help from me ……I ability unfeeling ignore she?……She had the mind of the suicide again at that time!Parents again because of divorcing all didn't at she nearby.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;So you want to comfort her ……good accompany her to go to bed, again continuous don't it feeling?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;I drive soon you force crazy Lei!I and your nothing important good talk!……Break up ……you together will not have with me what happiness!&quot;
<br /><br />Dong3 Nuo2 enchanted oneself, she at love of road up, is walk top can't turn head only wooden bridge.Perplexity, pain and sufferings, but can't from pull out!She was received intelligence by the love ……resemble Huang to mismanage …… can't arrive to forever of the other shore!
<br /><br />&quot;You so say also not just once!Good, settle today!&quot;She picked up a chopper and grow crazy the ground rushed toward past.&quot;The person whom I can not get, the other people also don't think that to get!&quot;She towarded the person of favourite to once connect to split three knifes!The exhibition is even to evade confrontation with in the scare, by hand flurried cover!……
<br /><br />Bloody appearance continuously in Dong3 Nuo2 's brain Shan now ……
<br /><br />&quot;Come out, surgical operation be over.&quot;
<br /><br />Hear yell a voice, Dong3 Nuo2 just from bloodily of split to kill, flounder return to reality!She rush toward to come forward.&quot;Even, your wish forgive me?I know wrong!I dared not self-will any further!&quot;
<br /><br />Ma3 Zhan3 Ping2 is tiny to open eyes and looked around one eye everyone.The end fall view face in Dong3 Nuo2 , stare at of ten seconds he talked and again shut top eyes.Dong3 Nuo2 read to understand everything from his look in the eyes, she knew the love of this three in the last yearses with hate!BE arrive should be over of time.Though love dearly in the heart, have already miss too many!Follow with eyes the nurse push him to walk ……at the moment, she have already can't exceed footstep of move oneself.She hope the outside of the window, those in the sky hover around of shed leaves to float with the breeze zero, imitate the Fo is oneself!
<br /><br />Ma3 Zhan3 Ping2 harm good empress hospital discharge, return to parents of home, he forever of left him once with Dong3 Nuo2 together total set up of love nest!At the beginning, for the sake of love of freedom but rented it, now because of'is love but get hurt'again left it!……
<br /><br />The scar lookinging at oneself right hand arm top to leave!Grow long flection of shape, it as if the centipede dish Fu of much aer feet at top, prison ground in the prison tight bite at oneself.Flick it don't walk, rush through it don't go, destine will forever of chaperonage he whole life.He recalled much more of things of the past, deplore greatly medium don't know why to smile alone!……
<br />After the intense emotion of inhospitality
<br />  A day, Lung-chuan is from Gao Da4 Zhu4 there come back behind mood matchless depressed, total feel to have what in the bottom of the heart special suffered!He write so in the diary:1987 December 30 days, Yin, today is in Gao Da4 Zhu4's home, I met some person who feel resentment me, the men and women's gorgeous matter of their mouthful, have no to have scruples about completely naked of relate, why would I feel deplore greatly?These bawdy story, origin have no with me to anily embroil!……Why I knowing pain!I why knowing pain?……
<br /><br />Make track for a root to look for a source to look for answer in the brain.The kiss of month of Xiao remember fondly Lung-chuan ……Xiao month of kiss is to so be familiar with?!Return to have ……!?……She be no longer a clean and pure girl!……Lung-chuan dare not to think deeply bottom again go to, he feel a head more think more pain!A tore lately- write diary and rewrite:
<br /><br />?Make track for dream moonlight ?
<br /><br />Does the half sign a side to lie sleep at the bed, hope a month to not necessary push a window?
<br /><br />The silver Hui Xie go in to reflect a west wall and scatter Lian bottom point bead light.
<br /><br />Such as dream look down at a heavy star eye on nine Xiaos vacant.
<br /><br />Tour by imagination unreal to think from the Xia, the human life be much more gloomy to tie down.
<br /><br />Look back to ask who the shadow be alone and Lung-chuan feel more heart have already harm!
<br /><br />Drop into before the bed moonlight is dark, break my dream to come to soul uneasy!
<br /><br />Lung-chuan start bed, the color which multiply by a night arrive at Xiao for month before the window.He dozen a whistle, in a short while the door openned a sew, Lung-chuan drive Xiao month pulled to go in ……
<br /><br />So night return, miss me?&quot;Her Jue red lips.&quot;Quick close I once!&quot;She open a pair of the Bo that the arm mourn in Lung-chuan up.&quot;I still want ……still want ……!Not line, again close once!&quot;
<br /><br />Lung-chuan bend from the waist will she the whole individual embrace to put on the bed.Stretched hand to take out a cigarette, take out fire machine'Mao'ground a flame start to flee and the cigarette be spark.He was devouringly deep to take a suck at to vomit a smoke turn.&quot;I am once tired by walking to let me stop for rest first.&quot;For the time in Tao cigarette in Lung-chuan and the lighter, from the inside of the pocket take out a piece of slip to float to fall before bed, who also have no a detection!……
<br /><br />The month of the Xiao an once robbed the cigarette in hand in Lung-chuan to cast away ground up, without extra trouble pulled him to go to bed.
<br /><br />&quot;Alas!!Do you why bite me?&quot;Lung-chuan is angry of ask a way.
<br /><br />&quot;See your bsent-minded appearance, don't bite you to bite who?&quot;Her handle knob stretch to go into the bosom of Lung-chuan.&quot;The time is late.……Baby ……I want ……&quot;
<br /><br />The intense emotion in Lung-chuan is in the moment drive Xiao month spark, he concussion thousand<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape accounts</a>  times!&quot;The moon, I will not leave you of ……this present life, present life, forever!&quot;He is deep the feeling be gentleness infinite to untie an underwear of Xiao month.Hug her in the bosom, kiss Xiao with the intensely hot and very hot lips for month.Slowly ……gentleness ……he cultivated her heart all the way and sowed a happiness to her!Oneself also results sweet!
<br /><br />She continuously send out happily moan and she be without intermission light to call the name of Lung-chuan.Her with gratitude God let her own Lung-chuan!She felt him, at oneself of nearby, just existence oneself of.
<br /><br />In Lung-chuan is cultivate her shabby of heart, the his hand roved around to jump up to approach her the bush of that black in the meantime, that is life of forbidden ground!!!The month of the Xiao know the fawn which have a head of happiness to have already intruded into forbid of youth area, is cross that bushy black bush, absent-minded the panic nervous piece a head of bump into profound valley bottom.That fawn is slowly become to start to be cool-headed by the panic, already no longer frightened secluded valley of dark and damp.That river water which flow to drip make him no longer feel hunger and thirst, his academic association the return be leisurely and carefree of stroll!Be subjected to moisten of rain Lou ……be subjected to baptize of tide!The valley bottom become already no longer Anne, the beginning slowly flutter and the end day collapse ground crack!That pleasing and leisurely and carefree fawn in the day collapse for a day the crack shake to sway of suffer squeeze of mightiness in the clough.He is all the way disorderly blunt disorderly bump tired from rushing around on duty, want evade!Through turbulence of valley bottom slowly again instauration equanimity!The tired from rushing around on duty fawn seized an opportunity to escape valley bottom and arrive at export of secluded valley just but have no dint Tan any further to pour in that bush!……
<br /><br />Side body in Lung-chuan lie down Xiao to drill into his bosom for month.
<br /><br />&quot;Spring thank you!You let my feeling arrive own life to have meaning because of you!&quot;She is more charmingly feminine at the moment, the Jiao be soft lovely.&quot;You let my happiness!Let my happiness!Let me re- find out oneself!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;The moon, you be true lovely!My with gratitude God let to have you in my life!&quot;Lung-chuan such as empress rain new, the feeling be very much enamored to inebriate to concuss in the spring breeze.
<br /><br />&quot;Spring, I go to a lane a point water to wash once, also can't again stay you.My elder sister add the class in night to soon come back!Spring I good loathe to give up you to walk ……good loathe to give up you to walk!&quot;Lung-chuan farewell Xiao month walked in very unwilling to part withly ……
<br /><br />The month of the Xiao's sending to walk Lung-chuan is busy in tidy up a bed up, be her to bend from the waist go to ten grounds of up of smoke, detection that half Zhang La4 is in the slip on the ground.See a top write:
<br /><br />Does the kiss of month of Xiao so is familiar with?!……Still have ……she is no longer a clean and pure girl!……She read here, the tonight be all of happiness and joy immediately whole all vanish!Drop of tear son already the slide at the right moment drop at'clean and pure'two word top handwriting very quick have already become misty!……
<br /><br />Ah!Chen2 Huai2 Yang2, he dream to can't thought of destiny, either so the love open fun with him!How in tore the bottom the empress put into the pack?Take out it to fall while how can taking smoke at ground up?……Wretchedness of Xiao month she felt life again desert oneself, she feel life again cheat oneself!I why every time sincerely of pay, end change to is other people to cheat me and injury!She cry to finish to dare not speak of brave, can so at heart bottom heel oneself loudly of battle cry.Idiot!World the most stupid idiot!Every time why I think oneself to see very quasi-?Every time why my thinking oneself have already grow up mature?Every time why turn head to see just detection everything being all so absurd funny?Bogus!Bogus!Lies!Lies!……Man all would the oath solemnly pledged speak a beauty!Beautiful!Moving lies ……!
<br /><br />Life often love with each person open homology of fun!Each person seem to be to all know!But still just as since go toward, often don't aware of self or aware of self of drill go into it establish bottom of trap!In fact, she with he far too young ……to life have again how much understanding?Calculate their love aller than who true.They ability confidence oneself of the life guard that the most precious love?!
<br /><br />Chen2 Huai2 Yang2 really make Lei this time silly!He seek Xiao for month how many is all block at door outside, still keep being a head of fog water after go home?No one point out where is wrong path for him.What's the matter with her?Woman why all so kind change?Can't let the man also catch to touch forever!He tonight early and early of stay and wait at her go off work necessarily through of road up, time penny a good difficulty lead!He anxiously wait for ……!
<br /><br />Finally, he saw her.However, he how also dare not believe oneself of eyes, and is hard to believe at present fact!The her hand Wan wear Ping2 Qing Po and her friends to joke all the way just since the distance walk.
<br /><br />&quot;Month, Xiao month.&quot;Lung-chuan doesn't know and should say what, face to come forward to block a Xiao month bottom.
<br /><br />&quot;Move out of the way!&quot;Her Nu scold Lung-chuan.
<br /><br />&quot;The month of the Xiao, is this exactly and what happened?You are total and should let I dead understand!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;My nothing important good say of, you know it in heart by yourself ……why the need for ask me again!1 in fine:I am unqualified you ……you also not too suit me fine!&quot;
<br /><br />The Feng come forward an one step and cover a Xiao month at after death.&quot;You this person how so vexed!The month of the Xiao all to you say so clear!You still so dead worry a somebody else to do what?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;You roll a part to me go to, who want to talk with you!?&quot;Motion in Lung-chuan already hard from control, to the Feng roars!
<br /><br />The month of the Xiao give° the Feng to draw back.&quot;You don't want fierce to my friend!There is spirit blunt I, big not be also a dead, have what terrible!&quot;
<br /><br />The Ping2 Qing Po's origin's desire come forward.When he see that bloodshot eyes in Lung-chuan, spread all over infinite intention to murder!He didn't be courageous to come forward an one step again.
<br /><br />Implicit tears light in the Xiao month eyes.&quot;Lung-chuan, I don't have the I am sorry you of ……you walk you of road ……I walk my road ……good ……? K!I have no what want again to say of ……I not love you ……!I wave with pure love ……can't?&quot;
<br /><br />Round the crowd of view, have been more and more!Her figure gradually disappear an end in street ……
<br />In the hair gallery, after
<br />  Two year later.In remember fondly with pain and sufferings of endure long hardship, Chen2 Huai2 Yang2 like spend endless of two century, the person gradually have been emaciated!The temperament be big to change, besides which, he unique constant of be cool to love to write verse.See him and bend over desk to write down at the mid-night:
<br /><br />?The flower love ?
<br /><br />Last night temporary parting spring, the flower blossom near evening.
<br /><br />Long separation stranger, have long time no see a mistake good spring!
<br /><br />BE a flower be open, should vomit a pistil, flower bloom fall, ask who true?
<br /><br />10001000, night after night, deeply.
<br /><br />Long long, short, cent cent!
<br /><br />The Mo sigh flower Zi short, the flower fall term breeze to blow.
<br /><br />Sad, fly, the life bitterness be been short where return?
<br /><br />Fall to with the breeze, alone vulgar!
<br /><br />Have no Die difficult is Mei, have no pistil flower become ash, look back restraining tears, the red Xiu flick.
<br /><br />Smile to see ask for a person to inebriate, ask heart have Kui!Having no pistil the flower fall, inwardly sad!
<br /><br />Last night temporary parting spring, the flower blossom near evening.
<br /><br />Have long time no see a heartless person, the bitterness degree be two springs!
<br /><br />&quot;The elder brother of the spring how shear?Change a hair style good?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Not, still heel past similar ……46 cent ………trim, wash bottom line.&quot;Huang2 Gui4 Lin2 moved a stool to sit in Lung-chuan after death, the scissors in the hand'Ka Ca, Ka Ca'the ground keep ring.Habitual ground in Lung-chuan touched in the body bottom, took out a cigarette, open a see just an empty box.He took a piece 10 dollar money to the laurel wood's Tu son order:&quot;Winter winter buy smoke for me.&quot;
<br /><br />At this time from flank station a person come, passed for him a cigarette,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape gold</a>  Lung-chuan after spark the smoke careful conjecture this person.His shape not Gao Ren2 be some to grow fat, the biggest characteristics be a neck very thick.There aren't a few Zhui meat on the face making eyes seem to be small, have a liking for to the person very the spirit be capable, behavior conducting be good at improvise!&quot;You is ……?See my this power of memory, how at that time can not recall ……is really sorry ……!&quot;Lung-chuan know from have never seen this person already, he proceed from manner to have to so ceremonious.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="faa9c608171669c1f70c97978a01c5da" url=""><![CDATA[slice ground<br/><br/> this time, under the set of Liu3 Tian doesn't already and to Chuang be happy its humality:&quot;The elder brother of the Huo is severe?Luckily I bought Huo Xu3 Ying2, as for exactly how much, ha ha ……&quot;in the meantime 1 I ratio Huo severe appearance, adoration I!
<br />  Have no dust to arrive at Wu3 Dian4 Qian2 a rightness little Lin2 Pai4 Zhang3 door Xuan origin master's way:&quot;Teacher, I hurt!&quot;
<br />  The Xuan origin sigh a way:&quot;No harm, remember to want low-spirited never!Wu3 Dao4's road is boundless leisurely long!&quot;
<br />  Have no dust:&quot;BE!Teacher!&quot;The decision also having firmness in the eye in the meantime!
<br />  The respected master of each influence also is to don't already marvel, Huo, the devil of<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape power leveling</a>   person's form, who also surprisingly have no the dust incredibly would lose, Be a respected master, but true realistic slice ground a feeling to the Huo energy in Xu3 Ti3 only have top-grade highest point of state, although have already been aware of his body strength strong, who ability thought of would such of terror?But two beauty Zhang the door is also the United States eyes flicker!
<br />  But at this time of the set descended the person of view war to also sank into Huo Xu3 Ying2 game of confusion medium, after all before compete but seldom someone will thought of Huo to will win!So the big and parts of person all lost much money, only minority have great foresight for the future, knowledge extraordinary ……of the person bought Huo Xu3 Ying2, Liu3 Zong Dao4 also won not a few, at that time the whole place top emergence let person unable to cay or laugh circumstance, a part the person be complain have no the dust incredibly lost, return have a part lost the person of money to be not put blame on have no dust skill not equal to person, not a few stab a leader head bottom call way:&quot;Mean saint Huo, why do you want to win?Doesn't your lose is all right at a time?You the next time win all right!&quot;In Huo Xu3 Wu2 Yu3 , thunder!Saw the spot public to sink into such of quarrel, that respected master class judge to say:&quot;Peaceful!&quot;Imitate the Fo ear explode ring 1 fry thunder, person Meng of the spot, moment peaceful come down, although have no harm person, the Wei of respected master exert show, but be ability like this big of voice but not harm the person present a respected master class a superior more of extraordinary!
<br />  &quot;Who think the challenge sword saint Huo?&quot;
<br />  The super and top-grade nature of the rest has already thought challenge Huo of person, but now can not does the that time wait?This batch super and top-grade superior win already can say have no the artistic skill of dust be regarded as the most strong, since have no the dust all hurt, so the person of rest certainly can't go to stem know perfectly well the affair that can't win.
<br />  Led about appearance of half minute, no one come out.Judge a way:&quot;So the Huo little Xia you can wait for in a side first?You can rest challenge respected master empress a short while, please!&quot;
<br />  The Huo Xu3 La's light rain arrived at one side, , however seem a finger of Huo continuously at light rain center of palm Nao wear Yang, there is some minds in the light rain surging, in the eye almost ability drop water come, cast a glamour very much!Huo saw the look in the eyes of small fox sort in the meantime, E, signed Ma3 Fang4 a hand.Light rain's ear in Huo lightly way:&quot;Huo, you to I too good, I can't maltreat you, either, ha ha!&quot;
<br />  At this time the super and top-grade superior of on the stage in addition to light rain still have a young female superior of parties Mt. Heaven, two young superior who walk alone, there is also three superior with bigger age, is little respectively Lin2 Pai4 Jian4 empty, Wu3 Dang Ban Pai4, Li3 Yuan2, , there is also a Zhao4 Meng3 who is a green city parties.
<br />  &quot;Ask toward the everyone respected master, don't know which respected master would like to go on stage?&quot;Several people together way.
<br />  &quot;Ha!&quot;Six respected master of several general situation dint fly up a pedestal, but original walk alone of respected master but was 1 and also don't come up, but is know can win end of now of Wu3 Lin2 leader of alliance Xuan origin master don't say, be win of words, difficult way several general situation dint meeting listen to of darling oneself of?Impossible of, on the contrary later pole probably become resist an evil way of hour of respected master class hatchet man, thankless, naturally can't someone came up.All superior know, so of Wu3 Lin2's conference also undertake general situation dint further shuffle cards, enlist to walk alone of superior return the person's experience and training opportunity to provide of capable under charge just!
<br />  &quot;Please!&quot;A respected master rightness Mt. Heaven parties of female superior's way, the female superior make moves, ha, is make for an instant, lose!&quot;The XX respected master win!&quot;
<br />  &quot;Please!The &quot;two respected master make moves in the meantime difference to walk alone Wu3 Zhe3 Gong go to, 1 of &quot;bang&quot;, two respected master 1 have already walked alone 1 Wu3 Zhe3 Ji2 to come off stage, &quot; XX respected master win!&quot;But another respected master be more distress, although oneself ability use to work properly to feel all-directions to know a make moves of super and top-grade youth superior, this isn't super and top-grade superior but is obvious is speed type the superior who also is a personal hand to hand fight in the meantime, oneself of the recruit type can hardly launch, &quot;ha&quot; respected master class the superior sent out power bigger on recruit, the Wei which see respected master, in the air spread jangle repeatedly, fly a sand to walk a stone, is Mount Taishan parties of the respected master sent out an Aeolian leg in of on recruit, youth very quick was enter by book pole soon in dragon book, the Wei of respected master it is thus clear that extraordinary, almost lead to move world.Soon the sand dust spread go to, the super and top-grade superior is already sparse to fall of a few cloth was stained with a body, but the vital part peeped out, he hurt, his eyes in but is a war idea to disappear to reduce.That:&quot;This small friend would like to come to parties in Mount Taishan to do a guest?Later pour is to much and much contest once!&quot;That:&quot;Good!&quot;Parties in Mount Taishan success pulled 1 the superior of potential again.However already failure of that walk alone Wu3 Zhe3 to be also draw together by numerous noble family.
<br />  The now on the stage still leave three superior with bigger age to see empty, Li3 Yuan2, Zhao4 Meng3 Chao top-grade superior, &quot;attention!&quot;Three respected master make moves, offend toward several people respectively, that is at that time, the on the stage fly a sand to walk a stone and almost drowned 50 meters long breadth of Gao Tai2, but Huo have to start to support defense cover, either for oneself still have a light rain to resist to fly to come over of strength spirit still have sandstone.
<br />  Very long, the war let up.See empty, Li3 Yuan2, return to have Zhao4 Meng3 is stand erect in Taichung.A few respected master beside guard.&quot;Ha&quot; see a burst of perturbation of the world vitality, led for several minutes and let up.See empty, Li3 Yuan2, return have Zhao4 Meng3 body explosion a burst of of the Wei press, promotion, they now have already become the superior of respected master class, the Wei of body press a current idea of manifestation also in the meantime is just promotion respected master class the superior can't refrain from rash action of helpless.Present and numerous top-grade superior and the following of Wu3 Zhe3 even rise can't resist respected master the mind of one shot.Reach to the inborn, the nature and man unite as one, lend the Wei of world, the Wei of respected master exert to show doubtless.Led a short while again, several talented person pressed Wei to refrained from rash action down.
<br />  &quot;Congratulations congratulations!&quot;
<br />  Each general situation dint to this how many new Jin respected masters still have it the group of place to offer congratulation, little wood, Wu3 Dang Ban, the Zhang door of the green city parties nature is a smiling face to mutually face, after all that group many a respected master class would the superior be not happy?But a few respected master nature be also an overbearing pride blunt day, satisfied not already, but is a little wood, Wu3 Dang Ban's person O.K. some, green city Zhao4 Meng3 bad noodles toward the sky.At the moment, Huo felt new Jin respected master even be some become famous already a long time of the force for respected master be weaker of cool, and the person on the person overbearing pride, after reaching to the respected master, almost station at the customs even is Wu3 Lin2's top.Although the respected master still may wither under the various condition, they can be treated as the top force of river's lake, is also Wu3 Lin2 existence prosperity prosperous sill.
<br />  Light rain way:&quot;Huo, the pressure that is just's being true be a lot too big.&quot;Still by hand clapped to clap oneself's breast in the meantime to alleviate pressure.
<br />  Huo cold way:&quot;The respected master is a flock of extraordinary person, is also an only a group of person, ha ha!&quot;
<br />  Light rain's ising some doesn't understand Huo.
<br /><br />A spool of Wu3 Lin2 the winds and clouds Wu3 Lin2's conference of chapter 258 war respected master
<br />    Fragrance of books house renewal time:2010-7-99:40:30 origin chapter word number:2242
<br /><br />&quot;This war XX, XX, the XX respected master win!&quot;Judge a way.&quot;The Huo little Xia, want challenge this three respected master?&quot;
<br />  Huo Xu3 Dao4:&quot;Good, I want to challenge a green city parties respected master Wu2 Dong!Wu2 Dong's elder generation knew can?&quot;
<br />  The set descend the audience big Hua, Huo incredibly think with top-grade highest point of state challenge a be a veteran warrior of use a sword superior, although know Huo body abnormal condition, also impossible same use sword abnormal condition?Public all some worry, but green city parties Zhang door very is excitement, finally have opportunity to vanquish Huo, with report disgraceful of enemy.
<br />  Wu2 Dong Zhan4 come forward, Ao however way:&quot;Have can't!War!&quot;
<br />  The two people station settle, Wu2 Dong Ba2's sword but, petting smooth sword body way:&quot;This sword is named green fire, just match Lian with Yun iron and precious mineral for 12 days but become, is an absolute being soldier, don't know the sword of the Huo little Xia?&quot;
<br />  The sword Shu of Huo ground the hand which appear at the Huo in, the sword blade be also sharp and matchless, is from the mustard seed space to take out, don't know Huo Xu3 You3 the person of the mustard seed space to be a surprise very much, very is doubt Huo where take out sword from?But Wu2 Dong received a Zhang door to spread a sound, know Huo to have a space ring.Also have no too much surprise, Be just eye in very hot.
<br />  The Huo sword ratio of Xu3 Dao4 Na2 row, seem a the new hand which have never used sword, slowly way:&quot;I its sword is also an adoption Yun iron refining but become, however just thick refining, can not compare with the green fire of the absolute being soldier of Wu2 Dong's respected master, let the respected master laugh!Ashamed!Good, today this sword be named Hong to receive sword and the day after tomorrow will gain considerable fame world.&quot;The sword in Huo Xu3 Shou3 seem to be very happy and have very tiny tremolo.The body of Huo is to send forth self-confidence and very thick war idea.
<br />  Public is also not from the infection, Huo of the image be not get up by Gao Da4 in the public heart.Wu3 Zhe3 Dang Ban such, although may hurt still war it not unique, that Wu3 Zhe3 at way of beginning have never experienced how many failure and teach?
<br />  Wu2 Dong and Huo is opposite but sign, suddenly, Wu2 Dong made moves.See Wu2 Dong of green fire sword top send forth to go to battle a light of fire, a sword send out, a the foot have five meters long of the fire red sword long grass send out, dash forward Huo since then, Huo suddenly felling arrive world of remaining be this sword, oneself of Be involved in fire sea in, can't escape from, have already known for the sword power Zhe, at that moment shout at top of voice, body form rock, hope avoid to lead such one sword, but don't think this line sword a long grass to imitate Fo ability drive control from a distance general, want ?only Huo Xu3 Wei2 change position, is also change to, follow guided missile?Huo wry smile.At that moment no longer move, ten thousand swords return person's sword of religion, the dint of 50 mentally dense turn of spirit the sword send out, a the handle handle small sword change into a shield, wait for the approach, bang of sword long grass, fire red the sword long grass is already an in a flash to come right away Huo in front and crash into shield on, Huo felt very of heat, hot!In a flash, sword long grass already drive dissipation, but 50 handle mentally dense small sword seem to eat satisfied drink foot general, fully rise 20 Li rices, at Huo Xu3 Shen Zhou continuously of hover around.This is what sword method, incredibly ability send out so many of spirit sword, even return ability eliminate energy of melt the other people strong oneself of attack, everyone respected master mind surging, good sword method!Public is also a burst of Hua however.
<br />  Wu2 Dong sign at this time at at first, the sword in the hand haven't take back and keep hair sword of the carriage be a very surprised Huo such easy of dissolved respected master is one shot, even spirit all breathe heavily.However the respected master be finally a respected master, know oneself send out of the sword long grass be useless, nature can't again literally send out energy attack, at that moment plan near body attack, but don't be forget, Huo at this time nearby still have more than 50 handles spirit sword haven't set up achievement.
<br />  Huo*Zong wear 50 handle spirit the sword offend toward Wu2 Dong of each vital part, see a pedestal on spirit the sword speed, it be magnificent, spirit sword of speed ratio it the speed of the respected <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape accounts</a>  master quick many, Wu2 Dong be a burst of to fluster, the respected master be also extraordinary, ability feeling arrive attack oneself of spirit sword will from where arrival, may may avoid, but Huo of*Zong but is slow one rhythm, respected master cow!See on the stage bomb Ming continuously and smoke and dust rush toward.Smoke and dust didn't°yet spread go to, Huo Xu3 Chen4 Shi4 Shan jump a Wu2 Dong nearby, that speed ratio it Wu2 Dong be also not bad and make moves speed sooner, although Wu2 Dong You3 heart avoid, is also difficulties, the Hong receive sword is already the Bo which kill Wu2 Dong.Had no dint to return to day!Smoke and dust spread go to, green city parties respected master Wu2 Dong Bai4, Wu2 Dong place district I five meter inside is descended one meter fully, the fossil become ash!The power is a lot too big!
<br />  &quot;This war sword saint Huo Xu3 Sheng !&quot;
<br />  Public and big Hua, but everyone the respected master be also startled, incredibly a superior of respected master Class so hurt, hurt to give one was super and top-grade and attain of person, more class challenge also can't so, connect jump two classes, the villa of world however so is broken.Shouldn't, many respected master be at that time hard to accept, end, Xuan origin master's way:&quot;The natural intelligence carry is uncommon, bright abnormality!&quot;Many respected master has no language, Liu3 Tian be some happy, green city parties Li3 Tian then gnash teeth in hatred, hate can't now go on stage Xu3 Duo4 the Huo.Green city parties this time throw a person to throw big hair.The person of view war is particularly super and top-grade, top-grade superior now is already very to admire Huo, more two class challenge, he be our models, the many people all is deliberate whether oneself can also take a shot?At that time, many Gao Yi Ji2 be stare at top of the person be greatly terrified.
<br />  Wu2 Dong is some self-effacing, Huo Xu3 Dao4::&quot;Wu2 Dong's respected master, need not put this matter in the mind, you can also see me use sword not well-trained to even say inferior, rely on of just oneself of speed just, this time win very by luck.&quot;Can say the skill speed of respected master class, of the quickly passing time sort sword speed's still having the usage of clever strategy is stillthe Huo Xu3 Ying2's challenge of importance reason, if want theory protracted warfare, return is real to have a competition the words of sword skill, Huo very difficult win, Wu2 Dong like this thought of, at that time some release however.Wu2 Dong returned to green city parties see of place Taiwan after toward Zhang door the offense of Li3 Tian Gao4.
<br />  &quot;Don't know which respected master think the challenge Huo little Xia, perhaps which respected master does the Huo little Xia think challenge?&quot;At that time silent.
<br />  Huo cold way:&quot;I think challenge on the stage of two respected master!&quot;
<br />  The judge of respected master class is very surprised, incredibly want in the meantime a challenge two respected master and ask a way:&quot;The Huo little Xia, your assurance?&quot;
<br />  Huo Xu3 Dao4:&quot;Yes, I challenge two respected master!&quot;
<br />  The respected master Chen2 Hun2 of Mount Taishan still has slight that the respected master Zhang La4 of Wu3 Dang Ban Pai4 can not stand Huo to still have extremely conceited, together way:&quot;Want to fight war!&quot;The vehemence burst out, the Wei press Huo, Huo Xu3 Kui however motionless way:&quot;Many thanks two elder generation, war!&quot;
<br />  Public don't understand Huo very much why want in the meantime a challenge challenge two respected master, true is an extremely conceited too.Liu3 Tian also very is penitence call Huo go on stage, if Huo in this time challenge wrong words, old dad affirmation would fierce K oneself of, a future super respected master youth early die or severely wounded, Liu3 Tian at that time it head big!
<br /><br />A spool of Wu3 Lin2 the winds and clouds Wu3 Lin2's conference of chapter 269 super and top-grade
<br />    Fragrance of books house renewal time:2010-7-99:40:30 origin chapter word number:2705
<br /><br />The Du Qian Qian worry Huo very much, hands grip, but she know Huo is can't change oneself of idea of, she know Huo although peacetime some lazy frivolous, but is a person whom have much of definite view.&quot;Don't have an accident!&quot;
<br />  Light rain then at one side loudly call way:&quot;Huo encourage and vanquish them!I believe you!&quot;
<br />  Each big sit person's head of Chuang big, calculate, how should settle compensate a rate?Win of the sword saint Huo the noodles be too small and settle a little bit big, so!But many ZJ in the mind be also a strain, should can't be a Huo again Xu3 Ying2?At that time put up stakes of the person be since then also a Feng to hug, a few all green, so many person the vein sword saint Huo Xu3 Ying2, E, however everybody's put into isn't too many, look some the person of red-blooded river's lake Be just dozen from spirit support Huo of challenge.Hence ZJ that be that one be happy, calculate to compensate also can't too many.But when they see two respected master class a put into of superior, is almost done not grieve, in addition to how many big note, be almost a kitty 32, exactly who does the meeting win?
<br />  Gao Tai2's center already leave two respected master Chen2 Hun2 , Zhang La4 still have the sword saint Huo, the person of rest include a light rain to all return to see on the stage, respected master class of judge then station at Gao Tai2's edge, quite good viewpoint, to war too fierce always can open to slip away at any time.
<br />  Xuan origin master's way:&quot;Don't know everyone to think who does the meeting win?&quot;
<br />  Green city parties Zhang door Lee's God's way:&quot;Although Huo be just a the superior of top-grade highest point, I think the Huo Xu3 Ying2's possibility bigger!&quot;Although angried Huo Xu3 Sao3 oneself a face very much, still spoke oneself of in the mind words.
<br />  Mt. Heaven parties Zhang door day jade the United States the eyes be shining, way:&quot;Huo!&quot;
<br />  The bluish cloud parties Zhang door Zhao4 Qing Dao4:&quot;Huo!&quot;
<br />  Wu3 Dang Ban, Zhang door Zhang Feng of Mount Taishan, Zhu Song Tao then don't answer, or silent, or roar with laughter of, obviously Zhang Feng not hope oneself the group lose, but Zhu Song Tao be then inattentive and lost again how, really contest didn't°yet beginning!But is the war of each parties Zhang door.
<br />  Liu3 Tian and several person of big noble family is to don't answer, also is to have dispute of oneself.
<br />  Xuan origin the light tone drink a way:&quot;Beginning!&quot;
<br />  See Huo Xu3 Ba2 Jian4 in hand, rush at two respected master and the speed be very quick!
<br />  &quot;Ha!&quot;Ten thousand swords return the person of religion a sword luck since, several handle small sword tie up to round Xu3 Shen Zhou at the Huo, the right hand Hong receive sword, mentally dense gold just body luck, left hand become boxing.Or boxing or leg or sword, again or mentally dense spirit sword attack, two respected master also is to offend, the Chen2 Hun2 Aeolian leg method launch, one leg under, a little tiny dragon curl hair offend toward the Huo, although small, under Chen2 Hun2 's control, more and more strong, arrive Huo in front of is to attain five meters size, Huo don't fear to, control ten handle small sword fly past, go directly to center, bomb, like high explosion play, the dragon winding be ground and change into strong breeze.But Chen2 Hun2 and Zhang La4 is already in the meantime to rush to come forward at this time, Zhang La4 of too pole achievement with too very about, belonged to just lend dint dozen dint type with the soft gram, very is similar at Taichi of the previous incarnation, Huo thought of.But dissimilarity of is this world too pole achievement the power be much bigger, inside spirit operation not only ability formation spread all over whole body of rebound spirit cover rebound attack, Zhang La4 's artistic skill be also extraordinary in the meantime, the boxing feet be familiar with, or offend or guard, enter back a degree.Two respected master all the superior of near war, Chen2 Hun2 's Aeolian leg method near body the power be on the contrary larger after.Huo at this time that time one be miserable, can keep not to hurt, other people dozen oneself 56 times, oneself just may may ability offend once, angry!
<br />  However Huo return inside religion to ten thousand swords at this time of near war the sword method still have long range attack of spirit sword, mentally dense gold just body, light Shan skill of usage is also originally and more well-trained, the mentally dense Jue in the body operation is also continuously speed.
<br />  At two respected master be strive for calculate how dozen arrive Huo it, Huo sank into static, but is not always either bottom go to, be next time attack arrival of, Huo openned an eye, one mentally dense in eye.Huo Xu3 Wei2 Yi move, once hid Chen2 Hun2 's attack, Zhang La4 Gong come of too inside pole spirit drive also Huo not wear use of firework the dint of the mentally dense tie up, then dissipation.
<br />  Two respected master shockingly, Huo incredibly at this time break, only afraid he in the meantime challenge two respected master be dozen of this idea, funny oneself two people still think him it's too insolent, oneself two people become he break the state reach to the free physical labor of higher layer, however still very is expectation he will become have much strong, the respected master that is under the set be also startled.
<br />  However shocked at this time of time, Huo Xu3 Gong Lai2, his speed very it quick have already attained a 260 m/s, come to a respected master class even already exceed general respected master, at least ratio at this time of two respected master quick, the mentally dense is small sword speed sooner, all fly toward two respected master, the Hong receive sword to offend toward Zhang La4 , Zhang La4 is to don't fear to, too pole achievement luck, too pole strength dint explosion, plan tie up Hong to receive sword, in the meantime make Huo, the Chen2 Hun2 Aeolian leg is also an opportunity to hold tight to keep kick Huo, don't think Huo give up Zhang La4 Zhe2 to turn to offend to Chen2 Hun2 .At this time the speed of Huo sooner, once rounded Chen2 Hun2 attack, the sword stab behind heart, Chen2 Hun2 quickly fold to turn a protection, is stab isn't divertive up a sword.
<br />  But don't think Huo at this time Shu ground to accept sword, mentally dense gold just body luck, ha, two huge Zhang clap.Two respected master is to don't fear to, too pole strength dint, the power huge tornado all hair come out.1 of bomb, about ten meter inside, exactly descended 1.5 meters, all change into smoke and dust.
<br />  Very long, the person of view war finally see three people present, all of three people be a dust all over the face, tiny shiver, obviously that some kind of attack isn't so pleasurable.
<br />  Huo Xu3 Shuang Yan3 also the instauration settle clear, receive Hong sword to accept into mustard seed space, embrace a boxing way:&quot;Many thanks two respected master help and accept to let!&quot;
<br />  Chen2 Hun2 , Zhang La4 Dao4:&quot;The Huo little Xia doesn't  be an ordinary mortal and my etc. be not equal to!&quot;Stand down a pedestal go to, big have empress Yangtze River a wave to push an ex- wave, front wave the dead is in the feeling on the sandy beach.The clothes of two people chest have 1 very attractive of ten word cracks is a Huo at war it use sword row.Two people reaction can not compare with, lose.
<br />  The mentally dense Jue of Huo has already broken 4 F at this time, body strength 9300, defense 9300, the dint energy of mentally dense inside the body value attain 9300:00, the skill tallest speed 270 m/s, in the meantime Huo of fight the intuition integrate soul, already super and top-grade Jing.
<br />  &quot;This war, the Huo little Xia win!&quot;Although not too would like to believe, judge such as solid declare to conclude a fruit.
<br />  Set bottom buy Huo the person of the victory is a burst of shout, the person, who loudly appeal to the public sword saint, but lost money, then not too care, oneself luckily have never spent too many money to buy two respected master to win.However Liu3 Zong Dao4 be then full of smiles, although isn't too many, the Xuan origin, Zhao4 Qing, the day jade be also similar, even green city parties Li3 Tian is also such, pour is Wu3 Dang Ban, Zhang door in Mount Taishan be depressed, lost a challenge to also lose money, although isn't too many!All many?The E is very uncanny.
<br />  Although early have already predicted Huo Xu3 Neng2 Ying2, many respected master be also one Zheng, Huo Xu3 Ying2!
<br />  Very hot is very happy in the Du Qian Qian eyes, after all he be oneself's husband.Two beauty respected master Zhang the door be also a burst of the United States eyes reflection, although to to war two respected master of words oneself wait for someone also possibility victory, impossible such easy.Young Xia young womans of young lady female that are under the set are also a red heart in eye to keep emit, complete take no cognizance surroundings male fellow citizens of feeling, at that<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape gold</a>  time Huo that but extremely proud of success, luck in love of possibility the index number continuously soar!
<br />  The light rain rush toward Huo, soft track:&quot;Huo, you won, too good!&quot;
<br />  See a light rain, Huo be also very happy:&quot;Quack Ga, I finally break super and top-grade!&quot;BE a mean person to enjoy success very much, even trivial, don't know him is how think.
<br />  Light rain light tone way:&quot;You are really too severe, I will give you preparation is better delicacy!&quot;Huo Xu3 Wu Han2 win.Huo Xu3 Da4 Hui wolf sort way:&quot;Small girl, you can since departure regrets!&quot;
<br />  Light rain heart bottom some nervous, don't know to derive from where, b
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5a8a3d5b9c119ef44c0703139d336bf0" url=""><![CDATA[facts with<br/><br/> The purple Jing just wanted to speak up and once the eye wave turn and wish and hum!Early want give this smelly pretty son a little severe lo lo, now unexpectedly someone make moves to help each other, is really that the day help me also!
<br />&quot;My of course not was his wife!Your lo lo!I which point long of be like his wife!I am clear is been<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape power leveling</a>  strong by him to commit robbery something to hold!He still threat I say, if I dare to have a little bit a changes or dare to speak true facts with person, he chock to death me right away!&quot;
<br />Purple Jing wretchedness looking at of Xi Xi horse childe, put on an act of by hand put on to wipe off tears, in fact just is steal to smile.
<br />&quot;Everyone see didn't!The small Ye say this miss to be hold for ransom by him of!Hum!And don't say your The Huns recent years to repeatedly make my frontier!Say your today to dare in broad daylight under hold for ransom me Central plains woman!Damn!Small Ye now judge your[one] capital crime!Immediately the place cut!&quot;
<br />The horse childe stare with anger the Nu Mu admire red, the Nu voice drink a way.
<br />Round the crowd of view more and more, not much hour then round the whole busy streets ram-jam full, horse childe say a words, in the crowd explosion a burst of thunder Ming the applause of the sort, horse childe again say a words, in the crowd explosion a burst of war whoop, wait until a horse a childe to say integrity sentence words, the common people which round a view absolutely will madness, spring up in succession, point at Nu Mu admire red lambaste, have of person beginning go toward Nu Mu admire the red body throw the cabbage leaf fixed menu in restaurant Geng son to still have a smelly egg and have of the person can not find thing to throw, take out the product of body in succession, for example silver, the shoes even is a lately- buy steamed stuffed bun, in succession toward Nu Mu admire red throw go to, have of person true can not find thing to throw, even beginning on the ground grope for piece of stone.
<br />&quot;Sentence to death!Sentence to death!The childe of the horse is dominant!&quot;
<br />People of the concussion loudly and together shout.
<br />Nu Mu admire red hard-pressed avoid often fly in the crowd of&quot;concealed weapon&quot;, flurried of avoid, but head top still unfortunate of is hit by a few smelly egg and lousy vegetables leaf medium.
<br />The purple Jing from a distance avoid to one side, the Wu wear a mouth and looking at hard-pressed Nu Mu admire red, don't live of steal to smile, satisfied thousand times wish in the heart, smelly pretty son!Does this descend still not whole dead you?Hum!
<br />&quot;Good!Stop!&quot;
<br />The horse childe ride on the horseback and occupy vantage point of looking at Nu Mu to admire red, toward concussion matchless public slightly on wave hand signal hint public stop bottom.
<br />Round the common people of view immediately peaceful come down, original people raised piece of stone and smelly egg to prepare to again hurl also stopped to start in succession and peaceful and serenely wait for theirs &quot;spiritual leader? &quot;s give order.
<br />&quot;This miss!The small Ye ask you!Your surname very who!Why is the meeting hold for ransom by this The Huns!&quot;
<br />The horse childe looking at purple Jing and the light tone ask a way.
<br />&quot;Return to childe!The young girl house live Hangzhou!West Lake personage!Father early Wu, live in a cake of with the husband and the husband's parents, original families joy melt!Who know one day this person suddenly intrude into in home, kill my husband and husband's parents entirely, subsequent then strong committed robbery to hold me, run to all the way here.&quot;
<br />The purple Jing Wu wear face and miserably the voice say.
<br />This words are 1, unexpectedly is an one to pour to absorb marvel of cool spirit in the crowd.
<br />&quot;Unexpectedly have a such kind of matter!Absolutely was a completely lawless and godless!Hold for ransom a capital city from Hangzhou unexpectedly and all the way!&quot;
<br />The horse childe stare big double eye, the looking at of surprised Cha Nu Mu admire red, the Nu voice drink a way.
<br />&quot;The childe hasn't to know!This person all the way top the inside of the mouth has been read aloud Dao, go to capital city inside, again hold for ransom several more beautiful miss, then toghter bring back beyond the frontier to be a wife!And he also say, rob will rob the other people's wife!Robbing to the wife who be oneself to the other people's wife is the biggest honor!&quot;
<br />The purple Jing slowly say.
<br />This words are 1, in the crowd of have the man of Fu, with feme covert in succession frightened not already, husband tightly oneself of the wife hug in the bosom, wife in succession head cover up into husband of fear 1 carelessly in the bosom was admire by the Nu Mu red have a liking for, oneself of the wife rob.
<br />&quot;Brave!Unexpectedly dare to speak this kind of the words of the shameless pole!Good 1 meanly adopt a flower a thief!If this kind of person not and immediately sentence to death!We the evening how to sleep have peace of mind!Later who still dare daughter-in-law's son of trust the oneself to go shopping alone!&quot;
<br />A the middle age which have wife man all over the face angry countenance, face drive spirit be red, shiver hands and keep Nu Mu to admire red, harsh voice drink a way.
<br />&quot;This words have a reason!Everyone all has the person of wife!Hear this kind of words who not angry!&quot;
<br />A young man also loudly drink a way.
<br />Rounding all of the woman of view is that the tremble with fear be scared, there is object of in succession head the bosom which cover up into the object, have no object of hurriedly by hand face the Wu live, the station arrive the rear of crowd go to, fear to let the Nu Mu admire red see oneself.
<br />&quot;Sentence to death!Sentence to death!&quot;
<br />In the crowd continuously of loudly appeal to the public.
<br />&quot;The miss Mo is afraid!Went to a capital city, there is the place of small Ye, dare to carry on misdeed for the nobody!You come over!Arrive small Ye here!&quot;
<br />The horse childe toward a purple Jing light tone to say.
<br />&quot;BE, everything relied on a childe to rescue.&quot;
<br />In the purple Jing heart a pleased, toward a horse a childe slightly on salute, then walk toward the horse childe.
<br />&quot;Purple Jing, where do you go?&quot;
<br />Nu Mu admire red on seeing purple Jing and walking, in the heart a nasty, then desire blunt come forward to pull purple Jing.
<br />&quot;The dog claw released you!&quot;
<br />Chaperonage a Nu scold, a long whip as if thunderbolt lightning flash sort of toward Nu Mu admire red set of come, even now, but listen to Nu Mu admire a red big drink, stretch hand then will long the whip steadily grasp in hand.
<br />The horse childe's noodles take tiny Nu and mercilessly stare Nu Mu to admire red, Mao foot with all strength can not also take out whip son back.
<br />The Nu Mu admire red after all is also the Ba of the steppe of Chi Mao lord, if have no whole body true effort, again would not dare to the celibacy go to the capital city.
<br />The purple Jing returned to overdo lo the Nu Mu admire red one eye, wish, this person's effort return true severe, don't know this an only very thin horse childe dozen not dozen lead he?In the heart inwardly for horse childe the misgiving get up.
<br />&quot;Horse childe caution!This person's fighting skill get!&quot;
<br />The purple Jing is panic flurried favour of rushed a horse a childe a body side, raise head, the nasty voice say.
<br />&quot;You several protection good miss!Small Ye and go to the meeting his a short while!&quot;
<br />The horse childe toward after death many soldier to say and fly once the body jump and then jumped to go out from the horseback, lend the pull of long whip the dint and admire toward the Nu Mu red fly a body but go to.
<br />&quot;The horse childe encourage!The childe of the horse is dominant!&quot;
<br />People on seeing a horse a childe fly to go out from the horseback, crowd immediately medium again explosion a burst of thunder Ming the applause and war whoop of the sort.
<br />&quot;Hum!Still think with you with my dozen!You are still too a little bit delicate!Return again to practice well is eight years for a decade!Practiced this weak body to seek me again!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire the horse childe whom the looking at of red despise fly a body since then and grasp long once the right hand of whip put out strength, toward part jilt go to, horse childe immediately drive long whip of the strength took to go out and is jilted a side, the eye see will hit a side girlie restaurant of placard up.
<br />The straight-tempered reaction of horse childe is quick and see oneself will bump the placard of girlie restaurant, the legs was one Deng, then on the placard of girlie restaurant kick once, the one more lend dint, then again toward Nu Mu admire red fly past.
<br />&quot;Light the achievement be very bad!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire the horse childe whom the looking at of red despise fly a body since then, slightly a light smile, the right hand put out strength to return on making longer a whip, horse childe immediately drive long whip of the strength take of rapid toward Nu Mu admire red fly.
<br />Press to say at this time a horse childe to originally should immediately let go, hark back, but his refuse stubborn be a person who be willing to easily admit defeat and be eager to do well in everything the obstinate personality that the Dou win make of his knowing perfectly well the other party be intentionally to pull him past, he also is willing to let go.
<br />The horse childe's heart read on turn, simply agreeable the Nu Mu admire red strength to fly toward him to, once the hands stretch, dark make inside the dint, admire a red chest to keep shot toward the Nu Mu.
<br />The Nu Mu admire red looking at a horse childe, don't feel a break into laughter voice, straight chest, also don't evade confrontation with, the chest keep of face top the horse childe's double Zhang.
<br />Horse childe the mouth Cape start to hang up a put on light smile, wish, is really pretty cow!Unexpectedly dare to face mine &quot;iron filings Zhang&quot; with the Qu of flesh and blood, see me don't make your dozen wear the belly the bowel be lousy!
<br />Who know this bottom to go to, unexpectedly such as shot arrive adamant Wan stone top general, the other party not only even the facial expression have never changed, oneself of hands on the contrary ache can not compare with.
<br />Horse childe the surprised Cha looking at near at at present of Nu Mu admire red, mouth Zhang De2 Bing4 consumedly of, the heart know, doomed, this be the real superior, basically can't harm him a heel hair, dead settle!
<br />&quot;Inside dint very bad!Return again to eat several more year rice!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red tiny on smile stretch hand then is one shot toward the horse childe's chest, see a horse a childe whole individual immediately as if shed leaves general, very light then toward a side flew to go out, 1 of &quot;bang&quot; then fell ground up.
<br />Present and public all all silly eye, the foolish Leng Leng looking at to be shotted down a horse childe in ground.
<br />&quot;!Mr. …childe …&quot;
<br />Always the station is in the rear of soldier the feet be big disorderly, in succession blunt come forward go to, will fall to start to hand at the horse childe on the ground.
<br />See a horse a childe drive public start to hand, complexion pale, suddenly&quot;&quot; of 1, then vomitted an one mouthful blood to come out, reply and fell flop to go to.
<br />A side round the common people of view to see a horse a childe unexpectedly black-and-blue to throw up blood, immediately seethed, cry and scream a voice, bawl out a voice, not unique at the ear, not a few people collapse of kneel to pour in the ground, prostrate on the ground to cry bitterly.
<br />&quot;Unexpectedly dare to kill a horse a childe!I put together with you!&quot;
<br />A the old roars is 1, Wei Zhan Zhan of then admire toward the Nu Mu red rush go to, stretch out hands then in the Nu Mu admire red chest top fierce pound.
<br />&quot;!The childe of the horse!Horse childe unexpectedly dead!How do we do!Later still have who come to the peace or chaos of the protection our common people!&quot;
<br />The middle age man kneel to pour in the ground and prostrate on the ground to cry bitterly.
<br />&quot;Horse childe how can dead!If these years have no horse childe protection common people in our capital city of peace or chaos, we again how could life of such comfort!The now horse childe was unexpectedly puzzlingly killed by this cruel The Huns!This call person's too much to bear!Everyone went to put together with him!&quot;
<br />The small youth put on go to the tears on the noodles, the shout loudly of grief and indignation be 1 and then admire toward the Nu Mu red blunt past.
<br />This sentence as if the surprised thunder was general to fry to open in the crowd, crowd immediately seethe, the mans all fisted a fist, in succession toward Nu Mu admire red blunt past, the womans then shake with fright of hide at behind, some courage big of the woman grope for piece of stone on the ground, silently toward Nu Mu admire red toss.
<br />The Nu Mu admire red impatient the old that has been beat an own chest a push away, the old immediately is pushed one side, the along while also can not get up from lying position.
<br />Only 1 which listen to &quot;Pa&quot;, Nu Mu admire red head top got again a cake of stone son, hence, the Ba of this steppe lord finally cut up rough, see Nu Mu admire once red two feet open and&quot;drink&quot; of 1, toward to run about wildly but the comers be a roars, run at most front of people drive in succession this is deafening big drank a voice earthquake to fly to go out, crowd of blunt power drive immediately Zu come down.
<br />&quot;Hum!You insist on and walk into death!That no wonder that I!Dare to close to mine!Kill!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red chilly looking at public, the Nu voice drink a way.
<br />&quot;Live …stop!The Mo want to act rashly!You aren't his opponent!The Mo wanted to waste to send life!All come back!&quot;
<br />In the bosom which see a horse a childe lean on soldier, force support to start son, anxiously looking <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape accounts</a> at the common people of madness, the nasty voice shout a way.
<br />Once people listen to this words and immediately stopped bottom footstep, return in succession overdo go to, detection horse childe didn't°yet dead, people face top immediately peeped out a surprised and pleased facial expression, have of person even concussion of flow tear falls.
<br />&quot;!The horse childe has no dead!&quot;
<br />Explosion in the crowd a burst of war whoop.
<br />&quot;The horse childe has no dead good!Is really too good!With gratitude heaven!&quot;
<br />BE pushed over the old in ground to cry bitterly of say.
<br />The purple Jing looking at this act, can not help shake head to sigh, wish, return to think this horse childe many severe, who know unexpectedly is that embroider a flower pillow!Useless!Not only didn't teach there smelly pretty son, anti- pour black-and-blue throw up blood!Really grieve me also!See the appearance want at this pretty the cow body beg for what cheapness return is really not easy!
<br />At this time, the clop which listen to rear spread a burst of vastly and mightily, a man who wear silver white battle armor ride white Ma3 Ji2 Ben since then and after death heel several heavy Kai knight.
<br />&quot;Qian Qian!You have no matter!&quot;
<br />The man of silver white battle armor ride a horse toward the this place disease rush since then, the noodles take an anxious color and disease in the mouth shout a way.
<br />&quot;Elder brother!&quot;
<br />The horse childe looking at to ride a horse since then of silver white battle armor man, raise a hand part fierce flick, part shout loudly a way.
<br />&quot;You good big courage!I is soldier's department the son of the book still Ma3 You4 Liang2!Brave The Huns!Unexpectedly dare to humiliate my younger sister!Good shameless!&quot;
<br />Ma3 You4 Liang2 point at Nu to scold to admire a red Nu voice to scold a way.
<br />&quot;!The horse childe is daughter's body!&quot;
<br />In the crowd immediately one Hua however.
<br />&quot;Unexpectedly always the horse childe of the protection son people's peace or chaos of our capital city be unexpectedly a daughter's body!Really make person worthy of respect can wear!&quot;
<br />People small voice comment.
<br />&quot;Indeed as expected is a woman don't let man!&quot;
<br />The middle age man praise highly a way.
<br />&quot;The childe of the horse …not!Should call she young lady Ma3!Young lady Ma3 unexpectedly with daughter body protection the people's peace or chaos of son in our capital city so several year!This call we these big man's too much to bear!Young lady Ma3's ising true be too great!I really admire!&quot;
<br />The small youth droop wear a head and the light tone say.
<br />&quot;Your younger sister?&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red doubt of looking at Ma3 You4 Liang2, become overdo to took a look to lie Ma3 Qian Qian who throw up blood on the ground again, immediately clear in the heart, origin think this is a thin and feeble of small white face, have never thought unexpectedly is female dress up as men's wear!In the heart not from have to dare the courage creation which exchange blows with oneself 1 to admire to Ma3 Qian Qian.
<br />&quot;Hum!You good big courage!Contused my younger sister!I want you to pay for it!Take a life!&quot;
<br />Ma3 You4 Liang2 Nu drink 1, then from the horseback a jump but go to, after death of two knight cooperate will one pole silver white long gun go toward in out of the sky a throw, but see once Ma3 You4 Liang2's body turn, then steady be be of silver white long the gun knead in hand and hold long gun, toward Nu Mu admire red spare no effort on stab, then blunt past.
<br />&quot;Have several cent true effort!If practice again for a several years!Will be a the good brave fellow son which take place to kill an enemy!Regrettable not just my opponent!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red tiny on smile slowly say.
<br />&quot;Don't useless talk!The subordinate see a true chapter!&quot;
<br />Ma3 You4 Liang2 despise of looking at Nu Mu admire red, silver white long the gun nowise show consideration of stabbed bottom.
<br />But see Nu Mu admire once the red body be partial to, Ma3 You4 Liang2's long gun then stabbed empty, in the Ma3 You4 conscience an angered, use to return to Ma3 Qiang, once the gun body turn, then again toward Nu Mu admire red stabbed back.
<br />Nu Mu admire red although bare hands, noodles top the slightest there is no half sharing heart and always keep to win a coupon on the noodles in control of thin settle smile, skill backward on back, then and lightly loose loose of averted from Ma3 You4 Liang2 of long gun.
<br />In the Ma3 You4 conscience a surprised, the heart know to be to run into a superior, but at the thought of oneself of the younger sister be after death humiliate by the person, have so many common people and inferiority to looking at again, oneself if get cold feet, in the days to come at these human face front still have a prestige can speech?The gentleman living can, dead can, only lost a face can't!
<br />Then again toward Nu Mu admire red use on recruit rain-storm pear flower, see once Ma3 You4 Liang2's legs open, firm be steady be of Ma3 Bu4, hands tight seize firmly long gun of empress carry, then toward Nu Mu admire red or so shot go to, gun body flashback, as if rain-storm pear flower general dazzling, the gun body violently tap air, with air creation mightiness of rub, sent out repeatedly the earsplitting sound of &quot;Mao Mao Mao&quot;.
<br />This recruit if used for battlefield to kill an enemy, will have intention to surprisingly of super and strong effect, but if used for two people to war, perhaps is to so take advantage of, a come to this recruit attack scope wide but big, but if the other party have to take precautions against, have intention to back to open, then can hardly shoot, two come to this recruit very consume physical strength, two people to war what to pay attention to is reserve physical strength, if physical strength drive rapid consume almost exhausted, perhaps more difficult win victory.
<br />&quot;Boy!You are still too a little bit delicate!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red tiny on smile, Ma3 You4 Liang2, who looking at to pant noisily, slowly say.
<br />In the Ma3 You4 conscience complain of hard lot Die not, but is a there can be no returnning back at the moment, have to hair, know perfectly well an enemy however the other party, also have to crustily skin of head to continue.
<br />See Ma3 You4 good minister after use breeze thunder to connect to stab, disease Ma3 Qiang, entirely and all harm not Nu Mu admire red very small amount, anti- pour pair of oneself tired asthma not already.
<br />&quot;Boy!See you return to be regarded as a material that can build!Put your[one] way out!You and leave!Return again to practice a several years interest Xu3 Hai2 Hui4 be a good brave fellow son!If you insist on again!Rest to blame me Don't mention it!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red say with a smile.
<br />&quot;Not …need not useless talk!Who want you to let!You aren't willing to make moves!Lo I not?&quot;
<br />The Nu voice of Ma3 You4 Liang2 drink a way and reply and lift a gun toward the Nu Mu admire red blunt go to.
<br />&quot;Hum!Heaven have road you don't walk!The hell has no door you intrude into!Seeing to you is to insist on to try to commit suicide!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire the flash across in the red eye a Hai a person cold light, all over the body and suddenly now repeatedly murderous look, finally towarded Ma3 You4 Liang2 to make moves!
<br />See Nu Mu admire the red left hand lightly hold tight Ma3 You4 Liang2 of silver white long gun, right hand thunderbolt general of in Ma3 You4 Liang2's chest connect shot several times, &quot;bang bang bang&quot; chaperonage Nu Mu admire red of each once boxing, Ma3 You4 Liang2's chest all sent out a depressed of sound, Ma3 You4 Liang2's eyebrows be more wrinkly more tight, tight bite lips, dead dead of stare Nu Mu admire red, suddenly, only 1 which listen to &quot;bang&quot;, Ma3 You4 Liang2 be whole individual then as shed leaves flew to go out, layer after layerly fall off ground.
<br />Public and surprised and foolish, Ma3 Qian Qian frighten more could not say words, after death of the knight also return to absolute being, jump down a horse in succession and rush toward oneself's superior.
<br />See Ma3 You4 Liang2 be started to hand by a knight, the inside of the mouth&quot;&quot; of 1, finally vomitted an one mouthful a blood, later on head a slanting, then broke spirit.
<br />The knight shiver hands, will make moves toward Ma3 You4 Liang2's nose bottom explore go to, where still have half cent breathing?
<br />&quot;Head … head son … dead … dead … didn't spirit son …&quot;
<br />The knight cry a funeral face and miserably the voice shout a way.
<br />&quot;!Horse childe dead!&quot;
<br />In the crowd immediately explosion a burst of Ai Ming, the common people prostrate on the ground to cry bitterly in succession, the knights station at at first, the looking at of Zheng Zheng break spirit of Ma3 You4 Liang2, start put on to attract attention tears.
<br />&quot;Elder brother …elder brother!&quot;
<br />Ma3 Qian Qian shout a way toward Ma3 You4 Liang2's direction surprised voice, gesticulate and then want to stand up, the helpless whole body be tired, flounder along while but just tired oneself again vomitted an one mouthful blood just.
<br />&quot;The head son is really a teacher don't Jie body first dead!Unexpectedly didn't°yet really top led battlefield to once kill an enemy, now unexpectedly so dead!Is really unworthy!&quot;
<br />After death of a knight part cry, part mumbling to oneself way.
<br />&quot;This**!Put together with him!&quot;
<br />In the crowd explosion mightiness of bawl out a voice, people point at Nu Mu to admire in succession red denounce openly.
<br />&quot;Who dare to come forward!Live impatiently and all!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red stare with anger public, the Nu voice drink a way.
<br />Purple Jing eyebrows a wrinkly, on seeing kill a person, the heart know circumstances severity, walk to Nu Mu to admire red toward his head before the body fierce knock once, the Nu voice scold a way, &quot;enough!Have already killed a person!Might it not be you still want to kill the light to all of the common people of capital city!At present have to darling to follow them to return to Ya door!When the time comes identity with authorities enunciation, the nobody dare to move you!&quot;
<br />&quot;All right!Listen to you!These dullards can't also harm me!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red touched touch be knocked by the purple Jing of place, sink a voice to say.
<br />&quot;Good!Everybody!The Mo want again noise!Please everyone eldest brother this person before tie?upping soldier's department a writing form still!Please soldier's department a book to still handle!Everyone don't again blunt come up!&quot;
<br />The purple Jing toward concussion of public loudly shout a way.
<br />Once the concussion matchless common people listen to this words and immediately stopped down and stand at at first, purple Jing and Nu Mu of the looking at of Leng Leng admire red.
<br />The public and foolish Leng wear, who also dare not true of top go to Nu Mu admire red tie?up, refuse to budge so, silent.
<br />See suddenly a young knight station to start, stretch hand to put on go to the tears on the noodles, take out a cordage from the knapsack of horseback, then toward Nu Mu admire red big step walk past.
<br />&quot;Afraid bird!Big not one dead!Tie?up!Let his old man's house decide by oneself before taking soldier's department a writing form still!&quot;
<br />The young knight has no to be afraid of admire toward the Nu Mu red walk to, walk to Nu Mu admire red stretch hand then before the body cordage go toward Nu Mu admire red body set go up.
<br />Once after death many knight see Nu Mu admire red to unexpectedly and nowise resist and immediately let go of heart, in succession your book courage dynasty Nu Mu admire red walk to, public seven hands eight feet of then Nu Mu admire red tie?upped knot to fructify solid.
<br />&quot;Walk!Escort a soldier a department to go to!&quot;
<br />Public push Sang Nu Mu admire red, then toward soldier department line go to.
<br />The common peoples will step aside a way in succession, will slowly but line of public surround, again beginning go toward Nu Mu admire red body fierce still lousy vegetables leaf and cabbage Geng.
<br />The Nu Mu admired a red head top to get quite a few to descend lousy vegetables leaf and smelly egg again, in most distressed, a burst of and angry toward in the heart public drink a way, &quot;stop!You are true to think this lousy cordage tie?upped me!Tell you!I demand lightly on move free from tangle this lousy cordage for the ability!If do you go toward my head top again to throw thing!Rest to blame me Don't mention it!&quot;
<br />Once the common peoples listen to this words, is live by the Hai while ascend, stopped to start in succession in of action.
<br />&quot;Hum!Know severe line!Honesty point!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red cold hum 1, the Nu voice say.
<br />&quot;Everyone don't listen to his blah!If the his ability flounce to open to early escape!Again meeting darling of is tie?up to soldier's department!&quot;
<br />Youth man the roars be 1 and then admire the lousy vegetables leaf in the hand later on red toward the Nu Mu with sudden force toss go to, only 1 which listen to &quot;Pa&quot;, the lousy vegetables leaf then stick at the Nu Mu admire red forehead up.
<br />The Nu Mu admire red heart in angry thousand times, but turn to read on think, after all isn't a beyond the frontier here, is not oneself of site, have already killed 1, if again these stupid of the common people toghter kill, perhaps Yin Ren there not so good explaination.
<br />If ask for when the time comes the Yin Ren lose temper, the oneself celibacy be one person, strong dragon also Dou however ground head snake, when the time comes affirmation want to suffer a los, or endure first.
<br />The common people see a form, reply and raise the lousy vegetables leaf in the hand and smelly egg and admire toward the Nu Mu red throw.
<br />&quot;I endure!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red helplessly say.
<br />The food for powder escort Nu Mu to admire red, after death followed behind several common people, vastly and mightily of go toward soldier department line go to.
<br />Not much hour, then line go to soldier's department, a few soldier then escort Nu Mu admire red walked to go in, the person with no duty at then is blocked down, the common peoples eye see impossible again go in, then in succession spread go to, grief and indignation in heart not already and inwardly curse and scold Nu Mu admire red.
<br />Soldier's department still book Malaysia be wise to kneel to pour in the ground, the corpse body which embrace an own son don't already cry bitterly, at the thought of oneself unique of the son be kill by the person, little daughter again was beat by the person of neither dead nor alive, now can not help feel sadness welling up still in the salvage, the feeling read aloud heaven unjust, unexpectedly want grey hair a person to send the black hair the person.
<br />&quot;Bearer!Drag along the this brave crazy Tu went out to chop down!&quot;
<br />Malaysia is wise to point at to be tie?up of the knot fructify solid of Nu Mu admire red, the Nu voice drink a way.
<br />&quot;Hum!Want to chop down me!Tell you!I am a Nu Mu to admire red!The Ba lord of big steppe!All get khan with eight set beyond the frontier!You want to chop down me!Went first to once ask your south Chu's big Huang!&quot;
<br />The Nu Mu admire red chilly looking at Malaysia wise, slightly on putting effort, but listenning to 1 of &quot;Pa&quot;, the rope of body then crack to open, change into the small rope residue of innumerable and fall ground.
<br />Malaysia is wise on listenning to this words, ascend stunned speechless, lightly let go of the son's corpse, station start, carefully conjecture Nu Mu admire red, wish, recent definite heard an emperor to want long princess take go to to the Nu Mu of beyond the frontier admire red marriage, such see, must letter!If this person is really a Nu Mu to admire red, that can 1000010000 move can not, still look for person first to spread a message for emperor, see an emperor how to there say.
<br />&quot;Horse still book, this is true, I be south Chu of long princess, if you not letter, though parties go to go an elder brother Shao message to the Huang into the temple.&quot;
<br />The purple Jing helplessly sighed tone, wish, matter till now, if not for this pretty cow enunciation identity, perhaps this soldier's department don't know again dead how much person, if early know this person fighting skill such deep, at the beginning and then shouldn't for the sake of personal private provocation Ma3 Qian Qian and he fight each other and that Ma3 You4 Liang2 need not die unjustly, either.
<br />Say around, all strange oneself personal personal desires, just harm Ma3 You4 Liang2 be young to then waste to send life.
<br />Malaysia is wise on listenning to this words, canned not help pour to absorb an one mouthful cool spirit, the heart know this matter ten to one, also dare not to neglect, life person Nu Mu admire red pass enter the big prison sternly watch, purple Jing then was arrive by the arrangement in guest room rest, oneself then hurriedly leave into the temple, the noodles saw an emperor go.
<br />Tirelessly arrive to a temple in, then plea for interview an emperor, told this matter in detail Yin Ren.
<br />Once the Yin Ren listen to this words, a burst of in the heart doubt, wish, dare<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape gold</a>  to openly kill a person in inside in the capital city, this is definite have a little be like Nu Mu admire red style, hence then wear slack suit, took a few personal bodyguard, along with Malaysia wise go to a soldier's department big prison.
<br />The Yin Ren arrive at a soldier's department big prison, an eye then saw Nu Mu to admire red, the Nu Mu admire red also an eye saw Yin Ren.
<br />The Nu Mu admire red a see Yin Ren come, hurriedly the station start, way, &quot;you can come!Quick call them let out me!Suffered dead!&quot;
<br />&quot;Boon.&quot;
<br />The Yin Ren looking at Nu Mu to admire red, lightly say, lightly of point nod.
<br />Malaysia is wise on seeing this battle, the heart know this matter not false, a burst of distressed in the heart, enemy whole life which see to a son didn't think report, hurriedly hello prison guard Nu Mu admire red put to come out.
<br />&quot;Malaysia is wise, this matter you should know should how processing?&quot;
<br />The Yin Ren looking at Malaysia wise, sink a voice to say.
<br />&quot;BE!BE!Descend an officer understand!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6ff747b45d7c4482bb1f62653bcd50e6" url=""><![CDATA[the autumn<br/><br/> person hear Ke Yue4 Quan2's voice back overdo, this person isn't an autumn does Chu smell be who?Autumn Chu smell a surprised and pleased way:&quot;Miss?&quot;The pleased way of Ke Yue4 Quan2:&quot;The childe of the autumn, you how also here?&quot;Autumn Chu smell say with smile:&quot;We the invitation which received Hua Mountain<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape power leveling</a>  parties to deliver in the autumn house, my father not like a person many of place, so let I representative the autumn house come to attend Hua Mountain theory sword and the growth descend a knowledge in the meantime.Rightness, the last time miss you walk so hurried, what affair make you so nasty?Let me connect an opportunity to send off to you all have no.&quot;
<br />The last time of Ke Yue4 Quan2 leave the time of autumnal rains country villa, think later should can't again meet, so in the letter literally wrote the reason for leave without a word, have never said Lee's madam to be night with she dialogue of affair.Ke Yue4 Quan2 have never thought and also unexpectedly met again no longer than a month.
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2's way:&quot;Also ……the nothing important important event be just all some individual's affair.&quot;Autumn Chu smell a way:&quot;So, have that processing already been over?Demand I help?&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2 smell speech hurriedly shake head to put a hand way:&quot;Need not, need not all finished do.&quot;Autumn Chu smell ask a way:&quot;Rightness, miss you also representative your teacher attendance Hua Mountain theory sword of?&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2's way:&quot;Not yes, I just hear and hold Hua Mountain a theory sword, so come right away to come over a knowledge bottom just.By coincidence lately- know friend of the road has invitation, so come up.&quot;
<br />Autumn Chu smell a way:&quot;Theory sword would not° until wait a little while also beginning, we might as well walk everywhere first, appreciate how is the landscape which descend Hua Mountain?&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2 say with smile:&quot;H'm, good ah.My heel that three friend said a, don't need of look for person when the time comes.&quot;Autumn Chu smell original think Ke Yue4 Quan2 will leave once and go to with her friend dozen voice hello of, have never thought Ke Yue4 Quan2 turn head to toward crowd to shout a way:&quot;Three greatest Xia!My heel my friend occupied to leave first and you slowly played.&quot;The south of the crowd spread the voice way of big-nosed at this time:&quot;Good, you go to, we slowly play.&quot;The southwest side spread big mouth of voice way:&quot;This place in the Hua Mountain is a hideous mess, remember to take map and otherwise get lost bother.&quot;The big mouth just said that finish and then hear, 1 of Pa, the head which listen to this voice should be a big mouth be again clapped.Immediately after heard ox-eyed to reprimand angrily to a way:&quot;You think miss be like you so stupid?The somebody else go out to certainly take map, you should say that remember to take up the dry ration food, otherwise got lost and eat of how do?Knew Yao?&quot;
<br />Autumn Chu smelt Leng once a way:&quot;Miss ……you of the friend be pretty special.&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2 say with smile:&quot;H'm, this be their special features.&quot;
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2 is a time come to Hua Mountain, autumn Chu smell past once came several times, to Hua Mountain return calculate acquaint with.Walk for the side side say some legend concerning Hua Mountain for Ke Yue4 Quan2, for example, the aloes wood split mountain to save a mother, blow Xiao to lead Feng, huge work properly Bo mountain, Huang2 Qiao3 Xian2's wreath, reunion and reconciliation what of.Listen to Ke Yue4 Quan2 such as Chi such as inebriate, connect the voice shout bravo.Two people imperceptibly walk to behind mountain, people all gather Wu3 Chang3 at the Xi at this time up, so empress the mountain be that the one is peaceful.
<br />Be two people sink to immerse in this beautiful scenery of time, suddenly hear to break empty of voice, immediately after two people see three dark shadow flee into front of forest.Then the inside of the forest spread vehemence of fight voice.
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2 and autumn Chu smell two people hurriedly caution of close to past, want and see is who unexpectedly dare at Hua Mountain theory sword of time to cause trouble.
<br />Two people are concealment in the forest and go toward inside hope.Detection's is to have three people is fight and have two people is to wear black dress, be covered with black cape, head take black red side of rain hat.The black dress person of this two per Gao Yi Ai3 see to is a, two people be cooperate to deal with one dress ash dress man.That ash dress person probably 30 come year old, the skin You be black and hang eyebrow to hang up a nose.
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2 see there two black doubt a way:&quot;That two black dress difficult way is an east Cuan person?&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2 see a black dress person that special of attire and then remind of past of affair.That is just with childhood of Wu2 Shi4 En understanding in a little while, at go to white wood the road of the country up, on the way a wine spread inside also meet of a flock of black dress person.Their attiring with now that is two look exactly alike, those black dress persons claim to be east Cuan a person at that time.
<br />Autumn Chu smell a way:&quot;That's right, attiring so should be an east Cuan person.This several in the last years they have been taking a stroll everywhere in river's lake and hear to be seek a be one rebel.&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2's way:&quot;Is that ash person it they that want to seek rebel?&quot;Autumn Chu smell a way:&quot;Probably, we first quiet view it change.&quot;
<br />The black dress person got entangled in fighting medium little fellow Nu way:&quot;Cuan east ? !You are this rebel, sought you so for several years and today of Lao Tze be finally found out you.&quot;The dress person of Gao Ge4 Hei sink a way:&quot;The Cuan east ? hand over a Mi book!Stay your whole corpse!&quot;Ash dress person Nu say with smile:&quot;Useless talk is little to say, the subordinate see a true chapter!&quot;Say that finish and then stormed go up, with one enemy two get entangled in fighting with black dress person.
<br />See according to their circumstance for duel, all of three people be the superior whom the yin and yang turn five lines of state.Two black dress person's Zhang strength, the shot dozen ambiguously have the voice of metals on the rock and see is five line exchange gold.But ash dress person, be each a recruit a type all would skillful make profit to use the piece of stone on the ground, mud to attack black dress person, should is five line Gen soil.Two black dress recruit type is big to open big match, keep around each a recruit to all take thunderbolt of power.Ash dress person be each a recruit all stagnate empress heavy, imitate an of Fo every act and move to have thousand catties of heavy burden, the strength all press in it, as if cloudy day muffled thunder sort.
<br />Three people belligerence, the boxing feet hand over to add, you come I go toward.The Zhang strength once swept its place tree to break and the stone ground soil fly.The tree in three Human body sides, the rock be all destroy and the shot be ground.It is also the pit pit Wa Wa on the ground.Although all of three people is rightness with bare hands definitely, but is also dangerous thousand times.
<br />Although the ash person be severe, with one enemy two not and in a short while and gradually fell in breeze.
<br />At Ke Yue4 Quan2 and autumn Chu smell two people hesitant to want and don't go up of time, suddenly!Opposite of fly a Shan two shadow of human figure in the forest, that two people pull out sword to soar to the skies to stab toward two black dress person's vital part and force the black dress person have to give up an ash dress person, let ash dress the person get the opportunity of a short moment breather.
<br />It a Gao Ge4's black dress person sink a track:&quot;Is you who?This is us the affair in the clan, please don't meddle in other people's business!&quot;Sneak attack the black dress person's one among those persons drink a way:&quot;BE you big Ye!My busybodies?Big Ye I that year drive almost you of under charge a Zhang kill, today be to revenge!&quot;
<br />&quot;BE him!&quot;The Yan of the surprise of Ke Yue4 Quan2 wear a mouth to say.That's right, the burst upon of two personal is exactly Wu2 Shi4 En with become Lin Lin.Wu2 Shi4 En, that year was clapped one Zhang by an east Cuan person who wear white rain hat, if it weren't for into a view breeze's help to find out a judge eye medical treatment, Wu2 Shi4 En early dead, therefore Wu2 Shi4 En special malicious these east Cuan person.
<br />The dress person of Gao Ge4 Hei sink a track:&quot;Little devil I root incognizant you, this big Ye today have no time to accompany you to play!You now walk still in time!&quot;The Nu way of Wu2 Shi4 En:&quot;You are incognizant I, I can understanding you!You of the body form harmony sound I but the memory be deep!&quot;Short black dress person Nu way:&quot;Say not beneficial more, don't walk dead!&quot;Two black dress person offended to come over right after words sound fall.
<br />At this time pant over come of ash dress person roars way:&quot;All give I go to dead!&quot; The double which see at this time him Zhang blue vein suddenly and violently, the muscle band together a pair of Zhang big of abnormality.The ash dress person shout at top of voice and fiercely hit double Zhang toward the ground!Bomb!Two jet of gas strengths are from the ash dress person's palm project, appeared two lightning flash sort like the underground, break ground to dash forward two black dress person.Two black dress person reaction come over of time, the leg have already been is true spirit by the ash dress person's Gen soil to invade, legs like with the land merge into an integral whole sort, a move to can't move, either.Wink, their place of square the circle be two ground in the Zhangs, like boil of boiled water sort, under the surging that sturdy spirit strength, piece of stone mud continuously and suddenly and violently crack, jump up, vacillating.
<br />At this time two black dress person's legs because be subjected to Gen soil true spirit of invade, drive ash dress person of spirit strength influence, blood vessel sudden rise, sinew and flesh distort, continuously have a blood to spout to shoot but.If at this time black dress person's leg if have no true spirit to protect, the leg bone be early like those rocks similar burst, the sinew and flesh then be like those muds similar drive distort of not presentable.Return have be previous black dress person reaction enough quick, true in the Gen soil spirit still the time in feet department, control breath inhibitted Gen soil true spirit of invade.If let the Gen soil true spirit spread all over whole body, two black dress person early was distort by this of not adult's form, drive mix blend in this.
<br />At by this time and suddenly!Underground spread a sound of muffled thunder sort, connect a Zhao ground a burst of vibrate, tight connect the Zhao ir place of that big slice the place suddenly felled bottom to go to!
<br />Owner all have never thought this ground would suddenly collapse to fall bottom to go to, two black dress person and ash dress person all didn't surplus of the strength escape to go out, along with collapse to fall of the ground together plunged.Wu2 Shi4 En pull into the hand of Lin Lin to want to escape there, but fall of quick, two people run didn't two step, Wu2 Shi4 En with become Lin Lin is also collapse to fall of the ground gobbled up to go in.
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2 Jiao drink 1, the luck foot 100% capability turn to make a go to silver light blunt go up, a hold tight a Wu2 Shi4 En's hand, another hand hold tight one piece of stone and Ke Yue4 Quan2 haven't grasped a prison, that piece of stone also rolled to fall in, and Ke Yue4 Quan2 also together dropped down.At by this time autumn Chu smell fly a body to catch a Ke Yue4 Quan2's hand and the skill pull one rock.
<br />Wu2 Shi4 En pull into the hand of Lin Lin at this time, the skill of Ke Yue4 Quan2 catch Wu2 Shi4 En, another a hand and autumn Chu to smell of the left hand grasp together, autumn Chu smell of the right hand mercilessly button up in a hugely of the rock of the blind side.
<br />The ground vibrate at this time although died down a lot, on all sides piece of stone and mud still keep being continuously collapsing to fall and roll to fall.
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2 shout a way:&quot;The childe of the autumn!Can the persistence live!&quot;Autumn Chu smell grind teeth to get entangled in fighting a way:&quot;Ah ……all right.&quot;Autumn Chu smell use the energy of whole body all in the right hand, the sharp angle of rock blind side be sharp abnormality, firm enter autumn Chu smell of palm, let Chu in autumn smell of the hand blood be not only.
<br />At this time at most underneath of become Lin Lin suddenly yell way:&quot;Don't , don't !&quot;Wu2 Shi4 En and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape accounts</a> Ke Yue4 Quan2 quickly turn head on see, detection a black dress person positive in hand feet counteract of upwards climb, stretch hand the feet which prepare to live into Lin Lin.Become the Lin Lin legs Deng several bottom, do not kick there black dress person, drive on the contrary black dress person a is grasped her feet.
<br />Autumn Chu of original unbearable heavy burden smell, undernea Quan2 a public quick of crash down, Ke Yue4 Quan2 quickly distinguish a direction to adjust a body form, in order to prevent fall to the ground of the time get hurt.Hua!Ke Yue4 Quan2 have never thought underneath unexpectedly have water, foot a slippery, 1 stumble to almost fall down, quickly the spirit sink pubic region, a 1000 catties fall to steady lived footstep.Here water abnormality icy cold, deep go to knee and flow see come is underground river.
<br />Five people be same times, same directions drop to drop down of, therefore each other is in a scope.Autumn Chu smell the left side in Ke Yue4 Quan2, there is four distance around.The Wu2 Shi4 En is in Ke Yue4 Quan2's right side, about ten outside.At Ke Yue4 Quan2 opposite more than ten step, across to fall in of mud heap of another part, then Lin Lin with just held tight the short and black dress person of her leg, become the Lin Lin and black dress person about mutually be apart from six, seven step.But previous the black dress person of tall fellow and Cuan east fall in ? , respectively station in the public or so both sides.
<br />At this time Ke Yue4 Quan2 just see clear surroundings of environment, the on all sides cliff be tactful, have no Leng have no Cape, see come should is underground course of river.The cliff is hollow to haven't a few silt with Ji Cape at this time, in spite of is an or so both sides, be still that the cliff of coping all have silt.Look previous here the noodles was filled with by the mud of, but recently for consecutive days overcast and rainy, cause water current enlarge, this just passage inside pile up of all of mud to flush.Didn't the mud fill, the passage that is at this time became the hollow, so when Cuan east ? at top make use of ground to attack black dress person of time, hence didn't prop up of hollow passage, end and unbearable heavy burden get collapsed to fell down.
<br />This hole hole high is about four Zhangs, the breadth be about six Zhangs, headstream two the utter darkness could not see of end, don't know the depths.Water being icy cold in hole at this time quiet flow, top of entrance to cave now still often have mud piece of stone to roll to fall, drop to send out to burst into Shui-li, burst of voice, this voice in this the expanse of the hole response write.
<br />The inside of the hole is peaceful at this time of frighten a person, in addition to the mire piece rock of Shua Shua roll to fall of voice, be burst burst of response.Everybody in the hole keep silence an on every occasion, double eye continuously at surroundings Human body top sweep to take aim go to of.
<br />This entrance to cave's leaving ground doesn't calculate Gao, light achievement a little bit point of all ability easily leave here.Although everybody want to leave so,everybody dare not to move.Because in spite of and 1 go up of is who, is which stir of person, will encounter the attack of opponent.So everyone see me, I see you, who also do not make a noise, all respectively ruminate in mind.
<br />At this time, the entrance to cave of everyone's overhead spread the voice of Shua Shua again, the immediately after a burst of mud sandstone dropped to come in, immediately after Shua Shua ……of voice more and more big.Although everyone be ill at ease,everyone dare not diverted see, afraid a don't be careful drive side person sneak attack.Connect the top of the Zhao spread depressed of bomb Long, bomb Long ……of voice, entrance to cave gradual of get dark.Public frightened, quickly the rise have a liking for.This see impending, top a quick three people match to embrace of big rock just at continuously of tilt to one side!It is the mud piece of stone which continuously roll to fall, let the big rock lose balance.That big rock if fall flop of words, drive so big of the rock lived entrance to cave.When the time comes calculate fighting skill again severe also useless.
<br />The rock fall flop at this time of speed suddenly speed!Bomb!One is huge to ring, that huge rock is on the entrance to cave.Ke Yue4 Quan2 feel the inside of the hole immediately one utter darkness, what also can't see, all of the ear be the response which bomb Long Long.
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2 suddenly hear a front spread a burst of Hua water voice, don't know is who is run to move.This ring, immediately after dark medium ring out of on exclaiming a voice, is become Lin Lin of voice!Tight connect one that the Zhao hear bang stuffy ring, someone was stuffy to hum 1 in the meantime, saw to was in someone to recruit.Don't know is what person is come to grips.A short moment trip water voice rise everywhere, at this time echo in the hole continuously, this that the Fu can't let Ke Yue4 Quan2 distinguish clear where did the voice once spread to come out from.
<br />At this time Ke Yue4 Quan2 what also could not see, on all sides one utter darkness, let Ke Yue4 Quan2 feel oneself imitate Fo drive desert in limitlessly the blackness.The on all sides noisy voice let to suddenly feel a burst of in the heart of Ke Yue4 Quan2 to fear difficult to expressly, want to escape so.Just on move, is suddenly held tight arm by a hand, Ke Yue4 Quan2 frightened positive desire flounder, hear an acquaint with of voice at oneself of the ear small voice say:&quot;Don't be afraid is me and shut eyes to once see for the ability.&quot;This voice that acquaint with is exactly an autumn Chu smell of voice.
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2 hear is autumn Chu smell of the voice calm mind and shut bottom eyes, this time be on all sides also gradual of peaceful come down.When Ke Yue4 Quan2 open eyes of time, eyes already orientation dark of environment, already the ability saw a whole circumstance.
<br />The detection of Ke Yue4 Quan2's become Lin Lin at the right side of oneself is two Zhangs and the left hand grasp right hand arm, see to may be to get hurt.But the Cuan east ? then appear before become Lin Lin station of place, Wu2 Shi4 En at the back of he five step place.Originally station at become the short and black dress person beside the Lin Lin, now at Cuan east ? opposite not distance, dress person of Gao Ge4 Hei also station arrive he after death.
<br />In addition to the party concerned, now probably who also hard to say clear just occurrence what affair.
<br />At this time everyone's eyes all orientation dark of environment, everyone vigilance of keep each other of distance.Ke Yue4 Quan2 and autumn Chu smell caution of to become Lin Lin to walk through go to, Wu2 Shi4 En also took notice of, also slowly close to come over.But Cuan east the ? and two black dress person also didn't move, each other keep invite the distance of half Zhang.
<br />At this time in addition to Ke Yue4 Quan2 and autumn Chu smell have no big Ai, the dissimilarity get hurt of degree of everybody here.Although at this time two black dress person also all is harm, just deal with Cuan east ? also not what difficult matter.But previous there is Wu2 Shi4 En with become the Lin Lin make moves to help each other Cuan east ? , now if make moves toward the Cuan east ? of words, they certain make moves to help each other.And now Ke Yue4 Quan2 and autumn Chu smell also with they station together, obvious is a.So if dozen the words for get up, black dress person didn't also the confidence which necessarily win.
<br />Cuan east the ? is previous that recruit to use to make an effort and the plan and black dress person put together a fish dead net to break.Unexpectedly the ground suddenly collapse to fall and fail by a small margin.Now Cuan east the dint in the ? consume lead big, true spirit difficult continuous, more origin isn't two black dress person's opponent.
<br />Ke Yue4 Quan2, autumn Chu smell with Wu2 Shi4 En and become four people: Lin Lin although harm of most light.But four people win, only autumn Chu smell be what yin and yang turn five go state with Ke Yue4 Quan2, and Ke Yue4 Quan2 still just primer of.In spite of is a list dozen only Dou still four rightness two, isn't all black dress person's opponent.
<br />Be also say at this time who also do not have confidence to remove to deal with.
<br />Wu2 Shi4 En toward into Lin Lin to ask a way after close to:&quot;The younger sister of the teacher, did you get hurt?How is condition of the injury?&quot;Become the way of Lin Lin:&quot;Nothing important matter just may be swept by that black dress person's Zhang strength.&quot;Wu2 Shi4 En looking at Ke Yue4 Quan2's way:&quot;Miss ……you how here?&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2's way:&quot;It's a long story to tell, later slowly say again.&quot;The point of Wu2 Shi4 En once head, H'm 1.
<br />Now everybody in the hole an on every occasion take precautions against of others.
<br />Autumn Chu smell a small voice a rightness so Ke Yue4 Quan2's way:&quot;It if this continues is not a way either.&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2's way:&quot;That what way do you have?&quot;Autumn Chu smelt want once take out a bosom of the fire fold son, pulled out to open a bamboo cover to lightly blow once, the fire fold son to send out weak of light of fire, everyone's vision a while drive attraction come over.Autumn Chu smell a clear voice way:&quot;If this continues isn't everyone a way either.The now export is stopped up completely, I feel now most important is find out other of export.Have what gratitude and grudge go out is say again.&quot;
<br />At this time Gao Ge4's black dress humality:&quot;That's right, if can not find other of export, no matter who it is, lose who win end all would dead here.&quot;Should is at drop to come in of time the rain hat drop to water, was washed away by water and now two black dress person's black rain hat all be missing.The black dress person who lean against a weak light of fire ability to see Gao Ge4 is long face convex sum, thin sharp-eyed nose.The black dress person of short is the round face small eye, the flat nose thick lips.
<br />Become the Lin Lin small track:&quot;The difficult way nobody would come we?&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2 say:&quot;The position is strange here, again nobody attention arrive we, find out here should didn't so easy.&quot;
<br />The Cuan east ? way:&quot;Small brothers what you say right.That where beginning do we seek from?&quot;Autumn Chu smell a way:&quot;Water here since is flow, so certain have export.We first along the water current go below to seek.&quot;Say finish and then take the lead agreeable this water current go below, everyone feel Chu in autumn to smell say of have, so also each other keep distance heel go up.Walked to is an end in a little while, because passage at front of changed a direction, get down flection.Autumn Chu smell and then take the lead to return to walk, everyone still keep silence of follow to walk, if the front was also a dead end to surround dead here.
<br />A group of people go upstream to walk in a little while, suddenly detection cliff top was dig by the person to once engrave of trace, this elucidation front probably have exit, thought of here everyone not from of speed footstep.
<br />Not in a short while public stop bottom footstep, go forward is a dead end.But block in their in front of isn't a cliff, is a wall!A granite brick carve of wall!Public looking at the wall of this oddness a gape.
<br />Wu2 Shi4 En's way:&quot;How can there is wall here?Does difficult way someone live here?&quot;The dress humality of Gao Ge4 Hei:&quot;Tube does he have a person to live an inside?Importance of is the road that can find out to go out!&quot;Autumn Chu smell a way:&quot;That's right and find out is an urgent matter of the moment.&quot;Say that play and then squatted down come down.Originally wall top leave a ground of place of eight inch Gaos to have a the fish head of one sculpture carvings, see that shape should be a drainage outlet.Autumn Chu smell an in hand top have some water, then the handle knob put a fish, not and in a short while the water stains of finger stem.Autumn Chu smelt a station get up a way:&quot;The inside contain breeze and the inside have export.&quot;Ke Yue4 Quan2 knocked to knock this wall to ring out depressed of voice, Ke Yue4 Quan2 knit the brows a way:&quot;This wall is very thick, break this wall have a little difficult.&quot;
<br />At this time always the station walk to come forward in the Cuan east ? of behind, Chu who arrive at an autumn smell them flank way:&quot;This have difficult.&quot;Say that finishing handle knob stick on the wall, immediately after the voice which send out a sand sand of the blind side of brick piece, voice more and more intensive, such as hear silkworm eat mulberry in together the silkworm building leaf of voice similar.Immediately after the Cuan east ? arm is one earthquake and bomb!The wall collapse 1 oneself the entrance to cave of Gao.
<br />Immediately after Cuan east ? and Ke Yue4 Quan2, autumn Chu smell wait for<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank">runescape gold</a>  someone together get into an inside and wait until Cuan east ? to back what Chu smell in autumn after death of time, two black dress talented person come in.
<br />The inside is a passage, the passage be very narrow two shoulder breadth.Autumn Chu smell discover at this time there is unexpectedly oil lamp on the wall, quickly point bright oil lamp, lay up quick burn away of the fire fold son.Although this oil lamp isn't a brightness, at least fold son than the fire much stronger, at this time finally ability more clear of see surroundings of environment.
<br />At this time how hasn't been talk of become Lin Lin suddenly, of a!The scream get up.Become the Lin Lin shiver of point at a ground frightened way:&quot;Ground up …… ground up ……&quot; is public quickly go toward once the underground see and unexpectedly spread on the ground full paper copper money, this be an emperor's mausoleum!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f009f20c54680f07cee2542f57cbdfa8" url=""><![CDATA[childhood years<br/><br/> Gang of now Hao has already done not  be four year agos to hunt the son of door.He now the fighting skill be unsurpassed, remarkable artistic skill, if necessarily is an affairs in<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS10emhhYXItZmlnaHQtY2F2ZS1jLTI5XzMyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">fire cape</a>    regard to river's lake of now rare top-grade superior.
<br />The 20-year-old Cui Gang Hao is already a breadth of view high ambition.At childhood years of time his side once listenned to river's lake is how of magic.But after Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance right and cold frost was harmed dead by the traitor, river lake on appeared a hundred years difficult meet of big rob difficult.
<br />Wu3 Lin2 turbulence, everyday see of is all glint and flash of cold steel, kill Nue innumerable, an end still a bad person succeed.Overlorded among states Wu3 Lin2.The eminent family is virtuous to exert Dai to be pursue.Some man with justice's desire kill crafty revenge for Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance, with instauration Wu3 Lin2 hospice.But end drive all eventually the traitor harm dead.The only a few person, who leave, doesn't think again to follow the bad example of others with that for bad person, but is again the disability turn round situation.At river lake on foolish, will cruelly injury secretly, so all conceal countryside folks, withdraw river's lake ……
<br />The rest big and parts of person all is swear allegiance in traitor under, was his accomplice, act in collusion for evil purpose with traitor.Make this several years river lake on is agitated, but the civil common people be more misery.Therefore Cui Gang the father of the Hao then hold of the family arrived at here.
<br />The Cui Gang Hao ask a father the overlord among states Wu3 Lin2 of person is who, after he grow up must do obeisance teacher to learn a skill, uproot crafty bad, bring benefit to for the people, do a big Xia, a big hero.
<br />After his father listen to, the facial expression be big to change, say Hao son to him, river lake now is already no longer what it was before, bad person in power, but the good man is to have a foothold of ground, think stem some kind of big industry is more difficult top to add difficult, return not equal to in the countryside do 1 to hunt a door freedom comfortable.Why the need for walk the road that don't return?
<br />If the Cui Gang Hao listenned to a father, greatly puzzled, why the daddy know a river lake up so many affair, their being certain have already lived in the mountains here for more than 10 years, in normal times daddy again not go out.The Cui Gang Hao of cleverness thoughted of what, but dare not famous saying, just ask him whether dad know that bad person to be who or not again?
<br />His dad tell him that person to be a leaf a cold autumn, is Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance in nowadays.But 20 year ago only is a very small hall lord.
<br />The cold autumn of leaf is a cruel hand hot, human face monster the Tu of the Si.20 year ago is'double hawks'seven 12 lord.'Double hawks'of the Zhang door be Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance right and cold frost to become sworn the brothers Cui a life time Tong with him to create.Cui a life time Tong is'double hawks'of pair Zhang disciple.
<br />Right and cold frost, Cui a life time Tong two people show the deepest sincerity, behavior straightforward unruly, line Xia battle righteousness, wide knot Wu3 Lin2 Ge4 road Hao the friend is a river well-known chivalrous man of the lake, Wu3 Lin2 Ren2 call'have no quantity double Xia'.End they two people make concerted effort, make Wu3 Lin2 no longer have already kill, no longer the matter of occurrence gravamen regardless is the lake person of river of mafia or white way to all call them as big Xia, respect and admire them, wish with it mutually hand over.
<br />They two people be with one action pushed Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance, afterwards the elder right and cold frost is positive leader of alliance, old two Cui a life time Tong is pair leader of alliance.
<br />They at that time all is 20 many year old, belong to temperament middleman, to anyone all too trust, with as for that craftiness crafty leaf the cold utumn be organic and can multiply by and won leader of alliance of trust.The position that is in' the double the hawks' increase Gao day by day.
<br />Two Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance is an all free and unfettered person and basically lead not to spoil that drive whole day heavy duty tie up a body of life, because they be joyful, free and unfecttered.So then hand over Wu3 Lin2's matter to take charge of in cold autumn of leaf.Hence the two people decision keep off a river lake to ten thousand inside outside of desert in make a living away from home.
<br />Decade inside, two people all don't at river lake top the emergence lead.They arrived at desert.Don'ted want to meet mightiness of'camel breeze', then again is a strong sandstorm, in addition top have no the source of water have no the Ji of food, they are in the desert enchant direction, end collapsed and fainted.
<br />After drive Wang2 Chou2 Hao2 in the desert feeling save.This person lake of originality river on of chivalrous man, loyalty liver righteousness Dan, the spade be crafty in addition to bad.But be subjected to control of Wu3 Lin2, the day canning not get use to a dozen dozen to kill, play can not the Er worry my Zha of river's lake, hence withdrew river's lake, arrived at desert on, a personal carefree ……
<br />The enemy Hao feeling behavior is straightforward unruly, dare to friend's two ribs to put knife again, save a person at water fire, as a result in the prestige in the desert very Gao.He courageously had already strive for, the once strong storm almost wanted the life of owner in the desert, and he save everyone.This after, people more trust he, respect he, support and adore him as the king of desert.
<br />Right and cold frost and Cui a life time Tong two people be after enemy Hao's feeling saved then lived bottom in the desert, they three personal personality homology, again is an all straightforward person, aspiration homology, very quick knot for the sake of different clan surname friend.
<br />At two people in the desert a live be long seven years, they where married a wife, the freedom was comfortable, unrestrained.Decade after, three people take a wife and returned to a river lake on.But river's lake in now is already no longer what it was before, with compare decade ago is also falter unbearable, bad person in power, kind basically can't have a foothold.
<br />While step into Wu3 Lin2, right and cold frost and Cui a life time Tong two leader of alliance be make track for by person to kill, they three people regardless go where is make track for by the person to kill.Therefore, they basically can't return'world Chuang'-Wu3 Lin2 the biggest group be also the house of Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance.
<br />Enemy Hao feeling not only is a fighting skill Gao Qiang2, more is that one is easy to permit a superior.He right and cold frost and Cui a life time Tong two people be easy to permit common of Wu3 Lin2's person, arrived at to receive guest building-everyone river personage in the lake come together together discussion Wu3 Lin2's matter of place.
<br />They find out, why right and cold frost and Cui a life time Tong does two Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance unexpectedly encounter to make track for of each road of river's lake to kill?By a happy chance this time river's lake all just at comment why right Cui two traitor how can again appear lake at the river up?So their problem combine never the doubt have what not appropriate place, but not with realize them, still each say respectively of.
<br />They three people see no man and should answer their problems, all attend to oneself of discussion:Right and cold frost they how dare again lake at the river top emergence, don't know again vital part how many persons of life?
<br />They three people is also doubt don't understand, time in this decade, exactly occurrence what affair?They settle to want this matter of before and behind cause and effect understanding clear.
<br />Hence:
<br />Right and cold frost say:&quot;Lake friend of everyone river, at bottom right day Kun.BE that the way just didn't soon and not know to say of is the matter of that river's lake?Because hear to relate to leader of alliance, hence curious.The hope give the friend is us continuous the way be some kind of.Today from at come down pay, today to receive guest though the owner of building eat though drink, I wish and everyone the knot don't know to for the friend how under the idea?&quot;
<br />&quot;You calculate where stranger?A small hair Zai son, dare to let Lao Tze come to a stop?&quot;A big fellow of all over the face beard do with malice of walked to a right day the in front of the Kun, make an effort to hold tight a right day the shoulder of the Kun.
<br />'Mao'of 1, the arm of big sweat drive rebound come over, bump at flank of chair up:The big fellow angry small voice of the all over the face beard of&quot;you ……&quot; say gutter language, seem to dare not believe.
<br />The person who receive guest building has already stopped down and looking at this act.
<br /><br />A spool of dangerous early sign seven cloud:Unrestrained price
<br /><br />The right day Kun answer a way:&quot;Though everyone eat, drink.I hand over a friend with this good friend.&quot;Smile to pull that big fellow to him originally the place of station.
<br />That big fellow tactful, have already know at present this person remarkable artistic skill, since he have already descended for own step, that oneself only have should.He quickly ha ha of smile a dozen a circle a field to say:&quot;Rightness, rightness.We hand over a friend.Small two, best wine real jam.Ha ha ……&quot;his defying see of spirit a right day Kun very be one eye.
<br />&quot;Excuse me, where be the brothers come from?The artistic skill is quite good!&quot;The say of big fellow despise of all over the face beard.
<br />The right day Kun doesn't mind and still keep say with smile:&quot;At bottom just 1 just the small potato of the way, teacher religion however is some unknown person, said you is also don't know, so friend don't again ask.Today of meal tips I, however still hope also spoke the affair that I ask, otherwise aftertime occurrence what affair, I dare not guarantee.&quot;Say that finish, eat of equanimity vegetables.
<br />&quot;Ha ha ……&quot; big fellow say with smile:&quot;You are in the threat I.&quot;
<br />The &quot;dare not ……&quot; right day Kun say:&quot;I the inquisitive affair just always haven't coulded not do.&quot;
<br />The big fellow is angry:&quot;Good crazy tone, who be your knowing a grandpa ?Just so say is to you of polite, see you is worthy of hand over of friend, you don't want to not worth and annoyed me'Ba noodles king'smile a day crane.Hum!Know the grandpa's means!&quot;
<br />Public on listen to, a burst of and tiny and cold, they think peacetime this to smile for a day, the crane take advantage of power to bully people, never put anyone in the eye, today how so of polite?BE originally very treacherous, frighten a person more than the peacetime!
<br />'Ba noodles king'smile for a day, the crane is a river the person of the lake mafia, the means be very of cruel, kill people innumerable.The day of a pair of earthquake hammer never leave a hand and do a to the utmost bad matter.But Gao Qiang2 because of fighting skill, no man presume it do rightness, is a lake person of a river to smell it extremely frightened of mean mean person, people general never ask for him, as far as possible avoid it ……
<br />Public can not help for at present of young worry, he how dare with'Ba noodles king'this brutally of the Si do rightness?Today's certanly will settle will die a tragic death here.Regrettable!Public shake head, have of even is silently keeping off two people, good a bad Dou will soon beginning.
<br />The right day Kun is also a say of despise:&quot;'Ba noodles king'BE which road of person?BE descend a river lake experience still shallow, once listenned to'weak noodles king'do not know but friend?Ha ha ……&quot;
<br />Smile for a day, the facial expression of crane spirit change, public not language, hear'Dong' of 1, they have a meal of that table was already the powder body ground bone.They three people but be missing a trace and shadow, see again smile for a day, crane an on every occasion of the station is on the ground and the double hammer leave a hand.
<br />Public careful one lo, just understand smile a day crane have already been lived acupuncture points by the point.The laughter spread, is originally right day Kun they be three people, at this time just on a table food and drink of public back.
<br />&quot;Good quick artistic skill!&quot;Spread in the crowd a burst of marvel:&quot;At bottom rush river's lake so long, also have never seen such of the person of quick artistic skill, dare to ask big Xia what name?&quot;A feature is beautiful and slender handsome young ask a way.
<br />&quot;Originally call by the sword quick Zhao, the green sword be known for world of'the sword ask a day'original Wu2 Xiao4 Yuan2 big Xia.&quot;The right day Kun say.
<br />Original Wu2 Xiao4 Yi be surprised, they can't be certain is new way, oneself how otherwise don't know a river there is this number person on the lake, the difficult way is a river lake top people of talent coming forth successive, do they embed not Lou?Original Wu2 Xiao4 doubt of looking at them.
<br />Right day the Kun be open a smile:&quot;The originally original big Xia is to embed not the person of Lou!&quot;
<br />&quot;Why see?&quot;Original Wu2 Xiao4 don't understand of ask <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS1iYXJiYXJpYW4tYXNzYXVsdC1jLTI5XzMzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Fighter torso</a>  a way.
<br />&quot;This smile for a day, crane what'weak noodles king'what Wu3 Lin2's superior, unexpectedly don't know original big Xia here, unexpectedly such of overbearing, this is not Lu class before the door the lane big ax, not simply tactful.Original big Xia this isn't you to embed not the place of Lou?Ha ha ……&quot;
<br />&quot;Laugh, at bottom just occasionally process this place, past to listen to them talk some river a lake matter, don't want to appear.Don't miss you to unexpectedly let me come out, should is real embed not Lou of the person be you!?Ha ha ……&quot;original Wu2 Xiao4 Xiao4 ask a way:&quot;Who is daring to ask big Xia ?Why form of address?&quot;
<br />&quot;Big Xia?&quot;The right day Kun smiled:&quot;Would not dare to be?We are just river lake on of unknown generation, just way only this and no more just.What also still not all understand, how and original big Xia?Fighting skill Gao Qiang2, again in addition to bad river's lake, the reputation ring unique world.Be this the big Xia?&quot;
<br />&quot;BE descend embarrassed by undeserved praise!&quot;Original Wu2 Xiao4 Yao2 shake head.
<br />Original Wu2 Xiao4 is the sword absolute being parties pupil, because of not original the Ju is at the vulgar rules, hence left sword absolute being parties of site, celibacy one person swim to rush river's lake, with chivalrous is day, sword the person whom kill and should kill, hence call'green sword'with'the sword ask a day'be known for, is also a river lake on enjoy one of the famous persons in recent years.
<br />&quot;We are this time arrive at river's lake is last to think two leader of alliance of understanding river's lake of matter just.&quot;The right day Kun say.
<br />Original Wu2 Xiao4 Shuo:&quot;If everyone not suspicion, original some would like to for speak to understand.&quot;
<br />&quot;Would not dare to put?to the trouble original big Xia, quick please sit down!Everyone sit down, small two, best wine, real jam.We listen to'Ba noodles king'speak for us.&quot;The right day Kun say.
<br />The words sound just fell, smile for a day, the crane sat on the ground, his acupuncture points have been already untie, who also do not see right day Kun make moves, very fierce!Public all foolish, hope a right day Kun!
<br />See their three people or big cup drink to heart's content, just let to smile for a day and the crane be quicker to speak.
<br />Receive guest none in building a person to talk, everyone be just quietness of looking at that three heel have no matter person general of the background be not clear, fighting skill Gao Qiang2 of stranger.That smile for a day in seeing ground, crane, the inside be smug and arrogant in normal times, have never put anyone in the eye and is frighten at this time of foolishly sit on the ground, on on every occasion lookinging at a right day Kun, the sweat bead that is on the forehead agreeable the cheeks fell down ……
<br />&quot;Our endurance is limited, you do all sorts of evil in normal times, if today send to your uthorities, end you be certain understand.&quot;Right day Kun mildly say, however tone in leak this dignity.
<br />Smile a day crane one earthquake.
<br />&quot;Would not dare to?&quot;Start to climb from the ground, smile for a day, the crane be a face of unnatural say with smile:&quot;Right and big Xia, say this affair get from before decade of the time speak of ……&quot;
<br />Public can not help admiring a right day Kun more.Several decade come always no one dare to move to smile for a day, the crane be 1, don't even say that let smile for a day, the crane listen to who order about of person.But today smile a day crane thoroughly of.The outside of the mountain contain mountain, someone outside the person.Than his severe person ten million?If a person do misdeed too many, isn't a report not, Be just hour non-arrival.God's justice is all-encompassing, Shu but gastight, from of old who escape again of lead?
<br />The &quot;good, &quot; right day Kun say:&quot;Today we listen to you say here that finish.Have who want to walk, at bottom also don't obstruct, the dishes to go with wine which want to stay be some to pay and also calculate to hand over a friend!? &quot;
<br />&quot;The many thanks right and big Xia!? &quot;The public one act in cooperation, sit down in succession and have never had a person to leave.Anything but for begging for rice money of this cheapness.
<br />&quot;Smile for a day, crane, you also sit down!&quot;
<br />&quot;The many thanks right and big Xia!&quot;Smile for a day, the crane be grateful of say. affair is so of, before decade, right and cold frost, Cui a life time Tong left river's lake, at Wu3 Lin2 on all business all have a leaf to take charge of for the cold autumn.Cold autumn of leaf he at Wu3 Lin2 on is to cover up tracks, stem exerted a bad matter, do evil things continuously.The name door of Wu3 Lin2 Ge4 is virtuous to all encounter his persecution, but those are afraid to die, unorthodox and slanting pour of the person all go and live with with his door bottom, listen to his to assign.
<br />Wu3 Lin2 Ge4 front door parties the decision cooperate to resist, but because of he be Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance of representative, so everyone didn't pick first clear, all let him ask leader of alliance to come out to manage justice.But at this time of leaf cold autumn influence and it of huge, say two leader of alliance and several decades ago already dying, unjust cloth Wu3 Lin2 be subjected to a loose of leader of alliance life, afraid Wu3 Lin2 bring about great repercussions.
<br />Public not letter, in succession the claim pay respects to the body of leader of alliance.He but artful self-defence leader of alliance the corpse have been already cremate, the cremated ashes have already floated with river's river to everywhere.Public not letter, leader of alliance Wu3 Lin2 Gao be strong, absolute being monster the esteem highly of person of the world, difficult way who kill of they?Who again does the ability kill them?
<br />Leaf cold utumn falter I of could not say the reason why.Public early know noodles to be some clues here, suspect be him to injury secretly leader of alliance, the person, who have, look for the whereabouts of leader of alliance everywhere, positively not the letter leader of alliance be now injury secretly by him go to life.But all of everythings be a bite on granite, several year without results and all waste.
<br />They no longer look for leader of alliance and the decision revenge for the leader of alliance.Regrettable in this several years middle  period cold autumn he unexpectedly consociation evil teach-day the sun teach.The influence is huge, already non- Xi ratio.
<br />The day sun teach to meet several decades ago an unique of big rob difficult, from now on don't know Zong, people listen to a river lake hearsay, that calamity have already make for a day, and the sun teach destroy completely.But recently river's lake again hearsay, the day sun taught and disappeared at all, that calamity make for a day, and the sun teach thousand Chuangs 100 bores, but living an interest for rest and recuperate of several decadeses.The day sun teach already and cold ashes burn again, the influence be getting more huge, just don't know where hide, secretly activity, the time is propitious moment of the one day there will.They certain meeting again appear river's lake.
<br />The cold autumn of leaf doesn't know again from where practice evil achievement-sun and moon star method.Absorb others of inside dint, exaltation oneself of inside achievement, now he was already without equal in strength, return have a person to presume him to set against?
<br />Eminent family a virtuous drive his persecution, only agreeable his Chang, but negative he is certain to die.This is many in the last years he no longer know to kill how much of hero.See not ? him make for of person's all having already retired river's lake, but wanting to have a foothold have to then be obey orders in him at the river lake, again have who presume him to match?
<br />It probably is for the sake of to live a public, quell many Nu to cover up himself/herself.Soon the cold autumn of leaf then announced the Mi book of Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance in river's lake:Right and cold frost and Cui a life time Tong is evil because of collaborate with to teach, desire persecution Wu3 Lin2 hospice in order to try to make profit from it, luckily cold autumn of leaf in time discover, can not make its scheme succeed.They they see scheme have already hurt, don't know to flee from home where, have a proof again for with.The end leaf cold autumn isolate one-self Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance and reside at Wu3 Lin2 on.
<br />No one believe leaf cold what the autumn said, is the leader of alliance already a world peace, strive for again what benefit?Although know all of what he says to draw up, no man have ability to answer criticism, everyone have to swallow a consequence in the belly, the stuffy air suppress in mind.
<br />&quot;That cold autumn of leaf say Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance dead already, they just not is say Wu3 Lin2's leader of alliance and appear lake at the river on.Is this actually and why?&quot;The right day Kun don't understand of ask.
<br />&quot;Alas, that cold autumn of leaf in a short while say leader of alliance dead already.In a short while again say leader of alliance don't dead again is to escape, true true or false false who cent of clear?However we feel two leader of alliance of right Cui don't certain dead, hence at this discussion.&quot;Smile for a day, the crane say.
<br />&quot;That river lake be the matter which spread to make track for to kill leader of alliance He2 Yi4 again?&quot;
<br />&quot;In fact we really don't know also just listen to a hearsay.Say ex- heavy river's lake of Wu3 Lin2 Wu3's wood's leader of alliance to be plot secretly against by person, if is really, those people must be a leaf the cold autumn parties is in the river the lake of scout cutthroat.&quot;Smile for a day, the crane say again:&quot;They together still have a person, fighting skill very Gao, but who can not know.&quot;
<br />&quot;That person is an enemy Hao feeling.Ten several year ago retire the roaming swordsman of river's lake.&quot;Public with reputation go to BE'the sword ask a day'original Wu2 Xiao4 Shuo.
<br />&quot;Original elder brother's how can knowing that person is how canan enemy Hao feeling.&quot;Ask of the enemy Hao feeling oddness way.
<br />&quot;This is ……&quot; is original Wu2 Xiao4 Wang4 right day Kun.
<br />&quot;He is my three younger brother enemy first river, flank of is me two younger brother Cui Lyu3 Jin4.&quot;The right day Kun introduction say.
<br />Original Wu2 Xiao4 is to their one Yi and the small voice shout:&quot;His ising you is three younger brothers ……&quot;
<br />&quot;Ha ha ……&quot; right day its idea with understand Kun, smiled 1:&quot;You are to say him bigger than me, how again will be me is three younger brothers?We with order of sequence is brothers of, he be what our end end become sworn, hence is me is three younger brothers.&quot;
<br />Original Wu2 Xiao4 embarrassedly say:&quot;BE at bottom tiresome, the enemy elder brother failed to show due respect.&quot;To enemy first the river be one Yi.
<br />&quot;Don't mention it.&quot;Enemy first the river say with smile.
<br />&quot;Just the enemy elder brother ask how to know enemy Hao feeling, in fact easy.&quot;Original Wu2 Xiao4 Shuo:&quot;His shape as early as Wu3 Lin2 Shang4 got abroad.I just get news first.&quot;
<br />&quot;The original elder brother is wonderful, non- ordinary people also.&quot;Enemy first the river Kua great way.
<br />&quot;Dare not.Dare not.&quot;Original Wu2 Xiao4 Shuo:&quot;At bottom just good at hearing all news of long some.&quot;
<br />Public smiled to get up.
<br />&quot;Original elder brother good would play trick, don't know an original elder brother to this matter understanding how much, again how comprehension?&quot;The Cui Lyu3 Jin4 Wen4's way.
<br />&quot;BE not original some big speech, at bottom already the sequence of events of this matter understanding clear.&quot;
<br />Public frightened, the right day Kun say with smile:&quot;That is to ask an original elder brother to speak understand, with solution our heart in of doubt, don't know can?&quot;
<br />&quot;Being descend nature would like to, in fact that cold autumn of leaf is already an insolently ambitious person and regrettable right Cui two leader of alliance believed him too much, didn't see his greed.After the leader of alliance hand over big little thing in him, he secretly and outsider plot, intention rule Wu3 Lin2.Disappear leader of alliance back after for several years, his greed more obvious, kill a virtuous person, collaborate with with mean person of the matter impartially do.&quot;
<br />He continuously does exercises in gymnastics, hurl with evil teach.Because of elsewhere the matter be tactful, deep of the religious leader like and give to his fighting skill.Day the sun religious leader be clay-cold, he again with another an evil teach of the person seduce crafty.That woman after become the religious leader pass him a ?sun and moon star method ?fighting skill Mi book.
<br />He now is already that the fighting skill be without equal in strength, so rightness original the leader of alliance also have no have scruples about, therefore Be getting more unrestrained.But also is to have weakness at the strong person.He know two leader of alliance of right and cold frost and Cui a life time Tong to all love Wu3 Cheng2 Chi's person, so saw for several years, must be to conceal to fix Lian fighting skill, don'ted know to create how absolute being achievement, the fighting skill state don't know to attain that kind of state again.As a result have a parties the person to every day run about river's lake, see leader of alliance appear and then shoot on sight.
<br />All of the person of his partieses are a fighting skill top-grade superior, is what he decade come train, in addition to he who haven't seen the shape of cutthroat as well.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f7b084b1ddabf3cf6cf1dfd0322febce" url=""><![CDATA[organized in the<br/><br/> already been blow by the breeze to fall, even blew away, but an a table be still a well organized in the house.
<br />The breeze blow not to fall it, can't even blow it to move a very small amount.
<br />This small grass shed origin set up on a cake of stone ground, but four feet son of this table, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS10emhhYXItZmlnaHQtY2F2ZS1jLTI5XzMyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">fire cape</a>  unexpectedly have already had a half deeply of insert stone ground.
<br />Table side station a person, a big fellow of iron pagoda sort, although two of his leg didn't insert stone ground, he a Mang form at the side of body copper turn, minimal have 1/3 mergence inside stone ground!
<br />Although the breeze be nasty and fierce, he aweather but sign, the least bit also have no this repeatedly the strong breeze put in the eye.
<br />Two people who sit by the side of the table to the Yi also didn't put this breeze in the eye!
<br />They three people was like to regard as this breeze music, is appreciate this music kind!
<br />Have never see to eat of, but the Xiao have no Lai still very excitement!His interest flavor full of lifely walk past!
<br />Still don't arrive ten step, that iron pagoda big fellow once turned round and stare with anger Xiao have no Lai!The Xiao has no Lai but smile happily of stare at him, looking at his that upper half completely naked of body, the You blackly become bright!
<br />The big fellow loudly drink a way:&quot;What person?&quot;
<br />His voice seem from the bell kind in the temple and keep Weng Weng to make ring!
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to lower the head to examine oneself of clothes, seemed to be to also arrive to want red the situation of, can he don't care.Don't know why, ever since that time he feel by himself need not dead, he just detection this world very the United States very brilliant, so, the others also become very brilliant!
<br />Ha ha smile, the voice which learn that big fellow ask a way:&quot;What person?&quot;
<br />That big fellow is first stunned speechless, favour answer way:&quot;Snake Wang2 Fu4 be invincible!&quot;
<br />The Xiao had no Lai and this time smile, but shockedly stared at him that in all seriousness of appearance, he go up and down of conjecture several time, then laugh loud to looking at that 2 to the person of Yi!
<br />Regrettable BE, this 2 to the person of Yi but seem to have never heard Xiao to have no the arrival kind of Lai, still keep being devoted to play chess!
<br />What to play chess is that one monk is a!
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to looking at this three eccentric and the tiny Shen say with smile:&quot;You this three people is really of!&quot;
<br />The sound fall, snake Wang2 Fu4 invincible harsh voice way:&quot;What person are you ?I am ask you of words!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to this time toward his way:&quot;I am to have no Lai!&quot;Say that finish, the big step continue to go straight up go to, the slightest and didn't see them!
<br />The &quot;Chi Chi&quot; voice ring!
<br />The Xiao had no Lai to see a head and return and stretch hand at the body to literally flicked several bottom, immediately after with jilted to go out, is also &quot;Chi Chi&quot; voice ring, but is a path to keep dynasty that three people shoot!
<br />&quot;? &quot;
<br />Those are unexpectedly a few pawn with what to flick, unexpectedly whole all shoot to go into that, give°ed their tables to fry!
<br />Snake Wang2 Fu4 is invincible at the behind loudly drink a way:&quot;His Niang of, unexpectedly still meeting guy of!&quot;
<br />But the Shan is in the Xiao have no Lai front of unexpectedly is that 2 a to a monk of the Yi!Monk gray full-length gown, the eyebrow be long over the ear, the right hand hold a crescent moon spade, but that then blue way tunic, green thin big eye, carry lance!Two people unexpectedly are like to see a strange thing kind at this time and keep stare at the Xiao have no Lai to see, then loudly say with a smile:&quot;Your boy still doesn't depend on, unexpectedly the ability pick me up that 11 pawn!H'm, is peculiar!BE peculiar!&quot;That long Le wear a pinch goat beard, despise of way!
<br />The monk then stare at eyes that the Xiao have no Lai, then the way of Xuan Fo:&quot;Old monk in this 20 years, have never seen someone can be on the hoof from inside in the death valley to come out!Your boy is one person!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to shockedly turn head to point at after death that mountain, ask a way:&quot;Is that a death valley?&quot;
<br />&quot;Why does the old monk want to cheat you!&quot;The long eyebrows monk's hands match 10, &quot; family not the dozen stroll language!Amitabha!Is the benefactor young unexpectedly to be on the hoof to walk through to die a valley?Think necessarily benefactor you to settle to carry an incomparable skill!This Chuang just demand you so of talented person!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai Hey Hey on smile, way:&quot;I don't know to call to die a valley there, also didn't carry an incomparable skill!I know now hungrily and desperately and edible a head of cow!&quot;
<br /><br />When knife didn't meet chapter 41 invincible
<br /><br />That long Mi wear small eyes but keep stare at Xiao have no the chest of Lai, seem he use this vision ability see through his idea kind!Sneer at 2, the side Duo wear step son side to say:&quot;Old way I with stupid the master is here already 20 year, have never seen be like you so not afraid dead of person!Still so unbridled in our in front?Boy, do you exactly want to live?&quot;
<br />&quot;Want to live how?Don't want to live again how?&quot;The Xiao has no Lai to turn head to looking at to get mad of snake Wang2 Fu4 invincible, straight-tempered sit on the ground, take a couch grass to bite in the mouth!
<br />Snake Wang2 Fu4 be invincible to keep Rang Rang in the behind:&quot;Mother of, this boy got fed up with live!The withered wood way is long, don't say with him much, I call him first have much heavy!&quot;
<br />The sound fall, he shout at top of voice, be like thunderbolt fury kind and keep to have no Lai to sweep toward the Xiao come a turn!
<br />Start to turn to turn to fall, an easy action, can but in the Fu the invincibility of the hand, but is a variety!See to turn medium road, become all of a sudden ten turn, carry the power of thunderbolt, arise repeatedly strong breeze to keep to have no Lai cover toward the Xiao!
<br />At Fu invincible they think the Xiao have no Lai to is certain to die, they have never seen Xiao have no the corpse of Lai, but detection Xiao have no Lai still carry ground station at the Fu invincible of back, positive wearing a smile looking at this Mang Han!
<br />This light achievement, keep let withered wood way long openned widely rat eyes, stupid monk's eye emit green light!Because this variety be big to come from their ideas to anticipate!
<br />The Fu is invincible just the beginning be still very happy very satisfied, be wait until to discover Xiao have no Lai of figure disappear at his at present, he Nu, cut up rough of like fierce tiger, the head don't return and turn but all over the place of to from already the back hit!
<br />The withered wood way long and stupid monk see Fu invincible use while make moves to usually kill &quot;decline evil 18 turn&quot;, they certainly know Fu invincible of effort, certainly very believe firmly Xiao have no Lai the whatever kind can't evade confrontation with this time!So, they face top peeped out satisfied smiling face, however, this smiles is like winter of snow kind, give to solidify on their faces a while!
<br />Xiao have no the body of Lai seem the one leaf in the ocean, at Fu invincible of walking stick constantly float to float, regardless Fu invincible turn up the effort how of severe, but how all can't one leaf in dozen, the one have ego consciousness of leaf, much less, they all don't know, Xiao have no eyes of Lai be how of sharp-edged, he already will this 18 turn of make moves the angle all saw pure, therefore, he then can turn nautical mile here natural and unrestrained from such as!
<br />18 turn later on, a full day of dance in the wind of shed leaves and sand dust all stop, the Fu which leave cut up rough be invincible with roar with laughter of Xiao have no Lai!
<br />Withered wood and stupid all have already stare at with awe, they know this 18 turn of power, think from this 18 turn bottom so easy but the person of , perhaps this boy still 1!Two public inside not from of inwardly shocked, this boy which come of?
<br />Two human face face reading the Qu wear and the in the mind all have a question<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />ifficult way is really from evil teach to come?
<br />The Fu is on the contrary invincible but didn't think so, draw back his that throat which break Luo, loudly call way:&quot;Can your boy not hide?&quot;
<br />The Xiao had no Lai to sigh a tone way:&quot;Deal with you, a recruit enough!&quot;
<br />The Fu is invincible to bite the tooth keep ring, suddenly loudly roars way:&quot;Call your boy stroll!&quot;
<br />Make moves this time luck foot unexpectedly dint inside the 12 F, vehemence and power which turn top all already exertive arrive thoroughly of state!
<br />Xiao have no the Lai looking at this to turn and looking at to turn medium turn again, know him this to turn medium conceal at least 18 kinds of variety, the cover lived at least oneself of 12 dead cave!
<br />The few someone's ability avert from this to turn!
<br />Few person can here most relentless of on turning an inside find out the flaw of &quot;decline evil 18 turn&quot;!
<br />But, the Xiao have no Lai at least saw this to turn medium have a flaw!
<br />The light red light Shan move, the alas voice which ride on You You sigh, everything of action all stop!
<br />A full day ofly flew sand and leaf and come to a stop, what to come to a stop was the Fu invincible Mang form copper to turn, the Fu be invincible of the whole action!
<br />He turn a method to contain flaw, an unique the little person ability see out, more unique the little person ability offend to break of flaw!
<br />But this combine be unequal to complete no one an ability confidence this kind of opportunity, with one action the shot break Fu invincible of&quot;decline evil 18 turn&quot;.
<br />Xiao's hasing no Lai is an one of them.
<br />In this world perhaps the power have no complete have no fighting skill of flaw, &quot;decline evil 18 turn&quot; how could exception?
<br />So, is fly sand a stop split second, withered wood and stupid see Fu invincible of the neck is last handle knife, one handle be like the knife of new moon and just be suffused with light of red and dazzling ray of light!
<br />Knife, this knife from where come?
<br />Everyone has never see to have knife, see on putting on red light, how have a knife on his neck?
<br />Withered wood and stupid more shocked, they believed more oneself of judgment:He is evil teach of pupil!
<br />Fu's ising invincible is a very upset tunnel:&quot;You won!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to smile happily ground to ask a way:&quot;Can I walk?&quot;
<br />The withered wood head draw a deep sigh to draw a sword, way:&quot;The I still want to accept you of knife method!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to shake a way:&quot;My knife method can't see!&quot;
<br />&quot;Why?&quot;
<br />&quot;My knife method use to come to kill people, not see to the person!&quot;The Xiao has no Lai lightly of take away knife, looking at the knife in the hand serious tunnel.
<br />Only himself very clear, that&quot;Ba knife method&quot; really too violent in action, too strong, now, he not already, a certain meet blood!
<br />The withered wood way grow to gloomily smile a way:&quot;The I always believe the sword in the own hand!The boy connect to recruit!&quot;
<br />Drink voice export, but see his Kuo sword to empty on flap release a line of swords a shadow cent to flow out before the body toward him while sign!Follow of and would be a furious wind arise of a full day of flying rock!
<br />To know the hair sword of ordinary people all offend an enemy by stabbing shot, what to use be a sword point, but the withered wood way be long is a horizontal sword to release.
<br />Particularly he push sword Yang since of a line of swords shadow, unexpectedly like armor huge round, billowing never-failing row empty since then, keep want pair of person indeed under the sword round general!
<br />Xiao's hasing no Lai has never seen this etc. threatening force, consumedly of eat a surprised.Feel the other party this etc. sword power, let person have no from make moves to ward off.Say nothing of the ability see his make moves angle!
<br />At heart a nasty, suddenly remind of &quot;the Ba knife method&quot; in on recruiting &quot;the absolute being be evil to face any ghost knife to cut&quot;, at that moment the disease raise &quot;day very evil eye star&quot;, flap wrist hair knife and keep to billowing since then of sword shadow split past!But the voice of the gold iron crazy Ming listenning to a burst of and nasty suddenly, continuous mount sudden attack 13 ring, Xiao have no Lai of a personal shadow, suddenly take off a billowing sword shadow of besiege.This 13 swords, is not only held up by him, unexpectedly still cut one knife!
<br />The body form moved once, immediately after continuous retreat five step just steady live Chun.The withered wood raise head, two deep cold vision shockedly keep note the Xiao have no Lai:&quot;You this knife isn't the knife method of the human life!&quot;The sound fall, the green tunic which see his body spilt open, a light long long of the knife scar of new moon sort!
<br />The knife scar had been row till a left waist before the chest from the better arm, blood didn't°yet run off, the flesh of both sides still tightly match together.If isn't the words that his ash tunic is blown crack by the breeze, also don't know him to have already got hurt!
<br />&quot;&quot;.The withered wood still lowered the head to vomit black blood!
<br />&quot;Good one knife of violent in action!&quot;The withered wood way is long to say while finishing<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS1iYXJiYXJpYW4tYXNzYXVsdC1jLTI5XzMzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Fighter torso</a>  this words, the knife scar of body just slowly leak out blood!
<br />The stupid monk and Fu is invincible at this time just know a withered wood way long get hurt, favour dash away past, apply medical ointment for him, return feed a tablet for him, immediately after hand him to part lean against tree trunk!
<br />Stupid monk way Fo:&quot;Amitabha, benefactor, you make moves too cruel!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no the hand of Lai inside already have no knife, play to play the dust of body, smile happily of ask a way:&quot;Dare not!Dare to ask master's 1!&quot;
<br />&quot;What?Ask the benefactor say!&quot;
<br />&quot;Is not master's thinking just 13 swords of that chief cruel?&quot;
<br />&quot;…… , That is that the withered wood way be long for the sake of in addition to evil Wei way, so ……&quot;
<br />&quot;Ha ha ha.&quot;The Xiao has no Lai to laugh loud a way, &quot; in addition to evil Wei way?Wasn't true not to thought of, I only come out from the this place, become evil?Ask a master, evil is what?&quot;
<br />Stupid monk's facial expression suddenly change, immediately after way:&quot;The knife in the your hand!&quot;
<br />&quot;Knife?&quot;The Xiao has no Lai to don't understand ground to ask a way.
<br />The stupid monk is solemn of point nod a way:&quot;Quite good!Be the knife in the your hand!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai this time but the cachinnation wear a way:&quot;This knife, isn't this knife very common?&quot;
<br />&quot;Not, it belong to evil teach!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai this time silly, the clock spread person and Qi son Ba to not and all say this knife is belong to evil boundary?How, this time this monk but say that being evil teach?Is the difficult way evil boundary evil to teach?
<br />Hence, his peristalsis the mouth ask a way:&quot;Are not you an evil boundary?&quot;
<br />The stupid monk point nod, way:&quot;Can also say to be an evil boundary!&quot;The Xiao has no Lai this just easy of comfortable tone, himself all not understand, why meeting hope really have the evil boundary this parlance, may be a kind of curious!
<br />The stupid monk loudly say:&quot;We will not let you re-appear river's lake!&quot;
<br />&quot;Why?&quot;The Xiao had no Lai to almost jump to get up to ask a way this time.
<br />Is this what rubbish?A monk would so of say!
<br />&quot;Because you take evil teach of come out from the death valley in knife!&quot;
<br />&quot;This ……this again what's wrong?&quot;The Xiao has no Lai double the eyes keep stare at stupid monk!Assume a serious look way, &quot;do you still speak not reasonable?&quot;
<br />Stupid monk's way:&quot;World person all can with the reasonable, only you these are evil to teach Nie Zhang can't reasonable!&quot;
<br /><br />Chapter 42 force when knife didn't meet
<br /><br />&quot;Am I evil to teach Nie Zhang?What about you?You would be robber's bandit!&quot;The Xiao has no Lai Duo Nu way that wear feet's exasperation!
<br />&quot;What?You does this smelly boy unexpectedly dare to say us to be robber's bandit?You go to dead!&quot;The Fu is invincible blunt come over, the way of Nu Chi, the hands turn once the copper button up, is need a Nao body but up!
<br />The Xiao has no Lai a full face of angry countenance, loudly threaten:&quot;How how?Do you defy?This time let you go to dead!&quot;
<br />The stupid monk pull Fu invincible of body, loudly toward his way:&quot;Can't make a mess of!&quot;Fu invincible spirit keep call, turn a copper yongli cha into the ground up!
<br />The stupid monk sigh a way:&quot;Have you ever seen a clock spread person and Qi son Ba?&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai a full face of consternation stare at him, ask a way:&quot;Your understanding they?&quot;
<br />&quot;Baloney.Certainly understanding, not, we so many people at here etc. top how many decades do what?&quot;The Fu is invincible didn't good spirit!
<br />The Xiao has no the brain of Lai to turn very quick, immediately after ask a way:&quot;You Qi son does Ba Suo3 get up?&quot;
<br />&quot;Suo what does he make?We is ……, &quot;the stupid monk suddenly become to happily ask a way, &quot; did you say Qi son Ba Suo3 to get up?&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai point to nod, hence will see Qi son Ba of the scene say that let them listen to, and still said to them, now they two people all already dying several day!
<br />They hear Qi son Ba and clock spread a person all dead already, happily smile to get up, the stupid monk turn head to toward a withered wood way long way:&quot;See, our withered etc. of this 20 years wasted!Ha ha ha!&quot;
<br />The withered wood way is a little bit long to nod but talk, because his viscera drive all that knife almost to earthquake moved!
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to looking at their this happy appearance, wrinkly eyebrow way:&quot;What great enmity do you have with them?&quot;
<br />&quot;Ha ha!You don't ask and we will also tell you!A simple words be, Qi son Ba also the clock spread a person, is all evil teach inside of person, they once by a hundred years at Central plains Wu3 Lin2 kill brutally innocence!Afterwards, under the leadership that little wood manage, Central plains Wu3 Lin2 arrive to them this to die a valley in, after still parties three person, Ma3 Ru4, this death valley, but to now didn't°yet a personal ability on the hoof come back!So, our teachers receive order to stay and wait here, must wait until someone back and understanding arrive Qi son Ba and clock to spread the person's whereabouts!&quot;
<br />Xiao have no the Lai take stupid monk of the breather, ask a way:&quot;Is not clock's spreading a person a fairy?Isn't that Qi son Ba the person in the evil boundary?&quot;
<br />&quot;What?Does your boy unexpectedly still believe that this in this world have fairy and devil?&quot;The stupid monk shockedly stare at him!
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to also use same of the vision stare at them, one word one ask of word way:&quot;Don't be to say, since the thou of dish open a day to split ground, world cent person, absolute being, evil three boundaries?But clock's spreading a person is a Qi son Ba at a friend of boundary understanding in day?&quot;
<br />&quot;This world which the meeting have absolute being with evil?Boy, you must be the story which listenned to and believe before that a hundred years evil boundary warrior Tu2 Long2!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to stare eyes of larger, the ear Shu have to keep more, this is he listen to come interesting again most complications of matter, exactly have a person, absolute being, evil three boundaries, have that Qi son Ba Tu2 Long2 a say?However, his in the mind in hopes of this be a fact!
<br />&quot;The world has no absolute being with evil, only have from the person go into evil person with from person in mental concentration person!You know of, is all legend, an incorrectly pass on a mistaken message of legend!In fact all false!Everything is all false!What Tu2 Long2, what repair a day, they only regard as this to invade Central plains an of borrow of Wu3 Lin2 just!&quot;Stupid monk angry of way, &quot; I know you to still know 6'the month soul make track for a soul'of matter!They the certain meeting say must lend this thing then can arrive west pole!&quot;
<br />Xiao have no Lai point nod, can heart but a piece a piece of downwards fall, person fall into ice hole kind, his beginning understand, past that legend afraid is false, the world basically have no absolute being with evil!
<br />&quot;West pole, quite good, is to have a such a place!However, it be a name of island, is also that they is evil to teach a location!That year, evil teach prosperous, once will Central plains Wu3 Lin2 Ya breathe heavily however spirit, just don't know why, evil teach of the three greatest elders unexpectedly will change sides in war with evil teach for the enemy, so, evil teach would be compelled west a pole!But, they have no don't want to emphasize back Central plains!So, they would parties Qi son Ba in advance arrive at Central plains and assassinate that year betrayal evil teach of three greatest elder!This three greatest elders is gold dragon, silver dragon and copper dragon, so, they this time the code of activity be'Tu2 Long2'!
<br />'The month soul make track for a soul'but is true, only is six this to come together, then can find out that west pole of position!So, for the sake of will evil teach this leftover evil how to exterminate, we would guard here, don't let whichever and evil teach the leftover evil how to pass here!&quot;
<br />Stupid monk suddenly seem to became Xiao have no the Lai can't exceed of a high peak!
<br />The Xiao has no the Lai brains inside a burst of mentally dense, don't know why, feel a pair of feet hair soft a while, seem the at heart have a ten million mountain to press kind and press he have to fall to sit on the ground, double eyes have no the absolute being ground looking at to be suffused with an expanse of white ground, but the stomach be continuously have muscular spasms!
<br />&quot;Meeting why so?Meeting why so?……This is why?&quot;
<br />His mumbling of yell, pain and sufferings of weep over.He prefer to believe an evil boundary, not because oneself want to go into it's evil, but is for the sake of their wishes!He is also understand, regardless is a Qi son Ba still a clock spread a person, all of them be a hope oneself return to evil teach!
<br />&quot;? &quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai not to know a quilt what things dozen in the body, oneself unexpectedly and without any reason fly on the half empty and then heavily fall on the ground, keep fall he dimmed eyesight the confused vomit a blood!
<br />He slowly climbed to get up, the wry-mouthed vomitted a blood, the inside of eyes seem to have 1:00 live spirit, stare at their three people's that shocked appearance, looking at stupid monk shiver of hand, suddenly understand, just be this monk sneak attack he!
<br />Really, the stupid monk saw Xiao have no make moves of Lai after, know a list dozen only Dou anything but his opponent, so, take Xiao have no the Lai soul occupy to give up it, adopt sneak attack, though the means have already owe bright, for the sake of the whole river lake to say, personal reputation be small!Just coming from what his idea anticipate BE, from already this Zhang, not only can open stone crack stone tablet, be ten cow can also a Zhang split dead, can this Zhang dozen on this boy's body, but will he dozen fly three Zhang outside, vomit blood, but oneself retreat have 67 step!This boy of inside dint how so male Hun?
<br />He is this Zhang and not only was frightened to death oneself, return is long withered wood way and Fu invincible all frighten gape to stare at Xiao have no Lai!
<br />The Xiao has no Lai eyes the Lou be cruelty and wipe a mouth Cape of blood, slowly one step one step of walked to come over toward them!
<br />Stupid monk and Fu invincible but felling arrive alignment their isn't a person, but a wolf, a cruelty and matchless wolf!This wolf give their pressure a lot too big, unexpectedly let their one step one step of go toward withered wood way long take side, but withered wood way long also force station get up, with stupid monk station become a triangle.
<br />They have a strategies, is their teachers for overcoming &quot;the Ba knife method&quot;, finish whole life energy, specialized research come out of a strategies, regrettable of BE, now of withered wood way long already body negative severely wounded!
<br />Being a blessing is a disaster, whole see respectively build to turn, said again, is a disaster to also hide however!
<br />The withered wood way is long although endure whole body of spasm, still keep supporting to draw out lance to fight shoulder to shoulder with them!
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to vomit phlegm, ruthlessly way:&quot;DOing not thought of your this monk would use so paltry trick?&quot;
<br />Stupid monk's facial expression fusion, heart abnormality of shame, but Fu invincible loudly Rang Rang:&quot;Deal with you so of evil teach Nie Zhang to still use wear to speak what river lake rules?&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai eye to emit a fury, Nu way:&quot;Are you certain to think the person whom I am evil to teach?&quot;
<br />Stupid three people have no speech, all hold breath, will inside dint luck foot 12 cent, silently stare at Xiao have no Lai!
<br />The Xiao has no Lai to face upward to loudly roar and seem a wolf at crazy Hao write!This interjection, but keep an earthquake stupid three people have a little dizzy and giddy, the heart be all inwardly strange call:This boy of inside the dint unexpectedly return than Qi son Ba Hai2 Qiang2 deep, is this what is the row?
<br />The Xiao has no Lai call over after, the motion fell calm, dispassion of stare at them, then way:&quot;I don't want to kill you!&quot;
<br />Stupid they three people shockedly looking at him and ask a way:&quot;Why?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5fcd1eff0056b470c1c36469bdc1b925" url=""><![CDATA[know his name<br/><br/> very hard to extrude stem to smile, way:&quot;Xing4 Xiao4 of ……good boy, you be the life star old adopted son, Te also the life be big!&quot;
<br />The Xiao has no Lai first stunned speechless, this old man son how can anyone know his name?Immediately after layer after layer cold hum a way:&quot;Old man son, I don't want to kill people!I <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS10emhhYXItZmlnaHQtY2F2ZS1jLTI5XzMyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">fire cape</a> want to know you why want to come to plot secretly against me?&quot;
<br />The complexion cruel Yin Zhi, the old man point engrave of way:&quot;Xing4 Xiao4 of, you are big to hurt before the month'ten thousand saint country villa', you of agile and fierce early at river lake top get about, especially, you be evil to teach of do misdeed, so, we also only stop at nothing to remove you!&quot;
<br />The Xiao had no Lai to see one eye young girl!
<br />The full head black silk float to spread, the half body was stained with dust, that knife is pole have proper restraint but make her a burst of to adjust an interest here in again slow lead strength, however, from this young girl of noodles top facial expression, can guess to get for this time mission of failure, will encounter with the result that of bad result is how of make person's heart palpitates, at least at present have to face a ruthlessness physical fight.
<br />The Xiao had no Lai to helplessly smile to say with smile:&quot;Why is this matter again?H'm!&quot;Turn head to toward this old man son way, &quot; you leave!I don't think kill people and want ?only later you don't want again to force I!&quot;The sound fall, he also fly a body horse, flick horsewhip to sail out of the room, can his heart, but is very heavy!
<br />This station provide of ask knife copyright to belong to author cut up rough of small week.Ask a knife details contents, the book review belong to its personal behavior and have nothing to do with the website.
<br /><br />&quot;The west of the road method, how?&quot;The benefit Ao ask a way.
<br />&quot;All right, owner all already the preparation is ready, etc. three boundary passages open and then can go out!&quot;The west of the road method answer a way.
<br />Benefit Ao point nod, &quot;this time go out, don't immediately with they hard put together, dispersed arrive person's boundary much understanding some circumstance, accumulate Zan some real strenght, those absolute beings like dozen and then let they with person dozen go to!&quot;
<br />Road method west point nod, &quot;I be understand.&quot;
<br />&quot;Don't know that person how?&quot;The benefit Ao is light to say.&quot;Don't know, but he gave I a felling, absolute isn't easy to handle, such as not necessity, we temporarily have no a necessity to ask for him!&quot;The west of the road method say.
<br />Benefit Ao point nod, &quot; make the madder thin with he go to dozen, we enjoy a play!&quot;The road method west point head way, &quot; BE, however, absolute being king, she be true of does the meeting and mankind begin?If she also similar to us choice?&quot;
<br />The benefit Ao shake head a way, &quot;can't of, I too understanding she, she would never again under etc. go, I affirmation!&quot;
<br />Road method west point nod, for absolute being Wang2 Qian4 Fei , the benefit Ao is very definite understanding!This he early know, since so, so nothing important problem, be mankind and absolute being Dou after get up, regardless result how, all absolute is beneficial to night boundary!
<br />……
<br />Person's boundary,
<br />&quot;How?&quot;The chaotic is free and unfettered to ask a way.
<br />&quot;All get ready, regardless any circumstance we all the ability cope with!Let them come!&quot;The penknife say.The chaotic is a little bit free and unfettered to nod, &quot;eldest brother didn't°yet news?&quot;The penknife sighed tone, &quot; maple the elder brother still kept coming to, don't know when an ability to rush through back!&quot;The chaotic is a little bit free and unfettered to nod, &quot; eldest brother not at, we also want pair of this is good, we is free and unfettered reside of person!Have confidence for 1:00!&quot;
<br />Penknife point nod, smiled bottom, &quot;boon, in fact, the maple elder brother don't come back, the star elder brother come back all right a point, alas!&quot;
<br />The chaotic was free and unfettered to helplessly shake to shake head, &quot;just say that finish, again so, good, their head quarter come back of, there is confidence for 1:00, difficult way be your thinking them back to see free and unfettered to reside run everywhere by what somebody else humiliate?Or direct have already dismissed?&quot;
<br />The penknife smiled to smile, &quot;stop worrying, all right of!I was just some to miss them!Didn't be certain this time any problem of!&quot;
<br />The smiling face lookinged at penknife face up the self-confidence, the chaotic is free and unfettered smile also a smile.
<br />&quot;To, this you want an attention point elder brother's wife them, although their real strenght be also very strong, absolute can't let them have any mishap!&quot;The chaotic is free and unfettered to say.
<br />&quot;Understand, if even they all protection not, I still how can see maple an elder brother!&quot;The penknife say with a smile.
<br /><br />A the voice which pierce ratio meat remind of, blood light four splash.The sons and daughters of Nan all cannot help but shut up eyes with old companion and treat a long time listen to have no other voice, have of person oddness of open eyes.But go into a purpose, but is not Nan person the head separate, but those two oneself that owner out of the leader all lie on the ground, didn't breathing.
<br />But at this time, Nan front of just station 1 don't calculate emaciated also not calculate big and strong man.Can see a figure in their directions.
<br />But at this time, oneself of father's(grandpa) a face of positive concussion looking at that man.A few son's daughter with biggest age of the in home once and then recognized to come out, that person is to at the beginning arrive at own in home and became an oneself father from the old man of decrepitude many young middle age of person, be also oneself father be the brothers that can mutually give by life in.
<br />The time that Lee together rush through at the right moment see Nan families drive two oneself is in inside in the house, also not worried, since he arrived to the other party to even want to make moves to also in time save up the person bottom.Just that two sons of the Nan dead some wrong, if oneself early come to one step he also at least can't dead.
<br />Saw final reckoning, Nan still the attitude be resolute, Lee together also inwardly admire oneself of good brothers.Afterwards see the other party and descend cutthroat, Lee together just quickly make moves to help each other.
<br />When the Nan think oneself is certain to die, have already shut the time of last eye, but suddenly felling press oneself of hand loose open, but that split to oneself of one knife a slowly fell in.Treat the Nan open a pair of eye, see the time that Lee together and just smile to looking at him, the Nan unbearable old tears maneuver.
<br />Etc.50 year, finally and again see oneself of good brothers.And was oneself to be once and almost put out whole family by the person in this crisis juncture.
<br />Although oneself of two son dead, he for himself of the son feel proud.
<br />Lee together on wave hand, the cordage auto which bind Wang2 Jia's grandchildren untie, public have of come forward to hand Nan, have of rush toward to two sons front of put a voice to cry bitterly.Lee together although know this old two is to fall into a round back, also incapable is a dint.After all with he fix for perhaps return shortage with arrive that hell ghost boundary look for to return to ghost.
<br />The Nan shiver to looking at Lee together, way:&quot;Together elder brother, you finally came, otherwise, I be this old and the young ……&quot;
<br />Lee together comforter way:&quot;Good Nan, you my brothers also say these, hate me come of night some, small good he ……alas!You don't want too sad.&quot;Leave to come to time here in former times rightness three son of the Nan and two daughter still comparison acquaint with, also ability call famous word.
<br />Say, Lee together chop down of ground the knife absorb to come to hand an inside and hold that chop down knife to imitate Fo and return to at the beginning whole day chop down person everyone of year.Remind of that insurance dead wreath living of Jing ground, Lee together more grateful Nan, if have no him, which like now of oneself.
<br />Think, Lee together chop down of the inside of the hand the knife pass to give Nan way:&quot;Brothers, I am that***two oneself to stay, you begin by yourself.Also reckon small good revenge!&quot;
<br />The Nan don't hestitate of once connected to see, turn round facing that two oneself blunt past, that two oneself is together forbidden by Lee, wanting to move can't move and helplessly looking at the Nan take knife to toward oneself connect firm take to see.Not big short while then didn't the breathing was already a dead.
<br />Nan Leng the station of the Leng at at first, the along while just shiver to walk to after oneself already dying of son's in front.At this time, Wang2 Jia's wife have already cry mix past.Pour is Wang2 Jia of the daughter kneel to arrive at Lee together in front and sorrowly say:&quot;Grandpa Li3, you be a fairy, you save my father.His dead have to wrong too much and beg you.Save my father!&quot;Say, the head Ke of an is on the ground, different meeting then the Ke bleed.
<br />Other sons and daughters also all a face of entreaty, a few brothers sister of that Wang2 Jia also all come over entreaty Lee together.Lee together and hurriedly start to hand one by one they and see oneself of brothers the Nan also see toward oneself.Together some Jian Se in Lee, way:&quot;Perhaps difficult!&quot;
<br />Listen to a Lee together tone in of difficult, Nan also know perhaps this matter isn't what Lee together ability do, hence way:&quot;Good, all don't over there give you uncle Li3 to add disorderly.Small good dead of worthy of, is good kind of, we should be proud for him!&quot;Say, the voice sob.
<br />Lee with one mind bottom also sad, see oneself of good brothers such suffered, want at the beginning two people to show the deepest sincerity of time, two people in that time can say is even pants all part each other, joss-stick hot eat together, knife sword together be!Brothers!The this lifetime of person's ability include how many such of brothers?1, foot.
<br />At that moment, Lee together a grind teeth a way:&quot;Good, for the sake of my brothers, the knife mountain fire sea I also want to create, that hell ghost boundary even have difficult to cross, I settle to look for small good psyche back!&quot;
<br /><br />A spool of 100001000 achievement methodses spread Ru absolute being an achievement at the whole body chapter 45
<br />The help of please everyone who like this book recommend and collect~
<br /><br />In the Wang2 Jia public heart a pleased, but close behind Nan way;&quot;Together elder brother, if in danger, calculate, a son didn't, I notted want to throw again lifetime of brothers.&quot;
<br />If Lee together and more listen to Nan, more isn't a taste in the heart.Strong say with a smile:&quot; Nan, my Lee together to you what kind you know farely well, matter concerning you, I when afraid lead dead?&quot;
<br />The Nan whole body be one earthquake, in the eye also gradual bright get up, no longer decline a way:&quot;Good brothers, the joss-stick be hot to eat together and the knife sword be together.&quot;Just because of understanding just needed much speech, this be the brothers.
<br />Lee together know the brute force of Nan came up again, hurriedly way:&quot;I tell you, you can prohibit to go to with me.My dead don't be only, this isn't my own body, for you throw also no harm.But you with I go to but is certain to die, return will implicate me.You the dead body which need to think ° to be good your son at home would be!&quot;
<br />Once the Nan listen to, originally Lee of the in front together and unexpectedly just 1 divide time, although the exclamation in heart fix Lian boundary of magic, also let go of heart.The Nan know Lee together for the sake of oneself really of may try very hard to, besides 1 divide time, at that moment also no longer much speech, two people's at the beginning imitating Fo be at the beginningeach other of the shadow be similar, that is mutually possibility than each other oneself more understanding the other party.
<br />Lee isn't worried either, way:&quot;Small good new arrive hell ghost boundary, believe to at that time also can't bear again.Not first nasty, I have a friend of immensely resourceful and wait her come I together left for with her, a to is to have to look after, two come to this hell ghost boundary for me also definite don't acquaint with.Have her is can also much tell me more some thing, besides make here so big, you can't also continue life here.&quot;Say, Lee together wanted to think, sought the medicine cream of a Shu mountain sword parties in the body first and give Wang2 Jia's wound on the corpse all 1 F.That wound then with very quick speed instauration, a short while, Wang2 Jia's body's look have already had no wound.There is just no soul.
<br />After, Lee together took out a cake of very cold hard ice in the bracelet again, this hard ice be together Lee of three the time which divide time to leave humble room find out outside humble room of, each divided time to all take some.These can be all expel by mentally dense raw water of miscellaneous quality, though is a miscellaneous quality, but also best of the Lian device anticipated.After all so-called miscellaneous quality is also cent what contrast of, with mentally dense raw water ratio?What water isn't the thing of attribute a miscellaneous quality?
<br />Hard the ice be very cold, if isn't Lee together and hurriedly in the ice of surroundings arrange the 1 F insulate knot boundary, perhaps only this is very cold and then will make Wang2 Jia public moment become ice stick.
<br />Take out cold ice a be one person's much hole, then put into Wang2 Jia's corpse.Seal the exit again after.Then Lee together arranged with the crystal stone in the package a stability of insulate strategies, so algidity can't outside Lou.Then once the big Xiu flick, that absolute being machine absolute being feather oneself also have the function that a part take a person and then take all of the old and the youngs of Wang2 Jia Yi to move disappear in a sudden at at first.
<br />The time again come out, public have already appear inside in a knoll valley in the cluster the mountain, Lee together say with a smile:&quot;Stop worrying, here distance Nan-chou City very far, is already a X province inside of cluster mountain in the middle.You have peace of mind bottom be.&quot;
<br />After, Lee together again control gold of spiritual influence with very quick of the speed <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS1iYXJiYXJpYW4tYXNzYXVsdC1jLTI5XzMzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Fighter torso</a> spend for an hour public constructed a big hospital to Wang2 Jia, inside the house is a lot of.Although just roughly construct, inside of the thing still want to be tidied up by themselves by them with decoration, however Lee together also don't realize, these affairs hand over to them the do-it-yourself good.
<br />Let the descendants of the Nan arrive inside choice oneself of room and decoration, those descendant although to Lee together of magical power big in order to marvel, still very obedient of get into courtyard in the middle beginning choice oneself of house.Lee together seek Wang2 Jia's corpse also a cabin put and stay to treat later come round it to use.
<br />Lee together pull the Nan arrive at a big stone to sit in seat of honor bottom, Lee together ask Nan way:&quot; Nan, I think that letting you take your whole family practice moral teachings, just I also the observation lead, you of these sons and daughters' grandchildrens can be all quite good, just that kind of under the circumstance all have no 1 beg for mercy of.I also trust to let you lead them to fix Lian together.&quot;
<br />Nan exultation, say with a smile:&quot;Good, my children I have a number, all of them is good kind.&quot;
<br />Wanted to think, Lee together also didn't know and should let Nan's 1 fix Lian what group of Xuan achievement, after all now Lee together now in hand of the heart method be too many, at the beginning the appearance of the elder of the transformation other group, for getting dark day mentally dense achievement and big day mentally dense Jue Lee together but all fix of group Lian achievement the method all registered.
<br />Hence, Lee together ask a way:&quot;I haven't a few method door which fix Lian here and you say you to want to fix Lian which kind.&quot;At that moment, Lee together again fix Lian boundary a concerning Fo way an evil affair of three veins to tell to give Nan, and will among them various merit and shortcoming also all will.
<br />Once the Nan listen to and don't hestitate of say to fix Lian an evil door.Oneself be after all and at the beginning black of, now step go into fix true boundary he still like be black of.Besides chop down knife to use to become accustomed to, let him start also a little bit easy.
<br />Lee together wanted to think, the viewpoint of Nan be iner keeping with oneself of fix of big personal enemy&quot;blood knife door&quot; door Lian method, that group be with near body knife war but be known for.Again in keeping with however.
<br />At that moment, Lee together turn over to seek for the beginning.At the beginning Lee together arrangement three at the time that divide time, will among them big part fix to do exercises in gymnastics a method to all put at the gold divide time up, after all he also remember with oneself good brothers of engagement.So for let good the brothers contain a choice and then put an achievement method all at the gold divide time up.
<br />The achievement method is too many, together each bamboo strips in Lee a time seek 1 time to just find out.The Nan see Lee together a person sit stunned over there, also don't bother.Probably led time of half around hour, Lee together and finally found out record blood knife door achievement the bamboo strips of the method.
<br />At the beginning Lee together give the primer heart of the Nan method, the Nan fixed Lian exactly 50 year, although return can't the practical absolute being know, definite already existence.Just no one tell him, also don't know have absolute being the existence for know, always also can't practical.Now Lee together after telling him, his is very quick study will start.
<br />Then Lee together just give him the bamboo strips, let him fix Lian well.Treat attain gold Dan a period to pass his children of bamboo strips again, after Lee together again take out not a few build Ji pill and Cui body pill, these thing Lees together have already notted use top.And at the beginning got in the limits of the earth Cape not a few.
<br />Tell Nan of concrete method of using, after Lee be together not nasty either, anyway part want etc. joss-stick joss-stick to take oneself boundary to the hell ghost.Also conveniently accompany Wang family to live here, everyday in addition to oneself fix Lian be instruction the Wang family fix Lian.In the center even once went out to several times buy some home articles for home others, now of the Earth science and technology again had big leap, if isn't Lee together orientation the ability be a little stronger, perhaps return true some blurred.
<br />Together divide time to Lee to say, fix Lian don't fix Lian all differ not how much, be the body of mentally dense origin, they instinct of ability absorb surroundings in the whole world each attribute spiritual influence, although can fix Lian can speed some speed, also just speed some just.
<br />The Nan foundation after death build Ji to make his groundwork firm for 50 years, now had Lee together of instruction very quick got in to practice spirit period.Lee together take out absolute being Sui Dan, let the Nan take, then protect a method to let him quick Lian to turn for him.The Nan spend three time of month to just turn the absolute being Sui Dan Lian, the real strenght with one action come to an a gold Dan period, Lee together let him take to build Ji pill make stronger once sudden rise of fix for.
<br />Although Lee together want to give the Nan take better Cui absolute being gold Dan, what then now fix of Nan for still shallow, can't take.Such, the Nan also got in to fix Lian boundary on the whole, Lee together hence also let Nan blood knife the achievement method of the door passed his sons and daughters.Don't and tell the Nan let his sons and daughters fix to practice of the time of certain degree build Ji pill to take for them, the Ning practice a true dollar.
<br /><br />A spool of 100001000 achievement methodses are at the whole body chapter 46 again Cheng five line door
<br />Tomorrow on duty, fight for secretly running back to everyone renewal 1~~hope like of friend recommend, collect this book~
<br /><br />After, Lee together at oneself of store bracelet in the middle find out a be rated as the treasure knife of treasure machine, let him give to Nan, Nan immediately excitement of brandish.
<br />A burst of blood light flow out to move and see of the Nan younger generations an eyes emit light.Only the Wang2 Jia's wife female still the noodles have sad one silk to permit, Lee together also know, they are nasty Wang2 Jia's affair.
<br />This day, Lee together and just in the instruction the child son of Nan fix Lian, suddenly heart in on move tell child sub- Wang2 Xin oneself fix Lian.Then moment disappear at at first, but is Lee together felling arrive oneself that disciple step water's being cold be difficult.
<br />Step water is cold just pass soon, the real strenght be big into, then take to begin bottom to again recover to lose ground.Original at the beginning he almost whole inside country underground the influence unify, drive afterwards five line the door be big disorderly just again lose.Now the influence be big into, plused Lee to together put out that five line door of light breeze, immediately start take back original should belong to oneself of thing.
<br />Finally, the nation government again appear publicly an interference.Five lines of door has heart to ignore, but now they in nation the government lead long to pull too deep, want to get away is also not easy.So also can follow come, step water be cold to disappear five line the person of the door O.K., this see arrive immediately a double eye get very angry.
<br />Nation government parties come of big member, step water be cold can reception, and also repeatedly affirmation oneself will not do bane motherland of affair.But the underground real strenght of after all whole nation be too huge now control in one personal hand, difficult protect will appear what confusion.But government section again what then can not step water be cold, want to use troops, frightened step water be cold at that time angry is kill a Beijing leadership, so perhaps will big disorderly.So now be also a dilemma.
<br />And listen to five lines of person of door say, at step back with cold water, station a stronger superior, perhaps be five line the door all take top enemy's house also however.Immediately let the whole government all the earthquake move.
<br />Now again the parties person persuade, also only is effort once just.After all they are still more quite good to the step impression with cold water, several times three a time of seek him to talk, he peeped out impatient, and a time of assurance will not endanger oneself of motherland.But after all his existence be a time bomb, but difficult basically can't tore down in this bomb.
<br />This not, today early in the morning, country Anne department vice minister at five line accompany of door come down seek step water cold.Though the person seen five lines of door step water is cold the facial expression be all right not kind, livinged reception vice minister Chen2 Zhi4 Guo2.
<br />&quot;Chen's minister, I step water be cold already again and again commitment, person of our gratitude alliance will deal with foreign enemy, would never humiliate native common people.If have, detection 1 remove 1.This I already the commitment lead what time, difficult way we nation such don't believe oneself of common people?&quot;Step water be cold to again and sincerely say.After all be the same as one people, his establishment the main purpose of this gratitude alliance also is to deal with foreign enemy, but have never thought nation government such not trust, change to want, he can also comprehension.So also just polite again and again, though the government have already sent five lines of door to deal with himself/herself, step water be cold to still keep mutually treating by gift.
<br />Chen2 Zhi4 Guo2 also know now of oneself nothing important and can say of, after all somebody else the person of the gratitude alliance definite do of quite good, and this leader of alliance also is easy to talk, even the government calculate him, he still to oneself very polite.But this is top of request, he again have to come, can say of wry smile:&quot;This Chen2 Mou3 also know that just the existence of this gratitude alliance always let the party and people is ill at ease.&quot;
<br />Step water be cold and dark to sigh, these words he also listenned to a lot of time.But step water be cold also can't because of this oneself of the gratitude alliance dismiss.Think, step water be cold also some impatient, after all again good temper, drive person such again and again of persuade will also not bear.
<br />The rise see five line door of person, step water be cold unbearable sneer at:&quot;This five lines of door return is really government of bodyguard.&quot;
<br />Four once five lines of disciple facial expression which be responsible for a protection Chen2 Zhi4 Guo2 change, but endure, once Chen2 Zhi4 Guo2 see, know a step water cold and impatient, hurriedly dozen circle field way:&quot;Where where, the Gao of five lines of door people is also for the country for the people work hard at chores for a long time.Step leader of alliance, I that still some affair, returned first, hope leader of alliance good consideration consideration.Don't be being making party and government difficult to do.&quot;
<br />The time been treat Chen2 Zhi4 Guo2 to turn round to leave, die a natural death deathless of that five lines of 4 in of 1's unexpectedly and mercilessly staring a step water be unexpectedly and mercilesslycold one eye.The capability is big to enter of step water be cold to oneself confidence big increase, is about to let out once and ever at five line door be subjected to of have no bag spirit, immediately foot a Deng have already arrived at that pupil front of.
<br />That pupil a surprised, hurriedly raise to tee off a true dollar.Five lines of door fix Lian of is 5 lineses spirit, this pupil major of be good at attack of gold of spirit.The breathing of a gold tee off and take a silk spirited to cut water is cold toward the step.
<br />Step water's being cold also don't avoid being seen, with lend arrogant body direct grasp toward that silk true dollar, although feel one silk ache, remaining power don't reduce of grasp toward the neck of that pupil.
<br />Such near distance, that tee off a breathing root have no time to avoid being seen, drive step water be cold a hold tight neck.
<br />Step water the cold list make an effort and have already lifted pupil in the sky.Other 3 five line door of the person immediately come forward help, step water cold hum 1, list make an effort to lift in hand you of five line door the pupil neck twist into lousy mire, whole all fall because of losing neck at ground up, already dead can't again dead, one ray of light fly from the body of that pupil and send out a burst of hatred poison of point roar.Step water be cold also lazy get realize, turn head with another three people war together.
<br />That baby point roar once after, imitate Fo to just thought of own now be just weak of dollar baby, hurriedly the facing gate to a monastery fly.
<br />Bomb!
<br />Step water cold and other three people record towards put together a, the strength of the explosion fry the whole villa smash, if that Chen2 Zhi4 Guo2 not is have 1 five line tee off of disciple a soil yellow of the spiritual influence of soil perhaps also became ash ash.
<br />Chen2 Zhi4 Guo2 hurriedly run toward the distance to, he know and person Dou of this etc. fairy sort will get up his this ordinary people to be stained with 1:00 and then will become lousy mire.
<br />Step water be cold with one enemy three, unexpectedly tribe leeway, that three good hand which all turn absolute being for middle, at five lines of door be also that the elder is first-degree.Now unexpectedly dozen however a step water be cold and see come to this boy be a capability big increase.
<br />Just at this time, Lee together a Shan body's appear be having already fried into the villa surroundings of ruins, those the gratitude alliance of the escort under charge at the moment is also hide from a distance.
<br />Lee together see oneself of the disciple didn't proceed from a leeway, also joy at leisure in one side, anyway Lee together one day will leave step water sooner or later cold, should also let he whet to practice to whet to practice by himself.
<br />Not big short while, Lee together some sit not to live.Because beyond the horizon fly to a group of person, the dozen be far to know while see as many as 100 people.Step water is obviously cold detection also someone close to, no longer dawdle, whole body evil dollar explosion, dark day mentally dense achievement inside of a set of difficult to understand skill-Huan step then display to open.
<br />This footwork, entry-level after only is exaltation oneself speed, attain medium class degree then ability creation unreal image to confuse enemy, wait until high class, then would only with lend an oneself of move let the other party creation mirage.Fix for the meeting of the Gao drive confuse at that time, fix for low of direct wine cup confuse of lose intelligent, sink into heart evil.
<br />Step water is cold obviously at this Huan step top and bottom lead some kind of effort, at this time use come already creation innumerable unreal image, although return can't creation mirage, also distance not wish.
<br />This one step fell to display to open, the other party three people be immediately in most distressed, the step water cold turn per hit three people's head one pulpy.Also don't spare no one, permissive three cent of the dollar baby leave.
<br /><br />A spool of 100001000 achievement methodses are at five lines of whole body chapter 47 it change
<br />The penknife doesn't fail in mission luckily, finally on duty of the time took advantage of an opportunity to secretly run to come back renewal, HOHO.
<br /><br />Treat the horizon when a group of person fly to it, on the ground just three corpse.Lee together at a help through observation detection, this five line door not Taoist orthodox tradition, but fix Lian of five line it spirit.They can control five line it spirit formation various shape attack, and can also carry on five line escape Shu, also calculate fresh.Decision at that moment and inwardly make five lines of fix of 1 set Lian method a door to come to lo lo.
<br />At this time, that rush through of a group of person be positive present moderate a step water cold confrontation, the leader one person wear a gold hat, wear gold color full-length gown and seem to be very stylish.Step water be cold to say with smile:&quot;Unexpectedly five lines of Zhang door of door also finally showed face!&quot;
<br />Zhang door!Lee together and inwardly pay attention to, then this beginning in the humble room variety Zhang door of the appearance start search memory.After all the gold divide time with all of thises is Lee together, 1 see and then is tantamount to another 1 to see, Lee together nature can variety.
<br />But that at the moment but a full face of angry countenance way:&quot;Step water be cold, I ignore your teacher is which door that parties, but your teacher and pupil two people now kill my door in not a few pupil, true has gone too far in insult.Today I five line door do with you to settle!&quot;That ising main is a detection Lee together now not present, would such the daring talk.Perhaps if Lee together appear, his attitude can't such tough.
<br />Step water's being cold the slightest don't fear to, just sneer at of way:&quot;You not afraid my teacher etc. come down kill light you five line door?&quot;
<br />That a surprised, however also have no a performance to come out.The way just set up for apathy:&quot;How?You is that here?Why not call him come out?&quot;
<br />Step water was cold to just want to talk, a voice already remind of way:&quot;BE who want to see this adult?&quot;Lee together swayed longly to walk to come out from the crowd, wear a gold hat, wear absolute being feather and a gold color full-length gown seem to be particularly noble.
<br />But see in five lines of eyes, doubtless be an evil head!
<br />Zhang door origin want to sound out once, have never thought unexpectedly and really here, immediately heart in the dark way isn't good.Lee together also ignore him and pass to give step water a cold look in the eyes for applaud, then see fix a Lian a way in the middle of the sky toward those:&quot;If I ignore you five lines of door how at the beginning, but since I come, prohibit you be humiliate my Tu son, Fo and I put out your whole family!&quot;
<br />Say, Lee together no longer refrain from rash action body vehemence, that attain medium fairy of the metals fairy work properly it spirit suddenly explosion, strong vehemence immediately will opposite of more than 100 person blunt of together and together retreat, but he flank of step water be cold but the slightest have no Sun.
<br />Lee together that spirit which belong to the mentally dense gold crystal body to let out endless spirited at the moment, surroundings of ground, tree, the rock etc. be all direct change into unreal!
<br />Opposite of five lines of public immediately the felling imitate Fo oneself what to face isn't a person, but a head of fierce Hong Huang huge monster!Strong pressure's imitating Fo to let them carry a mountain is fly, a be all nerveless to fall on the ground, rise's looking at have already rise into the sky of Lee together, a burst of and helpless.
<br />Flank 1 only a turn of spread fairy to shiver of say:&quot;Fairy, fairy!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="96b734f7198c30865c5f179c9767b854" url=""><![CDATA[no the least<br/><br/> a mother-in-law to shake to shake head and sigh a way:&quot;Or just similar, whole have no the least bit amendment.&quot;Public also can not help sob Wan sigh after listen to.
<br />The Heng mountain Zhang door wonderful month teacher mark time too much but, to strange mother-in-law's way:&quot;Chiu's benefactor, this is this door of&quot; nine Jiang bead&quot;, to boxing Zhang internal injury also very valid, might as well let the little Xia try and see.&quot;Say that hold the previous longan size<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS10emhhYXItZmlnaHQtY2F2ZS1jLTI5XzMyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">fire cape</a>  , deep red like the tablet of fire, slowly pass to the strange mother-in-law.
<br />The strange mother-in-law hope toward the wonderful month teacher too, full to overflow grateful feeling on the face, immediately after point nod to show a gratitude.She certainly know that this&quot;nine Jiang beads&quot;s is a daughter difficult beg of treat the medicine expensive treasure.
<br />The strange mother-in-law sigh a way:&quot;The many thanks teacher work properly a medicine too much, but open this boy, perhaps be subjected to needless.At first I with teacher too general idea, see the Zhang in his body harm, think necessarily is harm and internal organs, at that moment give he&quot;return to soul jasper Dan&quot;, but after, whole have no the least bit effect.I then again is him careful check 1, square discover its Zhang harm not severity, main reason, would be his body to band together to accumulate a great deal of cold and damp spirit, but this algidity, at that time can't break up, with the result that Yin spirit lead prosperous, sun spirit shortage, both can't adjust to match with the result that.&quot;
<br />The wonderful month teacher hear too much and connect &quot;return to soul jasper Dan&quot; also whole ineffective, oneself of&quot;nine Jiang beads&quot;, say nothing of.&quot;Nine Jiang beads&quot; though abnormality precious of harm a medicine, but with ability come back from the brink of death of&quot;return to soul jasper Dan&quot; compare, indeed also big haven't equal to.
<br />At the moment son will go to, is exactly a month up the east wall, the hour of the star river Can Can.
<br />Strange mother-in-law's way:&quot;Just I with white the miss repeatedly negotiate, finally think to us a way, just still don't know how result is, anyway, we also get exert once the personnel fight, but can success, is also have never know it number.&quot;
<br />The strange mother-in-law see time a night already, then again way:&quot;Rare everyone the Zhang door be not late and hard working, such the dead hour still rush through to send greetings, old woman in really grateful very.Today everyone Zhang door rare gather head 1, in really and not much get of opportunity, many not if tonight then here lead a night, in case the traffic was weary and tired to return to wild goose shadow door.&quot;
<br />Public listen to her say that have already thoughted of a treatment way, anticipate to a tonight, necessarily would over the night for open salvage.Such see, solid not proper again stay a long while obstruction.
<br />Empty clear way:&quot;Chiu's benefactor need not polite, if isn't a benefactor with little Xia today volunteer to help, again ruin under the platform of explosive, we be this person, early and then fell into the hand of traitor, by that time really spirit luck difficult speech.Now time little Xia drive blood Yan the door contuse, is also because of this matter but, if say a many thanks, should be us this old guy be.&quot;
<br />Wu3 Dang Ban Zhang3's door the long spring be true humality:&quot;The master say a little quite good, say to us didn't°yet with does the small Xia thank.The time connect now harm of little Xia body, we can't also help previous favour, solid teach Za etc. sorry and ashamed have no ground.Great boon not the speech thank, present most important of, would be to cure first good harm of little Xia, ceremonious words also will not mention it.We then this in advance take leave, in case bother Chiu elder generation for the little Xia cure to harm, if the little Xia have what amendment, or want us ability help top what favour, there is vexed elder generation sending a person notice 1 would be.&quot;
<br />Strange mother-in-law though make every effort to request to stay, public is still ceremonious push to thank, also have to forget about it.The white winter snow connect Wu3 Shis with the life reorganization traffic, with line carry to send, and wait for someone with strange mother-in-law to send out front door.
<br />See visitor out to complete, the strange mother-in-law gather together public negotiate in the hall, connect a song according to rhyme also between each seat.
<br />The strange mother-in-law give relief to the method to what white winter snow put forward, 11 detailed and public say.
<br />History two Tang and top officer, all once was subjected to open of favor, all think as long as save open, the Zong go through hell and high water, also regardless the sacrifice.
<br />Listen to later on the strange mother-in-law sigh a way:&quot;Alas!In fact this method, old woman I pole not big approve, but again have no other way, if different try, open this a small life true difficult protect!Now trip so do, can say a right and wrong to can not help, Be just dialogue miss the ? be also true ……&quot;
<br />White winter snow way:&quot; Openned a younger brother to once save my younger sister son Wan Ting is one life, boon in the dialogue house meet not shallow, besides is the future husband of Wan Ting, can also be regarded as families.Besides kid sister after the cultivation&quot;Xuan female mutually the eclipse big method&quot;, to the matter among the men and women, early and then see not and very importance, the time in really save a person by this method now, don't  use to harm a person.If the ability therefore save open younger brother's one life, also be regarded as my[one] contribution, everyone also need not lie bosom for the kid sister, just doing not know this method can can be carried out just.&quot;
<br />The history bright way:&quot;Front the hour history some body be subjected to a body poison of harm, today ability the dangerous spot remaining years of life be also much white the miss don't hesitate sacrifice oneself honor and the battle righteousness give relief to.Miss such the heart clear and big righteousness, besides give up a body to hand Qing, solid make history some admire from the bottom of the heart, don't already admire from the heart.&quot;
<br />The history confession winter snow of two Tangs is their solution to the body poison, after saving to return to one life, early grateful not exert.After empress drive again open extrication from the blood Yan the door the hand, escape from to trap to forbid.This how many times and mutually save of virtuous, even if the powder body ground bone, also difficult recompense deep boon.The history is bright this talk, in really two people heartfelt words.
<br />The white winter snow is tiny on smile, way:&quot;The young girl is solid you do me too much honor, unless oneself practice&quot; Xuan female mutually the eclipse big method&quot;, believe everything to will rewrite to come over.&quot;She slightly move toward song to depend on a rhyme way:&quot;According to rhyme younger sister, I know ? and top officer of relation, now time so do, elder sister true very much obliged, if depend on rhyme younger sister would not like to, then put forward to come to like, never put in the mind.&quot;
<br />The song depend on a rhyme low voice a way:&quot;The elder sister please and don't say so, Liu3 Ge's matter, the winter snow elder sister believe also very clear.Up to now we are two people, didn't°yet the opportunity recompense 12, don't say that is so a matter, would be again dangerous 1000000%, I with Liu3 Ge will be also duty-bound.&quot;
<br />Top officer, Liu3 Dao4, :&quot;Rhyme younger sister well said, today we do of everything, whole is for wear save a person, in no way half cent sexual passion it read aloud, this matter be how sacred.Besides now time the person who save is open, we be more duty-bound.Everyone is Wu3 Lin2's middleman, river lake children, also need not again mother-in-law mother.Now still save a person important, really can't again delay bottom to go to, we be three people, everything then listen to white miss of order BE.&quot;
<br />Public also know what happened condition urgent, then call the small gold plus a few strong screen to separate by make in open the building the view open, return go to light candle, can't make he see white winter snow and three people's scene.
<br />Luckily open intelligent muddled, the brain be all day long muddle-minded, otherwise with his whole body male Hun of inside dint, besides have a night to stare at it an ability, how ability ability deceive him.
<br />When night the strange mother-in-law is still him line achievement, help him to urge to move inside body of true spirit, and want open hold breath Ning spirit, banish miscellaneous read aloud, with all strength display &quot;the universe hole leave a big method&quot;, absorb white winter snow from three Human body top get of sun interest.But white Wan the Ting and Tung be clinging two people, then at open a body a side to stay and wait to help each other.
<br />Open under the public leading, displayed a big method to absorb several times, cold hot inside body of spirit, indeed as expected immediately big reduce, just be depressed painful, also immediately slow Xie.Although he don't know white winter snow to use where the method treat to cure for oneself, F know this method can line, at that moment step up to urge luck inside the interest.
<br />Such led much twoer hour, history two Tang and top officer would be inside the dint again Gao, finally is the Qu of flesh and blood, again how ability consume have no of Jie is bottom go to.
<br />The white winter snow see three people's situation, then namely deadlock come down.Know again open although never complete Kang, life is already is no hindrance.Again remind of open capability once instauration, with his ear eyes such intelligent and severe, certanly will be hard to conceal bottom.The white winter snow call three people in advance take a rest back spirit and need tomorrow again for open medical treatment.
<br />Public see openned an amendment, all sorrow Yu exert eliminate, smile exultation.White Wan Ting and Tung's being clinging be also an all over the face to living a flower, pleased overflow tip of brow.When night two people then treat at open nearby, elaboration care.
<br />???
<br />Clear sky Wei basket, breeze nasty day Gao.
<br />See mountain way both sides, autumn orchid Wei Rui, every where Huang2 Hua gold, along with the autumnal winds, flutter to living Zi.
<br />A Gao Peng2's wagon, along the hill path of Wan Ting hope north but line.The wagon in front and back has more than tens to wear red dress, outside cover with a sable jacket, the waist hang the woman of lance to protect a line.See them all and uniformly ride a black horse, the side of the line Qian of the saddle silver, Pei Yang Lou decoration splendid, abnormality valuable.
<br />These woman ages are very light, and appearance Jiao the United States, with whole person's son which is a Jing to pick sieving.
<br />See a group of people each dress Lyu fresh and clear, the brigade form be tidy, imposing style pound ? .Among this more than ten persons, unique of male, then only a young carter.
<br />Si don't hour cent, this brigade person's horse arrive at a small town, on the town only an avenue, the company spread very few, far far have a teahouse.Say is a teahouse, in fact just wood Peng cover become, put several Zhang Ban3 Zhuo just.
<br />A group of people walk tired, spread a woman voice inside wagon:&quot;The everyone rest a short while start on again.&quot;
<br />On the town of person that once saw person's horse of this etc. imposing style, each see eyes stunned, return way this is what reach officer's magnate, Hao door the person way of the big clan through this place.
<br />Arrive at wood Peng, public toghter float a body to dismount, the car Wei slowly bring about, then see one male one the female come out wagon.
<br />Originally this to men and women not who person, male of unexpectedly is a Hua Mountain parties long door Xiao long breeze, female of would be a day Xi an officer the manager Luo frost Ru.See two people expression intimate, the double double arrive at a Zhang Mu4 Zhuo to sit down, it be like 12 days Xi maid-in-waiting pupil, another line cent sit 3 tables.
<br />But that young groom is exactly a day, the Xi temple protect method Kang to settle breeze and he sit on the wagon from the son, there is no the meaning for stand down.
<br />Small two carry up the tea and drinks, a little bit public some dessert, the dumpling, vegetables meat stuffing a round flat cake, twisted dough-strips...etc. be all some south countryside small food.
<br />The Xiao long breeze Xia one mouthful hot tea, dynasty<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS1iYXJiYXJpYW4tYXNzYXVsdC1jLTI5XzMzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Fighter torso</a>  Luo frost Ru way:&quot;Day Xi temple indeed as expected the temple rules be careful, the light see this sweet shoe clean sock, brocade the dress jade take, then it is thus clear that one spot.Ratio it parties in our Hua Mountain, the whole body Ruo hat long grass shoe, with expensive temple can differ a great deal, in really and mutually the form see Chu.&quot;
<br />Luo frost Ru lightly a smile:&quot;The door of Xiao Zhang's ising true will talk.That's right and the my temple be mostly all woman and have cloud:Jiu head flower Dian all over the face, not if Xu2 Fei Ban4's makeup.Then because the kind be just ugly, want the bead Cui makeup point, this is exactly the gold paint toilet, get surface scene just, again how ability and the Hua Mountain which not and falsely call parties compare.&quot;
<br />The Xiao long breeze ha ha say with smile:&quot;Luo manager is really condescension get tight, the ? see the person of expensive temple, each be beautiful such as flower, ugly one word, how ability say.The besides expensive temple is in this several years, river the lake middleman each Fu Yang, if the soil cow wood horse, that is this class of like line.So-called of 10 necessarily have luxuriant grass;The Yi of ten rooms necessarily have the Jun the private.Think soon future, the expensive temple can not fail to create new style and become prominent group in river's lake.&quot;
<br />Luo frost Ru say with smile:&quot;Prominent this four word, how also dare not to say, the door of Xiao Zhang cried up too much.&quot;
<br />Then suddenly listen to at this time the clop ring, big way top the dust float in the sky, public lift an eye to hope go to, but see a group of person, Ma3 Ji2 Chi2, since then.
<br />Go to before the town, then see a cluster ride Lei to settle, thin number under total have ten ride.Before get one person is that a shape be thin long, the air agile and fierce old, the Yi descend long beard grey, wear a leopard skin coat.
<br />The that old dynasty Xiao long breeze say:&quot;You but the Hua Mountain parties Xiao Zhang door?&quot;
<br />The Xiao long breeze and Luo frost Ru listen to, is not been one Xuan by eyebrows, all miss this person suddenly La La to run, necessarily have no good matter.
<br />Xiao long breeze the station start and embrace a boxing to say:&quot;At bottom would be the Xiao long breeze, don't know how your good self is form of address, seek Xiao some have what business?&quot;
<br />That old loudly way:&quot;We are just a nobody, name then need not much asked.Today is presumptuous to come to bother, just want to grant to lend Guan Hong a Mi book toward the door of Xiao Zhang a read.&quot;This person words voice the Hong be bright and see inside achievement not equal weak, definitely not the unknown person say by him.
<br />The Xiao long breeze hear his speech not kind, clear have no reason strong Suo, very supercilious in the tone seem to be whole don't put oneself in the eye, not from dark think to oneself way:&quot;This person such give big, unexpectedly dare to openly block road to challenge, lo he be this person's shape, seem to become calculate in the chest, have be quasi- have since then, but don't know to be what position?&quot;
<br />The Xiao long breeze ha ha say with smile:&quot;BE to is this since then, no wonder that you Ren sort impoliteness.Mi book then here, you have skill and then come over to take.&quot;
<br />He talk on fall, the saddle previous nine big fellow Shu ground draw out steel knife, turn over a body to dismount and a word row draw before horse.
<br />But that old, but safely sit right away.
<br />The old hear this words, the nature know Xiao long breeze and is say anti- adjust, wish:&quot;This person after all is a Hua Mountain parties Zhang door, effort naturally get, if is in the past, probably still hate you several cent, but yesterday you win five more cartilage tea, although medicine dint already solution, activity such as often, the capability in the body, there are no 34, can't completely instauration come over.
<br />See now, he be the most only have 34 success dint, again afraid you what come.&quot;
<br />The old thought of here and loudly say with smile:&quot;Rare the door of Xiao Zhang be such generosity, old man first at this many thanks, then have a vexed door of Xiao Zhang to take out good.&quot;Words Qi, then to under charge dozen expression of eyes, nine people abruptly go toward outside penny, public surround.
<br />Luo frost Ru sit to say with smile:&quot;The door of Xiao Zhang, this person good living impoliteness, we continue to sample tea's flavor and realize him to make very.&quot;
<br />The Xiao long breeze ha ha on smile say:&quot;The Xiao some nature doesn't want to realize, just this you allow of no I!&quot;
<br />Luo frost Ru's returning to Mou to hope is one eye toward the old and smile the way of Ying Ying:&quot;You is the honored guest of my temple, these from bark up from call of crazy dog, then from we to dozen hair good.&quot;Talk a square over, only 1 which listen to shout, day the Xi temple be 12 female pupil Shu the ground start to sign, immediately after at present green light disorderly Shan, 12 handle lance in the meantime sheath, block before wood Peng.
<br />That old Ju however a surprised:&quot;We this is to seek Xiao long the door talk, with side the person have no stem, more don't want to give offense to a day Xi temple everybody female Xia.&quot;Make reference to here, the vision Shu ground hope toward the Xiao long breeze, cold way:&quot;Is really surprisingly, an open Hua Mountain parties Zhang door, unexpectedly want a group of woman to bump to drive, if spread will go out, perhaps …… ha ha ……&quot;
<br />The Xiao long breeze listen to unknown big move, be suffused with while ascending on the face green, quickly station.
<br />Luo frost Ru jade once the hand lift and clime to him to take a big hand in hilt of a sword, dynasty he be charmingly feminine on smile, say:&quot;The door of Xiao Zhang need not spirit Nu, this etc. wayside crazy dog, again how go together with top the Zhang door make moves in person, still sit down to a Xia tea.&quot;
<br />Liu3 Mei2 Yi Yang empress the words, 12 female the pupil body form Shan move, have already rounded that ten people in the Gai heart, action it quick, be let everybody for it giddy.
<br />Nine big fellow see a red shadow float Huang, at that moment spread out, the formation be a circle and protect the old at central.
<br />Listen to that old look up at sky to say with smile:&quot;Day Xi temple these Wa son door, each all grow fairy to turn a person, all of us be the good brave fellow for cherish pretty girls, you can want caution, never harm and they be, play by that time big lose interesting aspect.&quot;Many big fellow hear and together the voice roar with laughter.
<br />The old come to before and early and then know farely well here.The his Ji Yu is this Guan Hong Mi book and the Xu heart already a long time once how many times sneaked in Hua Mountain to steal as well and all have no achievement but return.
<br />He kept to knew the Xiao long breeze fighting skill, today rare Xiao long breeze poisoned don't pure, is exactly a consumedly of a fair show, remaining the person be extremely not worth mentioning.He also thought of that since the person of the Xiao long breeze and day Xi temple together, if start a hand, the day Xi temple definitely account and can't sit on the sideline ignore.
<br />Rao is such, this opportunity how again the ability sit to lose.Day although the Xi temple fame ring, disciple very few at river lake top appear, how effort is and the person, who know on the way, be really few.
<br />The old see this all of the persons be a young Wa son and would be a door in have what unique learn, with these people's year Chi, by no means Gao Dao4 go there, from don't put them in the eye, as for with Xiao long the breeze together sit of Luo frost Ru, although he don't know how its skill is, also can not consider of so many.
<br />The old see play Dou have already settle at this time, of speech, any further be unlike just respectful sincerely.Looking at this moving young girl again, the sexual desire be tiny to move and speak of words come more unbridled, then and first have some argument of desire, good teach them the heart to save spirit Nu, start a hand come again many the 1 F win number.
<br />After anticipating Luo frost Ru to listen to, not only the spirit stop and think carefree, unexpectedly whole on the face have no Nu idea.
<br />See her tiny and smile slightly and raised to stir on transfering temples, say:&quot;Sister door, they since want to play, then with them play once.&quot;
<br />The words voice fall just, with see 12 silver light suddenly and violently Shan, immediately after the voice of the Zheng Qiang your work, both parties then the Dou will get up.
<br />With see red shadow Huang move, 12 female pupil is divided into 3 sets, each four people, become a sword while ascend, each round three big fellow at central.
<br />That old body form is one Shan and float a body to fall Ma3 Zhan4 in one side.See each young girl, the sword recruit abnormality unusual, fast have no Lun, back to offend to guard to avoid, all match flawless.
<br />Originally this, named&quot;day heart four match a sword method&quot;, can from 1-4 people is, much eacher one person, it power then mostly 100%, if four people connect hand is, the pick of this sword method, more ability exertive arrive thoroughly, formation an abnormality severe&quot;day heart four match a sword&quot;.
<br />This heart four match a sword, the essential points be the Teng of footstep directions to move variety, again match four people such as point such as pare, the sword which offend to guard to with each other repair recruit.While recruiting one type, all the ability system enemy's machine first, the opponent be as soon as cover with by the sword light, unless especially strong superior, sign then to inhibit move can not, in really a difficult to know sword.
<br />This sword method, original non- Ji's house early spread a sword method, is the Mi skill of 200 year ago&quot;more female door&quot;s.
<br />More female door in addition to day heart four match a sword, return to have skill&quot;quickly passing time 13 types&quot; sword method.This sword method essential points, whole with fast for still, it the recruit type is just as its, then such as the quickly passing time lightning flash sort disease soon, and float to suddenly work properly to move, make the person hard to catch to touch.If again the match a day heart four match a sword method, is also a power endless, be rated as is a the one and only of contemporary sword.
<br />But this two Mi skill, don't know why, unexpectedly fall the Xi temple temple lord precious jade Ji hand in day, doubtless then become
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>