<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="22">
		<document id="635009db1f3390db4b15cb6332da687b" url=""><![CDATA[Tool Room - Types of Tool Room Machines, Toolroom Setup<br/><br/>Tool room
<br />Tool room is the room where the tools are kept for storage, prepare, repairing and machining. The space area can be varied based on the types of the tool room machines and applications. Tool room machines may include high end electro-mechanical machineries for different applications like grinding, milling, shaping, slotting of metals. In lower scale, tool room can be defined as a small room to store all tools for servicing and repairing before giving it to the workers for operation. Tool room consisting the big racks, shelves, cupboards and workbench to store and repair the tools. Thus the tool room can have the facilities to design, manufacture and repair the custom machines as on requirements.
<br /><br />Types of Tool room Machines
<br />There are various types of tool room machines are manufactured by the machine tools manufacturing companies. Some of them are available with standard technical specifications as well can be manufactured as per industry specific application requirements. Major metalworking machineries are included in the types of tool room machines. The widely used tool room machines are <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3NwbS1hLWhlYXZ5LW1hY2hpbmUvdG9vbC1hLWN1dHRlci1ncmluZGluZy5odG1s" target="_blank">Grinding machine</a>, milling machines, shaping machine, slotting machine, bandsaw machine and hackshow machine.
<br /><br />Grinding Machine - This machine is categorized further in manual surface grinder, hydraulic cylindrical grinder and centerless grinder. Grinding of metals and other materials are carried out by these machines with manual or hydraulic pressure. The machines are widely used in various industrial applications including engineering, automobiles and electrical.
<br /><br />Milling Machines - Milling machines are used to shape the metals and solid materials as per the defined or custom specifications. The machine is executed manually or automatically based on the types of milling machines that are manual milling machine, mechanical milling machine and digital CNC milling machine for automatic execution.
<br /><br />Shaping Machine - V Belt shaping machine with wide industrial acceptance to cut metals in curvature shape or angularly. The machine strength is high to work on ferrous and non-ferrous metals.
<br /><br />Slotting Machine - Metal &amp; wood slotting is the prime requirements to cut and shape the metal slots on the head of metal and wood to create machine screws, bolts, wood screws and automobile custom parts. Slotting machine with variation from slow to fast execution depends on the types of available slotting machineries in the market.
<br /><br />Bandsaw Machine - This type of tool room machine is specialized for irregular cutting and curving of the metal shapes with precision accuracy. Based on technical features, various bandsaw machines from horizontal to double column are used in industrial applications.
<br /><br />Hackshow Machine - This tool room machine is used in wide range of industries for long time. The metal cutting efficiency of hacksaw machine is unbeatable with high accuracy and precision gathered with hydraulic hackshow machine. Mechanical and semi hydraulic machines are also applied in applications where it needs low pressure.
<br /><br />Toolroom Setup
<br />Tool room setup is the process to setup precision machinery as per the custom prototype machining for the operation, repairing and production. Setting up tool room required highly efficient and skilled execution with plan out the application installations for current and future requirements of tool room machineries. If you are looking for efficient and standard machine tools for the industrial applications, you should visit the state of the art machine tools manufacturing company website - <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a> for further details.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7dab91d2fe68bb44bd008685fff05a52" url=""><![CDATA[Lathe - Types of Lathe, Applications of Lathes, All about La<br/><br/>All about Lathe
<br />Lathes are widely used machine tools in the in the mechanical industries, factories, warehouses and manufacturing units. Lathes are generally applied to metal and woodworking units to shape or cut the workpiece with symmetry on all axis. Lathe rotates the object around the spindle for machining the metal in desired form. Lathe machines are available from small table units to large room units based on the type of industrial application. Based on the type of operation lathes are categorized in manual and automatic CNC controlled (Computer numerical control) machines.
<br />Lathes are designed to machine the metals, thus known as metal lathe, metalworking lathe, toolroom lathe, turret lathe etc. Lathes use tool bits or drill bits to remove the hard material from the rotating workpiece. Lathes are designed for different industrial applications but the basic features remains common. The main parts of lathes are headstock, bed, carriage and tailstock. The various features and functionalities make the lathes use for different types of applications. Modern technology with computing power gives more automization to the mechanical machineries for better functioning with precision and speedy work.
<br /><br />Types of Lathe
<br />Based on the type of machining, different variants of lathe machines are used. Various types of lathes are available in the market based on the machine tool functionality and technology used in manufacturing the lathes.
<br /><br />Center Lathe – Center <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL2xhdGhlLW1hY2hpbmUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">lathe machine</a> with dual head moves towards the fixed positioned workpiece to hole at each end with center drill. This lathe is also known as popular engine lathe or bench lathe.
<br /><br />Toolroom Lathe - Toolroom lathe is used for toolroom machining for quality work that is bit costly than center lathe.
<br /><br />Turret Lathe - Turret lathe is used for repeated production of duplicate parts. Turret lathe perform multiple cutting execution with different cutters. Different turret lathe perform variety of lathe machining.
<br /><br />Gang-tool Lathe - It’s a gang of tools set in a cross slide to index them in linear for each cutting cycle.
<br /><br />Multispindle Lathe - Multiple spindle execution in electronic controlled way for machining can be performed on this type of lathe. Single spindle execution is carried out through screw machine lathe is highly accurate lathe machine with high automization and efficiency
<br /><br />CNC Lathe – It is the most advanced featured and electronically controlled lathe machine for ease of operation with consistent and accurate output. The machine has inherent program for execution as well can be programmed at any point of time for custom execution. It requires very low human intervenes during the operation. CNC lathe is completely automized with computer program and required skilled worker having the knowledge of computer operation to handle the machine. There are many variants of CNC Lathe is available from different manufacturers but the basic elements for production and execution remains same. The variations in computer technology have evaluated different versions of CNC lathe among the manufacturers based on the type of operating system, programming languages and software applications used in CNC Lathe, it requires for workers to be well acquainted with the machine for easy operation. The price of CNC lathes vary based various factors and technology usage in the machine.
<br /><br />Mini Lathe for Home Applications - is a small micro lathe machine for home workshop. This lathe can be installed on a table for simple home machining for small work pieces. These lathes are small in size with high accuracy, precision shaping and cutting at very much affordable rate.
<br /><br />Lathe Machines based on above technologies are further categorized at machine tools manufacturing units based on capacity parameters like height of center, width of bed, maximum swing over bed and slide, maximum swing in gap, size of spindle bore and nose with speed and others. This can give machine variants like light duty lathes, medium duty lathes and heavy duty lathes used in different applications.
<br /><br />Applications of Lathes - Lathe is one of the most used engineering tools for various industries and different applications. Lathes are used to drill hole in any solid material including metals and woods with variable hole sizes. Lathes are used to create irregular metal shape or offset flanged parts with required complexity. Lathe is used to fix a screw thread inside the hole. It is used to derive screw thread on the top of the metal. Lathe machines are used in automobile, repairing shops, tool rooms, workshops of various industries like automobiles, power plants, steel rolling mills, paper, textile and mining industries etc.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c9592840599c5138f044917e23750038" url=""><![CDATA[Lathe FAQ - What is lathe, Types of Lathe, Parts of Lathe, H<br/><br/>Lathe FAQ
<br />Lathes FAQ will give you idea about the lathe machines and queries related to their operations. Here it is tried to describe the common queries and needful information for lathe machines. For further query about the machine tools and their technical specification, you can visit the website - <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a>
<br /><br />What is Lathe?
<br />Lathe is a powerful machine tool to shape or cut the metal and wooden workpiece symmetrically on all axis.
<br /><br />What are the different types of Lathes?
<br />Based on the type of machining techniques and technology, Lathes are defined as center lathe, toolroom lathe, turret lathe, gang-tool lathe, Multispindle lathe, CNC lathe and micro lathe. Center lathe, toolroom lathe, turret lathe, gang-tool lathe are executed mechanically with great human intervention. CNC lathe is computer operated lathe machine with automization for precision work where human presence doesn’t affect the accuracy standards. Micro lathe is available in manual and computerized form for small workshop.
<br /><br />What are the main parts of Lathe and their functions?
<br />Lathe is versatile machine cut the metal in shape of the rotating work piece. Numerous work features can be achieved through turning, facing, boring and parting of the metal. Lathe bed provides stability to the cutter and maintains the alignment of headstocks and tail stock. Headstock keeps the spindle in positioning with lathe bed with motor and power system. The tail stock on right side of the bed holds tool bit for different machining. Central positioned lathe carriage is the platform for machining.
<br /><br />How Operator should handle the Lathe?
<br />Lathe machine needs safety and security while operating as metal or wood machining is a bit risky process and needs high concentration to handle the process cautiously. The lathe machine is well equipped with safety features which must be well understood by operator and systematic trained with built in safety measures before executing the lathe machine.
<br /><br />How to use Lathe for beginners?
<br />Beginners must be trained well before operating the lathe machine independently. Perfect utilization of machine, proper maintenance and take care of safety measures are very much useful for smooth operation of lathe. First warm up the machine and lubricate the parts. Set the zero point with accuracy to start using your tool for machining. On getting the accurate precision shaping of all metal pieces, switch off the machine and put the machine in maintenance mode before leaving the place.
<br /><br />How to Execute Lathe Machining?
<br />Switch on the machine with warm up the spindle rotation at required rpm. Be ready with the cutting tool for the process. Prepare the raw material for shaping and cutting. Fill up the coolant tanks and bottles. Fit the metal piece in the jaws and stop the warmed spindle. Set the zero position for tailstock and turn the machine on. Counter clocking spindle insert the cut from front side and measure the depth of the cut with micrometer. Turn off the machine and remove the workpiece from jaws carefully without touching to the metal piece directly.
<br /><br />Where Lathe Machines can be used?
<br />Lathe machines are used in varies industries like engineering, metal rolling, paper textile and mining, automobile and power houses for woodturning, wood crafts, drilling hole of any size in solid materials, to define screw thread on metal top, regular or irregular shaping and cutting of metals etc.
<br /><br />What Precautions are required for maintaining the lathe?
<br />Stick to the procedure to continue the lathe machining for long. Continuous cleaning and maintenance will keep your machine in good shape. Make a habit to clean the lathe after usage. Clear metal chips scattered around the machine with sharpening the tool bit for next usage and get the accurate machining.
<br /><br />How to Buy Lathe?
<br />First decide the type of lathe you require as per your industrial needs. Consult with more than two machine tools manufacturers to confirm your requirements meeting with the models and the features of that machine, quality of work, work precision and accuracy, safety measures and easy handling. Compare the technical features like lathe RPM and commercials offered by the vendors for best selection. Check the client's experience and post sale support for smooth lathe operations.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="397cd07e975ebeda0ee96f51dbd6b587" url=""><![CDATA[Drill Machine - Types of Drills, Applications of Drill Machi<br/><br/><strong>Drill Machine</strong>
<br />Drill is a machine tool used for  drilling the holes in solid materials like metal and  wood with drill bit or  driver bit. Drills are used in wide range of applications in metalworking,  constructions and woodworking industries. The small drill is used for our  household requirements to make holes on wall and  materials. Drill machines are  available in various sizes and power capacities. Drill is one of the oldest  handy tools used from very beginning of the industrial era.
<br />Types of Drills
<br />  Varieties of drills are  manufactured as per the industrial needs. They are categorized based on  different parameters like manual drills and automatic drill machines. Manual  drills are referred as hand powdered drills used with hand pressure on the  device/material to drill a hole. Manual drill variants are Bow drill, Gimlet,  Breast drill and push drill etc. Automatic drill machines are powered with  electricity or compressed air known as electronic drill and pneumatic drill  respectively. Drilling work is carried out at different locations with various  types of drills including construction drill, wells drill, thermal drill etc.  All drills have different applications of drilling from small to bigger size  hole. 
<br />Pistol grip drill is commonly  used <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL2RyaWxsLW1hY2hpbmUvcGlsbGFyLWRyaWxsLW1hY2hpbmUvYm10LTM4LTQwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">drill machine</a> in our daily work. Right angle drill is used in plumbing and  electrical works. Hammer drill is similar to electrical drill with addition of  hammer action on the same device. Rotary hammer drill is equipped with rotation  mechanism used for drilling in solid constructions. Cordless drills with  inbuilt rechargeable battery power are used where electrical supply is not  reachable for drilling. Cordless drills consume high power. Thus need more  spare batteries on charge during the drilling work to replace effectively on discharge  of installed batteries. 
<br /><br /><strong>Drill Press/Pillar Drill Machine</strong>
<br />  Drill press is the drill machine  that can be stand mounted or fixed with floor or workbench through bolting.  Drill press also known as pillar drill consist base, column, table, drill head  and spindle. This bench drill use induction motor supply to execute the  drilling operation faster with small or bigger drill bit. Drill press is quite  lighter and efficient for operator compare to h and drill. The clamping of drill  press makes the convenient positioning of drill machine for precision and  accurate drilling operation. 
<br />Radial Drill Machine
<br />  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL2RyaWxsLW1hY2hpbmUvcmFkaWFsLWRyaWxsLW1hY2hpbmUvdi1iZWx0LWRyaXZlbi5odG1s" target="_blank">Radial drill machine</a> with geared  head put up press on large area without repositioning the work piece. Radial  arm drill press is manufactured with several dimensions of drill head and  varying base plate. Radial drill machine vary in capacity is used in different  engineering and industrial work. Different thickness and size of drill bits are  used here to drill from small to large size holes. Radial drill machines are  very much popular and widely used in automotive, workshops and garages. 
<br /><br /><strong>Drilling cum Milling Machine</strong>
<br />  Drilling cum <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9taWxsaW5nLW1hY2hpbmUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">milling machine</a> is  used for both drilling and milling operation. This lighter machine is having  great option of milling capabilities to save the space including the added  functionalities of shaping the materials. 
<br /><strong>Applications of Drill Machines</strong>
<br /><br />The basic function of drill  machine is to create hole of different size in solid materials. Different  drills are used for industry specific applications. Drill rigs are used to  drill water wells and oil wells. Hand drills are used for screwing and  fastening. Electrical pistol grip drill is used in common masonry works by  builders, electricians and plumbers. Hammer drill is specifically used by carpenters  to drill and fix the wooden parts. Cordless drills are useful where electrical  supply is not possible to get for drilling. Pillar drill machine (also referred  as drill press) is used in commercial applications where it required bulk  production of drilled materials in various size and shape like metal sheets,  plastic, wood, glass and concrete construction applications. The induction  based power supply is easily controlled in drill press to increase or decrease  the drilling speed and capacity. The capacity of drill press differs with  pillar diameter, spindle nose, spindle travel, spindle speed and electronic  motor used in the machine. Radial drill machines are widely used in automobile,  printing and engineering field to increase the durability and tensile strength  of the machine with effective execution to the resistive materials with quality  performance. Milling cum drilling machine is broadly adopted in the industries  where required mixing and grinding of solid and liquid substances.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5a9febd5a0edb29c8956aba101cdfcf" url=""><![CDATA[Drill FAQ - What is Drill, Types of Drills, Drill Bits, Safe<br/><br/>DRILL FAQ
<br />Drill FAQ will give you idea about the types of drill machines and their various industrial applications. Here it is tried to describe the common queries and needful information for drilling machine. For further query about the machine tools and their technical specification, you can visit the website - <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29t" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a></a>
<br /><br />What is drill?
<br />Drill is a machine tool used with cutter device like drill bit to drill various size of holes in solid materials like metal, wood and concrete etc.
<br /><br />What are the available types of drills?
<br />There are various types of drills such as manual hand operated drills like bow drill, gimlet, breast drill and push drill. Electrical drills are pistol grip drill, hammer drill, cordless drill, drill press, radial drill and drilling cum milling machine.
<br /><br />What are drill bits?
<br />Drill bits are the cutting tools used to create cylindrical holes in solid materials. Drill bits are held in the drills to get torque on rotation which creates holes.
<br /><br />What are the types of available drill bits?
<br />There are various types of drill bits used in Industrial applications. Universal drill bits are used to make holes in wood, metal, plastic and others. There are different variants of universal bits like twist drill bits, step drill bit, unibit, hole saw etc, Metal drill bits as the name suggest, is used in metalworking for drilling. Variants of metal drill bits are center and spotting drill bits, core drill bit, countersink bit, ejector drill bit, gun drill bit, indexable drill bit etc. Wood drill bits are used for drilling in wood with different types of bits includes lip and spur drill bits, wood spade bits, spoon bits, forstner drill bits, center bits, auger bits, gimlet bits and adjustable wood bits etc. There are other bits used for different materials like diamond core bits, masonry drill bits, glass drill bits, PCB drill bits etc.
<br /><br />Where Pillar drill machines are used?
<br />Pillar drill machines are used to drill the solid materials with different sizing capacities ranging from 13mm to 40mm. Additionally pillar drilling machine is used for tapping, screwing, counter boring, lapping etc. Easy installation and smooth operation with this type of drill press have made it more popular in commercial usage.
<br /><br />Where Radial drill machines are used?
<br />Radial arm to drilling machine increase the operation versatility. Drilling of large and heavy metals and solid materials are executed quite systematically with accuracy and precision. The high quality steel machine parts, drilling column, arms and geared work head increase the tolerance capacity of the machine. This heavy capacity radial drills are used where it needs to bear high drilling resistant for drilling heavy metals with precision work ranging from 25mm to 40mm.
<br /><br />Why to use all Geared radial drill machine?
<br />This is the advanced radial drill machine and used in the industries where required high performance and precision drilling. The machine equipped with gears can greatly handle and adjust the speed of spindle to enhance the drilling accuracy with high drilling force. This machine is used with auto feed and fine feed to drill 40mm, 45mm drilling capacities in metalworking industries.
<br /><br />Where to use Drilling cum milling machine?
<br />This two in one combo function machine is used for drilling as well milling and other machining like slotting and tapping. This high performance multi tasking drill machine is used where multiple job work needs to be done by a single operator occasionally or frequently.
<br /><br />What are the safety measures one must take during drilling operation?
<br />Drill machine is one of the risky instruments during drilling execution. Several precautionary measures can prevent the accidents like always use holding device to fix the work piece from being escaped. Don’t shake/adjust the work piece while drilling is on. Use brush to clean the drilled matter to avoid burn. Keep any of the flammable material away from the drilling place. Hold the drill machine straight during drill cutting. Keep the drilling table clean during and after the process. One must use face protector to protect face and eye during drilling. Drilling must be careful to avoid breakage of drill bits that can harmful to the operator. Check the drill bits and drill machine well before operation. Drill bits must be sharpened.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8b2763a943e53408bd87d046baf2121f" url=""><![CDATA[Machine Tools - Grinding Machine<br/><br/>Machine tools are the machines used for various processing  work on different metals. Machining works like cutting, grinding, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9zaGFwaW5nLW1hY2hpbmUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">shaping machine to shape the metal</a> workpiece,  boring, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9zbG90dGluZy1tYWNoaW5lLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">slotting on metal through slotting machine</a>, shearing and others are carried out by mechanical and electronic tools  are known as machine tools. Previously in 18th century before the industrial  revolution, the machineries were made from the wood. The bulk production with  precision accuracy evolved the mechanism to define metal parts from cast iron  and wrought iron but still there are were limitations of hammering and to  create required pressure on metal works. Gradually the further inventions as  per the requirements for machining evaluated the old wooden or metal  machineries to their existing form passing through several stages Previously manual  pressure are used for machining tools that can be transformed to electrical  pressure and mechanical pressure later on as the electricity invented. Earlier  machine tools used flywheels with gears and levers for controlling the machine.  After the mid age of twentieth century Numerical controlled machineries and  then CNC machineries were evaluated for better machining. &lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Grinding Machine</strong>&lt;br&gt;<br />Grinding machine is used to grind the metal and other  materials. This machine tool is well recognized as a Grinder in the Industries.  This machine consist the abrasive wheel, the rolling wheel used as a cutter. It  cuts the metal in chips. The importance of this machine tool is to make the  finishing of metal work piece by grinding the small chips from metal surface.  The process through which the grinding machine removes metal is called as  abrasion. Heat gets produced during this process. It requires coolant to cool  down the metal piece.&amp;nbsp; Various <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3NwbS1hLWhlYXZ5LW1hY2hpbmUvdG9vbC1hLWN1dHRlci1ncmluZGluZy5odG1s" target="_blank">types of grinding machines</a> are used in different industrial applications.&lt;/p&gt;<br /><br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Belt grinding </strong>– This grinding machine is used for grinding  wood and metals to finish, debar and material removing.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Bench Grinder</strong> - manual machine tools used for finishing  operation consisting two wheels of different grains.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Cylindrical grinder</strong> - with multiple grinding wheels to  create cylinder shape of metal. Precision tubes, rods and bushing are generated  through this grinder. &lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Surface Grinder </strong>- Most commonly grinder with manual use or  CNC operated surface grinder. The work piece movement in back and forth grinds  the surface of metal piece&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;There are many other types of grinder like tool and cutter  grinder, jig grinder and gear grinder used to grind metal piece for different  applications
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="48768bd8af712e2f166db965c012081" url=""><![CDATA[Press Brake – Uses of Press Brake, Types of Press Brake<br/><br/>&lt;p&gt;Press brake is an important tool which is widely used in cutting metals in various shapes and sizes. It helps in forming predetermined bends in metal sheets by clamping the material between matching punch and a die. Thus, a &lt;a title=&quot;press brake&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fpress-brake.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/press-brake.html</a>]press brake[/url] uses some kind of force to bend or shape the metal in a particular form. The shapes formed in the metal with the help of press brake are extremely accurate but it also depends on the kind of die used and ability of the operator. Press brake is a wonderful asset to any workshop, provided it is used correctly. If the press brake is not operated in an effective manner, the result may be not accurate and the end product produced will be of low quality. The combination of the right kind of punch, die and knowledge of the operator can enable a press brake to give an accurate output.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Uses of Press Brake</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Press brake is used in the manufacturing process of various housing products, automobiles, heavy equipments etc., where bending of metal sheet is required. The metal sheet once bended or shaped out of press brake is used in various manufacturing industries producing products used in our day to day life. The press brakes are available in various sizes to handle sheets of various sizes and thicknesses. Depending on the size and the thickness of the sheet metal, the type of press brake is used.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Types of Press Brake</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;There are various types of press brakes available like mechanical press brake and &lt;a title=&quot;hydraulic press brake&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fpress-brake%2Fhydraulic.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/press-brake/hydraulic.html</a>]hydraulic press brake[/url]. Mechanical press brake enables easier overloading but doesn’t enable the operator to adjust the stroke level while the process is in continuation. One has to complete the process and then adjust the stroke length. A skilled operator is required to use mechanical press so that precision in the end product can be achieved. In 1970s, the hydraulic press brake started replacing mechanical press brake because of its affordable costs and safety advantages. However, using hydraulic press brake resulted to high quality products manufacturing which benefited many manufacturing units. Due to this, hydraulic press brake became popular amongst all the press brake machines available in the market.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The mechanical press brake is made of iron whereas, hydraulic press brake is made of steel. As the hydraulic press brake is made of 100% steel, its structure is much more firm than a mechanical press brake. This eliminates the built-in stress in a hydraulic press brake and so the machine can be used for the longer period of time.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Hydraulic press brake uses hydraulic system, which is much more superior than a mechanical system as its power output is stable and its repairing services can be found locally.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;In hydraulic press brake, there are two cylinders controlling the beam’s vertical moving.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Hydraulic press brake under the CNC system can be controlled by the computer which results into accurate and fast production.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;In hydraulic press brake, the gauge is controlled by the electric device with the digital panel in the front. So, you can enter the data or manually adjust according to the aiming point.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;So, now if you are planning to buy a press brake, make sure that you read the manual and go through its features and after that only you can decide the type of press brake to be purchased. Always go for a perfectly designed press brake which consumes less power and incurs low maintenance costs. For more information on durable and user friendly press brakes.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3203bbec18d4afcc7ee586415cd410e2" url=""><![CDATA[Lathe Machine – How to Use Lathe Machine?<br/><br/>&lt;p&gt;Basically, a &lt;a title=&quot;lathe machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine.html</a>]lathe machine[/url] is a tool used to shape metals. In lathe machine, the material is rotated in the cylindrical motion and then touches a cutting tool to it which cuts the material. The metal sheet is fixed on the chuck of the lathe machine and then the chuck rotates in the vertical direction as well as right and left direction and touching byte’s tip to the material to cut the metal. The original lathe machine when invented used to complete tasks like cutting cylindrical metal sheets and then it was further developed to produce screw threads, tapered work, drilled holes, knurled surfaces, and crankshafts. The modern lathe machines available nowadays, offer the facility of rotating speeds as well as adjusting manually and automatically the cutting tool in the lathe machine. There are different types of lathe machines available like light duty lathe machines, medium duty lathe machines, heavy duty lathe machines, extra heavy duty lathe machines, all geared lathe machine, imported lathe machine, &lt;a title=&quot;CNC lathe&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine%2Fcnc-lathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine/cnc-lathe-machine.html</a>]CNC lathe[/url] machine, roll turning lathe machines and many more. No matter what type of lathe machine it is, you need to follow the below given basic instructions while using it.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;You need to ensure that the lathe machine should not be started cold. First of all, warm up the lathe machine for 10 minutes, setting its speed up to 1000 rpm. The lathe machine should also be well lubricated and you need to check all the tools and ensure that they are tight.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Now, the tool holder should be located and tool block should be inserted in it. The spot is supposed to be located in the tool block where you can insert a cutter. Also for safety reasons, you need to tighter the tool block as tighter as you can. The cutters allow the users to cut from left to right, which is also known as cutting on a Z axis.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The tail stock is to be located where drill chuck can be inserted. The tail stock is very useful as it helps in drilling holes in the metal. The crank at the end of the measuring device helps in performing precision depths to the cuts.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The next step would be to set your zero and stop the turning spindle. You need to get a tool holder and put in at least 0.5 inch block between the tip of your tool and the metal sheet. Slide the tool holder in and out on an X axis to tighten it. The micrometer wheel should be set to zero.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Also you need to set your X zero point by pulling the Z axis tool towards the spindle and slide 0.5 inch block between the tool and the work piece. You also need to set the X axis micrometer to zero and turn the wheel 0.5 inch away.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;So, now if you want to cut 0.5 inches from the metal sheet keep X axis and Z axis both 0.25 inches away from the metal sheet and then start the spindle.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Safety Measures to be Taken While using a Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;You need to get dressed correctly by rolling your sleeves above the elbow. Also remove rings and watch if you have worn.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Before making any adjustments to the tools of the lathe machine, always remember to stop the machine.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Spindle speeds should not be changed until the lathe machine has come to a complete stop.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Always wear protective eye glasses before operating a lathe machine.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;While the metal sheet is turning, never try to measure the cut.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Never lean on the lathe machine.&lt;/li&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8cce25cd36f5169f77c53affa9257554" url=""><![CDATA[Types of Lathe Machines – Light Duty Lathe Machine, Medium<br/><br/>&lt;p&gt;A lathe machine is an important machine tool in a workshop as it is basically used to shape the metal articles. Initially the basic operation of a &lt;a title=&quot;lathe machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine.html</a>]lathe machine[/url] was to cut cylindrical metal stock which was then further developed to produce screw threads, tapered work, drilled holes, knurled surfaces and crank shafts. A standard lathe machine provides a variety of rotating speeds and a facility to manually and automatically move the cutting tool into the work piece. &amp;nbsp;The workshop owners and the workers should be thoroughly familiar about the different lathe machines and its operations to accomplish the jobs of cutting, shaping and fabricating metal sheets. So below given are the different types of lathe machines used for different applications and you can choose one for your workshop according to the nature of the job to be completed.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Light Duty Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Light duty lathe machines are generally lathe machines of small size with a swing of 10 inches or less, mounted to a bench or table top. The light duty lathe machines are made of quality tested material and is used in electronic, electrical and automobile industries. The light duty lathe machines can be used in almost all machining jobs but may be limited due to the size of the material that can be turned.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Medium Duty Lathe Machines</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The medium duty lathe machines consist of a strong bed casting made of close grained cast iron. Even under high pressure and heavy load, these medium duty lathe machines can give best performance without vibrations. These medium duty lathe machines can be used in different industrial and mechanical applications like turning, shaping, facing, boring and threading of all kinds of metals. It has been successful in performing many difficult tasks of metal cutting and shaping in many manufacturing units.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Heavy Duty Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a title=&quot;heavy duty lathe machines&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine%2Fheavy-duty.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine/heavy-duty.html</a>]heavy duty lathe machines[/url] are manufactured from highest grades of material like iron and steel. This type of lathe machine is designed for performing many tasks efficiently like screw cutting, sliding and surfacing operations. The heavy duty lathe machine has dimensional accuracy due to which it ensures high tensile strength and longer service life. Moreover, heavy duty lathe machines are quite easy to install and operate.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Extra Heavy Duty Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Extra heavy duty lathe machines are considered as highly efficient lathe machines which are used in steel &amp;amp; paper mills, oil country, ship building, power plants, mining and textile industries. This type of lathe machine is available in various models of different technical specifications referring to type of bed, length and width of bed, lead screw diameter etc. Extra heavy duty lathe machines are manufactured using high grade durable material which enables it to have a long service life. Moreover, extra heavy duty lathe machines are well known for their low maintenance, long working life and accuracy in performance.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Roll Turning Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The roll turning lathe machines are suitable for extra heavy duty jobs like sliding, surfacing and screw cutting jobs. These roll turning lathe machines are dimensionally accurate, abrasion resistant, corrosive resistant and has high tensile strength. It can be used to its full capability because it embraces great toughness, ample power &amp;amp; control to drive the carbide tipped machine tools.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>All Geared Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;All geared lathe machines are used in different operations such as sanding, drilling, cutting, etc. Moreover, all geared lathe machines are further categorized as light duty all geared lathe machine, medium duty all geared lathe machine, heavy duty all geared lathe machines as extra heavy duty all geared lathe machine. All geared lathe machines work with excellent accuracy, perfection and smoothness. If maintained properly this type of lathe machine can work round the clock.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>CNC Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;CNC lathe&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine%2Fcnc-lathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine/cnc-lathe-machine.html</a>]CNC lathe[/url] machines are well known for higher production and lower costs. Moreover, it fulfils the requirement of quick results with high quality in many industries like electrical, automobiles, electronics etc. CNC lathe machines are highly used for manufacturing high quality components or parts as it operates with the help of a computer program. Therefore, it enables production of large quantities with less effort.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="58ff56be20740ffcd6bcbabd6e01cf81" url=""><![CDATA[How to Install Milling Machine – Horizontal Milling Machin<br/><br/>&lt;p&gt;A <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9taWxsaW5nLW1hY2hpbmUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">milling machine</a> is a workshop tool used to shape solid materials like metal, wood, plastics etc. A milling machine is different than a lathe machine because in a lathe machine the material to be cut moves, whereas in the milling machine, the cutting tool moves at a high speed. Basically milling machines can be classified into various types like horizontal milling machines, vertical milling machines, turret milling machines and CNC milling machines. Before knowing how to install a milling machine, it would be better to have some information about different types of milling machines as given below:-&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Horizontal Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Horizontal milling machine consists of overhead arm supports and cutters that are arbor driven. This type of milling machine is cost effective as it produces only high quality material. A horizontal milling machine requires less manpower which reduces the manufacturing cost of the material. A horizontal machine is an excellent workshop tool which provides several years of efficient performance. It just needs to take care of properly and proper steps should be followed while using it which will keep it in best condition for years altogether.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Vertical Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9taWxsaW5nLW1hY2hpbmUvYWxsLWdlYXJlZC9hbGxnZWFyZWR2ZXJ0aWNhbC5odG1s" target="_blank">Vertical milling machine</a> is just similar to horizontal milling machine in terms of performance and production of quality material. These both machines differ only because of the spindle axis orientation. Moreover, vertical milling machines are cheaper than horizontal milling machines and so are quite popular.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Universal Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The universal milling machine machines can be fitted with various attachments to enhance their operations. The indexing fixture, table swivel housing, rotary table, rack cutting attachments etc., are some of the attachments that can be made to the universal milling machines.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Turret Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9taWxsaW5nLW1hY2hpbmUvdHVycmV0LW1pbGxpbmcvaW1wb3J0ZWQtdHVycmVudC1taWxsaW5nLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">turret milling machine</a> can be repositioned at any time making this machine versatile and very functional. The versatility of the turret milling machine makes it more practical as many different kinds of materials can be produced with the help of turret milling machine&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;All the above types of milling machines can be further categorized to manually operated milling machines as well as computer operated milling machines which are also known as CNC milling machines. The CNC milling machines have many advantages as they give fast and accurate results. However, the steps to be followed while installing a milling machine depends on the milling machine you have purchased. If you have bought a milling machine from a reliable supplier of machine tools, then you will get a manual which specifies the steps to be followed while installing the machine you have purchased. Below mentioned are the common steps to be followed for installing a horizontal or vertical milling machine:-&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;For shipping purposes, the hand cranks are inverted to face the machine. To reverse them, engage the lock mechanism to saddle and table.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Lower knee approximately.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Withdraw the safety pin on the left-hand side of ram adapter.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Loosen the four unite head mounting bolts.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Support unit head manually and use a spanner on swivel bolt to wind into upright position.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Press the safety pin back to the ram adapter after passing the 25 degree mark.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Tighten the four unit head mounting bolts to a diagonal sequence.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Besides these installation steps, you need to follow some safety measures which are given below:-&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Wear safety shoes and glasses.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Follow safety instructions given in the manual.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Keep all your body parts away from moving parts.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Use proper point of operation safeguarding.&lt;/li&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a21ac85619b19f11b85ecdc027905902" url=""><![CDATA[Slotting Machine – How Does a Slotting Machine Work, Types<br/><br/>&lt;p&gt;A slotting machine is a machine which is used to slot materials made of metal and wood. A &lt;a title=&quot;slotting machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Ftool-room-machines%2Fslotting-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/tool-room-machines/slotting-machine.html</a>]slotting machine[/url] can make slots on heads of screws, bolts and other automobile components as well as other similar parts. The main purpose of a slotting machine is to shape and cut hard materials like metal and wood. The slotting machines are generally used in heavy industries like electrical, construction, furniture, automotive etc. Slotting machines are considered as heavy duty robust machines specially designed for quick and accurate metal productions. The slotting machines are well known for their high performance, low maintenance cost and longer functional life. Slotting machine is one of the important machine tools in the sheet metal industries as well in electrical, furniture and construction industries. The slotting machine is also known as vertical shaper consisting of base, column and table, ram and tool head assembly, saddle and cross slide, rams drive mechanism and feed mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Specifications of a Slotting Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The slotting machine is designed in such a way that it is of high standards, uniform and systematic. To elaborate, we can say that it has reasonable arrangement suiting to construction. While using it is quite convenient and easy to maintain.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The electric equipment of a slotting machine is suitable for 3 phases and A.C. power.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The slotting machine is just perfect for small batch production shop as well as the work shops where large production at high speed is required. It is used in various processes, model surfaces, key seating etc., of any workshop.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>How Does a Slotting Machine Work?</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The slotting machine can take up all the cutting forces because its base is rigidly built. The vertical column of the slotting machine has a front face and has guide ways in the reciprocating ram. That reciprocating ram supports the tool head to which the tool is attached. The material is mounted on the table which can be given horizontal and vertical rotary feed motion.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Types of Slotting Machines</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;There are two types of slotting machines available, standard slotting machine and &lt;a title=&quot;deluxe slotting machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Ftool-room-machines%2Fslotting-machine%2Fdeluxe.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/tool-room-machines/slotting-machine/deluxe.html</a>]deluxe slotting machine[/url]. Standard slotting machine is a heavy duty machine which removes metal from large castings and the deluxe slotting machine is designed with extra features and to work on high speeds than a standard slotting machine.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Applications of Slotting Machines</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The main applications of slotting machines are cutting keys, slots, metal sheets, grooves of various shapes and forming regular or irregular shapes used in many manufacturing units. The slotting machine can be used in any workshop where vertical tool movement is necessary and required to manufacture different metal objects.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>How to Select a Slotting Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;If you need to buy a slotting machine for your workshop, make sure that you buy from a reliable and reputed &lt;a title=&quot;tool room machines&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a>]tool room machines[/url] supplier offering slotting machines with significant features like durability, sturdy structure, spontaneous functional ability etc. The slotting machine should be manufactured from best raw materials and using latest technology. Ensure that you buy only technically advanced slotting machines so that your workshop manpower is safe and can perform at its best.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d484ec338407da2336448315fc3f3ccb" url=""><![CDATA[What is Press Brake?<br/><br/>Press brake is an important tool which is widely used in cutting metals in various shapes and sizes. It helps in forming predetermined bends in metal sheets by clamping the material between matching punch and a die. Thus, a &lt;a title=&quot;press brake&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fpress-brake.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/press-brake.html</a>]press brake[/url] uses some kind of force to bend or shape the metal in a particular form. The shapes formed in the metal with the help of press brake are extremely accurate but it also depends on the kind of die used and ability of the operator. Press brake is a wonderful asset to any workshop, provided it is used correctly. If the press brake is not operated in an effective manner, the result may be not accurate and the end product produced will be of low quality. The combination of the right kind of punch, die and knowledge of the operator can enable a press brake to give an accurate output.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Uses of Press Brake</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Press brake is used in the manufacturing process of various housing products, automobiles, heavy equipments etc., where bending of metal sheet is required. The metal sheet once bended or shaped out of press brake is used in various manufacturing industries producing products used in our day to day life. The press brakes are available in various sizes to handle sheets of various sizes and thicknesses. Depending on the size and the thickness of the sheet metal, the type of press brake is used.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Types of Press Brake</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;There are various types of press brakes available like mechanical press brake and &lt;a title=&quot;hydraulic press brake&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fpress-brake%2Fhydraulic.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/press-brake/hydraulic.html</a>]hydraulic press brake[/url]. Mechanical press brake enables easier overloading but doesn’t enable the operator to adjust the stroke level while the process is in continuation. One has to complete the process and then adjust the stroke length. A skilled operator is required to use mechanical press so that precision in the end product can be achieved. In 1970s, the hydraulic press brake started replacing mechanical press brake because of its affordable costs and safety advantages. However, using hydraulic press brake resulted to high quality products manufacturing which benefited many manufacturing units. Due to this, hydraulic press brake became popular amongst all the press brake machines available in the market.&lt;/p&gt;<br /><br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The mechanical press brake is made of iron whereas, hydraulic press brake is made of steel. As the hydraulic press brake is made of 100% steel, its structure is much more firm than a mechanical press brake. This eliminates the built-in stress in a hydraulic press brake and so the machine can be used for the longer period of time.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Hydraulic press brake uses hydraulic system, which is much more superior than a mechanical system as its power output is stable and its repairing services can be found locally.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;In hydraulic press brake, there are two cylinders controlling the beam’s vertical moving.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Hydraulic press brake under the CNC system can be controlled by the computer which results into accurate and fast production.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;In hydraulic press brake, the gauge is controlled by the electric device with the digital panel in the front. So, you can enter the data or manually adjust according to the aiming point.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;So, now if you are planning to buy a press brake, make sure that you read the manual and go through its features and after that only you can decide the type of press brake to be purchased. Always go for a perfectly designed press brake which consumes less power and incurs low maintenance costs. For more information on durable and user friendly press brakes, visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29t" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a></a>.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8b52a670b1e903c31238defdde4133f7" url=""><![CDATA[How to Use Lathe Machine?<br/><br/>Basically, a &lt;a title=&quot;lathe machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine.html</a>]lathe machine[/url] is a tool used to shape metals. In lathe machine, the material is rotated in the cylindrical motion and then touches a cutting tool to it which cuts the material. The metal sheet is fixed on the chuck of the lathe machine and then the chuck rotates in the vertical direction as well as right and left direction and touching byte’s tip to the material to cut the metal. The original lathe machine when invented used to complete tasks like cutting cylindrical metal sheets and then it was further developed to produce screw threads, tapered work, drilled holes, knurled surfaces, and crankshafts. The modern lathe machines available nowadays, offer the facility of rotating speeds as well as adjusting manually and automatically the cutting tool in the lathe machine. There are different types of lathe machines available like light duty lathe machines, medium duty lathe machines, heavy duty lathe machines, extra heavy duty lathe machines, all geared lathe machine, imported lathe machine, &lt;a title=&quot;CNC lathe&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine%2Fcnc-lathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine/cnc-lathe-machine.html</a>]CNC lathe[/url] machine, roll turning lathe machines and many more. No matter what type of lathe machine it is, you need to follow the below given basic instructions while using it.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;You need to ensure that the lathe machine should not be started cold. First of all, warm up the lathe machine for 10 minutes, setting its speed up to 1000 rpm. The lathe machine should also be well lubricated and you need to check all the tools and ensure that they are tight.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Now, the tool holder should be located and tool block should be inserted in it. The spot is supposed to be located in the tool block where you can insert a cutter. Also for safety reasons, you need to tighter the tool block as tighter as you can. The cutters allow the users to cut from left to right, which is also known as cutting on a Z axis.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The tail stock is to be located where drill chuck can be inserted. The tail stock is very useful as it helps in drilling holes in the metal. The crank at the end of the measuring device helps in performing precision depths to the cuts.&lt;/li&gt;<br /><br />&lt;li&gt;The next step would be to set your zero and stop the turning spindle. You need to get a tool holder and put in at least 0.5 inch block between the tip of your tool and the metal sheet. Slide the tool holder in and out on an X axis to tighten it. The micrometer wheel should be set to zero.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Also you need to set your X zero point by pulling the Z axis tool towards the spindle and slide 0.5 inch block between the tool and the work piece. You also need to set the X axis micrometer to zero and turn the wheel 0.5 inch away.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;So, now if you want to cut 0.5 inches from the metal sheet keep X axis and Z axis both 0.25 inches away from the metal sheet and then start the spindle.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Safety Measures to be Taken While using a Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;You need to get dressed correctly by rolling your sleeves above the elbow. Also remove rings and watch if you have worn.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Before making any adjustments to the tools of the lathe machine, always remember to stop the machine.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Spindle speeds should not be changed until the lathe machine has come to a complete stop.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Always wear protective eye glasses before operating a lathe machine.&lt;/li&gt;<br /><br />&lt;li&gt;While the metal sheet is turning, never try to measure the cut.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Never lean on the lathe machine.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;For more information on lathe machines, please visit our website <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29t" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a></a>, where you will get information about various types of lathe machines available.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4cb3ed50fb3cc4c2dc9e2412f141a1fe" url=""><![CDATA[Types of Lathe Machines<br/><br/>A lathe machine is an important machine tool in a workshop as it is basically used to shape the metal articles. Initially the basic operation of a lathe machine was to cut cylindrical metal stock which was then further developed to produce screw threads, tapered work, drilled holes, knurled surfaces and crank shafts. A standard lathe machine provides a variety of rotating speeds and a facility to manually and automatically move the cutting tool into the work piece. &amp;nbsp;The workshop owners and the workers should be thoroughly familiar about the different lathe machines and its operations to accomplish the jobs of cutting, shaping and fabricating metal sheets. So below given are the different types of lathe machines used for different applications and you can choose one for your workshop according to the nature of the job to be completed.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Light Duty Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Light duty lathe machines are generally lathe machines of small size with a swing of 10 inches or less, mounted to a bench or table top. The light duty lathe machines are made of quality tested material and is used in electronic, electrical and automobile industries. The light duty lathe machines can be used in almost all machining jobs but may be limited due to the size of the material that can be turned.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Medium Duty Lathe Machines</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The medium duty lathe machines consist of a strong bed casting made of close grained cast iron. Even under high pressure and heavy load, these medium duty lathe machines can give best performance without vibrations. These medium duty lathe machines can be used in different industrial and mechanical applications like turning, shaping, facing, boring and threading of all kinds of metals. It has been successful in performing many difficult tasks of metal cutting and shaping in many manufacturing units.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Heavy Duty Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br /><br />&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a title=&quot;heavy duty lathe machines&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine%2Fheavy-duty.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine/heavy-duty.html</a>]heavy duty lathe machines[/url] are manufactured from highest grades of material like iron and steel. This type of lathe machine is designed for performing many tasks efficiently like screw cutting, sliding and surfacing operations. The heavy duty lathe machine has dimensional accuracy due to which it ensures high tensile strength and longer service life. Moreover, heavy duty lathe machines are quite easy to install and operate.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Extra Heavy Duty Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Extra heavy duty lathe machines are considered as highly efficient lathe machines which are used in steel &amp;amp; paper mills, oil country, ship building, power plants, mining and textile industries. This type of lathe machine is available in various models of different technical specifications referring to type of bed, length and width of bed, lead screw diameter etc. Extra heavy duty lathe machines are manufactured using high grade durable material which enables it to have a long service life. Moreover, extra heavy duty lathe machines are well known for their low maintenance, long working life and accuracy in performance.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Roll Turning Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The roll turning lathe machines are suitable for extra heavy duty jobs like sliding, surfacing and screw cutting jobs. These roll turning lathe machines are dimensionally accurate, abrasion resistant, corrosive resistant and has high tensile strength. It can be used to its full capability because it embraces great toughness, ample power &amp;amp; control to drive the carbide tipped machine tools.&lt;/p&gt;<br /><br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>All Geared Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;All geared lathe machines are used in different operations such as sanding, drilling, cutting, etc. Moreover, all geared lathe machines are further categorized as light duty all geared lathe machine, medium duty all geared lathe machine, heavy duty all geared lathe machines as extra heavy duty all geared lathe machine. All geared lathe machines work with excellent accuracy, perfection and smoothness. If maintained properly this type of lathe machine can work round the clock.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>CNC Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;CNC lathe&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine%2Fcnc-lathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine/cnc-lathe-machine.html</a>]CNC lathe[/url] machines are well known for higher production and lower costs. Moreover, it fulfils the requirement of quick results with high quality in many industries like electrical, automobiles, electronics etc. CNC lathe machines are highly used for manufacturing high quality components or parts as it operates with the help of a computer program. Therefore, it enables production of large quantities with less effort.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;If you are in search of more information about lathe machines and different types of lathe machines in order to select a lathe machine just suiting to your workshop requirement, then visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29t" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a></a>, there you will find lathe machines made of high quality lathe machine accessories providing high performance and incurring low maintenance cost.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ed30f9cb200f25f1f889f93dcb644412" url=""><![CDATA[How to Install a Milling Machine?<br/><br/>A milling machine is a workshop tool used to shape solid materials like metal, wood, plastics etc. A milling machine is different than a lathe machine because in a lathe machine the material to be cut moves, whereas in the milling machine, the cutting tool moves at a high speed. Basically milling machines can be classified into various types like horizontal milling machines, vertical milling machines, turret milling machines and CNC milling machines. Before knowing how to install a milling machine, it would be better to have some information about different types of milling machines as given below:-&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Horizontal Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Horizontal milling machine consists of overhead arm supports and cutters that are arbor driven. This type of milling machine is cost effective as it produces only high quality material. A horizontal milling machine requires less manpower which reduces the manufacturing cost of the material. A horizontal machine is an excellent workshop tool which provides several years of efficient performance. It just needs to take care of properly and proper steps should be followed while using it which will keep it in best condition for years altogether.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Vertical Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9taWxsaW5nLW1hY2hpbmUvYWxsLWdlYXJlZC9hbGxnZWFyZWR2ZXJ0aWNhbC5odG1s" target="_blank">Vertical milling machine</a> is just similar to horizontal milling machine in terms of performance and production of quality material. These both machines differ only because of the spindle axis orientation. Moreover, vertical milling machines are cheaper than horizontal milling machines and so are quite popular.&lt;/p&gt;<br /><br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Universal Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The universal milling machine machines can be fitted with various attachments to enhance their operations. The indexing fixture, table swivel housing, rotary table, rack cutting attachments etc., are some of the attachments that can be made to the universal milling machines.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Turret Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9taWxsaW5nLW1hY2hpbmUvdHVycmV0LW1pbGxpbmcvaW1wb3J0ZWQtdHVycmVudC1taWxsaW5nLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">turret milling machine</a> can be repositioned at any time making this machine versatile and very functional. The versatility of the turret milling machine makes it more practical as many different kinds of materials can be produced with the help of turret milling machine&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;All the above types of milling machines can be further categorized to manually operated milling machines as well as computer operated milling machines which are also known as CNC milling machines. The CNC milling machines have many advantages as they give fast and accurate results. However, the steps to be followed while installing a milling machine depends on the milling machine you have purchased. If you have bought a milling machine from a reliable supplier of machine tools, then you will get a manual which specifies the steps to be followed while installing the machine you have purchased. Below mentioned are the common steps to be followed for installing a horizontal or vertical milling machine:-&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;For shipping purposes, the hand cranks are inverted to face the machine. To reverse them, engage the lock mechanism to saddle and table.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Lower knee approximately.&lt;/li&gt;<br /><br />&lt;li&gt;Withdraw the safety pin on the left-hand side of ram adapter.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Loosen the four unite head mounting bolts.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Support unit head manually and use a spanner on swivel bolt to wind into upright position.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Press the safety pin back to the ram adapter after passing the 25 degree mark.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Tighten the four unit head mounting bolts to a diagonal sequence.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Besides these installation steps, you need to follow some safety measures which are given below:-&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Wear safety shoes and glasses.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Follow safety instructions given in the manual.&lt;/li&gt;<br /><br />&lt;li&gt;Keep all your body parts away from moving parts.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Use proper point of operation safeguarding.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;If you need help or want to know more about milling machine, visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29t" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a></a>.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eea21ffd7a989336bde8f7e7ff3a29dc" url=""><![CDATA[All About Slotting Machine<br/><br/>A slotting machine is a machine which is used to slot materials made of metal and wood. A slotting machine can make slots on heads of screws, bolts and other automobile components as well as other similar parts. The main purpose of a slotting machine is to shape and cut hard materials like metal and wood. The slotting machines are generally used in heavy industries like electrical, construction, furniture, automotive etc. Slotting machines are considered as heavy duty robust machines specially designed for quick and accurate metal productions. The slotting machines are well known for their high performance, low maintenance cost and longer functional life. Slotting machine is one of the important machine tools in the sheet metal industries as well in electrical, furniture and construction industries. The slotting machine is also known as vertical shaper consisting of base, column and table, ram and tool head assembly, saddle and cross slide, rams drive mechanism and feed mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Specifications of a Slotting Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;ul&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The slotting machine is designed in such a way that it is of high standards, uniform and systematic. To elaborate, we can say that it has reasonable arrangement suiting to construction. While using it is quite convenient and easy to maintain.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The electric equipment of a slotting machine is suitable for 3 phases and A.C. power.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The slotting machine is just perfect for small batch production shop as well as the work shops where large production at high speed is required. It is used in various processes, model surfaces, key seating etc., of any workshop.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;/ul&gt;<br /><br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>How Does a Slotting Machine Work?</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The slotting machine can take up all the cutting forces because its base is rigidly built. The vertical column of the slotting machine has a front face and has guide ways in the reciprocating ram. That reciprocating ram supports the tool head to which the tool is attached. The material is mounted on the table which can be given horizontal and vertical rotary feed motion.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Types of Slotting Machines</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;There are two types of slotting machines available, standard slotting machine and &lt;a title=&quot;deluxe slotting machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Ftool-room-machines%2Fslotting-machine%2Fdeluxe.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/tool-room-machines/slotting-machine/deluxe.html</a>]deluxe slotting machine[/url]. Standard slotting machine is a heavy duty machine which removes metal from large castings and the deluxe slotting machine is designed with extra features and to work on high speeds than a standard slotting machine.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Applications of Slotting Machines</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The main applications of slotting machines are cutting keys, slots, metal sheets, grooves of various shapes and forming regular or irregular shapes used in many manufacturing units. The slotting machine can be used in any workshop where vertical tool movement is necessary and required to manufacture different metal objects.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>How to Select a Slotting Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;If you need to buy a slotting machine for your workshop, make sure that you buy from a reliable and reputed &lt;a title=&quot;tool room machines&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a>]tool room machines[/url] supplier offering slotting machines with significant features like durability, sturdy structure, spontaneous functional ability etc. The slotting machine should be manufactured from best raw materials and using latest technology. Ensure that you buy only technically advanced slotting machines so that your workshop manpower is safe and can perform at its best.&lt;/p&gt;<br /><br />&lt;p&gt;For more details on slotting machines, visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29t" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com</a></a>.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a0bdae172595f2fdd080ae752a76f679" url=""><![CDATA[History of Milling Machine<br/><br/>Rotary filling was the first in base of  invention of the first milling machine that reduced the efforts need to put on  hand filling and save the time. The development history of milling machine is  still unclear as the variety of custom machines performing the functions of  milling machine were available in individual shops and factories before. Rotary  milling was the ancestor of first milling machine. Milling machine is a unique  machine tools first manufactured during 1814 to 1818 in two federal armories of  the USA.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p align=&quot;justify]James Nasmyth is the famous name who built the advanced milling machine during 1829 to 1831, ahead of it’s time to mill the six  sides of hex nut. Gay &amp;amp; silver also used a prototype of milling machine for  vertical milling which was a better method than earlier milling versions. Till  then milling machine was a part of production machine and not toolroom  machines. &lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p align=&quot;justify]1840 to 1860 was the era of designing for  successful milling machine by Lincoln Miller. Different companies were making  the milling machines on the common configuration. George S. Lincoln &amp;amp;  Company first put the true commercial milling machine in the market on 1855.  Based on the company, the name to machine was given as milling machine.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p align=&quot;justify]Brown &amp;amp; Sharpe’s were the first to make  universal milling machine in 1861, which was unique in design and function  itself. This patented machine the milling cutters use to sharpen the teeth did  not change the form geometry.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p align=&quot;justify] Joseph W Roe, the founder of many machine tools  has created the first <strong>true milling machine</strong> in co-ordination with Eli Whitney,  the private arm maker during 1912 to 1916. Robert S. Woodbury and other  scholars had improved the design and functioning of the Roe’s first true  milling machine. Robert Johnson, Cap. John H. Hall, Simeon North, Roswell Lee  and Thomas Blanchard are the few names of researchers and engineers who had  contributed in development and improvement in the previous type of milling  machine. &lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p align=&quot;justify]From 1870 to the mid of twentieth century till  first world war, the various other forms of milling machines came into  existence like <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3NwbS1hLWhlYXZ5LW1hY2hpbmUvdG9vbC1yb29tLW1hY2hpbmVzL21pbGxpbmctbWFjaGluZS5odG1s" target="_blank">universal milling machine for tool room</a>, jobbing and production  use.&lt;br&gt;<br />After World War I, new advanced versions of  milling machines including jig machines and milling machine with CNC technology  have come up with various milling features and functionalities.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p align=&quot;justify]  For further details about different types of  machine tools including milling machines, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3NwbS1hLWhlYXZ5LW1hY2hpbmUvdG9vbC1yb29tLW1hY2hpbmVzL3NoYXBpbmctbWFjaGluZS5odG1s" target="_blank">metal shaping machines</a>, grinding machines, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3NwbS1hLWhlYXZ5LW1hY2hpbmUvdG9vbC1yb29tLW1hY2hpbmVzL3Nsb3R0aW5nLW1hY2hpbmUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">standard slotting machines</a> and their model features with functionalities, visit – <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%26lt%3B%2Fp%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com&lt;/p&gt</a>;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="22ca0327a57715332c5cbf75c3d66ad0" url=""><![CDATA[Installing Machine Tools in your Workshop<br/><br/>&lt;p&gt;A machine tool is a power driven equipment designed to drill, bore, grind or cut metal or other material. A tool is employed to complete the process of cutting, shaping or drilling in a machine tool to get jobs done quickly and accurately. In ancient times, the machine tools were controlled by human force but now machine tools work with the help of electrical or hydraulic force. A certain kind of cutting or deformation is done with the help of machine tools. All the machine tools have specific type of working which provides a guided movement to the parts of the machine to achieve the shape of the material required. The machine tool controls the relative movement between the work piece and the cutting tool which is also known as toolpath. To be precise, machine tools are the machines which help people in making things. The machine tools play an inevitable role in a factory or any construction unit. Thus, machine tools are required to make things work faster, easier and the most important is to generate accurate output.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;A workshop is a place where different machines are used to cut, shape and drill various materials like metals, plastics, wood, glass etc. The decision of installing machine tools for your workshop depends on the process you would like to carry out. There are some specific machine shop processes like turning, drilling, shaping, grinding, milling etc., and you need to install machine tools depending on the process to be carried out in your machine shop. For example, if you need to shape metals in your workshop, then you need to install a lathe machine and if you need to drill holes into any material, then you need to install a drilling machine. But before installing different types of machine tools in your workshop, you need to understand their specifications and applications which are given below:-&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Lathe Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;A lathe machine is considered as the most important machine tool in any workshop as it used to shape metal which is the most important process when any metal product is to be manufactured. Initially, a lathe machine was used to cut cylindrical metal stock but now it is also used to drill holes, tapered work, screw threads etc. There are different types of lathe machines like <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL2xhdGhlLW1hY2hpbmUvY25jLWxhdGhlLW1hY2hpbmUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">CNC lathe machines</a>, light duty lathe machines, heavy duty lathe machines etc. for various applications requiring fabricating metal. Every workshop has a different job to be done, and so the lathe machine for a machine shop is chosen accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Milling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Just like lathe machine, a milling machine is also used to cut and shape solid materials like metal, wood and plastics. But, a milling machine is different than a lathe machine because in lathe machine the material moves in order to give a specific shape whereas, in milling machine the cutting tool moves at a high speed. Basically, there are two <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL3Rvb2wtcm9vbS1tYWNoaW5lcy9taWxsaW5nLW1hY2hpbmUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">types of milling machines</a> manually operated milling machines and computer operated milling machine which gives ultimately accurate results. The milling machine you need to choose depends on the process your workshop requires to accomplish.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;<strong>Drilling Machine</strong>&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;The drilling machine, as the name suggests is used to drill holes in the solid material like metal and wood. Drill machine is an essential machine tool of any workshop as it is used in wide applications in various industries like construction, woodworking and metalworking. Different types of drilling machines are available but basically it can be categorized into manual drilling machines and automatic drilling machines. Manual drilling machines are operated with hand power whereas <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iaGF2eWFtYWNoaW5ldG9vbHMuY29tL2RyaWxsLW1hY2hpbmUvcGlsbGFyLWRyaWxsLW1hY2hpbmUvYm10LTM4LTQwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">automatic drill machines</a> are powered with electricity. All the drilling machines can be applied wherever small to bigger size holes need to be formed.&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Besides, the above mentioned machine tools there are various other machine tools for workshop like power press, grinding machine, sheet bending machine, slotting machine etc., which can be found in almost all the workshops. So, the machine tools you need to install in your workshop depends on the output required. Installing best machine tools in your workshop becomes necessary when accurate output is required. So, to enable proper flow of work, just collect the information about all the machine tools available at bhavyamachinetools.com and decide on which machine tools to be installed in your workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a03c124d889267d5b69a6490e189979f" url=""><![CDATA[How Lathe Machine Operates?<br/><br/>A lathe machine is a tool used in workshop which spins a block of material to perform various operations such as cutting, turning, facing, threading, sanding, knurling, drilling or deformation such as metal spinning with tools that are applied to the work piece to create an object which has symmetry about an axis of rotation. The lathe machine holds a piece of material between two rigid supports called centers, or by some other device such as chuck or faceplate which revolves about the center line of the lathe. In a lathe machine, metal is removed from the work piece using a hardened cutting tool, which is usually fixed to a solid moveable mounting also known as toolpost which is then moved against the work piece using hand wheels or computer controlled motors. The lathe machines which are controlled by the computer are known as CNC lathe machine used for mass production of parts. The lathe machines are commonly provided with a variable ratio gear train to drive the main leadscrew which enables different pitches of threads to be cut. Some older gear trains in a lathe machine are changed manually by using interchangeable gears with various numbers of teeth, while more modern or elaborate lathes have a quick change box to provide commonly used rations by the operation of a lever. To better know about &lt;a title=&quot;how a lathe machine operates&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine.html</a>]how a lathe machine operates[/url], it is necessary to undergo the details of the components of a lathe machine as given below:-
<br />Headstock
<br />The headstock includes the main spindle, speed change mechanism and change gears. It is required to make a headstock as robust as possible because of the cutting forces involved during the process of cutting or shaping metals using a lathe machine.
<br />Spindle
<br />The main spindle is generally hollow to allow long bars to extend through to the work area, which reduces preparation and waste of material. The spindle then runs in precision bearings and is fitted with some means of attaching work holding devices known as chucks or faceplates. This end of the spindle will also have an included taper, usually morse to allow the insertion of tapers and centers.
<br />Electric Motor and Gear Box
<br />The lathe machines use a gear box which is driven by a dedicated electric motor. The fully geared head in the gear box allows one to select the speed through the gear box.
<br />Bed
<br />The bed is a stationery base in a lathe machine which is connected to the headstock. It allows the carriage and tailstock to get aligned parallel with the axis of the spindle.
<br />Feed and Lead Screws
<br />The feedscrew is a long driveshaft that allows a series of gears to drive the carriage mechanisms. Like feedscrew, the leadscrew is driven by either the change gears or an intermediate gearbox known as quick change gearbox.
<br />Carriage
<br />The carriage holds the tool bit and moves it longitudinally or perpendicularly under the control of the operator. The carriage can be moved manually by the operator or automatically if the feedscrew is engaged with the carriage feed mechanism.
<br />Cross Slide
<br />The cross-slide stands atop the carriage and has a leadscrew that travels perpendicular to the main spindle axis, to perform permit facing operations.
<br />Compound Rest
<br />The compound rest is also known as top slide which is the part of the machine where the tool post is mounted. The axis of compound rest can be adjusted independently of the carriage or cross slide.
<br />Tailstock
<br />The tailstock is placed opposite to the headstock and directly mounted on the spindle axis.
<br />So, now when you have the information about how lathe machine works, if you want to &lt;a title=&quot;buy a lathe machine&quot;href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine.html</a>]buy a lathe machine[/url] to complete the processes at your workshop with accuracy then just visit bhavyamachinetools.com and view the specifications and details of various types of lathe machine which will help you to select just the right one to accomplish your metal shaping and cutting jobs quickly and accurately.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c81a586d6240e561f7d8ecd3d530ae76" url=""><![CDATA[How Power Press Operates?<br/><br/>A power press is a machine which converts metals into miraculous shapes. Various products like brackets, frame pieces, electronic enclosures etc., can be manufactured using a power press. There are many different types of power press machines like &lt;a title=&quot;C type power press&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fsheet-metal-machine%2Fpower-press%2Fc-type.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/sheet-metal-machine/power-press/c-type.html</a>]C type power press[/url] and pillar type power press which can be further classified into mechanical power press and hydraulic power press. Due to the advancement in technology, the power press has also undergone many changes. One of the most popular power press available today is the CNC power press having PC based controllers. But, the most commonly used power press is the &lt;a title=&quot;mechanical power press&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fsheet-metal-machine%2Fpower-press%2Fc-type.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/sheet-metal-machine/power-press/c-type.html</a>]mechanical power press[/url] which includes a moving ram used shape as well as bend metals and a stationery bed or surface where the material to be shaped can be placed. The power press punches the material, forms the material, bends the material, shapes the material using combination of different dies attached to the moving ram and bed. To transmit power into the press, clutch is used. The clutches remain engaged until the power press completes the full cycle. High accuracy in bending and shaping metals is provided by a power press. Besides the above working of a power press, you also need to have information about the basic setup procedure required for a power press as given below:-
<br />&lt;ul&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;The basic thing to be considered is the material thickness and the output expected. You need to review the drawing which specifies the type, dimensions and the angles required. This is very much important to determine the type of tooling and dies to be utilized in a power press.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;The tonnage should be determined which depends on the bending method.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;There should be accuracy in the positioning in tooling which is very important to achieve accuracy in the output.&lt;/li&gt;
<br /><br />&lt;li&gt;The parameters should be adjusted depending on the job to be completed. However, this requires trained and efficient operators. But, with the advancement of the machineries, this can be done by even untrained operators too.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;It is always recommended to do a test bend of the material in order to detect if further adjustments are to be done.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;/ul&gt;
<br />After knowing the above working of the power press and the setup process, it becomes necessary to know about the safety measures required to be taken while operating a power press. A power press if not maintained and operated properly can cause accidents which should be avoided using below mentioned safety measures.
<br />&lt;ul&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;The power press and its guards, control systems, ancillary equipment like automatic feed system should be maintained properly so that it doesn’t put people at risk.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;The maintenance work on the power press should be carried out when the machine is completely switched off and should be done by people who possess right skills and knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;Proper training should be provided to the operator responsible of operating the power press.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;The people operating the machine, supervisors and managing the use should be made aware about the specific safety measures to be taken while using power press through written instructions.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;The power press should be regularly and thoroughly examined by the competent person and ensured that it is sound and working in proper condition.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;It is always recommended to keep the record of the maintenance activities performed at a power press to ensure that the power press has been properly maintained.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;/ul&gt;
<br />As far as health and safety is concerned, it becomes very much necessary to follow the above mentioned steps in a workshop using a power press. The purpose of thorough examination and test of a &lt;a title=&quot;power press machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fsheet-metal-machine%2Fpower-press%2Fc-type.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/sheet-metal-machine/power-press/c-type.html</a>]power press machine[/url] before operating is to determine whether the power press and its parts have been installed properly, whether it is safe to operate and whether there are any defects which could make a power press unsafe to operate. Moreover, the law requires that the power press installed in your workshop is maintained properly which will also includes that your employees operating or maintaining power press have adequate knowledge and skills required to complete the job.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c8b18ad0c5cf39a7c040eefa2e2874b" url=""><![CDATA[Significance of Lathe Machine for Metal Shaping Industries<br/><br/>There is no doubt in saying that necessity is the mother of all inventions. All the machines are invented with a single purpose and that is to reduce labour work and get things done quickly. In ancient times, giving shapes to metal was a tedious job and time consuming process. The invention of lathe machine made the job of metal shaping much easier. Basically, a lathe machine is used to remove the unwanted part from the metals to give it a new shape. The material is rotated against the tool which trims down the material into shape. In olden times, lathe machine was operated manually but the machine got many innovative improvements after that. The technological changes brought many versatile changes to a lathe machine. There are many products which we use in our daily life using metals of different shapes and sizes. The production of all these products has been possible only due to a lathe machine. Every other industry is influenced by the lathe machine as it can even perform the complicated process of shaping metals. To manufacture any metal product, the basic requirement is to shape it and that is possible only due to a lathe machine.
<br />Elements of a Lathe Machine
<br />Generally, a lathe machine provides a variety of rotating speeds and different features which can enable manual and automatic controls for moving the cutting tool. There are various &lt;a title=&quot;types of lathe machines&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine.html</a>]types of lathe machines[/url] available like light duty lathe machine, medium duty lathe machine, heavy duty lathe machine, extra heavy duty lathe machine etc. No matter which lathe machine you choose, suiting to your job requirements, below are the common elements which are present in every lathe machine as given below:-
<br />Chuck – is used to hold the work piece and can be replaced with Jacobs chuck or centre for alternative work holding.
<br />Tailstock – is used to hold and located the tail centre and can be unlocked and slid towards the chuck.
<br />[Tail centre– is used to hold the end of long pieces of work, as the small lengths can just be held in the chuck. Centre can be removed and replaced with Jacobs chuck and drill and the advance wheel rotated to drill the work.
<br />Tool Post – is used to hold the cutting tool in a precise location.
<br />Cross Slide– it runs on the bed rails and has a mounting for the tool post which can be driven forward by the tool post advance wheel to bring the cutting tool on to the work peice.&lt;/p&gt;
<br />Cross Slide Advance[/b] – It is used to move the cross slide and tool post sideways and hence the cutting tool towards and away from the chuck.
<br />Drive pulleys and belts– are used to achieve various speeds by varying the belt position on the pulleys.
<br />[b]How to Choose a Lathe Machine?
<br />&lt;ul&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;As you know there are various types of lathe machines available having different features, you need to select as per your job requirements. For example, an average hobbyist would choose a light duty lathe machine which is small in size but if a metal work shop requires a lathe machine, then it would definitely go for an extra heavy duty lathe machine or a &lt;a title=&quot;CNC lathe machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine%2Fcnc-lathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine/cnc-lathe-machine.html</a>]CNC lathe machine[/url].&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;It is very much important to consider the bed capacity before selecting&amp;nbsp; a lathe machine as it depends on the material on which you require to work on.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;The core to any lathe machine is the spindle. The spindle comes in standard as well as non-standard sizes. So, you need to choose the spindle size depending on the metal shaping project you are working on.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;li&gt;Never go for cheap lathe machines, as you may end up &lt;a title=&quot;buying lathe machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine.html</a>]buying lathe machine[/url] consisting non-standard parts which are not going to last longer period of time.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;/ul&gt;
<br />&lt;p&gt;However, it is always advisable to buy lathe machine from a reputed manufacturer of machine tools like bhavyamachinetools.com to get better and accurate results which can save your time and money both.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d98827340068e1b450e7cc0dc376da42" url=""><![CDATA[Types of Machine Tools You Need to Install in Your Workshop<br/><br/>A workshop is a place where different kinds of machines and machine tools are employed to make, finish and repair machines or machine parts. Machine tools are the important requirements without which no workshop can function. Workshops can be found in diverse industrial and commercial establishments. Every workshop has a diverse requirement and depending on where and why the workshop is installed different kinds of machines tools are employed in it. However there are some basic machining equipment that are required in most of the workshops. Majority of the workshops where some kind of metal or wood materials are worked upon, machine tools for tasks like grinding, milling, drilling, cutting, shaping and finishing are most required. Therefore if your workshop is also one of these kinds of commercial or industrial workshop involving metal or woodwork, then opting to install the below mentioned machine tools will serve your purpose better.
<br />Lathe Machine
<br />To accomplish the jobs of cutting, shaping and fabricating metal sheets in your workshop, nothing can be much better than a lathe machine. With a lathe machine in your workshop you could handle a wide range of applications including production of symmetrical parts, screw threads, tapered work, drilled holes, knurled surfaces and crank shafts easily and efficiently with a single machine without having to install in number of machines used for each individual task. Moreover most of the lathe machines today come with a variety of rotating speeds and automatic cutting features. Therefore with an advanced lathe machine in your workshop you can accomplish your machining tasks much faster and to a better accuracy. Lathe machines are available in different forms today like light duty lathe machine, medium duty lathe machine and &lt;a title=&quot;heavy duty lathe machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Flathe-machine.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/lathe-machine.html</a>]heavy duty lathe machine[/url]. For installment in your workshop you can either go with light or medium duty machines which will give you efficient functioning for small scale machining requirements in your workshop.
<br />Milling Machine
<br />Milling machine is another variant of machine tools one could opt as metal cutting machinery for workshop. A milling machine is the best tool for cutting metals to the customized dimensions and shapes especially if the parts are to be cut or shaped to rectangular or uneven dimensions.
<br />Drill Machine
<br />While machining, repairing or making machine parts in a workshop one may require creating cylindrical holes on the solid materials. A drill machine is the apt machinery for the purpose. With an &lt;a title=&quot;advanced drill machine&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fdrill-machine%2Fpillar-drill-machine%2Fbmt-38-40.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/drill-machine/pillar-drill-machine/bmt-38-40.html</a>]advanced drill machine[/url] in your workshop you can very effectively carry out the hole making processes on metals and other solid materials with ease and much accuracy. Various other tasks like tapping, spot facing, reaming, counter sinking and counter boring can also be carried out efficiently with the help of these drill machines. Drill machines come in various models, customized dimensions of drill head, base plate and capacity and therefore can be possessed to best suit the requirements of your workshop.
<br />Grinding Machine
<br />Grinding machine is a very important tool used in most of the workshops for solid material grinding and shaping applications. This power driven machine tool can be run on desired speeds to accurately remove the unwanted parts from the work piece so that the desired shape and finish can be achieved. With grinding machine in your workshop, you can easily accomplish your metal shaping goals without much effort. There are various &lt;a title=&quot;types of grinding machines&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhavyamachinetools.com%2Fspm-a-heavy-machine%2Ftool-a-cutter-grinding.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bhavyamachinetools.com/spm-a-heavy-machine/tool-a-cutter-grinding.html</a>]types of grinding machines[/url] available in market today. For example there are belt grinding machines used for debarring and grinding of metals with coated abrasives, bench grinders for roughing and finishing of tool bits, tool &amp;amp; cutter grinding machines used to perform customized and most accurate grinding tasks and much more. Selecting the one with most apt specifications for your workshop will best serve your solid material shaping requirements at your workshop.
<br />Mentioned above are the basic machine tools which are found at most of the workshops and best to install at any workshop where metal or other solid material applications are to be executed. But however apart from these there are yet various other forms of machine tools too available in the market today. Depending on your requirements and work in your workshop, you should decide which machine tool with what specifications will suit your applications and is the best for installation in your workshop.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>