<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="c14debc71b646256fb5b7c1c7ee6f366" url=""><![CDATA[Time now for a joke !<br/><br/>All this great stuff
<br /><br />The little camel went to his mother and asked, &quot;Mother, why do we camels
<br />have such big eyes?&quot; 
<br />She looked on him lovingly and replied, &quot;You see, my son, when we are walking in the dessert and the wind starts to blowing and there's sand everywhere, we need these big eyes to keep an eye on one another so that we don't get lost.&quot; 
<br />&quot;Oh!&quot; he said. &quot;And why do we have such huge feet? 
<br />&quot;Well,&quot; she said, &quot;they allow us to walk easily in the dessert sands and help us avoid sinking into the dunes.&quot; 
<br />&quot;Wow,&quot; he said, &quot;great equipment. What the heck is this stuff on our backs for?&quot; 
<br />&quot;You see,&quot; his mother informed, &quot;we can walk for days, even weeks without food or water, so we use it to store fat during those times. But why do you ask me  all these obvious questions?&quot; 
<br />&quot;Well, mother,&quot; said the young camel, &quot;I was just wondering, if we've got all of this great stuff, what are we doing in the zoo?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="34bb36a8c71ed67b64028c038a4f1a8c" url=""><![CDATA[The Truckers Prayer<br/><br/>Just something I used to have in my truck before I retired
<br />I thought I might share with you all.
<br /><br />The Truckers Prayer.
<br />Dear God Above,
<br /><br />Bless this truck I drive,
<br />And help me keep someone alive.
<br /><br />Be my mortal sight this day,
<br />On streets where little children play.
<br /><br />Bless my helper fast asleep,
<br />When the night is long and deep.
<br /><br />And keep my cargo safe and sound,
<br />through the hours big and round.
<br /><br />Make my judgement sound as steel,
<br />And be my hands upon this wheel.
<br /><br />Bless the traveller going past,
<br />And teach him not to go so fast.
<br /><br />Give me strength for every trip,
<br />So I may care for what they ship.
<br /><br />Make me mindful every mile,
<br />That life is just a little while.
<br /><br />AMEN.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b1cce14931b9640289c589649a27b67a" url=""><![CDATA[An Email worth passing on<br/><br/>Good morning world,
<br />A friend sent  this email to my in box the other day, 
<br />and I think it is worth posting here : 
<br /><br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; I don't know if this will work but can't see the harm in trying at least!!
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; How to protect your 'e-mail' address book
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; A computer repairman says this is like having gold. 
<br />&gt; &gt; This  is a good thing. 
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; I learned a computer trick today that's really ingenious in its simplicity.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; As you may know,
<br />&gt; &gt; When/if a worm virus gets into your computer it heads straight for your email address book,
<br />&gt; &gt; And sends itself to everyone in there, thus infecting all your friends and associates.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; This trick won't keep the virus from getting into your computer,
<br />&gt; &gt; But it will stop it from using your address book to spread further,
<br />&gt; &gt; And it will alert you to the fact that the worm has gotten into your system.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; Here's what you do:
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; First, open your address book and click on 'new contact,'
<br />&gt; &gt; Just as you would do if you were adding a new friend to your list of email addresses.
<br />&gt; &gt; In the window where you would type your friend's first name, type in 'A'.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; For the screen name or email address, type <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=AAAAAAA@AAA.AAA">AAAAAAA@AAA.AAA</a>
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; Now, here's what you've done and why it works:
<br />&gt; &gt; The 'name 'A' will be placed at the top of your address book as entry #1.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; This will be where the worm will start in an effort to send itself to all your friends.
<br />&gt; &gt; When it tries to send itself to  <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=AAAAAAA@AAA.AAA">AAAAAAA@AAA.AAA</a>,
<br />&gt; &gt; It will be undeliverable because of the phony email address you entered.  
<br />&gt; &gt; If the first attempt fails (which it will because of the phony address),
<br />&gt; &gt; The worm goes no further and none of your friends will be infected.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; Here's the second great advantage of this method:  If an email cannot be delivered,
<br />&gt; &gt; You will be notified of this in your &quot;In Box&quot; almost immediately. 
<br />&gt; &gt; Hence, if you ever get an email telling you that an email addressed to <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=AAAAAAA@AAA.AAA">AAAAAAA@AAA.AAA</a>
<br />&gt; &gt; Could not be delivered, you know right away that you have the worm virus in your system. 
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; You can then take steps to get rid of it!
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; Pretty slick huh?
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; If everybody you know does this then you need not ever worry about opening mail from friends.
<br />&gt; &gt;
<br />&gt; &gt; ........... DO IT NOW.......... And pass this on to all your friends ..........
<br />&gt; &gt;  
<br />&gt; &gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="82d84717fab5cd6724632377ec0f0745" url=""><![CDATA[A PETS PRAYER<br/><br/>This was given to my wife about 20 years ago by a Vet in NSW.
<br />Author Unknown.
<br /><br />Please feel free to copy this,
<br /> and if you want me to email you a copy, just let me know.
<br /><br />A  PETS  PRAYER
<br /><br />If it should be, that I grow frail and weak, 
<br />And pain should keep me from my sleep, 
<br />Then, you must do what must be done,           
<br />For this, the last battle, can't be won.
<br /><br />You will be sad, I understand,
<br />Don't let your grief then stay your hand,     
<br />For this day, more than the rest,       
<br />Your love and friendship stand the test.
<br /><br />We've had so many happy years,      
<br />What is to come can hold no fears,       
<br />You'd not want me to suffer, so,           
<br />When the time comes, please let me go.
<br /><br />Take me where my needs they'll tend,          
<br />ONLY,  STAY WITH ME TO THE END,     
<br />And hold me firm and speak to me,             
<br />Until my eyes no longer see.
<br /><br />I know, in time you will see,         
<br />It is a kindness you do to me,          
<br />Although my tail, its last was waved,      
<br />From pain and suffering I've been saved.
<br /><br />Don't grieve it should be you,          
<br />Who decides this thing to do.           
<br />We've been so close, we two, these years,         
<br />Don't let your heart hold any tears.
<br /><br />Smile, for we walked together, for a little while.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ef78d90c1cbda9ddb6bdaf547e1d1c0b" url=""><![CDATA[Frost<br/><br/>Woke up this morning to a very severe frost. 
<br />It actually looked like it had been snowing and stayed 
<br />that way until lunch time, at least it has otherwise been
<br />a good day weather wise. here when we get the frost it
<br />usually turns out fine unless the wind comes in and 
<br />then it's a right bastard of a day.
<br />Where ever you all are, I wish you a safe and happy weekend.
<br />Oh yeah, and don't do anything I wouldn't do! 
<br />( now that leaves the door wide open for just about anything ! )
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4310546145084cd5b7c16c4ab264c1da" url=""><![CDATA[Gardening<br/><br/>Good afternoon world.
<br />Well, I have finally gotten round to the vegie garden - usually do it earlier, but the weather has been so bad that I haven't been able to do anything at all outside lately.
<br />So, my plot which is 33 X 3ft has now been all weeded, dug out and a fresh compost layer placed in the hole  and the old soil dug over with a good helping of blood and bone added 2 kg before all the old soil has been put back on top of the compost and all has been watered well before I covered the lot with a cover I have made from the thick black plastic and all held down with a couple of dozen  house bricks.
<br />Usually I do this every year around the beginning of July, but have I mentioned the bad weather we have had here ths year ?
<br />OH NO! Not again! I can hear you saying.
<br />OK, I'll leave you all alone for a while.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2f586c8fbda2498f07bed9fc0fb6253e" url=""><![CDATA[The Echidna<br/><br/>Good morning world.
<br />I am just sitting here thinking how one thing leads to another and I thought I would tell you all about the Echidna. 
<br />About a week ago I went to the local Salvation Army op shop to see if I could get myself a decent belt, as the buckle on my old one had broken. So any way, I found none that were long enough for me and was told to give it a few days and then come back as they were always getting new belts in.
<br />So I went back last Monday, and while I was there after I had found a belt that was suitable, and as I was walking out the door, I noticed an old computer tower sitting in the corner. So, my being the noisy person I am, I naturally asked how much they wanted for it, only to be told it had been left at the front door that morning and as they were not allowed to sell electrical items, I could have it if I wanted to make a small donation. So, as the belt was going to cost me all of $1-, 
<br />I offered to give $4- for the computer and so came away with not only the belt, but also
<br />2 monitors, a printer and the computer tower. Getting this all home I found the hard drive has Windows 98 loaded into it, the problem being there was no mouse. So I rang the local computer repair man who lives down the road here at Dodges Ferry, and left a message on the answering machine, after not hearing from him all week, yesterday I decided to go and see if he was home. Now, I know you are wondering what this all has to do with the Echidna?
<br />Well on the way back home from picking up a mouse to suit the computer ( another $5 -  $9 so far ), we saw a yung echidna crossing the road and as this is a very busy road, ( more of a highway ) I had to get out and stop the traffic so as the echidna could get across without being runover. So, only for a broken belt, an old unwanted computer, I would never have been there at that time and there may have been one more dead Echidna on the side of the road.
<br />Just thought I would share this small part of my week with you all.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e4b8fc669560c20fb87e7f04cc95a65f" url=""><![CDATA[$9 - Computer<br/><br/>The 2nd hand computer I  bought for $4 - + $5 - paid for the mouse had windows 98 on it and all the files had been stripped out.
<br />Unfortunately for me though, the screen has started to come up with a message saying there is a fatal error on drive C, so I have given the computer and all else to the local computer repair man so as he can see if he can salvage any parts from it.
<br />I felt that was a better idea than just dumping it at the local council tip.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="67fcbd9db7b7035a11dcfa82c273c883" url=""><![CDATA[Scam Messages on Blog Sites<br/><br/>Good morning world.
<br />I hope this morning finds you all safe and happy, just a bit I fell I should say about the Scams that are beginning to turn up on Blog sites.
<br />As some of you will know I also have a site on Windows Live and have been recieving a few of these lately, and felt I should post one of these for those of you who have as yet not seen one.
<br />This is the type of thing being sent around at the moment, and please keep in mind that a lot of children may see or even recieve these. So, for those who have children, it may be an idea to tell them about this.
<br />Now to what I found in my inbox this morning.
<br /><br />Dear Jackson,
<br /><br />I am Barrister fedelia Michael (SAT)a solicitor at law, personal attorney to Engr.P.B.Jackson, who used to work with Shell Development Company in Ghana. Here in after shall be referred to as my client. On the 21st of April 2006, my client, his wife and their only daughter were involved in a ghastly car accident along Kalama express road. All occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost their lives.
<br /><br />Since then I have made several enquiries to your embassy here to locate any of my clients extended relatives, this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, In my disparate search for urgent assistance, I decided to track his last name over the foreign mission guestbook, to locate any member of his family hence I contacted you.
<br /><br />I have contacted you to assist in repatriating the fund valued at USD$7.5 million left behind by my client before it get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the Security finance firm (BANK) here in Accra-Ghana, where this huge amount were deposited.   And now the bank has issued me a notice to provide the next of kin or have his account confiscated within the next seventy one official working days. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for over 2years now, I seek the consent to present you as the next of kin to the deceased since you have the same last names, so that the proceeds of this account can be paid to you.
<br /><br />Therefore, on receipt of your positive response, we shall then discuss the sharing ratio and modalities for transfer. I have all necessary information and legal documents needed to back you up for the claim. All I require from you is your honest cooperation to enable us see this transaction through. I guarantee that this will be executed under legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Urgent response to this letter by forwarding your information below will be proudly appreciated.
<br /><br />1. Your full name
<br />2. contact address
<br />3. Direct telephone number
<br />4. Occupation
<br />5. Marital status
<br />6. Age
<br />7. Email
<br /><br />Pls write to me on this email: <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=fedeliamichaels@aol.com">fedeliamichaels@aol.com</a>
<br /><br />Best Regards.
<br />Barrister fedelia Nanakaobi Michael
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e1c3fc7e743ca0cfdc2ab8e6ecc38295" url=""><![CDATA[Still thinking of moving<br/><br/>We have seen a place up at Triabunna this morning 
<br />which is about an hour away so we are going to go 
<br />look at it sometime this coming week. Looks ok, 3 bedroom place 
<br />on 1/4 acre right near the ocean so I'll let you all knpw what it's 
<br />like after we have seen it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="647f58be6db431d1b942f56e7f8f5d08" url=""><![CDATA[Triabunna - the hole<br/><br/>Good Afternoon World !
<br />Triabunna is no good for us as the house seems to at one time 
<br />been two old shacks that have been joined together by a long 
<br />covered in walkway. The kitchen and the bathroom / toilet is
<br /> in one and the other has 3 bedrooms and a small living area.
<br />So, next Saturday we are once more off to Campbell town to 
<br />have a look at a 2 bedroom house with a fully fenced backyard.
<br />Had we known about this one we could have gone and seen it 
<br />at the same time we saw the other one there that was falling apart.
<br />Trouble here is the distances, as this is a 2 1/2 drive for us from 
<br />where we are. I guess this is the only way we will ever find a place,
<br />getting a bit sick and tired of looking though. I'll let you all know 
<br />what this turns out like. Sounds good though.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="796d59028b63db6e8d2d6e4c86c36b45" url=""><![CDATA[Campbell Town - Looking Good.<br/><br/>Good afternoon world,
<br />Last saturday we went up to Campbell town to have a look at a two bedroom house. Campbell town, is a one hour and thirty five minutes drive from where we are at forcett, a quiet country town, situated approx. half way between Hobart and Devonport.
<br />This place is on approx. 1/4 of an acre and the house itself is neat and tidy, fully fenced with a large kitchen, lounge room with a large open fireplace plus a recently refurbished bathroom. Although this was advertised as a two bedroom place, in actual fact it has as well as the two bedrooms, another room which could easily accommodate a single bed, another small room big enough to be used as a study or home office,and a passageway large enough to be used as a sun room down the side leading to the back door.
<br />At the rear of the house is the laundry and also a room big enough to be used as a garden shed, so we won’t have to buy a shed as we were originally going to do.The house seems to be what we want and today we submitted an offer and are now waiting to hear back from the estate agent as to whether our offer has been accepted. I'll let you all know what happens
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ede859f9fc44bd86ce667ce7697d44b3" url=""><![CDATA[Just an update on Campbell Town<br/><br/>Good Afternoon World.
<br />We signed the purchase papers on the house at Campbell Town this morning
<br /> and the Real Estate Agent came round yesterday afternoon to take the photos
<br /> for our place here to go on the internet.
<br />So, if any of you have a spare $210,000, why not come down here and buy my house?
<br /> I'll let you know how we go, we have till the 23rd of December to sell here as that is
<br /> the settlement date.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca169c204f948b1e446ec51822a0dbf6" url=""><![CDATA[Campbell Town - I now think not.<br/><br/>Good morning world,
<br />As you are all aware, we placed an offfer on the house at Campbell Town, and actually signed the Contract of Purchase, However it now transpires that this place is owned by some Corporation, somewhere in Queensland, and after a week of waiting for them to get the contract signed and back to us we were told that they still needed a week to decide if they were going to sign, so we decided to cancell the contract and keep looking. My feeling is that this place is in some kind of family dispute and only some of the family members are wanting to sell it.
<br />In 2 weeks time we are heading over to the other side of Tasmania to Waratah ( a five hour drive from here ) to have a look at 2 properties over there that sound pretty good. If that fails we then have a place up near George Town ( a three hour drive ) that looks promising. At least we don't have nothing down here to look at, and we want to leave here, we don't have to. 
<br />Everyone have a good weekend where ever you are.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a6d7c27064629cbc40da09b03e77dc97" url=""><![CDATA[Looking for Football Cards<br/><br/>FOOTBALL CARDS : Australia only
<br />Trying to collect a full set of the cards found in the small Smiths Potato Chips packets. 64 in the collection and I need another 20, but shops no longer sell them here. Have many spares I can swap, any help appreciated.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b6d38b4626faa52da8bd4a718bfaebb6" url=""><![CDATA[Waratah<br/><br/>Last Saturday we took a drive for the day over to Waratah which is on the North West side of Tasmania. Waratah is 350klm's from where we are here and it took us 5 3/4 hours to get there. The reason for the journey was that there were 2 houses for sale in our price range, and as you know we have been looking fo another place to live, a bigger house and smaller land. So, after going all the way over there and most of it in really bad weather ( when we left home at 7am it was looking to be a really good day ), but by the time we got into the mountains we had to go over, it was pouring, and did so all the way over and for most of the way back home. We had the appointment with the real estate agent at 12.30 and actually arrived there 25 minutes late, only to find the estate agent had been and gone, you would think, knowing how far we had to come over, that she would at least wait for 1/2 hour, but when we hadn't arrived by 12.45, she left. Now I know what you all are thinking, why didn't we ring her on the mobile and tell her we were on our way? Well, we tried that, only to find that the mobile phones don't have any coverage in the area due to the high mountains surrounding the township. Had she told us this to begin with, we would never have decided to go there in the first place. As the weather conditions in the mountains were so bad on the way over, we decided to come back the long way over the top of the island, through Burnie and devonport. This added an extra 160 klm's to the trip home, and all up the wasted day cost us $80 in petrol and 11hours travelling time. As you can imagine, we are not very impressed, seems every time we try to find a place, something goes wrong. Still, we will just have to keep looking.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="977f08667298a65598a246a2430bdf25" url=""><![CDATA[The Eagle Trees are down<br/><br/>Good morning World.
<br />Those of you who know me know I have a background in zoology, having worked extensively in Zoos in different parts Australia.
<br />So you will realise why the following is so upsetting to me.
<br />Since 2000, I have been watching and recording the habits of the Tasmanian Wedge Tailed Eagle in my area here and up on the hill overlooking the valley all this time has been a line of dead gum trees, 9 in all, these are only the skeletons of the trees ( approx 1/2 a mile away ), as I have been told that when a major bush fire came through this area in the 1970's these trees were all killed in the fire.
<br />In the very strong winds we had here a few weeks ago, the 2 smaller of these trees blew over.
<br />Now, these are on a ridge, in no way pose a danger to any house and yesterday, a tragic event occurred, SOME BASTARD came along with a chain saw and cut all the remaining dead trees down except the tallest one on the very end of the ridge. 
<br />So, now more will we see these birds and be able to closely observe their habits, I have seen an old black female teaching her two young ones to hunt from those trees, and they have been the main dropping off area here for the female to leave her young ones when it was time for them to be left to fend for themselves. I guess from now on, with only one lone dead tree standing, as far as my diary is concerned, these birds will become a thing of the past in this area. I wonder how long it will be before the remaining tree is also cut down to be left on the ground to rot?
<br />To me, very sad, very upsetting thing to do with no point to it at all.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="83ebaafce40657cf3a935457aa1a4a88" url=""><![CDATA[Is It True, Could It Be? Is Spring Truly Here?<br/><br/>Good morning world!
<br />Well, it seems that spring has finally arrived here in Tasmania!
<br />The last 3 out of 4 days here have actually been fine and the temp up in the low 20's, and after the winter we have had, it makes for a very welcome change.
<br />As I think I mentioned earlier some time last year, round the corner from my place ( 3 miles ), here we have what is known by the locals as the Lewisham duck Pond. Now this area of approx 25 acres of natural low lying swamp has since I have been living here ( 1997 ) always been full and a breeding ground for the many different species of native wild life as well as the black Swans. OK, so I am taking my time getting to the point, which is this : For the past two years this entire area has been dry, all the birds have left and as they leave, so have all the Raptors ( Eagles, Hawks etc ). Now this winter has been so wet, that the entire area is now once more a small natural lake, slowly the water birds are returning and for the first time in 3 years, we are now once more able to see the Black Swans with young. This year must have been their first nest, as they only hatched out 1 chick and the female is now again sitting on the nest, and all the small native ducks are now either sitting on eggs or have young ones following them about.
<br />A  sign that the good weather is here to stay, I think?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aac51329d1cb50f63f794874f44debf8" url=""><![CDATA[My first Blue Tongue for the year.<br/><br/>Good Morning World,
<br />This morning I went around to buy the sunday paper, at my local paper shop, as I usually do on a sunday morning and on my way home came accross a large Blue Tongue Lizard lying in the middle of the road sunbaking. Here in Tasmania this is a rather common sight during the warmer months, and I always stop and pick the lizard up to check for ticks as these poor things are quite often heavily infested with them. I have seen and removed up to 50 ticks, they get under the legs and also into the ears, a few times I'v found lizards that couldn't walk properly due to the number of ticks attached to the armpit area of the legs. This one this morning was one of the few lucky ones I have seen over the years, only having 9 ticks attached. trouble with ticks is they get under the scales and sometimes the colour of the scales can make it difficult to see the actuall tick. I have found the best way to remove them is with a pair of tweezers, and once they have been removed, I kill them by dropping them into a small container of metholated spirits. Then I take the lizard back to where I found it to release it. I know this may seem to some a waste of time and effort as the ticks will soon be replaced with others, but I always feel better about having done it, and it's always feels good to me to see a tick free lizard go back into the bush. 
<br />So anyway, Having gotten distracted as I often do when writing or talking about such things, my point I started to make is,   SUMMER APPEARS TO HAVE FINALLY ARRIVED !!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3cdf7ee6df696120fd0ae8687b740e7" url=""><![CDATA[My House for sale<br/><br/>Good afternoon world.
<br />I have a one bedroom cottage at Forcett here in Tasmania for sale.
<br />Open plan living with verandah,  3/4 acre fully fenced with water and rural views.
<br />Quiet area, close to shops and beaches, 20 minutes to Hobart Airport
<br />Priced at between $176,000 to $189,000.
<br />If you know of anyone who may be interested, please let me know.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="27731677b862abe3be45629ff2ce9e03" url=""><![CDATA[Information required<br/><br/>Good morning World.
<br />I have started to write my new book and am after Home Remedies and cures for sick or injured animals. Anything that the old farmers used to use on the farm animals. This book will include Birds, Dogs, Cats, Fish, and Reptiles.  I am interested in any and all forms of old time cures that were used in the days before Veterinary Practices were an everyday accepted way of having a sick animal treated. Any information you supply you will be given full credit as having supplied it when the book is published. If you have any ideas I might be able to use, please let me know
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5254dafa17a7fd7119d8f3916a27551" url=""><![CDATA[From my inbox this morning<br/><br/>Just thought I would Blog this , Please read.
<br /><br />Blood  Clots/Stroke - They Now Have a Fourth Indicator, 
<br /> the Tongue
<br /><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/85157689_3753239_28449564.jpg" />
<br />STROKE:   Remember the 1st Three Letters....S.T.R. 
<br /><br />It only takes  a minute to read this...
<br /><br />A neurologist  says that if he can get to a stroke victim within 3 hours he can totally reverse the effects of a stroke...totally. He said the trick was getting a stroke recognized, diagnosed, and then getting the patient medically cared for within 3 hours, which is tough.
<br /><br />RECOGNIZING A STROKE :
<br />Thank God for the sense to remember the '3' steps, STR. Read and Learn!
<br /><br />S  *Ask  the individual to SMILE.
<br />T  *Ask  the person to TALK and  SPEAK A SIMPLE SENTENCE (Coherently)
<br />(i.e. It  is sunny out today.)
<br />R *Ask  him or her to RAISE  BOTH ARMS.
<br /><br />If  he or she has trouble with ANY ONE of these  tasks, call emergency number immediately and  describe the symptoms to the  dispatcher.
<br /><br />New Sign of a Stroke -------- Stick out Your Tongue
<br /><br />NOTE:  Another 'sign' of a stroke is this: Ask the person to 'stick' out his tongue.. If the tongue  is 'crooked', if it goes to one side or the other, that is also an indication of a stroke.
<br /><br />A cardiologist says if everyone who gets this e-mail sends it to 10 people; you can bet that at least one life will be saved.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f8dd7aad650899c53bc5d891c5056f0e" url=""><![CDATA[My new book<br/><br/>My new childrens book is now at the printers and should be available from me within the next couple of weeks. As yet I have still to put a price on it and will let you all know when I do. 
<br />45 pages, 4 colour plates inside and a full colour front cover, this is the story about a small native mouse and his family and other assorted animal friends who have to find a new home due to a bushfire going thru the area where they are living. Would make a great christmas gift for the young children between 4 to 7 years old.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8313e2959b8729cc21e944a796ee4527" url=""><![CDATA[My latest book available<br/><br/>My new book is now available from me @$20 a copy which includes postage.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>