<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="19">
		<document id="adb142bdaa280e64c83cd64db4a51ac" url=""><![CDATA[Man is unique in the creation of God, How & Why?<br/><br/>Man is born in purity of nature, unsullied, designed by God. In addition to intelligence, he is gifted with freedom of choice and the sense of good and evil. All these elements have put him apart from the whole animal kingdom. 
<br /><br />Man is accountable for whatever he does, for 'no one shall bear the burden of another'; he should, therefore, be heedful. He shall one day be brought to Judgment; the proof of this has been planted in his very nature. He has been equipped with the faculty of distinguishing between right and wrong; and so long as he does not blunt it altogether by the persistent rejection or neglect of its voice or signals, it keeps on warning him. The conscience of man is equipped with this faculty, which is the proof of his ultimate accountability. It also provides the convincing proof that there is God and there is life after death.
<br /><br />Within the sphere of his responsibility man has been given a choice, to follow one course or another. His choice, according to Divine law, would result in good or harm. In that sense, it is Divine law that determines the consequences of all action. The wrong action, or default may not have been deliberate, or of purpose, and may be followed by repentance.
<br /><br />On the negative side, not only must every kind of trespass against person, property and honor be avoided; but ill behavior and evil thoughts and designs must also be guarded against.
<br /><br />On the positive side, it is not enough to be just; that is, to return good for good and to exact only proportionate punishment for a wrong suffered.  He who seeks the pleasure of God must be benevolent; that is, he must do good without any thought of return, and forgive wrongs and injuries till beneficence towards fellow beings becomes part of his nature and flows out of him as naturally as affection for close kindred.
<br /><br />&quot;God enjoins JUSTICE and BENEVOLENCE as between kith and kin; and forbids evil designs, indecency, and wrongdoing. He admonishes you that you may take heed.&quot; A brief admonition comprising a whole philosophy of conduct!
<br /><br />&quot;O Man! What has made you careless-and-deluded about your Lord, the Most Generous, who created YOU, fashioned YOU in perfect proportion, and set a BALANCE in YOU.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="20feacc1b0f2b3b6384d4d0076e18d24" url=""><![CDATA[What is the basis of social security?<br/><br/><strong>&quot;The State&quot;
<br /><br />Justice and honesty, not religion nor atheism
<br />Is required for the protection of a state.
<br /><br />- Jami</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="167d8b3a1869e921757784c084153ef1" url=""><![CDATA[Life is full of questions.<br/><br/>Life is full of questions. There are deeper questions, too. Some are
<br />trivial, some are serious - and some tremendously important.
<br /><br />+ Who am I?
<br />&gt; I'm a human being. I'm creature of God, a servant of God.
<br /><br />+ Why am I here?
<br />&gt; To do will of God as a servant of God, to do good to man, to live a righteous life
<br />by thinking right, speaking right, doing right, to live a life of decency.
<br /><br />+ Where am I going?
<br />&gt;&gt; If we obey God, and do good works, will go to Paradise. If we disobey His commands,
<br />and commit sin and evil,  will go to Hell.
<br /><br />+ Does life have any purpose?
<br />&gt;&gt; God has created man to serve God, and to test who is good in works.
<br /><br />But the ultimate questions are about God.
<br />-----------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />+ Does He exist?
<br />&gt;&gt; By seeing starry heaven in the night and Nature in the day, and moral sense in man
<br />we understand that there is God. Nature is a spread book of God, a man
<br />with insight can make careful study of it and know God and His creations.
<br /><br />+ What is He like?
<br />&gt;&gt; God is One. He is Absolute. He begets not, Nor is He begotten. He is peerless, nothing is
<br />like unto Him. He is the source of light, of heaven, and of earth.
<br /><br />+ Can I know Him and experience His power in my life? And if so, how?
<br />&gt;&gt; We know God from Holy Books, the prophets who had communication with God...
<br />And by reflection, contemplation and thinking about God's creations.
<br /><br />+ While it is impossible to 'prove' God in a mathematical sense, the
<br />evidence is very convincing.
<br />&gt;&gt; Man is accountable for whatever he does, for 'no one shall bear the burden of another'; he should, therefore, be heedful. He shall one day be brought to Judgment; the proof of this has been planted in his very nature. He has been equipped with the faculty of distinguishing between right and wrong; and so long as he does not blunt it altogether by the persistent rejection or neglect of its voice or signals, it keeps on warning him. The conscience of man is equipped with this faculty, which is the proof of his ultimate accountability. It also provides the convincing proof that there is God and there is life after death.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="134ea4ecb8300edb8fb90d0fc7858194" url=""><![CDATA[The Road to Mecca<br/><br/>The Road to Mecca 
<br />Muhammad Asad 
<br /><br />The extraordinary account of how Leopold Weiss, born in Lvov in 1900, 
<br />became a Muslim. A journalist (and later Pakistan's representative to 
<br />the U.N.), Asad writes of his travels, transformation and attachment 
<br />to Islam and the Arab world. His book takes the form of stories told 
<br />during a camel ride to Mecca (one of his many adventurous journeys 
<br />through Arabia and the Near East in the 1930s).
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e34d955738b3257c2793908b0a14b008" url=""><![CDATA[Leopold Weiss<br/><br/><strong>&quot;Islam appears to me like a perfect work of architecture. All its
<br />parts are harmoniously conceived to complement and support each other;
<br />nothing is superfluous and nothing lacking; and the result is a
<br />structure of absolute balance and solid composure.&quot;</strong> Thus Asad spoke of
<br />Islam.
<br /><br />Writer, traveller and explorer, Muhammad Asad had a truly chequered
<br />life spanning three continents and two cultures. Born Leopold Weiss in
<br />the summer of 1900 in the Polish city of Lwow, then under Austrian
<br />empire, he was 14 when he escaped school and joined the Austrian army
<br />under a false name, only to be recovered by his father and taken home,
<br />now in Vienna.
<br /><br />Leopold's grandfather, an orthodox rabbi in Crzernowitz, Bukovina, had
<br />wanted his father to follow the family's rabbinical tradition, but he
<br />chose to be a barrister. For Leopold, however, he made sure that by
<br />the age of 13, he not only read Hebrew with great fluency, but also
<br />speak it freely and have a fair acquaintance with Aramaic. The young
<br />boy studied the Old Testament in the original; the Mishna and Gemara
<br />that is, the text and commentaries of the Talmud and became immersed
<br />in the intricacies of Biblical exegesis, called 'Targum'.
<br /><br /><strong>Islam had been revealing itself to Leopold in bits and pieces, but it
<br />was on a winter day in Afghanistan that a man, fixing an iron shoe to
<br />his horse, told him: 'But thou art a Muslim, only thou dost not know
<br />it thyself'. 'Why don't you say now and here: &quot;There is no god but God
<br />and Muhammad is His Prophet&quot; and become a Muslim in fact, as you
<br />already are in your heart', said the horseshoe-smith. 'I will go with
<br />you tomorrow to Kabul and take you to the amin, and he will receive
<br />you with open arms as one of us', he asserted.
<br /><br />Some time after September 1926, he sought out a Muslim friend of his,
<br />an Indian who was at that time head of the small Muslim community in
<br />Berlin, and told him that he wanted to embrace Islam. Elsa followed a
<br />few weeks alter. Leopold had become Asad, something which was strongly
<br />disapproved by his father and his sister. The relationship resumed in
<br />1935, after his father had at last come to understand and appreciate
<br />the reasons for his conversion to Islam.</strong>
<br /><br />His first title on an Islamic theme, Islam at the Crossroads,
<br />published in 1934, proved to be extremely popular and was translated
<br />in several languages. The Crossroads was a plea of Muslims to avoid a
<br />blind imitation of Western social forms and values, and to try to
<br />preserve instead their Islamic heritage which once upon a time had
<br />been responsible for the glorious, many-sided historical phenomenon
<br />comprised in the term 'Muslim civilization'.
<br /><br />'The Qur'an cannot be correctly understood', he wrote, 'if we read it
<br />merely in the light of later ideological developments, losing sight of
<br />its original purport and meaning'. That in fact was the whole stress
<br />in the vast body of existing Tafsir literature (renderings and
<br />explanations of the Qur'an) that took great care to reach and stick to
<br />the understanding of the original sources, the Messenger himself
<br />(sws), his Companions (rta), and those after them in the natural order
<br />of precedence.
<br /><br />He also wrote The Message of The Qur'an, a translation and brief
<br />commentary on the Muslim holy book based on his own knowledge of
<br />classical Arabic and on the authoritative classical commentaries.
<br /><br />The great strength of Asad's rendering, however, lies in its elegant
<br />and powerful prose, fluent and highly enjoyable. That is also its
<br />weakness, if and when, in the course of its long journey, the language
<br />happens to take a swing, the enchanted reader is unlikely to discern
<br />any gap between words and meaning.
<br /><br />Leopold Weiss was born on 2 July 1900. Muhammad Asad died on 20
<br />February 1992. He was buried in the Muslim cemetery in Granada,
<br />Andalusia.
<br /><br />-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />Some comments of Muhammad Asad (Leopold Weiss): 
<br /><br />Islam gave &quot;Yes to Action, No to passivity. Yes to Life, No to asceticism&quot;.
<br /><br />&quot;It was obvious to me that the decline of the Muslims was not due to
<br />any shortcomings in Islam but rather to their own failure to live up to
<br />it... It was not Muslims that had made Islam great: It was Islam that
<br />had made the Muslims great. But, as soon as their faith became habit
<br />and ceased to be PROGRAMME OF LIFE, to be consciously pursued, the
<br />creative impulse that underlay their civilization waned and gradually
<br />gave way to indolence, sterility and cultural decay&quot;.
<br /><br />&quot;EVERY MUSLIM OUGHT TO BE ABLE TO SAY: THE QURAN HAS BEEN
<br />REVEALED FOR ME&quot;, he said in an interview few years before his death.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="946fdd4277c36e5a74699daa530fea31" url=""><![CDATA[ONE WORLD, ONE HOMELAND.<br/><br/>There can be no doubt that modern discoveries and technology have made
<br />it essential for the whole earth to become ONE economically and
<br />administratively – <strong>not only essential but inevitable.</strong>
<br /><br />And, given time, this will quite certainly happen, whether we are
<br />willing or not, provided, of course, that we do not blow ourselves up
<br />first.
<br /><br />When that day comes, we need not bother about the problem of
<br />aggression, for, as we have already seen, there are more than enough
<br />evils to fight and more than enough problems to tax the best brains
<br />for centuries to come, and when we have dealt with these we shall
<br />probably find that we have grown up....
<br /><br />(Pears Cyclopedia  1961)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7b860a48f45fae0d7a04a5840b39165c" url=""><![CDATA[SONG OF UNITY - ONE GOD, ONE WORLD, ONE MANKIND.<br/><br/><strong>WE ARE IN THE SAME BOAT, BROTHER,
<br />IF YOU TIP ONE END, YOU GONNA ROCK THE OTHER
<br />IN THE SAME BOAT, BROTHER.
<br /><br />O LORD, LOOK DOWN, FROM YOUR HOLY PLACE,
<br />O LORDIE ME, WHAT A SEA OF SPACE,
<br />WHAT A PLACE TO LAUNCH THIS HUMAN RACE,
<br />SO HE BUILT HIM A BOAT WITH A MIXED UP CREW,
<br />WITH THE EYES OF BLACK, AND BROWN AND BLUE,
<br />AND THAT'S THE REASON YOU AND I HAVE
<br />JUST ONE WORLD, AND JUST ONE SKY....</strong>
<br /><br />[Excerpt]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9d55bd5ec69b1fbb24fbc831c454fd95" url=""><![CDATA[If................<br/><br/>If…………
<br /><br />If you can keep your head when all about you
<br /> Are losing theirs and blaming it on you;
<br />If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you,
<br /> But make allowance for their doubting too:
<br />If you can wait and not be tired by waiting,
<br /> Or, being lied about, don't deal in lies,
<br />Or being hated don't give way to hating,
<br /> And yet don't look too good, nor talk too wise;
<br /><br />If you can dream — and not make dreams your master;
<br /> If you can think — and not make thoughts your aim,
<br />If you can meet with Triumph and Disaster
<br /> And treat those two impostors just the same:.
<br />If you can bear to hear the truth you've spoken
<br /> Twisted by knaves to make a trap for fools,
<br />Or watch the things you gave your life to, broken,
<br /> And stoop and build'em up with worn-out tools;
<br /><br />If you can make one heap of all your winnings
<br /> And risk it on one turn of pitch-and-toss,
<br />And lose, and start again at your beginnings,
<br /> And never breathe a word about your loss:
<br />If you can force your heart and nerve and sinew
<br /> To serve your turn long after they are gone,
<br />And so hold on when there is nothing in you
<br /> Except the Will which says to them: &quot;Hold on!&quot;
<br /><br />If you can talk with crowds and keep your virtue,
<br /> Or walk with Kings — nor lose the common touch,
<br />If neither foes nor loving friends can hurt you,
<br /> If all men count with you, but none too much:
<br />If you can fill the unforgiving minute
<br /> With sixty seconds' worth of distance run,
<br />Yours is the Earth and everything that's in it,
<br /> And  which is more ; you'll be a Man, my son! 
<br /><br />~ Rudyard Kipling
<br />(This poem was written for his son).
<br /><br />[Excerpt]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="87355a570d4777ca2f9a5cb742a4cc46" url=""><![CDATA[Where the mind is without fear...<br/><br/>Where the mind is without fear and the head is held high 
<br />Where knowledge is free
<br />Where the world has not been broken up into fragments 
<br />By narrow domestic walls
<br />Where words come out from the depth of truth
<br />Where tireless striving stretches its arms towards perfection
<br />Where the clear stream of reason has not lost its way 
<br />Into the dreary desert sand of dead habit
<br />Where the mind is led forward by thee 
<br />Into ever-widening thought and action
<br />Into that heaven of freedom, my Father, let my country awake. 
<br /><br />- by Rabindranath Tagore (1861-1941)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="670d8f980f8c06152e52a2aa20a06bdd" url=""><![CDATA[EQUAL CONTRIBUTION OF TWO GENDERS<br/><br/><strong>I don't see any difference 
<br />Between a man and woman 
<br />Whatever great or benevolent achievements 
<br />That are in this world 
<br />Half of that was by woman, 
<br />The other half by man. </strong>
<br /><br />- Kazi Nazrul Islam 
<br />(National poet of Bangladesh)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d801389810f3d0f617c11d11a4d8293" url=""><![CDATA[On reading the Holy Qur'an<br/><br/>Please adhere to the study of the Qur'an which is a sure guide for entire mankind. Everyone has right to learn its message and enjoy its beauty. The Qur'an is a miracle without works, a victory without processions, even a book without writers. The message of the Qur'an is simple. It forbids us to commit evil and it shows us the way to love Allah - the One without Trinity, the Eternal.   Muhammad said: 'The ink of the scholar is even more precious than the blood of the martyr.
<br /><br />The Qur'an must be the only guide in our life of believers. I wish all people could think this way. Evidently, other studies are important too. The study of the Qu'ran is ESSENTIAL to any Muslim. And if other people who are not Muslims could read it without prejudice, they should find a treasure in Its pages.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c560913d6ba80ead1f0ecd1632879eb7" url=""><![CDATA[Believe in yourself…<br/><br/>Believe in yourself…
<br />in the power you have
<br />to control your own life
<br />day by day.
<br />Believe in the strength
<br />that you have deep inside
<br />and your faith will help
<br />show you the way.
<br /><br />Believe in tomorrow
<br />and what it will bring,
<br />let a hopeful heart
<br />carry you through
<br />for things will work out
<br />if you trust and believe
<br />there’s no limit
<br />to what you can do!
<br /><br />[Excerpt]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f9979199de931f20f5f74f69151c8d78" url=""><![CDATA[Jesus, son of Mary, was no more no less than a human being.<br/><br/>The Gospels (like the Qur'an) give us the same description of Jesus's biological origins.
<br /><br />The formation of Jesus in the maternal uterus occurred in circumstances which lay outside the laws of nature common to all human beings.  The ovule produced by the mother's ovary did not need to join with a spermatozoon, which should have come from his father, to form the embryo and hence a viable infant.
<br /><br />The phenomenon of the birth of a normal individual without the fertilizing action of the male is called 'parthenogenesis'.
<br /><br />In the animal kingdom, parthenogenesis can be observed under certain conditions. This is true for various insects, certain invertebrates and, very occasionally, a select breed of bird. By way of experiment, it has been possible, for example, in certain mammals (female rabbits), to obtain the beginnings of a development of the ovule into an embryo at an extremely rudimentary stage without any intervention of spermatozoon.
<br /><br />It was not possible to go any further however and an example of complete parthenogenesis, whether experimental or natural, is unknown. Jesus is an unique case. Mary was a virgin mother. She preserved her virginity and did not have any children apart from Jesus. Jesus is a biological exception.
<br /><br />Excerpt from <strong>&quot;The Bible, The Qur'an and Science&quot; - by Maurice Bucaille</strong>
<br /><br />Visit URL at: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fhome.swipnet.se%2Fislam%2Fquran-bible.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://home.swipnet.se/islam/quran-bible.htm</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f9ba303bd972510a7e5fcd4bc473e4ce" url=""><![CDATA[MUHAMMAD AND HIS MESSAGE.<br/><br/> 1] His forehead was noble, prominent, and bespoke a generous mind. His 
<br />smile put joy into you. His eyes, black with a touch of brown, were 
<br />well opened. His hand, on greeting, was strong. His step was as light 
<br />as if he were treading on water. When he turned to look at you, he 
<br />turned with his whole body. He was Muhammad, the Messenger of God. 
<br /><br />Muhammad was born in the year 570 AD. His father Abdullah never held 
<br />his son. He died when Muhammad was still in the womb, leaving him a 
<br />legacy of only five lean camels and a few sheep. When he was six, 
<br />Muhammad's mother Amina died and he was left twice an orphan. His 
<br />uncle Abu Talib took him as his own so the boy was never at a loss for 
<br />a home. Abu Talib even brought him up to Syria with the caravan, 
<br />schooling him in the occupations of Makkah, trade and transportation. 
<br />He began to trade in a small way, as his father had done before him. 
<br />Those merchants of Makkah counted well, but they couldn't write or 
<br />read. Muhammad was never taught. 
<br /><br />Muhammad had been a shepherd and had led out the sheep in the morning, 
<br />foraging for the black fruit of the arak thorn on the mountainsides of 
<br />Makkah, 'All the prophets',he said 'have been shepherds of sheep.' As 
<br />always, even in his ordinary occupation, Muhammad was not an ordinary 
<br />man. God chose to reveal His Word to an illiterate man, as if He 
<br />needed a man who had neither guile, nor sin in the written word, an 
<br />untempted man, who could not fall into the traps for a little 
<br />knowledge. 
<br /><br />2] Before Islam, in the desert, a child's fate was known even before 
<br />its toes were out of its mother's body. If the child was male it was 
<br />safe and celebrated; if female, unsafe and whispered over. Had they a 
<br />sufficiency of girls in the family or too many in the tents of the 
<br />tribe, she could be doomed. When she had bitten the cord, she was 
<br />taken out into the desert and the sand was shoveled over her. 
<br /><br />Muhammad always attracted children as if he had some music within 
<br />himself that only they could hear. He spoke language of every age and 
<br />would joke with children using jokes the same size as their own. 
<br /><br />3] Muhammad performed no miracles. He did not cure the sick or 
<br />miraculously ease the hurt of the beaten slave or raise any dead; he 
<br />did not walk on water or cause iron to swim, as Elisha did. 'I am but 
<br />a man… I am but a man…' he would mutter to those well-meaning people 
<br />who thought to please him by congratulating him on the Heaven that is 
<br />sure his, '…and I don't know what God has in store for me.' Muhammad 
<br />never said more than the common sense of Islam. 
<br /><br />4] Muhammad lived within the human capacity and died the human death. 
<br />Yet, God gave him a gift greater than he gave to any of His Prophets, 
<br />He revealed to him the Word. The Qur'an, a sure guide, is a miracle 
<br />for all. 
<br /><br />5] 'Islam is surrender to the will of God, Who is One God without 
<br />partners. Islam is doing right to all men, of every race, degree and 
<br />color. Being servants of sole Sovereign Allah, all men are equal in 
<br />Islam. Islam was revolution. Muhammad was not only preaching a new 
<br />measure of God, he was also teaching a new measure of man. Islam 
<br />threatened property, whether large of small, with Zakat (welfare tax): 
<br />those who have must share with those who have not, in money, produce 
<br />and possession. The evil of the world is property, that no one should 
<br />possess more than he needs, that Muhammad had only two shirts, one for 
<br />washing and one for wearing. Islam threatened the power of the 
<br />merchant nobility, whether personal of political, by giving rights of 
<br />the tribe. Muslims owed themselves to God, not to their families. 
<br /><br />Muhammad gave prime importance to learning and beneficence to 
<br />fellow-beings. 'The ink of the scholar is even more precious than the 
<br />blood of the martyr.' These were the Prophet's words. 'Work is 
<br />devotional service' and 'God loves the hand of a workman,' he would 
<br />say. 
<br /><br />6] Muhammad, the last of the Prophets, was the first to teach mankind 
<br />kindness to animals. Your may go to Hell for cruelty to a cat, he 
<br />said, and there will be a reward for anyone who gives water to a being 
<br />that has a tender heart. 
<br /><br />He forbade to overload the animals, to ride two on a donkey or to 
<br />over-estimate the strength of the camel. He had quick eye against 
<br />cruelty, and woe to any man who hurt an animal without cause – he 
<br />might feel the frown of a prophet. 
<br /><br />When the ten thousand strong soldier-saints were marching on Makkah, 
<br />Muhammad led the whole army a hundred yards off the road to avoid 
<br />disturbing a bitch in the labor with a litter of pups. These are the 
<br />Rules of War: 
<br /><br />You may not hurt a woman, or a child. 
<br />You may not harm the man who works in the field. 
<br />You may not harm old men or take advantage of cripples. 
<br />You may not cut down fruit trees. 
<br />You may not take a drink of water without permission or food without payment. 
<br />You may not tie up a prisoner or force him to walk while you ride. 
<br />The enemy who surrenders to you must be treated kindly by you. 
<br />You must beware of harming children. 
<br /><br />No sword, no threat, no twist, no broken bone, no bribe can bring a 
<br />man to belief. It is God, not man, Who decides who will believe in 
<br />Him. 
<br /><br />No soul can believe 
<br />Except by the wish of God, 
<br />Will you then compel mankind 
<br />Against their will to believe? 
<br />(Al Qur'an, Surah Jonah, Verse 100) 
<br /><br />How then Islam spread by the sword? But no matter how many times you 
<br />prove an impossibility there will always be someone to say it is a 
<br />certainty. 
<br /><br />7] At that time, before the Prophet gave women their rights, Makkah 
<br />was a city of scandalous inequality. A few women were well placed and 
<br />well-to-do, like Hind and Khadijah, but the rest of the sex were poor 
<br />and oppressed. They were men's chattels and their cisterns; by day 
<br />their backs bent forward and by night their backs bent back. Indeed, 
<br />it was a mystery that in Makkah, women were either prayed to or preyed 
<br />upon. Three of the highest gods in the House of Kaa'ba, Al-Uzza, 
<br />Manat, and Al-Lat, were female. But they did as little for their own 
<br />sisters as they did for their brothers. 
<br /><br />When Muhammad was preaching the equality of women in Arabia, in France 
<br />a council of Christian bishops was meeting to decide if women had 
<br />souls or not. Before Muhammad, a man might marry as often as his 
<br />thighs desired or his camels provided. Some had ten in bed, some 
<br />twenty, each one crawling over the other to get closest to her king. 
<br /><br />Islam limited the wives to four, with a commandment that made it more 
<br />comfortable to have only one. All four must be treated equally and 
<br />their claims on marriage must be satisfied equally by turn. If their 
<br />claims could not be satisfied, a man could take one wife only. 
<br /><br />In the desert it was customary to have many wives, not just because 
<br />men are rapacious but also because men are generous. So the limitation 
<br />of the wives was a bewilderment that at first seemed an unkindness, 
<br />even a cruelty, to women. 
<br /><br />Muhammad did not stop there – how could he, with an angel upon his 
<br />heart? He insisted that women, though different, were equal to men. 
<br />The difference is easy to find, men are clustered and women are cleft, 
<br />but to see equality in sex you had to shade your eyes. He told them 
<br />that women are complementary to men, each is the guardian of the 
<br />other. Both must submit to the same last judgment and both will 
<br />inherit he same fate. 
<br /><br />8] At twenty-five Muhammad married Khadijah, who was then nearly forty 
<br />years old and twice widowed. This marriage was so perfect and it was 
<br />the first step up towards his mission. Khadijah freed him from 
<br />poverty, allowing him to undergo the hard work of the soul, the lonely 
<br />agonies and contemplations, the doubts and uncertainties that were his 
<br />education. She comforted him in his despair and, when they called him 
<br />a liar, she alone remained true'. She was the first to believe in his 
<br />mission. 
<br /><br />9] Muhammad was alone in a cave on Mount Hira when the Angel Gabriel 
<br />came in to him. 
<br /><br />Gabriel said: 'Read!' 
<br />Muhammad replied: 'I cannot read.' 
<br /><br />Gabriel commanded again: 
<br />READ! In the name of your Lord, 
<br />Who created man from a sensitive drop of lowly cell, 
<br />Who teaches man what he knew not… 
<br /><br />Muhammad knew that the message from God was written within him. 
<br /><br />In the month of Ramadan, in the blessed night of Majesty, as called 
<br />Lailat Al-Qadr, God gave man his daylight. In this night God permitted 
<br />Gabriel, the Holy Spirit, to bring down the Holy Writ. In this night 
<br />God endowed His Apostle Muhammad, with his first knowledge. In this 
<br />night, Khadijah also believed and became mother of the Believers. In 
<br />this night God sent His mercy to mankind. In the Qur'an it is revealed 
<br />that this night is better than a thousand months. Some say it is the 
<br />seventeenth, others the twenty-third, or twenty-fifth, while others 
<br />insist on the twenty-seventh – yet only God Himself knows when this 
<br />night falls. 
<br /><br />10] God's revelations to His Prophet were not in words as we use them 
<br />to each other – surely God make our mouths as the very hollows of our 
<br />heads! The Message was pressed down on Muhammad's heart, and only 
<br />after the Prophet had got up and come back to us did God permit him to 
<br />recall the inspiration in words. But not one syllable, not one noun or 
<br />verb was out of its proper order. Then it was written down on skin or 
<br />bark or shoulder-bone of sheep – whatever was at hand. All was as 
<br />Gabriel gave it, unaltered. The Qur'an is a miracle without works, a 
<br />victory without processions, even a book without writers. Of the 
<br />immense lamps of the early verses one illumination is: 
<br /><br />Say: God is One, 
<br />The Eternal God, 
<br />He begets none, 
<br />Nor was He begotten, 
<br />No one is equal to Him. 
<br /><br />11] Every day now, five times a day, through all minarets from the 
<br />voice of muezzins you hear those words: 
<br /><br />God is Most Great. God is Most Great. 
<br />I witness that there is no Sovereign except God. 
<br />I witness that Muhammad is the Messengerof God. 
<br />Come to Salah*. Come to Salah. 
<br />Come to good work. Come to good work. 
<br />God is Most Great. God is Most Great. 
<br /><br />*Salah is allegiance service to God.
<br /><br />[Excerpt]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6b9e5fbd64e9333bf2c0a5712bd89de3" url=""><![CDATA[HOMEOPATHY AT HOME<br/><br/>Homeopathy is safe for home use as there are no dangerous side 
<br />effects. This, to many, is the principal that gets them interested in 
<br />homeopathy in the first place. 
<br /><br />There is also a popular misconception that other forms of alternative 
<br />medicine, such as herbal, nutritional supplements, or chinese herbal 
<br />are also completely safe to self-prescribe, because they are 
<br />'natural'. This is not the case; homeopathy is safe because everything 
<br />is very very dilute; many herbal remedies and supplements can cause 
<br />lasting damage if not taken carefully. 
<br /><br />When people use homeopathy 
<br />-------------------------------------------- 
<br />Most people first come to homeopathy when they feel they've been 
<br />failed by conventional medicine. It may be for a long-held, chronic 
<br />condition, or a short lived acute ailment. It may be that conventional 
<br />medicine has been unable to help at all, or that the side effects are 
<br />simply not worth the risk. 
<br /><br />This was from our survey in September 2003: 
<br /><br />For what do you most often use Homeopathy? 
<br />Long term illnesses which conventional medicine has been unable to treat 29% 
<br />Long term illnesses which conventional medicine is able to treat, but 
<br />with major side effects 16% 
<br />Long term illnesses which conventional medicine is able to treat, with 
<br />no side effects 12% 
<br /><br />Minor short term illnesses 39% 
<br />I've not yet used it 4% 
<br /><br />You can see that of those who use homeopathy on long term illnesses, 
<br />most do so because conventional medicine has been unable to treat 
<br />them, and a much smaller number use homeopathy to avoid the side 
<br />effects of conventional medicine. 
<br /><br />Long Term and Short Term - Chronic and Acute 
<br /><br />Long term (chronic) illnesses are deeper rooted than short term 
<br />(acute) illnesses, and are consequently more difficult to treat 
<br />successfully at home - normally guidance from a homeopath should be 
<br />sought. 
<br /><br />Short term illnesses can be treated much more successfully at home, by 
<br />a layperson. 
<br /><br />And finally, as you become more confident at treating conditions at 
<br />home, don't get over-confident. Stopping prescribed medication without 
<br />first consulting a physician can endanger your health. If symptoms 
<br />persist, always seek professional medical attention. Bear in mind that 
<br />even minor symptoms can be a sign of a more serious underlying 
<br />condition, and a timely diagnosis by your doctor could save your life.
<br /><br />[Excerpt]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d57bb4f1c7f4609a9b60c3ad28952a75" url=""><![CDATA[How does Homoeopathy work?<br/><br/>1] According to Dr. Willmar Schwabe, Karlsruhe, of West Germany:
<br />&quot;Homoeopathy (= Homoeotherapy) represents a particular form of
<br />medicational stimulation therapy. The prefix homoeo- means that the
<br />stimulation in question corresponds in similarity to the individual
<br />symptom produced by the disease to be treated.&quot;
<br /><br />2] &quot;Homoeopathy is described as a specifically determined or
<br />organ-specific threshold stimulation therapy. Both terms mean the
<br />same. It is the aim of this therapy to produce a &quot;reactivation&quot; or
<br />stimulation of the autoregulatory activity in the organism, which is
<br />not, however, of a general nature, but specifically directed or
<br />specialized in line with the pathological process in hand.
<br />Therapeutically specification may here be directed at a particular
<br />organ, a certain class of tissue, or the patient as a whole,
<br />respectively.&quot;
<br /><br />3] &quot;Regardless of its wide range of indications, homoeotherapy does
<br />not claim to be the best and only correct method of treating diseases
<br />in all cases. It is not a universal therapy or monotherapy, but one
<br />method of treatment among many. For example, homoeopathy is not able
<br />to simply replace or make unnecessary such forms as surgery, dietary
<br />treatment, chemotherapy, immunotherapy, psychotherapy and others.&quot;
<br /><br />4] &quot;From this position, it is a matter of course in homoeopathy that
<br />the physician using homeopathy finds himself in exactly the same
<br />obligation as any other of his colleagues when it comes to applying
<br />diagnostic methods for clarification in each and every case of
<br />disease.&quot;
<br /><br />5] &quot;It is this diagnostic obligation as well as the duty to select and
<br />apply the most suitable and indicated therapeutical method, which make
<br />it necessary that homoeotherapy be applied with all scientific
<br />responsibility.&quot;
<br /><br />[Excerpt]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a10f8e51c53a1be30bad8d65fdc7ca5" url=""><![CDATA[ZIKRULLAH - QUR’ANIC PERSPECTIVE<br/><br/>Zikrullah is the process of implanting the glories of Allah in the hearts of mankind, in the true spirit of the Noble Qur’an. They will hold aloft the shaft of science with one hand for spanning the world spaces with supersonic speed and with the other the shaft of supra-science for the steepest climb of the heart – the climb steeper than the icy steep of the Everest peak, of the steep apogee of the moon, the Mars and other celestial orbs in the planetary or stellar orbits. This steepest steep is beyond the ken of human brain but within the ambit of the human heart, the steepest height of the spiritual plane where only the justice (‘adl) of Allah and selfless services (ihsan) for God’s sake alone prevail. They liquidate greed, self-aggrandizement and wars of annihilation on the one hand, and on the other, slavery, hunger, destitution, disease, ignorance and all miseries of the body and the mind. The Noble Qur’an declares:
<br /><br />He has not yet attempted the steepest Steep. And, what is that Steep? Manumission of man from all kinds of slavery and drudgery or supply of adequate provision for feeding on a day of hunger, to an orphan – of close or distant relation, or a needy man dust-ridden (so as to liquidate misery for good from the face of the earth). And further on, he becomes one of those who have acquired the infinite power of faith and who inspire one another to remain steadfast and inspire one another to be gentle and benign. They are the fraternity of the right hand (Surah al-Balad/ 90: 12-18).
<br /><br />The climb up the spiritual plane must be co-operative and universal with no stay-behinds and no stragglers. The guiding motto of the climb in Islam is ‘everyone for all and all for the hindermost’. Obviously this climb can be only in the realm of the heart. It is purely spiritual.
<br /><br />[Excerpt]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="caedc0b8fc496cf52c2d4b9c929213a4" url=""><![CDATA[HUMANS FOR HUMANITY<br/><br/>Human beings are members of a whole,
<br />In creation of one essence and soul.
<br /><br />If one member is afflicted with pain,
<br />Other members uneasy will remain.
<br /><br /><strong>If you have no sympathy for human pain,
<br />The name of human you cannot retain.</strong>
<br /><br />Sheikh Saadi (in Persian: ????, full name in English: Muslih-ud-Din
<br />Mushrif ibn Abdullah) (1184 – 1283) is one of the major Persian
<br />poets of the medieval period. He is recognised not only for the
<br />quality of his writing, but also for the depth of his social thought.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8c7bbad658958b75487c27b87f94b90f" url=""><![CDATA[YOU CAN HELP TO SAVE MILLIONS LIVES.<br/><br/>PLEASE LET YOUR FRIENDS KNOW ABOUT THIS VERY USEFUL BOOK ABOUT HEALTH.
<br /><br />Medical knowledge should not be a guarded secret of a select few, but should be freely shared by everyone. ~ David Werner, Click below link to see &quot;Where There Is No Doctor&quot;.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hesperian.org%2Fmm5%2Fmerchant.mvc%3FStore_Code%3DHB%26amp%3BScreen%3DPROD%26amp%3BProduct_Code%3DB010R"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.hesperian.org/mm5/merchant.mvc?Store_Code=HB&amp;Screen=PROD&amp;Product_Code=B010R</a>
<br /><br />What good is all that wealth and success if you don't have good health? 
<br /><br />Cultivate the spirit of immeasurable love within you even as the love the mother feels for her child. ~ Buddha
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>