<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="b6b1e4f04130c231f5872015b5c11637" url=""><![CDATA[6th SiNELAB WORKSHOP SERIES starts jan 19<br/><br/>6th SiNELAB WORKSHOP SERIES starts jan 19
<br /><br />6th SiNELAB WORKSHOP SERIES / AS REQUESTED REGISTRATION ONGOING
<br />@ IFC Independent Filmmakers Cooperative Office
<br />#21 Kamias Road, Quezon City
<br />Workshop Outline : 8 Sessions
<br /><br />I. Material &amp; Script Development and Management (Narrative)
<br />( 3 Sessions)
<br />Mdf. Escarcha (instructor)
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP ONE : THE VISION AND THE ARTISTIC MODEL
<br />1. Who are the stakeholders of the vision?
<br />2. Is the vision relevant?
<br />3. What are the costs and benefits of the vision?
<br />4. What are the form and the substance of the vision?
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP TWO : FORMULATING AN IDEA
<br />An idea is a basic unit in constructing a working concept.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP THREE : BUILDING A CONCEPT
<br />The idea is the seed of the material while the concept is the cradle
<br />of the idea.
<br />1. Subject
<br />2. Genre
<br />3. Design
<br />4. Pattern of the Material
<br />5. Approach to Reality
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP FOUR : CONSTRUCTING THE PREMISE
<br />The premise has two components namely the character and the story.
<br />The said components operate within the structure of the premise.
<br />Often, the logline or pitching line comes from the premise.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP FIVE : CONSTRUCTING THE OUTLINE
<br />The outline has 8 major parts called movements.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP SIX : THE SEQUENCE TREATMENT
<br />The sequence treatment bridges the outline and the script. The
<br />treatment determines how many sequences will it take to execute a
<br />movement.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP SEVEN THE SCRIPT : FORMAT
<br />The script is made-up of 7 major parts.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP THREE : ELEMENTS OF THE SCRIPT
<br />The script has 5 elements.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP FOUR : SCENE BUILDING
<br />A. Structural Direction of A Scene
<br />B. Types of Scenes
<br />C. Visual Devices
<br /><br />II Alternative Production
<br />(5 Sessions)
<br />Mike Dagñalan (instructor)
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY 1
<br />1. -what is your project/genre?
<br />2. -financial capability
<br />3. -requirements
<br />4. -production staff/hierarchy
<br />5. -responsibilities
<br />6. -logistics
<br />7. -terms used
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY 2
<br />1. -pre-production process
<br />2. -production process
<br />3. -post production
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY 3
<br />1. -scheduling
<br />2. -traffic
<br />3. -getting the right crew/supplier
<br />4. -transportation
<br />5. -food
<br />6. -production design/props
<br />7. -casting
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY4
<br />• actual pre-production
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY5
<br />• actual production
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY6
<br />• actual post production
<br /><br />SiNELAB WORKSHOP SERIES
<br />@ IFC Independent Filmmakers Cooperative Office
<br />#21 Kamias Road, Quezon City
<br />(landmark : near the senior pedro lechon manok)
<br /><br />Starts First Week of January 2008
<br />Weekends : 8 Sessions : Fee - 6,000 pesos
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sinelab.blogspot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.sinelab.blogspot.com</a>
<br /><br />For Registration: Please indicate full name and contact number
<br />e-mail address: sinelab_workshop@...
<br />mobile phobe : 09215081060
<br /><br />Note that the fee of 6,000 pesos covers both Material and Script
<br />Development &amp; Management and Alternative Production. This is our
<br />commitment at Sinelab to come up with a complete basic package at a
<br />reasonable fee. Furthermore, there are two payment schemes under the
<br />workshop.
<br /><br />1. You can pay the full fee on the first day of the workshop.
<br />2. Installment Scheme / You can pay 50% of the fee on the 1st
<br />day. 25% on the 2nd day and 25% 3rd day.
<br /><br />For Details : Check out the following sites
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sinelab.blogspot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.sinelab.blogspot.com</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgroups.yahoo.com%2Fgroup%2Fsinelab_workshop"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://groups.yahoo.com/group/sinelab_workshop</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a4d3abbda2de99be34274f5d56cdca1d" url=""><![CDATA[Anime, Anima and Animus<br/><br/>Anime, Anima and Animus 
<br /><br />Carl Jung, a psychologist noted for analytic psychology, postulated an unconscious structure that represented the cross-sexual part of the psyche of each individual.  He referred to this structure as the anima for men and the animus for women.  The anima or the animus is not the conscious male or female self-image.  Rather, it serves as a focus for all psychological material that does not fit with an individual's conscious self-image as a woman or as a man.
<br /><br />In character construction, sex and sexuality are among the important components in determining a character's behavior.  A character has its own conscious self-image of a masculine hero.  But at the same time, his anima may include qualities that do not fit this conscious self-image.  The same holds true for women.
<br /><br />The dynamics of anima or animus is clearly exhibited in the Disney Feature Mulan.  Wherein, the principal character's conscious self-image of a woman differs from her unconscious self-image.  Here lies the conflict of the material, a character that challenges an existing social order that affects gender in terms of actions and activities. 
<br /><br />In Mulan's case, she has a definitive image of a man imprinted in her unconscious called the archetype.   Oriented towards inner processes, this archetype is one of the most influential regulators of behavior that mediates between unconscious and conscious processes. It contains all the ancestral experiences of a male or a female and impression made by man or woman. The archetype manifests itself through dreams and fantasies as figures of the opposite sex.
<br /><br />An individual's relationship with the opposite sex affects the development of the anima or animus. Mulan's father, for instance, influenced Mulan's animus. Thus, as Mulan defines herself in feminine terms, her animus, will include disjointed tendencies and experiences that she defined as masculine.   
<br /><br />As this disjointed tendencies and experiences mix with this conscious feminine definition, the idea of a feminine warrior emerges from the psyche. Mulan is able to reconcile the masculine warrior fighting skills with the feminine touch. Therefore, the quality of a fragile feminine form becomes an advantage because it conceals the masculine warrior fighting skills in the battlefield. 
<br /><br />The dynamics of the anima or animus is a feature often observed in eastern animation materials. Mulan, as an eastern animation material is a good example for this observation. Often, we observe Anime characters that engage in cross-sexual dynamics in terms of emotional and physical form and function.  A hero may look masculine but does feminine functions. Or a heroine may look fragile and reserve but kills people in cold blood. We do not see this, in general, in western animation where male and female stereotypes tend to dominate the western psyche. 
<br /><br />Perhaps this is the reason why Anime materials tend to go beyond gender boundaries. Men and women are able to relate with the same hero or heroine because of this cross-sexual dynamic. What we have is a situation wherein characters have features that appeal to both women and men and at the same reconcile gender aversions and transforms them into attractions.
<br /><br />Getting to know your character, in terms of animus or anima, is a good way of understanding its psyche.  The more we are familiar with the psyche, the more efficient we are able to determine the character's behavior relative to the human actions and activities. Anime, animus and anima, cross-sexual dynamics that often create interesting characters that capture the hearts and minds of both men and women
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6cb3fbad9248e1d935bdca8789690911" url=""><![CDATA[Music Video for Tonight, Tonight by The Smashin... (more)<br/><br/>Music Video for Tonight, Tonight by The Smashing P
<br /><br />Tonight, Tonight Lyrics
<br /><br />Time is never time at all
<br />You can never ever leave without leaving a piece of youth
<br />And our lives are forever changed
<br />We will never be the same
<br />The more you change the less you feel
<br /><br />Believe, believe in me, believe
<br />Believe that life can change
<br />That youre not stuck in vain
<br />Were not the same, were different tonight
<br />Tonight, so bright
<br />Tonight
<br /><br />And you know youre never sure
<br />But youre sure you could be right
<br />If you held yourself up to the light
<br />And the embers never fade in your city by the lake
<br />The place where you were born
<br /><br />Believe, believe in me, believe
<br />Believe in the resolute urgency of now
<br />And if you believe theres not a chance tonight
<br />Tonight, so bright
<br />Tonight
<br /><br />Well crucify the insincere tonight
<br />Well make things right, well feel it all tonight
<br />Well find a way to offer up the night tonight
<br />The indescribable moments of your life tonight
<br />The impossible is possible tonight
<br />Believe in me as I believe in you, tonight
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1a0a8df7389976c6db3447909f8fd1ec" url=""><![CDATA[MIS Net Education Character Design and Animation<br/><br/>MIS Net Education  
<br /><br />MIS Net Education is launching a program geared towards Original Content Character Design and Animation. This is the first program ever in the Philippines wherein creativity and technical knowledge of software and hardware are combined to come up with a contemporary program that answers to the immediate needs of the global animation industry and market. I am happy that MIS Net Education shares this Forum's desire to promote Filipino art and craft through original content animation. 
<br /><br />Please check out their site : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.misnet-education.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.misnet-education.com</a> or you can call  Juliet Chua @ 7512871
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="718b24c29fd9012aaf59801ef1e1b065" url=""><![CDATA[Animation Workers Unite!<br/><br/>Animation Workers Unite! 
<br /><br />Manual labor is the driving force in any outsourcing industry. Foreign enterprises need cheap and passive sources of labor to operate manual procedures and processes. But, third world countries are unaware that these enterprises are constantly developing technologies that will eventually eliminate manual labor in their corporate set-up. 
<br /><br />Say for example, in the outsourcing sub-industry called Animation Services, the bread and butter of Animation firms comes from the unprotected and underpaid labor output of animation workers. These are creative individuals exploited by our enterprising &quot;kababayans&quot; in animation sweatshops. Wherein animation workers are alienated from their work and often cheated from &quot;real&quot; compensation that they rightly deserve. 
<br /><br />Press releases coming from proponents of this &quot;business&quot; argue that the potential revenue such business will generate is significant.  But who will benefit from this potential revenue? Is it the animation workers? I do not think so. The big winners in this cycle of exploitation are the foreign animation studios who rely heavily on animation sweatshops in order to reduce their overheads. To make the story a cliche, fellow Filipinos are facilitating this system of exploitation. 
<br /><br />Animation firms engaging in animation services do not translate into a real animation industry and market. They are not the building blocks of what we aspire to be a genuine institution that nurtures original creativity and indigenous technological development in both hardware and software for animation.  It is a plain and simple cash cow economic strategy for those willing to engage in 'modern day slavery&quot;.
<br /><br />I have nothing against with animation firms but when they claim that they are here to help the Filipino People and build an Industry, I immediately draw the line. Yes, they provide employment but do they provide real employment? Does this economic exercise promote vertical or lateral movement in terms of employment? 
<br /><br />Animation Workers in the Philippine with a spirited voice I tell you that exploitation is not a lifestyle. It is an anomaly. It is against the law. It is against human morality. Stop the madness and unite. Do not expect these people will help you out in achieving proper compensation as well as protection and benefits. I urge you to fight back and regain your dignity. You are not a slave!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1bcab27479d407d4147e2d888b2e8fd5" url=""><![CDATA[Digital Movie Scriptwriting Tips : Keep It Simple!<br/><br/>Digital Movie Scriptwriting Tips : Keep It Simple!
<br /><br />When I started practicing my craft in the mainstream film industry, creative managers always tell me to think big. The practicality behind this suggestion is based on the notion that the process within material development and management is geared towards the trimming down of any idea. Meaning, if your idea is small, as it goes through the process, it will eventually disappear.  
<br /><br />The &quot;trimming down effect&quot; of the process is a direct link between artistic creativity and economic soundness.  &quot;Doing Film&quot; is an expensive enterprise, thus, individuals involved in the process make sure that the idea fits a certain mold the will yield the highest return on investment. 
<br /><br />Economic convention dictates that when you have low expenditures and high revenues, the end result is high profit margins.  Thus, if the idea is real and not just good, the trimming down effect of the process assures a predictable and consistent expenditure curve. 
<br /><br />The above paragraph may sound complex but in practice it is simple. The mainstream film industry is always adverse to big ideas because it is so expensive to execute such ideas. So, in order to maintain a certain level of economic profitability, trimming down a big idea into a manageable simple idea is a priority.
<br /><br />But the trimming down effect does not exist in the Digital Movie Industry. In fact, what is encouraged is to come up with small or simple ideas.   What happens next is what I call &quot;the napoleon effect&quot;. Meaning, as the idea goes through the process of material development and management, it slowly gains &quot;new elements&quot;&quot; and transforms itself into a big idea. 
<br /><br />The Napoleon Effect, just like the trimming down effect, is a direct link between artistic creativity and economic soundness. Bottlomline, it is less expensive to produce a digital movie compared to a movie that uses film as a media platform. Furthermore, the digital technology is far more forgiving as a media platform with regards to production or post-productions errors. 
<br /><br />If you will have a survey of Digital Movies, generally you will notice that Digital Movies that did well often have simple ideas behind them. And Digital Movies with Big Ideas tend to be flops. So next time, when you come up with ideas for digital movies, make it simple and let the process kick in.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3113d26b76583fabbd8137c77c987f53" url=""><![CDATA[Korea-Philippines IT Center : animation<br/><br/>Korea-Philippines IT Center : The New Moving Force In The Original Content Animation 
<br /><br />The Korea-Philippines IT Center is the new moving force in the original content animation in the Philippines. Proponents of the said institution plan to  launch a unified animation program that will cover, in a complete manner, the animation production process this coming year 2008. Under the said unified program, students will learn the creative and technological components of the pre-production, production and the post production procedures.
<br /><br />Future plans include, hope it will materialize, an animation learning school for High School Students patterned after the Philippine Science High School/ Philippine High School For The Arts and a genuine Animation Festival that will only cater to original content animation.  2008 is an exciting year for original content animation. Please support this endeavor by spreading this news to all students and schools. We are in a crossroad, we need to unite to stop the exploitation of animation workers by animation firms and support the construction of a genuine and robust Philippine Animation Industry and Market.
<br /><br />For more information, you can visit this website :<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.korphil.ph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.korphil.ph</a> or you can contact KORPHIL IT Center at these numbers 9384532 or  9383651 and look for J. Mendoza or J. Maza
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d2323a7da7b9fbc33b3b06aaf62b3925" url=""><![CDATA[E.I.A : Educational Interactive Animation<br/><br/>E.I.A : Educational Interactive Animation 
<br /><br />E.I. A or Educational Interactive Animation refers to the combined knowledge that emanates from education, animation and interactive technology. Currently, EIA is a staple feature in Western Educational Systems. In the Philippines, EIA is relatively new. In fact, companies engaging in this field is less than 1 percent of the total corporate population.
<br /><br />EIA has several branches that cover pre-school up to special education programs. This field is encouraging for animation and multimedia studios. The possibility in capturing Southeast Asian Market is not impossible. 
<br /><br />Unfortunately, companies that are currently doing EIA activities are incapable of developing high quality EIA products. This is due to the inherent monopoly due to the lack of other players in this field. Perhaps, this is your chance to explore this side of interactive animation
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6cc015d3b9f2174ee47e38b9f209e9f7" url=""><![CDATA[Korea-Philippines IT Center : Animation<br/><br/>Korea-Philippines IT Center : The New Moving Force In The Original Content Animation 
<br /><br />The Korea-Philippines IT Center is the new moving force in the original content animation in the Philippines. Proponents of the said institution plan to  launch a unified animation program that will cover, in a complete manner, the animation production process this coming year 2008. Under the said unified program, students will learn the creative and technological components of the pre-production, production and the post production procedures.
<br /><br />Future plans include, hope it will materialize, an animation learning school for High School Students patterned after the Philippine Science High School/ Philippine High School For The Arts and a genuine Animation Festival that will only cater to original content animation.  2008 is an exciting year for original content animation. Please support this endeavor by spreading this news to all students and schools. We are in a crossroad, we need to unite to stop the exploitation of animation workers by animation firms and support the construction of a genuine and robust Philippine Animation Industry and Market.
<br /><br />For more information, you can visit this website :<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.korphil.ph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.korphil.ph</a> or you can contact KORPHIL IT Center at these numbers 9384532 or  9383651 and look for J. Mendoza or J. Maza
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f13d48a48fd69fb26cd516bc20463538" url=""><![CDATA[MIS Net Education : Original Content : Character Design<br/><br/>MIS Net Education : Original Content : Character Design and Character Animation School
<br /><br />MIS Net Education is launching a program geared towards Original Content Character Design and Animation. This is the first program ever in the Philippines wherein creativity and technical knowledge of software and hardware are combined to come up with a contemporary program that answers to the immediate needs of the global animation industry and market. I am happy that MIS Net Education shares this Forum's desire to promote Filipino art and craft through original content animation. 
<br /><br />Please check out their site : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.misnet-education.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.misnet-education.com</a> or you can call  Juliet Chua @ 7512871
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fa20799e5312760c9411877a4df2e2" url=""><![CDATA[The 1st Original Content Animation School<br/><br/>The 1st Original Content Animation School : Multi-disciplinary 
<br /><br />To those who are interested to learn animation as an art,
<br />science,business­, medium and visual document... all you need to do is
<br />to send an email to this address
<br /><br />Maila Fermil
<br />Business Director of MindTap Studios
<br />mlfermil@yaho­o.com
<br /><br />This is a radical approach in terms of teaching genuine original
<br />content animation to both professionals and students. This is the
<br />first animation school that is implementing animation workshops that
<br />cover the different creative and technical procedures within the
<br />animation production at a reasonable rate.
<br /><br />Included in this animation school is the revised Basic 2-D Animation
<br />Material &amp; Script Development and Management Workshop ( Original
<br />Content/Narr­ative Application - Short Feature &amp; Feature)
<br /><br />If you feel that animation is a craft or an art, then this school is
<br />for you.
<br />Join in :
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgroups.yahoo.com%2Fgroup%2Fakiras_nightmare"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://groups.yahoo.com/group/akiras_nightmare</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fprofiles.friendster.com%2F32450630"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://profiles.friendster.com/32450630</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fakirasnightmare.multiply.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://akirasnightmare.multiply.com/</a>
<br /><br />check out
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindtap-ph.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mindtap-ph.com</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mobytoons.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mobytoons.com</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbottleduphiroshima.blogspot.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://bottleduphiroshima.blogspot.com/</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.abma-forums.tk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.abma-forums.tk/</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fakirasnightmare.blogspot.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://akirasnightmare.blogspot.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a2e130271521b529397b86399f6246a0" url=""><![CDATA[Intermediate Material and Screenplay<br/><br/>Intermediate Material and Screenplay Development &amp; Management ( starts April 2008) 
<br /><br />Intermediate Material and Screenplay Development &amp; Management
<br />Romantic Tragedy : Combined Genre
<br />Digital Movie Application - Narrative (Short/Short Feature/Feature)
<br />Creative Workshop April 2008
<br /><br />Parameters of the Workshop:
<br />1. Intermediate Material and Screenplay Development and Management
<br />Creative Workshop pertains to the structural and integral relationship
<br />between premise and genre.
<br />2. The workshop will tackle Romantic Tragedy as a combined genre.
<br />3. Because of the limited space of the venue, the Writer's Project
<br />will only accept 6 participants.
<br />4. Qualified participants are those who already took-up basic
<br />scriptwriting workshops in different training or academic venues.
<br />5. Certificates will be given at the end of the workshop provided that
<br />a participant finished the workshop with output.
<br />6. The Output is a Working Outline for a Digital Movie Feature (90
<br />minutes or 1hour/30mins). The Working Outline refers to a complete
<br />narrative material with 8 movements written on one page.
<br />7. Note: the profile of the lecturer is included in the e-group files.
<br /><br />Schedule/Venue
<br />1. The workshop will start April (summer 2008)
<br /><br />2. 5 Sessions
<br />3. Saturdays : 11am-2pm (3hrs.)
<br /><br />Payment Scheme:
<br />1. The fee is 5,500 pesos
<br />2. 50% down on the 1st day, 25% on the 2nd day and 25% on the 3rd day
<br />3. Participants who will pay the full amount on the first day will
<br />only pay 5,000 pesos.
<br /><br />1.  Text this mobile no  09215081060 and send the following:
<br />&amp;#61550; Basic Scriptwriting Workshop Attended
<br />&amp;#61550; Name
<br />&amp;#61550; Address
<br />&amp;#61550; Landline
<br />The above information should be complete and is subject to verification.
<br />2  The text message that you sent will serve as your registration.
<br /><br />Workshop Outline:
<br />1st Intermediate Material and Screenplay
<br />Development &amp; Management
<br />Romantic Tragedy : Combined Genre
<br />Digital Movie Application - Narrative (Short/Short Feature/Feature)
<br />Creative Workshop April 2008
<br /><br />Day 01 : Combined Genre : Romantic Tragedy
<br />1. Definition
<br />2. Genre Structure
<br />3. Genre Components
<br /><br />Day 02 : Premise
<br />1. Definition
<br />2. Premise Structure
<br />3. Premise Components
<br /><br />Day 03 : Premise vs. Genre
<br />1. Structural Relationship
<br />2. Relationship Between Components
<br />3. Written Exercise A
<br /><br />Day 04: Outline : 8 Movements Method
<br />1. Definition
<br />2. Structure
<br />3. Components
<br />4. Theoretical Integration
<br />5. Constructing the Diagram
<br />6. Execution
<br />7. Written Exercise B
<br /><br />Day 05: Outline vs. Sequence Treatment &amp; Screenplay
<br />1. Theoretical Integration
<br />2. Constructing the Diagram
<br />3. Execution
<br />4. Final Evaluation of the Working Outline
<br /><br />Intermediate Material &amp; Screenplay Development and Management Module
<br />is the property of SiNELAB : Sinehang Laboratoryo Workshop Series
<br />under the supervision of Sinelab Writer's Project. For more
<br />information about SiNELAB, comments and suggestions, check out the
<br />following website, blog and web accounts:
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sinelab.blogspot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.sinelab.blogspot.com</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsinelab.multiply.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://sinelab.multiply.com/</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgroups.yahoo.com%2Fgroup%2Fsinelab_workshop"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://groups.yahoo.com/group/sinelab_workshop</a>
<br /><br />You are also welcome to join a budding open web group for Digital
<br />Movie Scriptwriters. This open group is for writers who exclusively
<br />write for the Digital Movie Industry and Market. Unlike Screenwriters,
<br />Digital Movie Scriptwriters construct materials and scripts based on
<br />the potentials and limitations of the Science and Technology of the
<br />Digital Movie Industry and Market. Click this website and join.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fforum2007.multiply"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://forum2007.multiply</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e034abfa17211a6083cde572cadeac5a" url=""><![CDATA[7th SiNELAB WORKSHOP SERIES (MARCH 2008)<br/><br/>7th SiNELAB WORKSHOP SERIES (MARCH 2008)
<br />Workshop Outline : 8 Sessions
<br /><br />I. Material &amp; Script Development and Management (Narrative)
<br />( 3 Sessions)
<br />Mdf. Escarcha (instructor)
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP ONE : THE VISION AND THE ARTISTIC MODEL
<br />1. Who are the stakeholders of the vision?
<br />2. Is the vision relevant?
<br />3. What are the costs and benefits of the vision?
<br />4. What are the form and the substance of the vision?
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP TWO : FORMULATING AN IDEA
<br />An idea is a basic unit in constructing a working concept.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP THREE : BUILDING A CONCEPT
<br />The idea is the seed of the material while the concept is the cradle
<br />of the idea.
<br />1. Subject
<br />2. Genre
<br />3. Design
<br />4. Pattern of the Material
<br />5. Approach to Reality
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP FOUR : CONSTRUCTING THE PREMISE
<br />The premise has two components namely the character and the story.
<br />The said components operate within the structure of the premise.
<br />Often, the logline or pitching line comes from the premise.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP FIVE : CONSTRUCTING THE OUTLINE
<br />The outline has 8 major parts called movements.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP SIX : THE SEQUENCE TREATMENT
<br />The sequence treatment bridges the outline and the script. The
<br />treatment determines how many sequences will it take to execute a
<br />movement.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP SEVEN THE SCRIPT : FORMAT
<br />The script is made-up of 7 major parts.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP THREE : ELEMENTS OF THE SCRIPT
<br />The script has 5 elements.
<br /><br />&amp;#61550; STEP FOUR : SCENE BUILDING
<br />A. Structural Direction of A Scene
<br />B. Types of Scenes
<br />C. Visual Devices
<br /><br />II Alternative Production
<br />(5 Sessions)
<br />Mike Dagñalan (instructor)
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY 1
<br />1. -what is your project/genre?
<br />2. -financial capability
<br />3. -requirements
<br />4. -production staff/hierarchy
<br />5. -responsibilities
<br />6. -logistics
<br />7. -terms used
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY 2
<br />1. -pre-production process
<br />2. -production process
<br />3. -post production
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY 3
<br />1. -scheduling
<br />2. -traffic
<br />3. -getting the right crew/supplier
<br />4. -transportation
<br />5. -food
<br />6. -production design/props
<br />7. -casting
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY4
<br />• actual pre-production
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY5
<br />• actual production
<br /><br />&amp;#61558; DAY6
<br />• actual post production
<br /><br />SiNELAB WORKSHOP SERIES
<br />@ IFC Independent Filmmakers Cooperative Office
<br />#21 Kamias Road, Quezon City
<br />(landmark : near the senior pedro lechon manok)
<br /><br />Starts First Week of January 2008
<br />Weekends : 8 Sessions : Fee - 6,000 pesos
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sinelab.blogspot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.sinelab.blogspot.com</a>
<br /><br />For Registration: Please indicate full name and contact number
<br />e-mail address: <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=sinelab_workshop@yahoo.com">sinelab_workshop@yahoo.com</a>
<br />mobile phobe : 09215081060
<br /><br />Note that the fee of 6,000 pesos covers both Material and Script
<br />Development &amp; Management and Alternative Production. This is our
<br />commitment at Sinelab to come up with a complete basic package at a
<br />reasonable fee. Furthermore, there are two payment schemes under the
<br />workshop.
<br /><br />1. You can pay the full fee on the first day of the workshop.
<br />2. Installment Scheme / You can pay 50% of the fee on the 1st
<br />day. 25% on the 2nd day and 25% 3rd day.
<br /><br />For Details : Check out the following sites
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sinelab.blogspot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.sinelab.blogspot.com</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgroups.yahoo.com%2Fgroup%2Fsinelab_workshop"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://groups.yahoo.com/group/sinelab_workshop</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c0955b82063276c2b69d2bfa59d415ee" url=""><![CDATA[Southeast Asian Animation Forum<br/><br/>Southeast Asian Animation Forum	
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsaaf08.multiply.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://saaf08.multiply.com/</a>
<br /><br />We believe that Animation is a global industry and market.  Global powerhouses in animation like Japan and the United States have already dominated the market, making it difficult for small animation studios to make its mark in the global market. In this regard, the economic phenomena of regional groupings is an essential tool for small animation studios to have a competitive edge. This forum is making the initial step to form &quot;The Southeast Asian Animation Forum&quot;.  The forum seeks to link small animation studios, animation schools and animation students and professionals within ASEAN Member Sates.  This forum hopes that this small step will gradually snowball to a better regional cooperation that seeks to develop and manage animation in the Southeast Asian Region.
<br /><br />(send email address at <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=palarisconvention@yahoo.com">palarisconvention@yahoo.com</a> so that I can add you in the said forum)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="77de285ba97208bd4608aace2099c945" url=""><![CDATA[Southeast Asian Animation Forum<br/><br/>Southeast Asian Animation Forum	
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsaaf08.multiply.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://saaf08.multiply.com/</a>
<br /><br />We believe that Animation is a global industry and market.  Global powerhouses in animation like Japan and the United States have already dominated the market, making it difficult for small animation studios to make its mark in the global market. In this regard, the economic phenomena of regional groupings is an essential tool for small animation studios to have a competitive edge. This forum is making the initial step to form &quot;The Southeast Asian Animation Forum&quot;.  The forum seeks to link small animation studios, animation schools and animation students and professionals within ASEAN Member States.  This forum hopes that this small step will gradually snowball to a better regional cooperation that seeks to develop and manage animation in the Southeast Asian Region.
<br /><br />(send email address at <a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=palarisconvention@yahoo.com">palarisconvention@yahoo.com</a> so that I can add you in the said forum)
<br /><br />Check Out These Sites (Original Content Animation)
<br /><br />Original Content Animation Sites
<br />      Join in :
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgroups.yahoo.com%2Fgroup%2Fakiras_nightmare"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://groups.yahoo.com/group/akiras_nightmare</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fprofiles.friendster.com%2F32450630"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://profiles.friendster.com/32450630</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fakirasnightmare.multiply.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://akirasnightmare.multiply.com/</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgroups.yahoo.com%2Fgroup%2Fbrave_new_world%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://groups.yahoo.com/group/brave_new_world/</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tagged.com%2Fakirasnightmare"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.tagged.com/akirasnightmare</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myspace.com%2Fakirasnightmare"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.myspace.com/akirasnightmare</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/clan/brave_new_world" target="_blank">http://en.pan.netcom/clan/brave_new_world</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/akira524" target="_blank">http://en.pan.netcom/akira524</a>
<br /><br />check out
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pixelworx.com.sg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pixelworx.com.sg</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.glitchanimation.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.glitchanimation.com</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeradz.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.freeradz.com</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindtap-ph.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mindtap-ph.com</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mobytoons.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mobytoons.com</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.korphil.ph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.korphil.ph</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.misnet-education.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.misnet-education.com</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbottleduphiroshima.blogspot.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://bottleduphiroshima.blogspot.com/</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.abma-forums.tk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.abma-forums.tk/</a>
<br />      <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fakirasnightmare.blogspot.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://akirasnightmare.blogspot.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3ef6438e75b4de7fdd4c83778fcbd0d" url=""><![CDATA[http://www.mindtap-ph.com<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindtap-ph.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mindtap-ph.com</a>
<br /><br />Mind Tap Studios is the pioneering animation and multimedia group in the  Philippines that introduced the concept of a unified original content animation education. It is such an irony, that this valuable concept came from a small studio but creatively and technically capable studio with a big heart.
<br /><br />In summer 2008, Mind Tap will launch a series, take not &quot;a series&quot;, of animation and multimedia programs directed towards the development and management of original content animation, web design, digital imaging and comic book creative and technical construction. This is a mind blowing push towards its segmented plans to encourage creative and technical individuals to empower themselves through original content  development and management.
<br />========================
<br />Mind Tap Studios has an animation arm called MOBYTOONS, check out their site at
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mobytoons"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mobytoons</a> .com
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mobytoons"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mobytoons</a> .com/user/login?destination=forum
<br /><br />=================TO KNOW MORE ABOUT MIND TAP STUDIOS
<br /><br />The 1st Original Content Animation School : Multi-disciplinary    
<br /><br />To those who are interested to learn animation as an art,
<br />science,business­, medium and visual document... all you need to do is
<br />to send an email to this address
<br /><br />Maila Fermil
<br />Business Director of MindTap Studios
<br />mlfermil@yaho­o.com
<br /><br />This is a radical approach in terms of teaching genuine original
<br />content animation to both professionals and students. This is the
<br />first animation school that is implementing animation workshops that
<br />cover the different creative and technical procedures within the
<br />animation production at a reasonable rate.
<br /><br />Included in this animation school is the revised Basic 2-D Animation
<br />Material &amp; Script Development and Management Workshop ( Original
<br />Content/Narr­ative Application - Short Feature &amp; Feature)
<br /><br />If you feel that animation is a craft or an art, then this school is
<br />for you.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8bca1a5f71c8189671523c897c8440d6" url=""><![CDATA[Korea-Philippines IT Center :<br/><br/>Korea-Philippines IT Center :
<br />Launching Unified Program For Animation
<br /><br />Korea IT Center is launching its unified program for 2D /3D Animation
<br />(pre-production, production and post-production) in Quezon City,
<br />Philippines on March 2008. Their program seeks to correct the initial
<br />error of productionizing animation education in Philippines.
<br />Proponents are passionate in pursuing a unified and solid program in
<br />order to enhance original content animation in the Philippines.
<br /><br />Korea IT Center will also implement support programs that will help
<br />animation studios augment their resources by creating an open source
<br />pool. This is truly a brave move for such an institution. It is
<br />virtually going against organized groups of animation outsourcing
<br />firms and vendors who initially formed a group in order to cement the
<br />animation outsourcing dogma that virtually upholds the spirit of
<br />profit over animation workers welfare and protection. Furthermore,
<br />small studios will be given the fighting chance to challenge existing
<br />conventions through this open source construct.
<br /><br />As part of its unified program, it will spearhead animation workshops
<br />in schools, communities and small animation studios with the intention
<br />of setting up unified animation programs for the said venues.
<br /><br />This is truly a monumental event undertaken by visionaries in the
<br />field of animation. This forum salutes them and will pray for the
<br />eventual success.
<br /><br />================
<br /><br />For more information, you can visit this website
<br />:<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.korphil"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.korphil</a>.­ph or you can contact KORPHIL IT Center at these
<br />numbers 9384532 or 9383651 and look for J. Mendoza or J. Maza
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3bf56cc545f134309bfeba48f452bf2a" url=""><![CDATA[The 7th SiNELAB Workshop Series!(MARCH 02, 2008)<br/><br/>The 7th SiNELAB Workshop Series!
<br />(MARCH 02, 2008)
<br /><br />The SiNELAB Workshop Series is an on-going, out of school, alternative mode of educating the Filipino that he is a great storyteller in the moving-image media of motion pictures.
<br /><br />Coverage of the Workshop:
<br /><br />&quot;BASIC SCREENWRITING &amp; ALTERNATIVE PRODUCTION&quot;
<br /><br />3 sessions : material &amp; script development &amp; management
<br />5 sessions : alternative production
<br /><br />Venue:
<br />Quezon City
<br /><br />Schedule:
<br />Sundays, 2pm-5pm
<br /><br />Fee:
<br />PhP6,000 / 8 Sessions/ covers both the material and script development and management &amp; alternative production.
<br /><br />E-mail Address For Registration/Inquiries:
<br />(<a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=sinelab_workshop@yahoo.com">sinelab_workshop@yahoo.com</a>)
<br />mobile phone :09215081060
<br /><br />* workshop fee for lectures only.
<br />* students are required to finish their short films before graduation.
<br />* Limited slots available.
<br />* Only committed students will be accepted.
<br /><br />check out
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sinelab.blogspot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.sinelab.blogspot.com</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsinelab.multiply.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://sinelab.multiply.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c4dee20ce72d8ae65c5d4877a224f315" url=""><![CDATA[Building An Animation 1 Yr. Diploma Program : Kor-Phil<br/><br/>It is not a walk in the park to build an genuine and robust Animation Diploma Program. It requires of lot of thinking and a lot of contemplating considering that we are starting from scratch.  What is ideal is to come up with a program that is affordable but at the same time robust and &quot;of quality&quot;.  It is essentially quality animation education that is reasonably available to the general population.
<br /><br />The challenge is real and the possibility to overcome it is also real...
<br /><br />===========
<br />For more information about the Unified Animation Education Diploma Program @ Kor-Phil IT Center, you can contact the said individuals:
<br /><br />For more information, you can visit this website
<br />:<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.korphil"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.korphil</a>.­ph or you can contact KORPHIL IT Center at these
<br />numbers 9384532 or 9383651 and look for J. Mendoza or J. Maza
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="94b5d9e8c7a31317b2c4cfd5e3c79b74" url=""><![CDATA[4th Akira's Nightmare Basic Animation Scriptwriting Worksho<br/><br/>4th Akira's Nightmare Basic Animation Scriptwriting Workshop
<br />Re-Launching The 4th Akiras Nightmare Animation Basic
<br /><br />Akira's Nightmare was created 2 years ago to develop animation writers. This is the vision behind its desire to enhance the spirit of original content animation. But somehow, this vision was side-tracked by several distractions. Perhaps, I was a bit hasty in trying to expand the basic animation scriptwriting series into a full-blown animation pre-production program. For this, I apologize specially to those who believed in the initial program of this forum but was disappointed by its sudden evolution into a different entity.
<br /><br />The general economic difficulties of our nation, the silent assaults of elements that are oppose to original content animation development &amp; management and the covert unhealthy reactions of animation services proponents... truly contributed to the difficulties in giving the animation pre-production program the adequate spine to stand on its on.
<br /><br />The forum is going back to its roots and will adjust to the call of the times specially to the numerous requests made by individuals who believe in the goals of this Forum. In this regard, the Forum re-launching 4th AKIRA'S NIGHTMARE ANIMATION SCRIPTWRITING WORKSHOP SERIES ( MAINSTREAM APPLICATION)/ Month Of May. This new workshop series will focus on four distinct fields namely;
<br /><br />1. Animation Material Development and Management
<br />2. Animation Beat Outline Development and Management
<br />3. Animation Treatment Development and Management
<br />4. Animation Script Development and Management
<br /><br />Given the economic difficulties that our nation is facing, the workshop fee will be 4,000 pesos/ installment basis. The program will cover six sessions during weekends only so that it can cater to animation professionals and students. The venue will be situated at the center of Quezon City to facilitate for greater access.
<br /><br />The newly improved program will aid animation professionals create commercial animation contents that are within the contemporary sense and sensibility of the general population. For students ( UP, La Salle - St. Benilde, UST and Ateneo) who are about to take up their multimedia-animation thesis projects or are preparing for their thesis projects, the workshop will serve as a tutorial aid in order to augment their needs to finish their respective projects.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="63178ef34a905387de9bed5ff014d95e" url=""><![CDATA[The Growing Movement In Original Content Animation<br/><br/>I have this feeling that original content development and management in animation is slowly, with extreme emphasis, attracting more attention.  For me, this is wonderful news.   There are two main original content training grounds that are accessable to the public right now.  
<br /><br />The School of Arts and Animation is located at Magallanes, Makati City. To be specific, the school is under the Asia Pacific College.  This school is offering a unified program, from pre-production, production, post production and overviews with regards to marketing, distribution and exhibition.  You can visit their website for more information :
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindtap-ph.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mindtap-ph.com</a>
<br /><br />Korea-Philippines IT Center is a foundation under TESDA and the Quezon City Local Government. The said foundation is located at the QCPU Campus, Novaliches, Quezon City.  Currently, the center is applying animation pre-production course to its existing programs for both 2D and 3D Animations. You can visit their website for more information :
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.korphil.ph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.korphil.ph</a> 
<br /><br />I hope that more schools and more private groups will have the courage to explore original content development and management in animation. Through original content, we will be able to slowly build a more viable, genuine  and competitive animation industry and market.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="727ebbccd45d7a6637d460eb1c0b080" url=""><![CDATA[School of the Arts and Animation<br/><br/><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/31930704_15601588_10341633.jpg" /> 
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindtap-ph.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mindtap-ph.com</a>
<br /><br />* In ANIMA: Creating 3D Animated Shorts
<br /><br />(Special Program)
<br /><br />This intense one-year training program on 3D animation focuses on technical skills vis-a-vis the conceptual component of creating a 3D animated flick. It also tackles areas of specialization and a walk-through in standard studio procedures for the production of 3D animated shorts. 
<br /><br />The 3D Animation Process
<br /><br />Pre-production 
<br /><br />Scriptwriting for Animation 
<br />Advanced Techniques in Character Animation 
<br />Character Development and Design 
<br />Art and Composition in Background Design 
<br />Animatic 
<br />Sound Design and Engineering 
<br /><br />Production
<br /><br />Story and Dialogue Treatment 
<br />3D Modeling and Texturing 
<br />Rigging your Characters 
<br />3D Animation Basics 
<br />Advanced Techniques in 3D Animation 
<br />Art of Lighting and Rendering 
<br /><br />Post-production 
<br />Motion Graphics and Special Effects 
<br />Sound Editing 
<br />Compositing and Digital Editing 
<br />Elective:Mel Scripting for MAYA 
<br />Elective:3D Animation using Freewares 
<br />Elective:Intellectual Property Rights 
<br />Elective:Web Design and Development 
<br /><br />Schedule of Meetings: Saturdays and night classes only
<br />Duration: 12 months
<br />Enrollment Fee: Php 120,000.00
<br /><br />Contact Number : 7295951 (Maila / Bong)
<br /><br />(<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindtap-ph.com%2FMODULE.htm%23scriptcom"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mindtap-ph.com/MODULE.htm#scriptcom</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f68192c20271f575c8ba05acc8e11921" url=""><![CDATA[6th Akira's Nightmare Alternative Animation Basic Animation<br/><br/>6th Akira's Nightmare Alternative Animation Basic Animation Material, Outline, Treatment and Script Development and Management is slated for the month of October. Welcome to the participants of (5th Akira). 
<br />Fee :  Php 5,000 Schedule : Saturdays / 4 sessions            
<br /><br />For Registration: Please indicate full name and contact number mobile phone : 09215081060
<br /><br />This new workshop series will focus on four distinct fields namely;
<br /><br />1. Animation Material Development and Management
<br />2. Animation Beat Outline Development and Management
<br />3. Animation Treatment Development and Management
<br />4. Animation Script Development and Management
<br /><br />The newly improved program will aid animation professionals create commercial animation contents that are within the contemporary sense and sensibility of the general population. For students ( UP, La Salle - St. Benilde, UST and Ateneo) who are about to take up their multimedia-animation thesis projects or are preparing for their thesis projects, the workshop will serve as a tutorial aid in order to augment their needs to finish their respective projects.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b6ebac197568b46f10978084703ef5b0" url=""><![CDATA[The Growing Movement In Original Content Animation<br/><br/>I have this feeling that original content development and management in animation is slowly, with extreme emphasis, attracting more attention.  For me, this is wonderful news.   There are two main original content training grounds that are accessable to the public right now.  
<br /><br />The School of Arts and Animation is located at Magallanes, Makati City. To be specific, the school is under the Asia Pacific College.  This school is offering a unified program, from pre-production, production, post production and overviews with regards to marketing, distribution and exhibition.  You can visit their website for more information :
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindtap-ph.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mindtap-ph.com</a>
<br /><br />Korea-Philippines IT Center is a foundation under TESDA and the Quezon City Local Government. The said foundation is located at the QCPU Campus, Novaliches, Quezon City.  Currently, the center is applying animation pre-production course to its existing programs for both 2D and 3D Animations. You can visit their website for more information :
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.korphil.ph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.korphil.ph</a> 
<br /><br />I hope that more schools and more private groups will have the courage to explore original content development and management in animation. Through original content, we will be able to slowly build a more viable, genuine  and competitive animation industry and market.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>