<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="15">
		<document id="a31d83af15777aa48231af2e46e35c9f" url=""><![CDATA[Rat Control Tips and Advice<br/><br/>More natural methods can be used such as the removal of garden debris, domestic waste and construction waste etc. Other preventative methods can also be used like sealing openings into the home/premises etc. with the use of wire mesh, concrete and metal. Catch and release traps are sometimes used as a more humane solution.<br /><br />Rats spread disease and can cause serious damage to peoples homes, as well as posing sanitary and health problems.<br /><br /><strong>Some common questions often asked when referring to rats are </strong>:<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Where do rats live?<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; How do I identify a rat?<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; What do rats eat?<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Are rats harmful?<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; How do I know if I have a rat problem?<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; How do I get rid of rats?<br /><br />Common rats measure about 25cm ( excluding the tail ) and have an average weight of about 340gms. They can be grey, brown or less commonly black in colour. Although sometimes seen in the day rats are nocturnal creatures. They are active burrowers, good climbers and swimmers, have poor eyesight, acute hearing and a good sense of taste and smell.<br /><br />At 3-4 months old, rats are capable of reproducing, and may have 3-6 litters per year. The size of the litter can be around 6-11 young with a lifespan of between 12-19 months, and it is said there are 5 rats for every human being on earth.<br /><br /><strong>There are various ways to deal with rat problems depending on the type of infestation, and these can include :</strong><br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Chemicals/poisons<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Traps for rat removal<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Electronic rat removal<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Cage traps for removal<br /><br />o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Electromagnetic &amp;amp; ultrasonic devices for rat removal<br /><br />When seeking professional removal of a vermin infestation, bear in mind that not all services offer a fixed and convenient time for solving the problem.<br /><br />There are over 4,000 rodent species categorized based on their anatomy similarities and differences. Overall, three major groups with over 30 families make up the total rodent population.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Common Rodent Types&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The more common rodents fall into three major suborders. The suborder Sciuromorpha includes squirrels, chipmunks, marmots, woodchucks, prairie dogs, gophers, pocket mice, kangaroo rats, and beavers. The suborder Myomorpha is made up of mouse-like rodents and includes a large variety of mouse and rat species, such as hamsters, lemmings, voles, muskrats, gerbils, dormice, and jerboas. If you think there are a lot of rats in your house and you have had this problem for a long time now, you might consider calling a pest control service to eliminate the problem completely.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mbGl4eWEuY29tL2Jsb2cvNDIyMTIwMy9QZXN0LUNvbnRyb2wtRGlmZmVyZW50LVR5cGVzLW9mLVBlc3RzLVlvdS1OZWVkLVRvLVdhdGNoLU91dC1Gb3I_" target="_blank">Pest Control - Is It Safe During Pregnancy?</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="83be72dec41665c13253f771f5ec6770" url=""><![CDATA[Bed Bugs Treatment - Get Rid of This Biting Pest<br/><br/>They can reside anywhere their small flat bodies can fit into.<br /><br />That being the fact, the first place to look for a bed mite is still in or near the mattress.<br /><br /><strong>The Mattress</strong><br /><br />Aside from the telltale bite mark a person discovers after getting out of bed, small dark spots and casings are signs that these pests are present. Bug treatment of a mattress comes in two stages; cleaning and treatment.<br /><br /><strong>Cleaning the Mattress</strong><br /><br />When cleaning a mattress against these pests, there are effective ways to a treatment.<br /><br />These are:<br /><br />&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacuum the area thoroughly. Use a heavy duty vacuum. The places to focus on are:&lt;/li&gt;<br /><br />&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The floor, carpet and walls around the bed (widen the range to about 8 to 9 feet&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;around the bed);&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The mattress;&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The box spring;&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;The bed frame&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;<br /><br />&lt;li&gt;Wash all the beddings and linen in hot water. When using a dryer, dry on high heat.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Use a stiff brush and scrub the mattress thoroughly to get rid of eggs. Focus on all areas specially the seams of the mattress.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Although a fire hazard therefore not recommended, another bed bug treatment is using alcohol on the mattress. This must be done with extreme caution and with professional guidance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;<br /><br />A clean mattress does not mean that you're done treating bed mites. The next stage is the preventive treatment of bed mites.<br /><br /><strong>Treatment</strong><br /><br />&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Application of insecticides specifically products geared for bed bug treatment and mattress use.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Encasing the mattress in plastic or mattress covers that trap bed mites.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Using a steam cleaner on the mattress to kill any leftover bed mites.&lt;/li&gt;<br />&lt;li&gt;Ensuring that there are no bed mites left. If the bed bug treatment is not thorough and concise, a homeowner can risk another infestation regardless if a new mattress is used.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;<br /><br />Bed bug treatment is a constant process. One must be aware of these pests and how they behave to get rid of these from one's home.<br /><br />Different methods have come out in the hope of completely eradicating bed bugs at home, hotels, apartments and in other live-in places.<br /><br />Treatments aim to avoid the bugs doing damage to the furniture and creating human bites that can be manifested by rashes and visible skin marks that can be very itchy besides embarrassing. Whichever you used ensure that the manufacturers instructions are followed exactly.<br /><br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NjaWVuY2VzdGFnZS5jb20vZ3JvdXBfaG9tZS5waHA/Z2lkPTQzNzAyNTY_" target="_blank">Do You Need A Professional Pest Control Company</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mbGl4eWEuY29tL2Jsb2cvNDIyMTIwMy9QZXN0LUNvbnRyb2wtRGlmZmVyZW50LVR5cGVzLW9mLVBlc3RzLVlvdS1OZWVkLVRvLVdhdGNoLU91dC1Gb3I_" target="_blank">Is Pest Control Really Necessary?</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c1759d8fdfa5a703651781b539ddefe0" url=""><![CDATA[Pest Control: Getting Rid of Rodents<br/><br/>Therefore, the first step of safe and effective residential pest control is to accurately identify the pests in question, especially when it comes to rodent pest control, so that they find an accurate method of dealing with that specific pest.<br /><br />Though homeowners may not see much of a difference between rats and mice when it comes to residential pest control, rodent pest control experts find it important to differentiate between mouse control and rat control as the pest control tactics for each differs.<br /><br />Two rodents that are commonly mistaken for one another are the deer mouse and Norway rat. They both are found in the Pacific Northwest and share similar habits such as gnawing paper, books, wood, upholstery, plastic, cinder blocks, wiring, and other soft metals (which can cause fire hazards). As is common with most rodents, they are enticed by food within a home and can contaminate the food with their urine and feces. Not only that, but they also carry a plethora of terrible diseases that can put your health in jeopardy.<br /><br />In order to protect you and your family's health and safety, it is important to get in contact with a local pest control company upon detecting signs of a rodent infestation.<br /><br />Here is a look at how to tell whether the rodent control you require is for a deer mouse or Norway rat and how to identify an infestation in general:<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;About Deer Mice&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Native to North America, deer mice (peromyscus) have larger eyes than a common house mouse and can grow to 5-8 inches in length. Usually they have two-toned coloring which involves white bellies and darker colors on their backs. They are fast runner and jumpers and can squeeze through tiny holes. One way to partake in mouse control for these critters is to seal up any holes that are large enough for them to crawl through.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;About Norway Rats&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Found in the Pacific Northwest, Norway rats are one of the two main species of rats (along with the roof rat). Though the Norway rat is not in fact from Norway originally, it is thought to have come from Asia (most likely China). They can grow to 13-18.5 inches in length from head to tail, which makes them a larger breed than roof rats. They have whitish-gray bellies and the rest of their bodies are covered in coarse brown hair.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Which is Which?&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Though the sizes of adult Norway rats and Deer mice differ drastically, adolescent Norway rats are similar in size to an adult deer mouse at a glance. If you think there are a lot of rats in your house and you have had this problem for a long time now, you might consider calling a pest control service to eliminate the problem completely.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9icmFuZG9uYWNvbnRyb2wxL3Bvc3RzLzkzOTY0NS9JcytQZXN0K0NvbnRyb2wrUmVhbGx5K05lY2Vzc2FyeSUzRg__" target="_blank">Pest Control - Is It Safe During Pregnancy?</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="da85a5512c2477f184f0c3ba284e2d09" url=""><![CDATA[Bed Bugs Treatment - Get Rid of This Biting Pest<br/><br/>Can you imagine how fast an infestation can worsen in time?<br /><br />You also need to know that conducting bed bug treatment should not be done by yourself. If you insist on doing the bed bug treatment by yourself, you still need to contact professional exterminators in order to get professional advice and instruction. There are a lot of things that should be considered in order to be successful with bed bug treatment, and this will only be possible with the help of professional exterminators.<br /><br />There is no simple answer to the question, what is the best bed bug treatment? Treatments may vary according to the level of infestation observed. However while various methods can be used to control the bed bugs, the ultimate aim should be total elimination. The following procedures can be carried out in most cases to eliminate them. Sometimes not all of them may be required.<br /><br />The first thing to do is to make sure that there is a bed bug infestation. There is nothing to distinguish bite marks left by bed bugs from bite marks left by other insects like mosquitoes. So in order to make sure that there is a beg bug infestation the following methods can be used. Observe whether there are distinctive reddish fecal spots and marks left by the bedbugs on garments such as bed cloths or mattresses. Also look for eggs or skins shed in the process molting, in crevices and other places. For exact identification captured bed bugs can be compared with reference images available online from various sources.<br /><br />Once the infestation is ascertained, beg bug treatment can start. This would include several processes performed one after another or separately. One of the first steps should be to keep birds and bats away from the house. These animals' nests like human homes play host to bed bugs and that may have been the method by which they were introduced to the house.<br /><br />All the unnecessary clutter in the house should be removed so that the amount of hiding places available to bed bugs is reduced. Whichever you used ensure that the manufacturers instructions are followed exactly.<br /><br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9icmFuZG9uYWNvbnRyb2wxL3Bvc3RzLzkzOTY0NS9JcytQZXN0K0NvbnRyb2wrUmVhbGx5K05lY2Vzc2FyeSUzRg__" target="_blank">Is Pest Control Really Necessary?</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cueGluZy5jb20vZXZlbnRzL3Blc3QtY29udHJvbC1zYWZlLXByZWduYW5jeS05Njg4NjM_" target="_blank">Pest Control</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e757ac6adaa29f66cbd285a99a7e89f2" url=""><![CDATA[Pest Control - Different Types of Pests You Need To Watch Ou<br/><br/>And right now there many such services accessible that are focusing on the field. The variety of tools and rich experience that these companies possess may prove invaluable for campaigns. You will end up glad to learn that most from the companies offer environmentally friendly pest control services for their customers in a way that there is no threat with regard to environment as well as people subjected to these methods.<br /><br />By simply opting for an appropriate pest firm, you will be rest assured that problems associated with these undesired creatures will be a thing of past and you will sleep quietly thereafter. While some of the processes chosen by you may cost you a lot, they are worth all of the investment you may make. Shipping and delivery require the knowledge of rocket technology to opt for a suitable infestation control technique to deal with your problems. You can only require can to execute it frequently.<br /><br />Infestation control is not just to the bugs within the garden or perhaps the rats in the belfry. If you have pets you have fleas and wish to know all you can to defend your castle against this small invader.<br /><br />Based on the American Dog Products Manufacturers you will find 77. 5 million dogs and about 96 million cats declaring humans as pets in the united states. The numbers are not really which surprising when you think it through, people love their domestic pets. The problem happens when your pets bring home domestic pets.<br /><br />Fleas, Order Siphonaptera, are small creatures that live off the blood of their hosts. When you have pets then you definitely know how essential it is to have sufficient?? control program in place. The little insects can come into your home and yard bringing tiny suitcases of misery together.<br /><br />Infestation control for fleas is not a easy task nevertheless but it must be carried out. Fleas carry disorder, are a cause for asthma and allergic reactions and make your bad pet miserable with scratch.<br /><br />Many people seem to think the battle of the flea must be fought around the dog or cat, that however does not apply. The battle must start with a good control product in the backyard. Skip the lawn and clean the canine and as soon because Fido goes out to perform his business you will have 1000s of new fleas to deal with.<br /><br />When the yard had been booked you’ll need to attack the actual flea where it the majority of likes to hide. Again &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; about the dog, no, fleas like carpets, drapes and couches as much as one does. They view the family pet as being a traveling lunch and swing up for a meal but tend to jump back off the hang out there under your bed patiently waiting until they are starving once again.?? Endeavours inside the house are the next thing. A great pest control company can treat the house and yard for you personally with a the least fuss. An excellent vacuuming following the agent leaves may finish up. Do not forget to consider the dust bag outside as soon as you are executed although.<br /><br />Hopefully during all this control bad Fido or Fluffy has been safely locked in the bathroom and may now be managed. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wZXN0Y29udHJvbHRyZWF0bWVudC5jby51ay8_" target="_blank">London Pest Control Services</a> for them features a vigorous housekeeping, visit from a pest control expert and diligent follow up inspections to ensure they do not return.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8e2b672c8c47d104051d491e201e89fa" url=""><![CDATA[Rat Control Tips and Advice<br/><br/>These traps kill the rat immediately without subjecting the rat to undue suffering or prolonged agony in the trap.<br /><br />If the rat is located in a narrow or enclosed area of the home, then a glue trap may be a better option for rat control. The glue trap is covered by a layer of plastic that is peeled away to expose a long tray filled with a thick, glue-like substance. If the rat steps onto the glue trap, he will be trapped as effectively as if he had stepped in quicksand and there is no hope for escape. The rat and the glue trap can be disposed of together in the trash tied into a plastic bag so that no other wildlife can get into it.<br /><br />Rats can be very dangerous creatures that may contaminate your food, destroy your property, and even start electrical fires. Plus, rats, their feces, and rat fleas can carry disease, making them an especially risky health hazard. As such, it is very important to get rid of rats. Unfortunately, rats can be quite difficult to get rid of as they can inhabit many areas inside and around your home from wood piles, bushes, or trash cans outdoors, to insulation of walls and ceilings, crawl spaces, under cupboards and bathtubs, and near hot water heaters and furnaces.<br /><br />If you have spotted signs of rats including droppings; chewed-up siding, insulation, or walls; or evidence of contaminated food, it is time to take action. Rats and mice procreate often so you will need to be vigilant about finding and removing rats from your home. Traps can be an excellent method of getting rid of rats; simply bait the traps with dried fruit, peanut butter, or cheese and wait to collect the trapped rats. Experts recommend that you set the traps to right angles near walls where rodents are suspected to inhabit, with the bait side of the trap facing the wall. Always wear gloves and use a plastic bag to dispose of a trapped rodent to prevent the spread of disease.<br /><br />Usually, it is not advisable to use rat poisons as these are less immediate means of killing rats. A poisoned rat may have time to crawl away before it dies and as such you will not always be able to find it immediately. These dead rats then become breeding grounds for disease and bacteria. Furthermore, rat poisons pose a significant risk to the health of pets, wild animals, and children and therefore should be avoided.<br /><br />Ultimately, it can be incredibly difficult to clear up a rat infestation. If you think there are a lot of rats in your house and you have had this problem for a long time now, you might consider calling a pest control service to eliminate the problem completely.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JyYW5kb25hY29udHJvbDEuZG11c2ljLm5ldC9qb3VybmFsLzM3NzE0NA__" target="_blank">Is Pest Control Really Necessary?</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="16102a43230061f38a140e70948314ff" url=""><![CDATA[Bed Bugs Treatment<br/><br/>The first place to start is the furniture, turn everything upside down and vacuum all of it. Mostly focus on creases and tufts, and do that with every single piece of furniture you have.<br /><br />In fact vacuum every single crack in your home. Check the folds, the drapery, drawers, dressers, back of pictures and posters, floors, under carpet, or any place that seems like something small might be hiding there. One thing you need to do is empty the vacuum right away, you can be extra cautious and put the vacuum bag in a plastic container and place it in the freezer to freeze before you get rid of it.<br /><br />Since they react poorly to high temperatures, in fact they die from high temperatures; the second bed bugs treatment is washing with hot water or even better, steam cleaning. The process is basically the same as it is with vacuuming; only this gets rid of them much faster. The ultimate treatment would be a combination of both, first vacuum the apartment leaving no stone, or in this case furniture, unturned and after that steam clean the furniture and every other place in your apartment. That will insure 99% probability that you got rid of these pests once and for all.<br /><br />Bed bugs are making a comeback, and bug treatment and removal is starting to be a necessary evil in this century - no matter where you live or how clean you are.<br /><br /><strong>Bed Bugs Treatment Starts With Prevention</strong><br /><br />The best way to prevent a bed bug infestation is to keep them from getting into your home.<br /><br />Unfortunately, bed bugs are becoming a global problem, and since these little critters are fast and invasive, it can be tough to keep them out.<br /><br />When you travel, bring a flashlight. Check the mattress where you're staying for any small dark stains. Look in the crevices of the mattress, and the seams. Check carefully. It is unlikely that you'll see a bug, but you may see evidence of them. Whichever you used ensure that the manufacturers instructions are followed exactly.<br /><br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/brandonacontrolhayden/blog/blogid=7938204" target="_blank">Do You Need A Professional Pest Control Company</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JyYW5kb25hY29udHJvbDEuZG11c2ljLm5ldC9qb3VybmFsLzM3NzE0NA__" target="_blank">Pest Control - Types of Services Available</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24e736760690eb5c69f5e47db26f581b" url=""><![CDATA[Successful Methods of Rat Control<br/><br/>Variations of this and various other chemicals are available for indoor or outdoor application.<br /><br />As one would expect, the chemicals used in these rat poisons are highly deadly and should not be used if there are small children or animals that may come in contact with it. There is potential health risks associated with these chemicals touching skin or being inhaled as well.<br /><br />Unlike roach control, which can be accomplishing by spraying some chemical agents around the home, rat control requires a completely different approach. Rats are intelligent animals that can sense many types of danger and avoid it to stay alive. Handling a rat control problem can be a difficult pursuit if you do not know some successful methods of rat control.<br /><br />Find Their Living Areas<br /><br />The first step in successful rat control is to find out where the rats are living or where they are able to come into your home. Rats generally like quiet, dark areas to build their nests so you will be looking for a ball of fuzz and rat droppings in a dark area to determine where the rats are living. There may even be a trail of rat dropping leading from the area where they are stealing food back to where their nesting area is.<br /><br />Choose Your Weapons<br /><br />Once you have discovered where the rats have been living at, the second step of successful rat control is to choose the pest control items that you will use to get rid of the rats. There are a number of different options to choose from for effective rat control and the option that is chosen will depend on the area where the rodents are located and how accessible the area is for you. Certain types of pest control products are easier to place in small areas than others.<br /><br />If the rats are in a larger, open area such as the attic of a home, then a snap trap might be the fasted and most effective option for getting rid of the rats. This method of rat control uses a baited trap with a spring-loaded lever that clamps the jaws of the trap shut when the bait is taken. These traps kill the rat immediately without subjecting the rat to undue suffering or prolonged agony in the trap.<br /><br />If the rat is located in a narrow or enclosed area of the home, then a glue trap may be a better option for rat control. The glue trap is covered by a layer of plastic that is peeled away to expose a long tray filled with a thick, glue-like substance. If you think there are a lot of rats in your house and you have had this problem for a long time now, you might consider calling a pest control service to eliminate the problem completely.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JyYW5kb25hY29udHJvbDEub3Zlci1ibG9nLmNvbS9wYWdlcy9wZXN0LWNvbnRyb2wtLS1kaWZmZXJlbnQtdHlwZXMtb2YtcGVzdHMteW91LW5lZWQtdG8td2F0Y2gtb3V0LWZvci03MjA4NjIzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Is Pest Control Really Necessary?</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6d618b3d5af9141026f8e1ebdb78b3bb" url=""><![CDATA[Bed Bugs Treatment<br/><br/>I'd take cockroaches any day over a bed bugs infestation.&quot;<br /><br />This is because effective insect treatment is not just a simple application of chemical. This is going to take some careful effort on your part to eradicate them.<br /><br />Bed bugs sleep during the day and come out at night to feed on blood. Humans are a favorite target, although they will also feed on dogs and cats. They are fast little creatures who can hide in a space as small as the thickness of a credit card. These insects at maturity measure about ?? inch long.<br /><br />Picture a bug about the length of a single grain of rice.<br /><br />Evidence of an infestation can include bites on your person. They will typically feed in a small area, injecting an anti-coagulant substance under the skin to allow your blood to flow easily. You will generally see a small localized area of several bites on your skin to indicate the presence of these insects.<br /><br /><strong>Bed Bugs Treatment Step #1</strong><br /><br />First, remove any clutter. You'll want easy access to anyplace that bugs can hide.<br /><br />Bed bugs treatment starts with a vacuum cleaner with a disposable bag. You're going to vacuum everything! You need a vacuum that has a long hose and a crevice attachment.<br /><br />Start by vacuuming where you've seen evidence of the critters, like the mattress seams and cracks. Pull the mattress off the box springs and vacuum them carefully as well as underneath the bed. Take apart the bed frame to remove any hiding places.<br /><br />Vacuum the cracks where the carpet meets the wall, and anywhere you can see evidence of bugs. Bed bugs have been found to hide behind loose wallpaper, switchplate covers, and even behind baseboard, so you may want to remove these to vacuum behind them.<br /><br />Check out furniture too, because these insects can live in sofas and chairs as easily as they can live in mattresses. You won't see many bugs, but your vacuum cleaner &quot;offense&quot; will suck up any eggs that may be waiting to hatch.<br /><br />Once you've vacuumed every possible hiding place, take the vacuum outside and remove the bag. Whichever you used ensure that the manufacturers instructions are followed exactly.<br /><br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JyYW5kb25hY29udHJvbDEuYmxvZ3NwYWNlLmZyLzM5OTE4NDMvSXMtUGVzdC1Db250cm9sLVJlYWxseS1OZWNlc3Nhcnkv" target="_blank">Pest Control - Bedbugs</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JyYW5kb25hY29udHJvbDEub3Zlci1ibG9nLmNvbS9wYWdlcy9wZXN0LWNvbnRyb2wtLS1kaWZmZXJlbnQtdHlwZXMtb2YtcGVzdHMteW91LW5lZWQtdG8td2F0Y2gtb3V0LWZvci03MjA4NjIzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Is Pest Control Really Necessary?</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c18bb58a64faa1e5ac2b53ba59139caa" url=""><![CDATA[Successful Methods of Rat Control<br/><br/>Therefore, the first step of safe and effective residential pest control is to accurately identify the pests in question, especially when it comes to rodent pest control, so that they find an accurate method of dealing with that specific pest.<br /><br />Though homeowners may not see much of a difference between rats and mice when it comes to residential pest control, rodent pest control experts find it important to differentiate between mouse control and rat control as the pest control tactics for each differs.<br /><br />Two rodents that are commonly mistaken for one another are the deer mouse and Norway rat. They both are found in the Pacific Northwest and share similar habits such as gnawing paper, books, wood, upholstery, plastic, cinder blocks, wiring, and other soft metals (which can cause fire hazards). As is common with most rodents, they are enticed by food within a home and can contaminate the food with their urine and feces. Not only that, but they also carry a plethora of terrible diseases that can put your health in jeopardy.<br /><br />In order to protect you and your family's health and safety, it is important to get in contact with a local pest control company upon detecting signs of a rodent infestation.<br /><br />Here is a look at how to tell whether the rodent control you require is for a deer mouse or Norway rat and how to identify an infestation in general:<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;About Deer Mice&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Native to North America, deer mice (peromyscus) have larger eyes than a common house mouse and can grow to 5-8 inches in length. Usually they have two-toned coloring which involves white bellies and darker colors on their backs. They are fast runner and jumpers and can squeeze through tiny holes. One way to partake in mouse control for these critters is to seal up any holes that are large enough for them to crawl through.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;About Norway Rats&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Found in the Pacific Northwest, Norway rats are one of the two main species of rats (along with the roof rat). Though the Norway rat is not in fact from Norway originally, it is thought to have come from Asia (most likely China). They can grow to 13-18.5 inches in length from head to tail, which makes them a larger breed than roof rats. They have whitish-gray bellies and the rest of their bodies are covered in coarse brown hair.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Which is Which?&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Though the sizes of adult Norway rats and Deer mice differ drastically, adolescent Norway rats are similar in size to an adult deer mouse at a glance. If you think there are a lot of rats in your house and you have had this problem for a long time now, you might consider calling a pest control service to eliminate the problem completely.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JyYW5kb25hY29udHJvbDEub2JvbG9nLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">Pest Control - Fleas</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d2bd7b5a2f0ecee6e8a00cc9fca3b397" url=""><![CDATA[Top 5 Bed Bug Treatments<br/><br/>After clearing the furniture and garments, the premises should be inspected and vacuumed after scraping the bed bug hiding places to dislodge them. Collected refuse should be sealed and disposed. Then an approved insecticide with proven track record should be applied to all places where there were signs of bed bugs. Afterwards unnecessary crevices and holes should be caulked thoroughly so that they cannot be used again.<br /><br />In carrying out these actions it highly recommended that the householder obtain the services of a licensed pest control firm.<br /><br />If you have bed bugs and don't want to spend a few hundred dollars on pest control service there are two simple ways to get rid of them. The first one is by using their natural nemesis, your first weapon of choice, the vacuum cleaner.<br /><br />By vacuuming their dirt and bed bugs along you will be sure to get rid of them as they will have no place to hide. Bed bugs treatment focuses on their hiding place as they hide in filthy places, by removing such places you are limiting their options. The first place to start is the furniture, turn everything upside down and vacuum all of it. Mostly focus on creases and tufts, and do that with every single piece of furniture you have.<br /><br />In fact vacuum every single crack in your home. Check the folds, the drapery, drawers, dressers, back of pictures and posters, floors, under carpet, or any place that seems like something small might be hiding there. One thing you need to do is empty the vacuum right away, you can be extra cautious and put the vacuum bag in a plastic container and place it in the freezer to freeze before you get rid of it.<br /><br />Since they react poorly to high temperatures, in fact they die from high temperatures; the second bed bugs treatment is washing with hot water or even better, steam cleaning. The process is basically the same as it is with vacuuming; only this gets rid of them much faster. Whichever you used ensure that the manufacturers instructions are followed exactly.<br /><br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xvbmRvbnBlc3Rjb250cm9sc2VydmljZXMzMy53b3JkcHJlc3MuY29tLzIwMTIvMDMvMzEvcGVzdC1jb250cm9sLWRpZmZlcmVudC10eXBlcy1vZi1wZXN0cy15b3UtbmVlZC10by13YXRjaC1vdXQtZm9yLw__" target="_blank">Pest Control - Is It Safe During Pregnancy?</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JyYW5kb25hY29udHJvbDEub2JvbG9nLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">Pest Control - Different Types of Pests You Need To Watch Out For</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b53cb3de2d433ac46ea577b6f8e851d1" url=""><![CDATA[Residential Pest Control: Differentiating Between the Norway<br/><br/>They can grow to 13-18.5 inches in length from head to tail, which makes them a larger breed than roof rats. They have whitish-gray bellies and the rest of their bodies are covered in coarse brown hair.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Which is Which?&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Though the sizes of adult Norway rats and Deer mice differ drastically, adolescent Norway rats are similar in size to an adult deer mouse at a glance. By collecting a specimen for analysis, your local mouse and rat control company will be able to tell which rodent is infesting your home. Another identifying factor is the shape and size of the head of the rodent in relation to its body. A Norway rat's head will be large, stubby, short, and broad in relation to its body, while a deer mouse's head will be a triangular shape and small in comparison to its body. Deer mice also have a sharper and narrower snout and larger ears than Norway rats.<br /><br />It's best to let a rodent pest control expert handle a pest infestation in your home, even if you think you can identify the species. Both deer mice and Norway rats can carry the Hanta virus, which is extremely harmful to humans and is transmitted through rodent urine, saliva, and droppings. By getting in contact with rodent droppings and living in an infested home, you put yourself at risk of being exposed to the Hanta virus. It is because of this danger that you would be better off calling a residential pest control company for pest control assistance.<br /><br />Rats are the very last thing you want to see in your house all the more on your dining table or your closet. Don't you just hate it when you see one eating the food on your table? Rats are nasty dangerous creatures that can pose hazards to your health and your things as well. Getting rid of them is the goal of every homeowner. Did you know that rats have poor vision? Yup and they rely mostly on their other senses and they move through the dark making use of their long whiskers and guard hairs on their bodies to guide them.<br /><br />If you want to trick a rat and capture it, make sure you don't feed it with rotten food or anything it wouldn't like. It's hard to believe but rats have a discriminating taste too. They are very cautious as well which means that they will need to drag the food somewhere else and consume it. If you think there are a lot of rats in your house and you have had this problem for a long time now, you might consider calling a pest control service to eliminate the problem completely.<br /><br />[url=]Pest Control - Is It Safe During Pregnancy?[/url]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e51c5003da66b0d50abceca0786537ce" url=""><![CDATA[Bed Bugs Treatment - Get Rid of This Biting Pest<br/><br/>If you have woken up from a nights rest and notice any red bumps on your body, then it is important to treat it right away.<br /><br />One thing to note about these insects is that they come out extremely late at night and just a few hours before dawn so it is quite common to sleep through a nasty bite. Common ointments that work effectively include cortisone cream which you can get at just about any drugstore. You may also want to consider using herbal remedies such as aloe vera to soothe the irritation.<br /><br />Fortunately, most bites are not life threatening and treatment for bed bugs is especially simple with most cases going away in a matter of days. However, one of the biggest problems you have now is the possibility of a nest or colony of these bugs somewhere in your room. The first step in getting rid of them is to vacuum your entire room including your bed, furniture and floor while also using a steam cleaner.<br /><br />Most of the time this will be enough to eliminate bed bugs but depending on your situation, you may need to use a spray or insecticides. Of course the best treatment for bed bugs is not having to deal with the problem in the first place so taking preventative measures such as ensuring your room is always kept clean is essential.<br /><br />The existence of bed bugs is very annoying for all of us, but in order to properly conduct bed bug treatment, you should first understand how the infestation started. If you really want to conduct proper bed bug treatment, then you need to read this article. I will be showing you some of the things that you need to know regarding how an infestation starts. Reading this article will help you prevent any infestation, since you will have an idea of how they can come into your house.<br /><br />Bed mites can come from everywhere. It is very hard to pin point the exact source of the infestation, since bed mites are known as the best travellers. They can be brought to your house from an infested area with the help of your clothes. Whichever you used ensure that the manufacturers instructions are followed exactly.<br /><br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56aWtpLmNvbS9lbi9icmFuZG9uYS1jb250cm9sLWhheWRlbisxMDMzMjI2L3Bvc3QvUGVzdC1Db250cm9sLS0tKzE0MjExNjM3" target="_blank">Pest Control - Types of Services Available</a>, [url=]Pest Control[/url]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dc7d5a40bfb1525d48b85bc0a84b7dcc" url=""><![CDATA[Successful Methods of Rat Control<br/><br/>Not only that, but they also carry a plethora of terrible diseases that can put your health in jeopardy.<br /><br />In order to protect you and your family's health and safety, it is important to get in contact with a local pest control company upon detecting signs of a rodent infestation.<br /><br />Here is a look at how to tell whether the rodent control you require is for a deer mouse or Norway rat and how to identify an infestation in general:<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;About Deer Mice&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Native to North America, deer mice (peromyscus) have larger eyes than a common house mouse and can grow to 5-8 inches in length. Usually they have two-toned coloring which involves white bellies and darker colors on their backs. They are fast runner and jumpers and can squeeze through tiny holes. One way to partake in mouse control for these critters is to seal up any holes that are large enough for them to crawl through.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;About Norway Rats&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Found in the Pacific Northwest, Norway rats are one of the two main species of rats (along with the roof rat). Though the Norway rat is not in fact from Norway originally, it is thought to have come from Asia (most likely China). They can grow to 13-18.5 inches in length from head to tail, which makes them a larger breed than roof rats. They have whitish-gray bellies and the rest of their bodies are covered in coarse brown hair.<br /><br />&lt;b&gt;Which is Which?&lt;/b&gt;<br /><br />Though the sizes of adult Norway rats and Deer mice differ drastically, adolescent Norway rats are similar in size to an adult deer mouse at a glance. By collecting a specimen for analysis, your local mouse and rat control company will be able to tell which rodent is infesting your home. Another identifying factor is the shape and size of the head of the rodent in relation to its body. A Norway rat's head will be large, stubby, short, and broad in relation to its body, while a deer mouse's head will be a triangular shape and small in comparison to its body. Deer mice also have a sharper and narrower snout and larger ears than Norway rats.<br /><br />It's best to let a rodent pest control expert handle a pest infestation in your home, even if you think you can identify the species. Both deer mice and Norway rats can carry the Hanta virus, which is extremely harmful to humans and is transmitted through rodent urine, saliva, and droppings. By getting in contact with rodent droppings and living in an infested home, you put yourself at risk of being exposed to the Hanta virus. If you think there are a lot of rats in your house and you have had this problem for a long time now, you might consider calling a pest control service to eliminate the problem completely.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JyYW5kb25hY29udHJvbDEucG9zdGVyb3VzLmNvbS9wZXN0LWNvbnRyb2wtZGlmZmVyZW50LXR5cGVzLW9mLXBlc3RzLXlvdS1uZWU_" target="_blank">Pest Control - Types of Services Available</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2f81d393d7f06f737253c7e2538cf551" url=""><![CDATA[Bed Bugs Treatment<br/><br/>Among those that have been proven effective is bed bugs treatment by freezing.<br /><br />Studies have shown that bed bugs cannot stand extreme temperatures. In fact, they die after a few seconds of being exposed to extreme heat or extreme cold. Being exposed to heat however is not very much advisable because extreme heat may cause the disintegrating of materials that make up furniture. It can also cause burning and melting of some components of household pieces.<br /><br />This is why most professional pest control teams employ bed bugs treatment by freezing. It does not only get rid of the bugs, but it also preserves the furniture.<br /><br />Bed bugs treatment by freezing works by exposing the infested furniture into an extremely low temperature. The temperature reaches and penetrates even the most hidden part so all the bugs are killed after a few minutes. Even those that are hiding underneath the surface are made to come out. Another good thing about it is you don't actually piss the insects so it is not as bloody and dangerous.<br /><br />Keeping the furniture in a huge freezer is another way of treatment. The freezer acts to the core of the furniture so all the bugs that inhabits there do not survive. Even the eggs don't get to complete the cycles and are expelled even before they become full blown bugs. For best results, the furniture or house pieces are left in a very cold temperature for several hours.<br /><br />In some parts of the country where snow comes in season, keeping beds and other things in the house that are infected outside to catch the snow coming done can also be effective. Wrapping the pieces in snow for a few hours can be very effective. This is especially advised for furniture that is made of wood and other materials beside light fabrics.<br /><br />Bed bugs treatment by freezing can be executed by anyone with the proper instructions. It would however be better if made by a team that has expertise on exterminating these annoying pests. Whichever you used ensure that the manufacturers instructions are followed exactly.<br /><br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56aW1iaW8uY29tL0dlbmVyYWwvYXJ0aWNsZXMvUU9HZXF4MmRWcUEvTmVlZCtQcm9mZXNzaW9uYWwrUGVzdCtDb250cm9sK0NvbXBhbnk/YWRkPVRydWU_" target="_blank">Pest Control - Bedbugs</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5taWdlbnRlLmNvbS95b3VyX3BhZ2UvYmxvZy92aWV3X3Bvc3RpbmcuaHRtbD9waWQ9MjI2ODQyMiZhbXA7cHJvZmlsZV9pZD03MTQ3OTU1JmFtcDtwcm9maWxlX25hbWU9YnJhbmRvbmFjb250cm9sMSZhbXA7dXNlcl9pZD03MTQ3OTU1JmFtcDt1c2VybmFtZT1icmFuZG9uYWNvbnRyb2wx" target="_blank">Pest Control - Different Types of Pests You Need To Watch Out For</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>