<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="15">
		<document id="aae146909323cac7993187bfd1bf6bfb" url=""><![CDATA[The essential equipment of golf<br/><br/>As professional golf drivers, they should get quite familiar with the site on the length of each hole, the channel characteristics on the hazard, the green of the topography, and even local weather, and wind speed and finally of course the golf equipment.
<br /><br />Caddy need help came to a strange player to familiarize themselves with the venue site for the staff to develop the players play and tactics for each player's decision to bar the most reasonable opinions. When the ball flew into the complex hazard, into the golf fairway woods, ponds, back caddy is the bounden duty of goals conceded, so that a player from the penalty stroke added. In addition, the caddy is also tasked with a lot of balls such as the delivery of services with other little jobs for the players.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="322b1182883452fff128804d1860ff97" url=""><![CDATA[Ball, golf tour bags and shoes<br/><br/>in the early 19th century, the golf balls were done with a feather core, leather case sewing together, not only the process is difficult, and genuine low.
<br /><br />Golf tour bags are mostly club; about 8 inches diameter, good golf carry bags and stand bags should have a smooth home bar, smooth texture, firm and finally the overall framework. 
<br />The bottom of the golf shoe has 12 soles which can help to prevent sliding, so that players swing for balance. Golf socks can be the perfect partner.?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="516098890233c1efefbe98983638e539" url=""><![CDATA[Fresh to golf<br/><br/>According to the legend, Scotland is the birthplace of golf, when shepherds drive sheep often hit stones stick, the game was far and quasi-hit, and this is the early origin of golf UK.
<br /><br />As it is for now, the golf has become the noble sports. To a new starter, best golf drivers, who can give your guidance, are necessary. In the green grassland, perhaps the practice golf balls may inspire you to devote yourself into the game.
<br />If there are any incidents happened in the golf grassland, golf rescue and hybrids will prove to be necessary.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1510a3c9f59af905e1e430e8094f22c" url=""><![CDATA[golf definition<br/><br/>Golf, which means, people can enjoy the good life in the green and fresh oxygen. From this you can see, golf is a beautiful environments in the noble entertainment. As when you are attracted by the game, the expensive golf packages and sets will be bought, so in some countries we called it &quot;noble goals.&quot; 
<br /><br />Golf is a kind of long ridge golf wedges hitting the ball into the hole. Today, the noble sport of golf has become popular, but actually it is invented by a group of shepherds!
<br />It is a pleasure to enjoy nature while you are playing the golf, suitable golf sweaters and fleece could create an atmosphere of comfortable. Perhaps you may take consideration of buying a suit of golf apparel, which will make the competition more perfect.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="524506bdc33333d5b71945c596b50906" url=""><![CDATA[Golf clubs<br/><br/>In golf, in order to improve the grip effects, players usually wear golf gloves, often worn on the left hand, right-handed player, the type of players left on the gloves worn on the right hand in the left hand golf clubs, while the female players wore normal left and right. 
<br /><br />The emergence of golf gloves is from the United States. Gloves, the part of the golf apparel, a U.S. businessman thought of golfers to play with gloves, and then golf gloves emerged. However, gloves were not initially accepted by golfers, who have always thought that wearing gloves is a superfluous thing, and even affect the feel when playing with the top golf irons.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d548950ae25e02e5c781ad72466d48f6" url=""><![CDATA[Golf life<br/><br/>Golf equipment including clubs, balls, shoes, golf caps, gloves, golf sunglasses and clothing.
<br /><br />Here let’s take a deep look at the glove material. Golf gloves are basically three types of material: leather, PU materials, and cloth. The leather is divided into leather: sheep skin, goat, and other skin. Actual production may also take advantage of several materials.
<br />Leather gloves feel good; you can hit the new golf balls, the best feeling grip, is the UK golf shops' choice, the disadvantage is perishable, difficult to manage, but also the most expensive.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fffe45393877a010406bf27f59275a7d" url=""><![CDATA[Some points to golf beginners<br/><br/>from what rod to get started? 
<br />General domestic golf beginners are often recommended for entry to practice as a 7-iron shot from the top golf sets. But golf teaching abroad in general is P (Pitch) wedge shot for the entry.
<br />The importance of the sport is closely related to grip with the impact of the strike hit, but many beginners often overlook this important part. Actually choosing the suitable golf irons is quite indispensable.
<br /><br />Correct ball position is the only way to win good results; full swing golf training aids can help the new starter in the first step. However, some people hit the ball with incorrect posture, sometimes lucky hit get good grades and complacent, thinking that this practice according to a certain right. There is one more thing we should consider is that wearing the suitable golf sweaters and golf fleeces.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="52e1e9b3bef2afb0cbbf2335ba28671d" url=""><![CDATA[The sport spirit of golf<br/><br/>Different from many other sports, golf is mostly the case in the absence of judges carried out under supervision in the golf fairway woods.
<br /><br />Each participant in the campaign to rely on other players take the initiative to consciously abide by the rules and considerate and sometimes you should wear the suitable golf windwear jackets and tops. No matter how intense combat, all players should consciously regulate his conduct when using the golf equipment, at all times show humility and good manners of the sport. This is the essence of golf.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="62e0c1aa8b9717e2b011bdcb03c1e7cc" url=""><![CDATA[golf balls<br/><br/>Bat
<br />In 1879, a blacksmith manufactured a number of British top golf irons, soon it was used as the game bats. In 1920, an American businessman invented a copper hollow circular control the bat. Till 1924, this bat was designated as an official event with a bat.
<br />Ball 
<br />Stoned golf ball was first used. Then switch to leather ball, and later a rubber ball, in a small rubber compression, this is the modern ball or the origin of practice golf balls. 
<br /><br />Before the time the ball surface is smooth, but because of the collision and friction pounding the ball on the surface to become uneven, causing some swelling on the skin, people feel this could be uneven, with a protruding lump the ball smoothly but easy to use, This is why the surface of modern golf, with many of the small lumps to be the reason. Nowadays almost each golf-lover got the golf packages and sets.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e16a4921a748d20d809e76e11b03feb4" url=""><![CDATA[Golf Cart<br/><br/>The golf cart is also known as electric golf trolleys.Golf cart is designed for golf course design and development of environment-friendly passenger cars.
<br /><br />Golf trolleys can also be used at the resort, villas, garden-style hotels, tourist attractions, etc. Vehicle performance, design novel, safe and comfortable ride from the golf course, villas, hotels, schools to private users, will be your most convenient short-distance transport. While, the golf drivers will be the guidance of your whole round.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d6444c3e6899d341b12c52a5e17dc06c" url=""><![CDATA[golf life<br/><br/>Correct ball position is the only way to win good results; full swing golf training aids can help the new starter in the first step. However, some people hit the ball with incorrect posture, sometimes lucky hit get good grades and complacent, thinking that this practice according to a certain right. There is one more thing we should consider is that wearing the suitable golf sweaters and golf fleeces.
<br />The golf cart is also known as electric golf trolleys.Golf cart is designed for golf course design and development of environment-friendly passenger cars.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="943fbd5b5ae9406e65af7b0841b36e29" url=""><![CDATA[Fresh to golf<br/><br/>According to the legend, Scotland is the birthplace of golf, when shepherds drive sheep often hit stones stick, the game was far and quasi-hit, and this is the early origin of golf UK.
<br /><br />As it is for now, the golf has become the noble sports. To a new starter, best golf drivers, who can give your guidance, are necessary. In the green grassland, perhaps the practice golf balls may inspire you to devote yourself into the game.
<br />If there are any incidents happened in the golf grassland, golf rescue and hybrids will prove to be necessary.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ba9e1adee654f3bb52d82243cf6281e4" url=""><![CDATA[luxury golf<br/><br/>in the early 19th century, the golf balls were done with a feather core, leather case sewing together, not only the process is difficult, and genuine low.
<br /><br />Golf tour bags are mostly club; about 8 inches diameter, good golf carry bags and stand bags should have a smooth home bar, smooth texture, firm and finally the overall framework. 
<br />The bottom of the golf shoe has 12 soles which can help to prevent sliding, so that players swing for balance. Golf socks can be the perfect partner.?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e670eb9df74e679764011a0d4245ad3d" url=""><![CDATA[GOLF UK<br/><br/>playing golf is a sport with a special charm. Those people would play the golf in the natural elegance within the natural green grassland. A set of golf equipment UK will in some degree help to improve your skills.
<br /><br />If you are not familiar with the golf, the practice golf balls can assist you in the first ground. In the UK golf clubs, each person is not amateur, with top golf irons and excellent skills, a perfect match comes to our sight.
<br />The first involves the north coast of Scotland to play golf is the soldier, then gradually rise to civil court and nobility and the interest of young people and eventually become a tradition in Scotland project. And now it has become a popular choice for many people.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="57d783e579b3ba05d7ffefeeee7c5968" url=""><![CDATA[Golf online<br/><br/>There have been numerous variations concerning the source associated with golf. 
<br />The truth is that individuals don't truly worry about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb2xmaW50aGViYWdzLmNvbS8xOS1nb2xmLWJhbGxz" target="_blank">best golf ball</a>much regarding exactly where golfing precisely came from. People love it.
<br />Top golf clubs may be well-liked in the world. You will find best golf driver with regard to males, which makes it an ideal option to allow them to obtain calm, to savor enjoyable using their buddies, as well as understand brand new individuals who reveal <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb2xmaW50aGViYWdzLmNvbS8yLWdvbGYtY2x1YnM_" target="_blank">top golf clubs</a>actly the same pastime together.
<br />Females club that is obtainable, as well, provides <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb2xmaW50aGViYWdzLmNvbS80LWdvbGYtZmFpcndheS13b29kcw__" target="_blank">golf fairway woods</a>females an excellent chance to understand the reason why males tend to be therefore preoccupied in order to golfing, therefore producing all of them understand much better regarding males.
<br />Junior golf may also be a fantastic choice with regard to children from each and every grow older. Because everyone knows that you simply in no way deny the actual enjoyable associated with children. They'll therefore like it.
<br />Really it's this type of expert activity for individuals you'll want to discover golfing in the beginning, the same as when you're from college. There are plenty you need to know, for instance, golfing golf irons, that the greatest golfing car owner is perfect for a person, exactly what clothing goes for you personally, and so forth.
<br /><br />When it comes to clothes, suggestions is going to be created in the event that required, for instance, Nike tour premium shoes may therefore cause you to really feel gentle as well as comfy that you could put them on constantly, actually when you're not really the game of golf.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>