<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="52aabb3dc294f5cc3948a6910fee8f2f" url=""><![CDATA[so I'm here now<br/><br/>Hey Everyone w00t After 7 invites ( 2 ormore from one person <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> ) i finally joined, w00t <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f6cbe0621dec6589bcfd4160b025de04" url=""><![CDATA[grrrr<br/><br/>to much work to do!!!! gahh! i hate it!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />i will be glad when the end of this semester is over!!!!! exams are in two weeks!!!!!!! bleh!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e78e00eba824b897e1e3df435d177cb0" url=""><![CDATA[grrrr<br/><br/>to much work to do!!!! gahh! i hate it!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />i will be glad when the end of this semester is over!!!!! exams are in two weeks!!!!!!! bleh!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="34dabce1697969df8f769ba71bb76041" url=""><![CDATA[grrrr<br/><br/>to much work to do!!!! gahh! i hate it!! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />i will be glad when the end of this semester is over!!!!! exams are in two weeks!!!!!!! bleh!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="520b635cf4213cc1a02764c7fd097899" url=""><![CDATA[crazy dayz<br/><br/>Oh boy what a day so far. So i was late for teh bus this morning and i was running down our like 100 ft. drive way and just as a reach the end ( and my bus comes around the corner in full view ) I slip on a patch of ice and land in teh direction of the house, roll back up onto my feet and run teh last 10 feet trying not too collapse from laughter. I geton teh buss and when i sat down at the back three of four kids started clapping. Apparently I did the backwards flip in teh air and came down on my side, and when i rolled back up it looked like i did it on purpose. they said it was cool. lol  I'm all scrapped up, my shirts ripped and dirty ( pink sux's anyway) and my side, arm butt and writing hand are messed up but It's funny as hell. I wish someone would have video taped that! I want to see it!!!  
<br /><br />anywayz, math classes sux bawls. I wrote mike a three page note on how we're stating a video game cover band. lol we're going to play in teh open mic on thursday at school..... two dayz to practice. LOL
<br /><br />and not only that, but i have to write an economics test ( that i forgot about until i woke up this morning) and that stocks project to finish and pass on for this after noon. it took me 5 hours to do the first half yesterday after church. i have suck a head ache right now.  I think I'm broken.
<br />Oh well. if my luck is as random and ( happens just when i desperatly need a break) the north easterly will start soon and we will be sent home after lunch. no worries  
<br /><br />That and I hope my driving is cancelled this evening. &gt;.&lt; that and At-man can come over... my spinage is screwed. yesterday when i was playing guitar at practice, the starp and wiegt of the guitar dug into my right shoulder... it fells like i got implailed. OH! and upcoming events. Our bands CD&quot;s thankies to meh. is going to be in music world in town starting sometime this week. they went off contract and the manager is going to discuss it with me, but they will deffinatly take some!!! w00t!
<br /><br />Anywayz, I&quot;m gunna get back to work now.
<br /><br />later dayz!
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3b3cfd6232282fed01278020b182a609" url=""><![CDATA[ENough is enough<br/><br/>well another person is mad at me for no apparent reason. i have another event added to my list ofthings i need to get done and time is startign to run out.... bleh. i'll be glad when this semester is over and done with. I can't stand all this anymore... and worst of it is.. my closest friends are being asshats when i need them.... sock cuckin fother mucker! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2ab324f6b2b1a4b8c61f2045a061d82c" url=""><![CDATA[life facts<br/><br/>it takes one second to meet someone... an hour to respect them, a day to love them and a lifetime to forget them
<br /><br />Can i meet you? Can you give me an hour? a day? just even a minute? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />I'm bord!!!!!
<br /><br />come chat!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cc854c832277dcc41cf68a68ea7bdc0" url=""><![CDATA[I hate this<br/><br/>I'm at the point now where anythign anyone does bugs teh hell out of me. I'm trapped in teh house, Unhappy, no food, nothing to do, noone to hang out with, and i just finished my stupid homework that I've been doing fo rthe last 4 hours.
<br /><br />nothing is satisfying, unles sit's screaming at random people who don't know teh words &quot; angry, I hat eyou... and various other comments in the english language....&quot;
<br /><br />anywayz enough if this.....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d96a4229962af92d64ea0f74aab6fabb" url=""><![CDATA[HEY YOU!!!! YES YOU!!!<br/><br/>I am in desperate need of social contact. I've been snowe d in my house for the last three days with nothign to do and no one to talk to...... so come chat.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be2168ab247ac0f5cb82c0c280cdb8b0" url=""><![CDATA[what a day.<br/><br/>So i've decided to give up on my business class. I&quot;m almost completely failing out if it. fortunatly there's an opening in an animal science next semester. my friends coming back to take it so it should be good. hmm.... creative multi media in teh morning and bio and animal science in teh after noon. sounds like a plan to me. Our finals are coming up in a week. and all of my classes plan on giving us two assignments two weeks before iout semesters over. we have to do tax forms in math whcich is good. I get GST claims this year.. woot.  in business. we were seperated into groups and we need to teach a class on a chapter. plus we had these stock record projects, whcih was good becuase i discovered that i was quiet good, and invested in some for school.
<br />IN history we have two essays we need to finish. woot. one 2500 word and one  1500 word essay. both topics prepicked for us, I have to right on the first 14 prime ministers, and the halifax explosion/ ww1 woo hoo.... one's interesting ones a pain in the ass. both are due next week.
<br /><br />right after school i can get a good  head start becuase my friend has jazz practice for an hour and a half while i wait for him, i can do some reasearch in the library. we're supposed to go into toqwn right after that so i can get my paycheck and go to a gaming place to pwn some n00bs. lol  ha ha ha
<br /><br />I havn't had the chance to actully get out an enjoy myself in whil so it should be fun.
<br /><br />anywayz, that's all teh news i have for right now. ttul <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="961c38f00c56d43138a9ad2d9809d309" url=""><![CDATA[wanna play 21 questions?<br/><br/>1.Whats your Name?
<br />2. Are we close?
<br />3. What do you think of me?
<br />4. Do you hav a crush on me?
<br />5. Would u kiss me?
<br />6. Describe me in 2 words?
<br />7. If u Had Me for 30 Mins wat would you do?
<br />8. What was ur first impression of me?
<br />9. Do u still think the same?
<br />10.. What reminds u of me?
<br />11. If you could give me anything what would it be?
<br />12. How long u u new me?
<br />13. What do u like best about me?
<br />14. Ever wanted 2 tell me something u could'nt?
<br />15. Could you ever love me?
<br />16. Give me a nickname and explain why?
<br />17.R u gona put this on ur blog and c wat i say bout u?
<br />18.Anything 2 say b4 u go ?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="259b5bada3b650975f05e5c3b093662b" url=""><![CDATA[Chemistry of Hell<br/><br/>The following is an actual question given on a University of Washington Chemistry mid-term.
<br /><br />The answer by one student was so &quot;profound&quot; that the professor shared it with colleagues, via the Internet, which is, of course, why we now have the pleasure of enjoying it as well : 
<br /><br />Bonus Question: Is Hell exothermic (gives off heat) or endothermic (absorbs heat)? Most of the students wrote proofs of their beliefs using Boyle's Law (gas cools when it expands and heats when it is compressed or some variant.One student, however, wrote the following:
<br /><br />' First, we need to know how the mass of Hell is changing in time. So we need to know the rate at which souls are moving into Hell and &gt;&gt;the rate at which they are leaving. I think that we can safely assume that &gt;&gt;once a soul gets to Hell, it will not leave. Therefore, no souls are leaving. As for how many souls are entering Hell, let's look at the different religions that exist in the world today. Most of these religions state that if you are not a member of their religion, you will go to Hell. Since there is more than one of these religions and since people do not belong to more than one religion, we can project that all souls go to Hell. With birth and death rates as they are, we can expect the number of souls in Hell to increase exponentially. Now, we look at the rate of change of the volume in Hell because Boyle's Law states that in order for the temperature and  pressure in Hell to stay the same, the volume of Hell has to expand proportionately as souls are added.This gives two possibilities:
<br /><br />1. If Hell is expanding at a slower rate than the rate at which souls enter Hell, then the temperature and pressure in Hell will increase until all Hell breaks loose.
<br /><br />2. If Hell is expanding at a rate faster than the increase of souls in Hell, then the temperature and pressure will drop until Hell &gt;&gt;freezes over.   So which is it? If we accept the postulate given to me by Teresa during my freshman &gt;&gt;year that, &quot;It will be a cold day in Hell before I sleep with you,&quot; and take into account the fact that I slept with her last night, then number two must be true, and thus I am sure that Hell is exothermic and has already frozen over. The corollary of this theory is that since Hell has &gt;&gt;frozen over, it follows that it is not accepting any more souls and is therefore, extinct......leaving only Heaven, thereby proving the existence of a  divine being which explains why, last night, Teresa kept shouting &quot;Oh my God.&quot;    
<br /><br />THIS STUDENT RECEIVED THE ONLY &quot;A&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fad246440f5e86a96970b2d2573e231c" url=""><![CDATA[I"m not afraid of the question, I'm afraid of the ans<br/><br/>How do you tell someone you love them. Especially when your friendship , if you can call it that, is a joke, and you see them maybe once a week and talk to them  online on occasion.it's  no t the distance or the the fact that we work together that's the problem.it's teh fact that the more i brood over it and the less, or more we speak. It get's more ergant. that need... that desire if you will.
<br /><br />I don't know what to do. 
<br /><br />sometimes, i admnit, I&quot;ll find my thoughts wander to what he may be doing... or if i know what he's doing, is he being successful. is he having fun, is he thinking of me sometimes too? or Does it really matter at all?
<br /><br />It's tough to come to a conclusion when you can't adress the subject, or the time to do so is slow coming in turn.
<br /><br />Sometimes, I think there's signs or little hints, and it drives me crazy. coz even though we may be in teh same building... we get to talk for about 15 minutes tops scattered over a 7 hour period.
<br /><br />I want to make the move on this one. I really do. I have all teh go ahead i need but there's that something that always holds you back. Fear, anxiety. I hate them. I'm being completely overwhelmed in this thing and there's only one way out and it's through acceptence.. the only thing is,....
<br /><br />it lies in a yes or a no...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d6092ada9f10952cf4a1a341c8919b34" url=""><![CDATA[It finally happened<br/><br/>I broke last night.
<br />I just couldn't take it anymore.
<br />Everything I do is to much and my &quot;lowsey attempts&quot; are half assed becuase I&quot;m forced to concentrate on half of something, or compromise between things to be able to get some of them done.
<br /><br />As of right now, wha I&quot;m attempting to do is, university prep, meaning all my courses have to be over 70% and i need an 85% average to get the scholarships I need so I can go to montreal in august. I have that stupid band... th eold one. and i really can't take all teh drama that's going on within the group. The new band that were forming wiht a few friends. it should be fun ( starting after exams due to my schedual ) driving lessons and attempting to get the remaining 80 or so hours I have left to go before April. Work . 21 hours a week, trying to pay off a debt, trying to stay in shape and healthy, attempting to try to sleep ( which has become impossible ) trying to ge the money and cd's back from a buyer, and attempting to get them into music world, while trying to do various other things.
<br /><br />School right now exists of 2 major projects due ALL this week in all three of my courses. I present tomorrow in business class. exams are next week. final tests, studying......unuversity prep.
<br /><br />Band ( old one) consists of trying to figure out what THE FUCK everyones problem is. especially one girl. I want ot chock her. I don't know why she hates me and persist on tearing me apart, making me feel liek an idiot everychance she has and belittleling me to the point where i want to scream and throw my fucking guitar at her ugly blond face. She way to controlling, manipulative, bitchy , narsitic, and head strong. I know when i'm not included and unwanted but she doesn't have to rub it in my face. I do what i can, and apparentyl it's not good enough. i don;t think anythigns fucking good enough for her. she has to rip people down about the littlest things and make a big deal out of everything in front of everyone. not to mention that everyone else is starting to get the same opionion except a couple. but thier all family, and friends and in contact with each other. I'm just teh outsideer that goes along for the ride becuase i have to. I really want to resign. i really do. I can't put up with thier expectations of everything and thier drama over everylittle thing. especially when their already counting down the days till i leave anyway. planning all thses big events and rubbing it in at practices and saving them all until AFTER I&quot;m gone... oh boy. sock cucking fother mucker.
<br /><br />anyway.
<br /><br />it's to the point now wher ei can't deal wiht anyone or anythign with a clear head. I yell at friends,  at everyone, assume things in the worst prospect, I can't even justiufy the way people look at me anymore. I hat eliving like this.
<br /><br />It's to the point where i go to sleep at night hopeing that i don;t have to go through the next day. it's just one thing after the other all the time. i hat eit!!! and no one understands. what i got last night was a &quot; well it's our own fault. your not healthy and you don;t sleep and spend all yoru time on teh computer and don't schedual yourself. &quot; WTF are you calling me lazy? last time i checked i was doing homeowrk on teh computer and it's too the point wher ei'm just so on the go all the time my body refuses to realax. I'm tired all the time becuase I&quot;m run down to much  and can't cathc up to myself and i CAN
<br />'T  FUCKING  sleep. I just can't do all this shit anymore.!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5ea147df8146ec1f28c651711721eec8" url=""><![CDATA[Why do things have to be so damn complicated?<br/><br/>How on earth can you just come out and tell someone you love them. I keep imaginaing all these things and praying for the righ tmoment to just come out and spill the beans but i never get the chance.
<br /><br />Doing it over msn would be cowardice, and they deserve for me to say it to thier face, not to spill my heart out to a computer screen. but unfourtunatly that's easier said then done.
<br /><br />&quot;it takes a minute to meet someone, and hour to respect them, and a day to love them, 
<br /><br />It took me a second to pick you out in a crowd, a minute to meet you, an hour to respect you, a week to gain you as a friend, but from teh first second i saw you i knew I loved you.
<br /><br />Some day, i want to hug you...
<br />I want to have a face to face conversation with you
<br />I want to spill my hear to you
<br />I want to spill my heart for you.
<br />I want to kiss you
<br />I want to hold you and never let you go...
<br /><br />I want to make you happy.
<br />Cry with you when your sad
<br />give you strength when you need it
<br />Lift you up  when you feel pain
<br />share your  joy
<br />make you laugh
<br /><br />I never want to hurt you
<br />I never want to get you off my mind
<br />I never want to yell at you
<br />I never want to let you go&quot;
<br /><br />There's alot of confessions, i find hard to put to words. Somethings can't be translated from feeling to words, but none the less, i would like you to know.
<br /><br />I hope things will work out.
<br />I hope I can be brave enough to do the dead.
<br />I hope i can tell you I love you.. someday..
<br /><br />I hope I'll get it back....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="97bc253d64c6758f5eb9df5d740831ae" url=""><![CDATA[graahh!!!!<br/><br/>what a crazee day today!!!
<br /><br />alright. so i needed to refinish that video project. gawd, why do regukations have to exist! they block out the best and greatest ideas!!!!! that took me all of my lunch. my lunch that I had packed burnt on me so i didn't eat anything until 4 :30 -5:00.
<br />right after school, i went in town dropped it off to the imac studios to get it sent to Ottawa, then walked to work, but took a detour so i could try to find where he lives,.. ior at least walk in the vacinity to mak eme feel less.... nvm. ha ha ha, does this make me a stocker??? do some people find that attractive?? i hope so... either that, or i hope he didn't notice... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />anywayz, i sat at work for almost an hour... thought my walk would take longer then 45 minutes but oh well... now i'm home with not much to do. mom needs the compy tonight so i won't be getting much done.  i left my math at school, but i finished it anywayz.. damn tax forms.... damn you Robert Bordan for creating tax forms... asshole... not only do you bore my math class but i have to write an essay on you too <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />  * shakes fist *
<br /><br />graah.... i'm surprized no ones tried to give me a muzzle after all teh complaining and yeling I&quot;ve been doing all week.
<br /><br />half my friends thought i was crazy between last night and today. last night i burst out into unessesary laughter, then cried a bit, then laughed then got really angry fora while. i thought my head would explode... then when i was at school today, i';d burst out in histarics fo rno aparant reason at all , and i couldn't hol dit back, or help it too. lol good thign i was in a conference room during my history class... people would have thought i was wierd laughing histerically at 40 desiples in a library... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/dry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />oh well. I think i should go and start writing that 2000 word that due in two dayz... audios!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ce209efa7382d33f66b70eb98eb83c5a" url=""><![CDATA[graahh!!!!<br/><br/>what a crazee day today!!!
<br /><br />alright. so i needed to refinish that video project. gawd, why do regukations have to exist! they block out the best and greatest ideas!!!!! that took me all of my lunch. my lunch that I had packed burnt on me so i didn't eat anything until 4 :30 -5:00.
<br />right after school, i went in town dropped it off to the imac studios to get it sent to Ottawa, then walked to work, but took a detour so i could try to find where he lives,.. ior at least walk in the vacinity to mak eme feel less.... nvm. ha ha ha, does this make me a stocker??? do some people find that attractive?? i hope so... either that, or i hope he didn't notice... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />anywayz, i sat at work for almost an hour... thought my walk would take longer then 45 minutes but oh well... now i'm home with not much to do. mom needs the compy tonight so i won't be getting much done.  i left my math at school, but i finished it anywayz.. damn tax forms.... damn you Robert Bordan for creating tax forms... asshole... not only do you bore my math class but i have to write an essay on you too <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />  * shakes fist *
<br /><br />graah.... i'm surprized no ones tried to give me a muzzle after all teh complaining and yeling I&quot;ve been doing all week.
<br /><br />half my friends thought i was crazy between last night and today. last night i burst out into unessesary laughter, then cried a bit, then laughed then got really angry fora while. i thought my head would explode... then when i was at school today, i';d burst out in histarics fo rno aparant reason at all , and i couldn't hol dit back, or help it too. lol good thign i was in a conference room during my history class... people would have thought i was wierd laughing histerically at 40 desiples in a library... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/dry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />oh well. I think i should go and start writing that 2000 word that due in two dayz... audios!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="292db7bf0230d9cf278df2a45d04ba58" url=""><![CDATA[graahh!!!!<br/><br/>what a crazee day today!!!
<br /><br />alright. so i needed to refinish that video project. gawd, why do regukations have to exist! they block out the best and greatest ideas!!!!! that took me all of my lunch. my lunch that I had packed burnt on me so i didn't eat anything until 4 :30 -5:00.
<br />right after school, i went in town dropped it off to the imac studios to get it sent to Ottawa, then walked to work, but took a detour so i could try to find where he lives,.. ior at least walk in the vacinity to mak eme feel less.... nvm. ha ha ha, does this make me a stocker??? do some people find that attractive?? i hope so... either that, or i hope he didn't notice... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />anywayz, i sat at work for almost an hour... thought my walk would take longer then 45 minutes but oh well... now i'm home with not much to do. mom needs the compy tonight so i won't be getting much done.  i left my math at school, but i finished it anywayz.. damn tax forms.... damn you Robert Bordan for creating tax forms... asshole... not only do you bore my math class but i have to write an essay on you too <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />  * shakes fist *
<br /><br />graah.... i'm surprized no ones tried to give me a muzzle after all teh complaining and yeling I&quot;ve been doing all week.
<br /><br />half my friends thought i was crazy between last night and today. last night i burst out into unessesary laughter, then cried a bit, then laughed then got really angry fora while. i thought my head would explode... then when i was at school today, i';d burst out in histarics fo rno aparant reason at all , and i couldn't hol dit back, or help it too. lol good thign i was in a conference room during my history class... people would have thought i was wierd laughing histerically at 40 desiples in a library... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/dry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />oh well. I think i should go and start writing that 2000 word that due in two dayz... audios!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1a401b11a66b0e0a1eb033105c90fa22" url=""><![CDATA[graahh!!!!<br/><br/>what a crazee day today!!!
<br /><br />alright. so i needed to refinish that video project. gawd, why do regukations have to exist! they block out the best and greatest ideas!!!!! that took me all of my lunch. my lunch that I had packed burnt on me so i didn't eat anything until 4 :30 -5:00.
<br />right after school, i went in town dropped it off to the imac studios to get it sent to Ottawa, then walked to work, but took a detour so i could try to find where he lives,.. ior at least walk in the vacinity to mak eme feel less.... nvm. ha ha ha, does this make me a stocker??? do some people find that attractive?? i hope so... either that, or i hope he didn't notice... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />anywayz, i sat at work for almost an hour... thought my walk would take longer then 45 minutes but oh well... now i'm home with not much to do. mom needs the compy tonight so i won't be getting much done.  i left my math at school, but i finished it anywayz.. damn tax forms.... damn you Robert Bordan for creating tax forms... asshole... not only do you bore my math class but i have to write an essay on you too <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" />  * shakes fist *
<br /><br />graah.... i'm surprized no ones tried to give me a muzzle after all teh complaining and yeling I&quot;ve been doing all week.
<br /><br />half my friends thought i was crazy between last night and today. last night i burst out into unessesary laughter, then cried a bit, then laughed then got really angry fora while. i thought my head would explode... then when i was at school today, i';d burst out in histarics fo rno aparant reason at all , and i couldn't hol dit back, or help it too. lol good thign i was in a conference room during my history class... people would have thought i was wierd laughing histerically at 40 desiples in a library... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/dry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />oh well. I think i should go and start writing that 2000 word that due in two dayz... audios!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="140eb6c99756cb615dfdbf801c0c8a0e" url=""><![CDATA[I finally did it.<br/><br/>I did it.. yeesssshhh!!!!!!
<br /><br />I waited until the righ tmoment.. well... actully.... i waited until i just couldn't anymore. Patience is not one of my virtues AT all. lol.
<br /><br />He was on msn last night and we joked around for a while. I flirted... and then got daring and it just came out. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /> I asked him if he was doing anything &quot; on wednesday in three weeks&quot; ( that would be valitines ) and he said he'd like too. only thing is he can't go anywhere becuase he broke his leg... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />  but that's ok. It would be nice just spending a quiet evening.. get some take out.. lol do other things.... <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> it'll be good as long as I&quot;m with him, that's all i need to be content. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />Anyway.. so then I laid out my confessions... lol and we both got overly excited. I'm happy.. lol I even woke up smiling today. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />&quot; I've had my eye on you kitty &quot; lol ha ha ha h that's what he said onm msn last night. lol then we both agreed that i was obvious but that's alright lol. I&quot;m a big dork. lol ha ha ha ha. 
<br /><br />All in all it was good... only thing i am a little worried about was at the end of the conversation i was like &quot; would you be insulted if I added something else ( to our goonights)  he said no so, jst to be a jerk ( he did it to me several times ) I put this stupid emoticon thing up.. then said na &quot; i think I love you. &quot; lol and i waited aminute and he said it too which is good, but lol. i dunno. I'm supposed to call him at lunch too, and I'm going to go visit him at home after the screening tonight.<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> I can't wait, lol
<br /><br />I'm still kinda walking on air, and my friends are trying to adjust to me being overly happy instead of telling them off for little things. ( pre exam stress )  lol ha ha ha ha ha. they think i'm sick or somethign of the sort. lol
<br /><br />Any wayz. i have to go do that essay that due tomorrow that I STILL never started... tootles. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9214cce6cbe4de80a2ccb143012c5f32" url=""><![CDATA[well....<br/><br/>Today was a good day. I have all the evidence I need, and I am content.
<br />I spent the day between my own secrets and being beehived by everyone else. By now this seemed like it happened a couple days ago, when only it was a few short hours ago.
<br />I wish it was a few hours ago again.... I spent the hours of my eveing by his side. “Bringing the good cheer” meting the family. I was happy. Well more then that really. I spent most of the night in hystarics. I left like an idiot laughing at nothign all the time, but he sai it made him happy, so I was happy too.
<br />I talked alot with his mom. I t was awesome. I really think he like me too.There’s alot of really good signs. He’s really open with things, and he says he wants me to meet his friends. It’s always good, being welcomed into someone elss life like that. 
<br />The good ol’ msn chat was good too. We’re making good headway. We went from how well my first impression went to the whole “ Where we stand” conversation.He said that his parents thought i was “ just a co-worker” and that “ he should tell them”. I got intruiged becuase we had never really declared anything. Sure I asked if he wanted to do anything on v-day but...
<br /><br />He gained alot of respect from me then. Said he waned to put me off so he can ask me in person. He’s realy sincere. I really like him. His heads in the right place. Also, he got really protective when i tol d him how angry mike was and what he was going to do... lol “ no one hits Amy... lol”
<br /> he’s so sweet. I love him alot.
<br /><br />Well this “kitty” is out for now... tootles <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d0aa90b84d216925a15bd5e885343f9f" url=""><![CDATA[it's been such a long time<br/><br/>I'm sorry I havn't been on in such a long time!!!
<br />I can't believe how many visiters I've lost, lol
<br /><br />so how is everyone? good i guess? if y'all wanna chat, message me
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d25d89454a3c367b00cdcf7f12dd9137" url=""><![CDATA[nothing new yet<br/><br/>nothign much new yet. I'm kinda skipping bio right now, but not really. My partners not here and I finished everything the day before.
<br />I have to go to work tonight which sucks coz I&quot;m pretty much falling asleep. I almost did in housing class... but i hate that class anyways. I hiope i get to see my b/f tnight but with mom teh way she is, I&quot;d say that['s amost a garenteed no.... coz you know, who cares about what I want? lol ha ha ha ha ha ha oh well... nod and smile right?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="de6b12668b2e27a88c87d2e18db64935" url=""><![CDATA[omfg<br/><br/>I havn't been on here in like forever!!!! to busy geting all my shit ready for collage applications, family, shows, and work. not to mention exams and all this other shit. grr. I've been so busy. nothing really new though. I&quot;m still alive... which is a good thing.. and I've given up caffene!!!! ha ha no more coffee, no more pop.. it's been like 5 days and I&quot;m dying!!!! oh and as of today I am eligable to get my full lisence. WOOT!!!!!!
<br /><br />anywayz, that's all for now i guess
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>