<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="11">
		<document id="c3c8dd5adc0d724d22d5f9a09ed0263a" url=""><![CDATA[Answer these questions.<br/><br/>I dare you to tell me the truth:
<br /><br />Four things you wonder about me:
<br />01.
<br />02.
<br />03.
<br />04.
<br /><br />Three things you like about me:
<br />01.
<br />02.
<br />03.
<br /><br />Two things you don't like about me:
<br />01.
<br />02.
<br /><br />My best feature:
<br />01.
<br /><br />Two things you want to do with me:
<br />01.
<br />02.
<br /><br />One word that describe me:
<br />01.
<br /><br />One question for me:
<br />01.
<br /><br />I dare you to repost this see how many people do this to you
<br /><br />(&amp; be honest) reply to me
<br /><br />i know everyone out there wonders about everyone, dont be afraid to do this
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f7a5a8dd78b2b2cbaaefde42aebc5542" url=""><![CDATA[U can ask just 1<br/><br/>u can ask me 1 question n 1 question only n i promise 2 giv an honest answer!!
<br />copy and paste this 2 ur blog, u ul b surprised wat u get asked
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="87a24054bf961cb44815985dc5d02885" url=""><![CDATA[Call me<br/><br/>Name:___________________
<br />Number:___________________
<br />Best time to call:__________________
<br />I dare you to copy and paste this and see how many numbers you get.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d0199844297903b42c1bd9f11405beaa" url=""><![CDATA[If she only knew<br/><br/>im sorry
<br />that i bought you roses
<br />to tell you that i like you
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That I was raised with respect
<br />not to sleep with you when you were drunk
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That my body's not ripped enough
<br />to &quot;satisfy&quot; your wants
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />that I open your car door,
<br />and pull out your chair like I was raised
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That I'm not cute enough
<br />to be &quot;your guy&quot;
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That I am actually nice;
<br />not an asshole
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />I don't have a huge bank account
<br />to buy you expensive things
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />I like to spend quality nights at home
<br />cuddling with you, instead of at a club
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />I would rather make love to you then just fuck you
<br />like some random guy.
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That I am always the one you need to talk to,
<br />but never good enough to date
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That I always held your hair back when you threw up, and didn't get mad at you for puking in my car,
<br />but when we went out you went home with another guy
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That I am there to pick you up at 4am when your new man hit you and dropped you off in the middle of nowhere,
<br />but not good enough to listen to me when I need a friend
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />If I start not being there, and being used as a door mat, only to be thrown to the side when the new asshole comes around
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />If I don't answer my phone anymore when you call, to listen to you cry for hours, instead of getting a couple hours of sleep before work
<br /><br />I'm sorry that you can't realize.. I've been the one all along.
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />If you read this and know somebody like this
<br />but don't care But most of all
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />For not being sorry anymore
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That you can't accept me for who I am
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />I can never do anything right, and nothing that I do is good
<br />enough to make it in your world.
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />I caught your bf with another girl and told you about it, I thought that was what friends were for...
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That I told you I loved you and actually meant it.
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />That I talked to you for nine hours on Thanksgiving when your bf was threatening you instead of spending time with my family.
<br /><br />I'm Sorry
<br />That i cared
<br /><br />I'm sorry
<br />that I listen to you at night talk about how you wish you could have done something different.
<br /><br />Ladies always bitch and bitch to their friends that there is never any good guys out there, and they always end up with assholes who mistreat them. Well ladies next time you're bitching, maybe look up to see who you're bitching to, maybe that special someone is right there hanging on your every word as usual, screaming in his head &quot;Why won't you give me a chance?&quot;
<br />Because the person you are usually searching for is right by you.
<br /><br />If you're a guy and you agree with this letter, repost as &quot;if she only knew&quot;
<br /><br />If You're one of the few girls with enough balls to repost, and you would never make your guy feel this way, repost as &quot;To all the girls who look past the nice guy
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3eeed9c14cd782c7531ddfd90f8e63ea" url=""><![CDATA[Fill this out for me.<br/><br/>1. Wud u be in control? 
<br />2. Wud u pull my hair?
<br />3. Wud u whisper in my ear? 
<br />4. Wud u talk dirty to me? 
<br />5. Wud u kiss me with a little / alot of tongue? 
<br />6. Wud u say my name? 
<br />7. Wud u go down on me? 
<br />8. Wud u let me give u a hickie?
<br />9. How many rounds would we go? 
<br />10. What wud u wna do afterwards? 
<br />11. Wud u take off all ur clothes then take myn off slowly?
<br />12. Wud u lick and bite me all over? 
<br />13. Wud u like to play or get straight to the point? 
<br />14. Wud u want me2 take my time? 
<br />15. How freaky are u 1 - 10? 
<br />16. Wud u want me to go fast / slow? 
<br />17. Where wud u wna &quot;do it&quot;? 
<br />18. Wud u be loud / quiet? 
<br />19. Wud u mind if i lykd you? 
<br />20. Wud u do it today? 
<br />21. Wud u do it tomorrow? 
<br />22. Wud u call me in the morning? 
<br />23. R u going to re-post these so I can answer them for you
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="48f96f445e56aeb97040291f45d1ec8" url=""><![CDATA[Juggalo vs. Friend<br/><br/>&quot;&quot;SEND THIS TO ALL THE Juggalo's IF YOU GOT THERE BACK!
<br />IF YOU GET THIS bACK YOU GOT RESPECT
<br /><br />JUGGALO VS. FRIEND--
<br />Friend: Calls your parents &quot;Mr.&quot; or &quot;Mrs.&quot;
<br />Juggalo: Call your parents &quot;Mom&quot; or &quot;Dad.&quot;
<br />Friend: Has never seen you cry.
<br />Juggalo: Has the best shoulder to cry on.
<br />Friend: Asks you for your number.
<br />Juggalo: Asks you for their number.
<br />Friend: Will leave you hanging to be with a crowd.
<br />Juggalo: Always has your back.
<br />Friend: Runs for help in a fight.
<br />Juggalo: Jumps in the fight to help.
<br />Friend: Will bail your stale ass out of Jail.
<br />Juggalo: Will be sittin' right next to you saying &quot;That was fucking awesome!&quot;
<br />Friend: Will help you move out of a house.
<br />Juggalo: Will help you move a dead body out of the house.
<br />Friend: Bums you a cigarette
<br />Juggalo: Bums you his last pack
<br />Friend: Is there when you need them
<br />Juggalo: Is there even when you dont need them
<br />Friend: Gets drunk at a party and pukes on your carpet
<br />Juggalo: Feels worse than you do about puking on your carpet in the morning
<br />Friend: Hides you from the cops
<br />Juggalo: Is probably the reason the cops are after you in the first place
<br />Friend: Lets you make an ass out of yourself in public
<br />Juggalo: Is up there with you making an ass out of themselves too
<br />Friend: Likes you cause your always doing stupid shit
<br />Juggalo: Loves you even though you do stupid shit
<br />Friend: Is shocked to find out your actually gay
<br />Juggalo: Already knew but really could care less
<br />Friend: Doesn't tell anyone if you kill the guy who tried to kill you
<br />Juggalo: Helped you kill that asshole
<br />Friend: Comes with you to your moms funeral
<br />Juggalo: Cries with you at your moms funeral
<br />Friend: Tells you when his parents doesnt want him to hang out with you any more
<br />Juggalo: Laughs in his parents faces for saying that
<br />Friends: Fade
<br />Juggalos: Are 4 Ever&quot;&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dc1e023469ac7d8eb0dbf192364aa99d" url=""><![CDATA[NO KID SHOULD EVER HAVE TO GO THROUGH THIS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!<br/><br/>really hope everyone on my friends list will read this and repost i think any adult that would do this to a child should be beaten to death slowly then rott in hell. 
<br /><br />My name is Chris 
<br />I am three, 
<br />My eyes are swollen 
<br />I cannot see, 
<br />I must be stupid 
<br />I must be bad, 
<br />What else could have made 
<br />My daddy so mad? 
<br /><br />I wish I were better 
<br />I wish I weren't ugly, 
<br />Then maybe my mommy 
<br />Would still want to hug me. 
<br /><br />I cant do wrong 
<br />I cant speak at all 
<br />Or else im locked up 
<br />All day long. 
<br /><br />When im awake im all alone 
<br />The house is dark 
<br />My folks arent home 
<br />When my mommy does come home 
<br />I'll try and be nice, 
<br />So maybe ill just get 
<br />One whipping tonight. 
<br /><br />I just heard a car 
<br />My daddy is back 
<br />From Chariles bar. 
<br />I hear him curse 
<br />My name is called 
<br />I press myself 
<br />Against the wall 
<br /><br />I try to hide 
<br />From his evil eyes 
<br />I'm so afraid now 
<br />I'm starting to cry 
<br />He finds me weeping 
<br />Calls me ugly words, 
<br />He says its my fault 
<br />He suffers at work. 
<br /><br />He slaps and hits me 
<br />And yells at me more, 
<br />I finally get free 
<br />And run to the door 
<br />Hes already locked it 
<br />And I start to bawl 
<br />He takes me and throws me 
<br />Against the hard wall 
<br /><br />I fall to the floor 
<br />With my bones nearly broken, 
<br />And my daddy continues 
<br />With more bad words spoken, 
<br />&quot;I'm sorry!&quot;, I scream 
<br />But its now much to late 
<br />His face has been twisted 
<br />Into a unimaginable shape 
<br /><br />The hurt and the pain 
<br />Again and again 
<br />O please God, have mercy! 
<br />O please let it end! 
<br />And he finally stops 
<br />And heads for the door 
<br />While i lay there motionless 
<br />Sprawled on the floor 
<br /><br />My name is Chris 
<br />I am three, 
<br />Tonight my daddy 
<br />Murdered me 
<br /><br />And you can help 
<br />Sickens me to the soul, 
<br />And if you read this 
<br />and dont pass it on 
<br />I pray for your forgivness 
<br />Because you would have to be 
<br />One heartless person 
<br />To not be affected 
<br />By this Poem 
<br />And because u r effected, 
<br />Do something about it! 
<br />So all i ask you to do 
<br />Is pass this on! 
<br /><br />IF YOU ARE AGAINST CHILD ABUSE! 
<br /><br />PLEASE COPY AND PASTE THIS AND PASS IT ON !! 
<br /><br />REPOST THIS AS no kid should ever have to go through this 
<br /><br />Please don't just read this please continue to pass this on
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a0fe68da176f40b820142997028a38a2" url=""><![CDATA[One of my friends wrote this and I wanted to share it.<br/><br/>He says he loves her
<br />He says he means it
<br />And maybe he does
<br />Maybe its true
<br />Maybe he means it when he says I love you
<br />But at night she cries over him
<br />At night she fears
<br />He walks the streets
<br />He hangs with his gang
<br />And she fears,
<br />maybe one day he wont come back . . .
<br />Its his family
<br />Its his life
<br />And she knows theres nothing she can do
<br />So she says I love you . . .
<br />And as he leaves to walk the streets 
<br />She prays
<br />She prays she'll see him the next day . . .
<br />His gang's his family
<br />His gang is his life
<br />And theres nothing she can do . . .
<br />He walks the streets
<br />He has her in his heart
<br />And he's starting to make stupid mistakes
<br />Getting reckless . . .
<br />He runs to get home to her
<br />To let her know hes okay
<br />To let her know he survived another day . . .
<br />While as his homies are shot
<br />Seen so much pain flash before his eyes
<br />Seen so many people die
<br />But he tells her nothing going on
<br />Just wants to keep her happy
<br />Shes seen the shows
<br />Shes seen the news
<br />She knows
<br />But how can she be happy
<br />How can she smile when she fears for him
<br />She loves him
<br />Shes in love with him
<br />And she tries so hard to not let is show
<br />But she cant with the knowledge she knows . . .
<br />She tries to stay calm when it turns to days
<br />She tries to say shes okay
<br />Maybe it'll be another day
<br />But those fears turn to worry
<br />And that worry turns to depression
<br />Too many days have gone bye
<br />And she badly misses her guy . . .
<br />Shes crying over him
<br />Thinking maybe he wont be back this time
<br />She needs him . . . . . . . .
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b727bdabce224908231d7eb32b643297" url=""><![CDATA[I'd be this Boyfriend<br/><br/>When she walks away from you mad
<br />[ Follow her ]
<br /><br />When she stare's at your mouth
<br />[Kiss her ]
<br /><br />When she pushes you or hit's you
<br />[ Grab her and dont let go ]
<br /><br />When she start's cursing at you
<br />[ Kiss her and tell her you love her ]
<br /><br />When she's quiet
<br />[ Ask her whats wrong ]
<br /><br />When she ignore's you
<br />[ Give her your attention ]
<br /><br />When she pull's away
<br />[ Pull her back ]
<br /><br />When you see her at her worst
<br />[ Tell her she's beautiful ]
<br /><br />When you see her start crying
<br />[Just hold her and dont say a word ]
<br /><br />When you see her walking
<br />[ Sneak up and hug her waist from behind ]
<br /><br />When she's scared
<br />[ Protect her ]
<br /><br />When she lay's her head on your shoulder
<br />[ Tilt her head up and kiss her ]
<br /><br />When she steal's your favorite hat
<br />[ Let her keep it and sleep with it for a night]
<br /><br />When she tease's you
<br />[ Tease her back and make her laugh ]
<br /><br />When she doesnt answer for a long time
<br />[ reassure her that everything is okay ]
<br /><br />When she look's at you with doubt
<br />[ Back yourself up ]
<br /><br />When she say's that she like's you
<br />[ she really does more than you could understand ]
<br /><br />When she grab's at your hands
<br />[ Hold her's and play with her fingers ]
<br /><br />When she bump's into you
<br />[ bump into her back and make her laugh ]
<br /><br />When she tell's you a secret
<br />[ keep it safe and untold ]
<br /><br />When she looks at you in your eyes
<br />[ dont look away until she does ]
<br /><br />When she misses you
<br />[ she's hurting inside ]
<br /><br />When you break her heart
<br />[ the pain never really goes away ]
<br /><br />When she says its over
<br />[ she still wants you to be hers ]
<br /><br />When she repost this bulletin
<br />[ she wants you to read it ]
<br /><br />- Stay on the phone with her even if shes not saying anything.
<br /><br />- When she's mad hug her tight and don't let go
<br /><br />- When she says she's ok dont believe it, talk with her
<br /><br />- because 10 yrs later she'll remember you
<br /><br />- Call her at 12:00am on her birthday to tell her you love her
<br /><br />- Call her before you sleep and after you wake up
<br /><br />- Treat her like she's all that matters to you.
<br /><br />- Tease her and let her tease you back.
<br /><br />- Stay up all night with her when she's sick.
<br /><br />- Watch her favorite movie with her or her favorite show even if you think its stupid.
<br /><br />- Give her the world.
<br /><br />- Let her wear your clothes.
<br /><br />- When she's bored and sad, hang out with her.
<br /><br />- Let her know she's important.
<br /><br />- Kiss her in the pouring rain.
<br /><br />- When she runs up at you crying, the first thing you say is;
<br /><br />&quot;Who's ass am I kicking today baby?&quot;
<br /><br />If you do post this in the next four minutes the one you love will :
<br /><br />Call you.
<br /><br />Kiss you.
<br /><br />Love you.
<br /><br />Text you.
<br /><br />Guys post as: &quot;I'd be this Boyfriend.&quot;
<br /><br />Girls post as: &quot;A real Boyfriend
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="383a07e2f827150b2fbcbb1d3ab83722" url=""><![CDATA[Just a few questions that would be nice to have answered.<br/><br/>How old do I look?
<br />[]13
<br />[]14
<br />[]15
<br />[]16
<br />[]17
<br />[]18
<br />[]19
<br />[] other ___
<br /><br />How good do I look from 1-10 (1-ugly / 10-HoTT)
<br />[] 1
<br />[] 2
<br />[] 3
<br />[] 4
<br />[] 5
<br />[] 6
<br />[] 7
<br />[] 8
<br />[] 9
<br />[] 10
<br /><br />Would you rather..
<br />[] Do me
<br />[] Date me
<br /><br />Do I have pretty eyes?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br /><br />Would you be sad if I moved?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br /><br />Would you come visit me?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br /><br />Am I..
<br />[] Hot
<br />[] Beautiful
<br />[] Sexy
<br />[] Cute
<br /><br />Would you rather.. hmmm
<br />[] Makeout
<br />[] Cuddle
<br />[] Fuck
<br />[] Go out
<br /><br />Would you go out with me?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
<br /><br />Would you give me your number?
<br />[] Yes ( ... ) &lt;-----leave your number
<br />[] No
<br /><br />Are you going to repost this so I can answer for YOU?
<br />[] Yes
<br />[] No
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ce1f7241f2a1c72499f5357ea833e576" url=""><![CDATA[Juggalo vs. Fake Juggalo<br/><br/>FAKE HOMIES: Never ask for food. 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: are the reason you have no food. 
<br />_______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: Call your parents Mr/Mrs 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: Call your parents DAD/MOM 
<br />_______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: bail you out of jail and tell you what you did was wrong. 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: Would sit next to you sayin &quot;Damn ... we fucked up ... but that shit was fun!&quot; 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: never seen you cry. 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: cry with you 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: Borrow your stuff for a few days then give it back. 
<br />JUGGALOHOMIES: keep your s*** so long they forget its yours. 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: know a few things about you. 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: Could write a book about you with direct quotes from you. 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: Will leave you behind if that is what the crowd is doing. 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: Will kick the whole crowds a** that left you. 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: Would knock on your front door. 
<br />JUGGALOHOMIES: Walk right in and say &quot;I'M HOME!&quot; 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: Are for awhile. 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: Are for life. 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: Will take your drink away when they think you've had enough. 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: Will look at you stumbling all over the place and say &quot;Girl drink the rest of that you know we don't waste food up AND toke this joint up.&quot; 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: will talk nasty to the person who talks nasty about you. 
<br />JUGGALOHOMIES: Will knock their lights out 
<br />______________________ 
<br />FAKE HOMIES: Would ignore this 
<br />JUGGALO HOMIES: Will send this to all their real friends and hope to get it back!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>