<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="4afaf47db2a543e2c009773391ac349" url=""><![CDATA[Social security card will be a unified national social secur<br/><br/>In the future, will be a unified national social security card: ID number will serve as a social security card number, life-long, cross-regional barriers to the transfer of employment, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> classic tall&lt;/a&gt;social security is expected to continue to be addressed. Social Security Bureau said yesterday in Chengdu in July this year, the National Standardization Management Committee issued national standards for &quot;social insurance, the core business of data quality standards,&quot; the official launch of the development work, including Chengdu, IESS, including eight units were approved to participate in the drafting of the development of The &quot;national standard.&quot;It is understood, the State Department who unified this year is expected to issue 600 million social security card, replace social security card around the home-made. By then, the situation will start in Chengdu provincial social security card replacement, the current social security card replacement is being conducted in Chengdu research, is expected by the end of the formation of the first draft. &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bclassic"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html&quot;&gt;classic</a> short uggs&lt;/a&gt;Social security card will be a unified national standard,The social security card are now the provinces, cities and states made, card color, card number digits are not the same. &quot;For example, Chengdu, social security card is our 9-digit number from the card to the province, city states, the province can not be universal, social security information to end this national network, the transfer is a big obstacle to follow.&quot; Chengdu City IESS, the official said, Chengdu in the drafting of the development of &quot;national standard&quot;, the purpose is to realize the standardization of social security information management, unified social security card is the most obvious feature, as long as the standard uniform, and after a national network of social security information, anywhere in the country Any queries can be a social security card to the social security information, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Buggs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html&quot;&gt;uggs</a> bailey button&lt;/a&gt;and easy to use.In accordance with the requirements of the &quot;norm&quot; came out, China's social security card will be unified throughout the country, no longer appear since the number, identity card number as used in all individuals to participate in social security code, to facilitate mobility.Social security card to achieve national unity, national general, the insured's insurance information necessary to the national network. Chengdu IESS, the official said, including the insured's age, payment amount, pension, life and other core business data insured will be included in the national network, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> knightsbridge sale&lt;/a&gt;which will help the insured in the country's regional employment , follow the transfer of social security. The responsible person said, with the &quot;national standard&quot;, the data for model unified. By recording, tracking, insured accurate and complete standard data, the real social security services &quot;record life, service life, tracking his life.&quot;Chengdu Bureau of Human Resources and Social Information Center director Zhou Yan said, the new social security card for the IC card, magnetic card, compared with the active, higher security, and a storage function can be used to access the payment, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> cardy boots&lt;/a&gt;in short, on social security card Direct recharge payment, greatly facilitate the insured. Huang Yan Yao Changshou intern West City Correspondent.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="963a2d61c5010831302e7a971da26fb4" url=""><![CDATA[SAWS: current information that is really a moving vehicle ac<br/><br/>August 22, &quot;7.23&quot; Yongwen line railway traffic accidents particularly significant occasion in January, the State Administration of Work Safety committee member, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> classic tall&lt;/a&gt;Chief Engineer, Huang Yi, spokesman Xinhua invited guest to introduce the motor car accident progress of the investigation, and is being carried out nationwide high-speed railway projects under construction and safety inspection of the situation and communicate with friends online. Administration of Work Safety said the accident is really Wenzhou[Moderator] users Hello everybody, welcome to watch the interview with Xinhua. Today is August 22, from the &quot;7.23&quot; Yongwen major railway line in particular the occurrence of traffic accidents has been a whole month's time. &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bclassic"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html&quot;&gt;classic</a> short uggs&lt;/a&gt;The accident brought us a lot of grief, touched, doubt and difficulty, and a month later, the progress of our investigation of the accident in the end how it going? Can we prevent similar incidents in the future happen? Today we are invited to the State Administration of Work Safety committee member, Chief Engineer, guest Ben Wang Huang Yi, spokesman for the interpretation of all relevant topics, yellow Bureau hello, and our friends and say hello. netizens Good afternoon, thank Xinhua provide such opportunities, so that we can on the Internet on issues of concern to everyone in the discussions, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Buggs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html&quot;&gt;uggs</a> bailey button&lt;/a&gt;would like to thank friends for the safety of the care and support.Council two weeks ago, I saw you yellow and surfers, said &quot;This incident is not a natural disaster&quot;, and that the progress of this investigation team how to do? Could you give some information about it?the CPC Central Committee and State Council after the accident, accident investigation and handling of high priority, and timely component of the State Council, &quot;7.23&quot; incident investigation team and to further strengthen and improve the accident investigation team members and associated systems of work. A period of time, all the comrades of the accident investigation team in accordance with the instructions of the State Council, in accordance with rigorous, realistic and efficient principle, indeed around the clock, hard efforts to accelerate the progress of the accident investigation.the previous period, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> knightsbridge sale&lt;/a&gt;the accident investigation team has the scene of the accident investigation, investigation, and the scene of the accident simulation, while the original data collection, analysis, including interpretation of black box, while the relevant units and associated personnel were asked and the relevant information has also been analyzed, for the necessary experts. Through these hard and meticulous work, we should say we have mastered this accident cause analysis, identify some of the large amount of responsibility, valuable evidence and information.By preliminary analysis, we feel that this accident only exposed signal system design flaws, resulting in failure problems caused by lightning, but also reflects the failure, the emergency response and poor safety management loopholes. Can say, this really was an accident should occur, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> cardy boots&lt;/a&gt;avoid accidents and prevention together.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f6f483f5cfbe3dc1bb27d30ef8209def" url=""><![CDATA[Wenzhou Train Accident Investigation Unit will submit a repo<br/><br/>China's State Administration of Work Safety spokesman Huang Yi told Xinhua News Agency reporter 22 interview that a preliminary analysis by the &quot;7.23&quot; Yongwen particularly important railway line accident exposed many problems, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> classic tall&lt;/a&gt;this was not the place, and prevention of accidents can be avoided.Administration of Work Safety said the accident is really Wenzhou Train accidents Dragon TV &quot;Oriental News,Huang Yi said, &quot;7.23&quot; railway accident, the CPC Central Committee, State Council attached great importance to the accident investigation, accident investigation team in time the composition of the State Council, and to further strengthen and improve the accident investigation team members and associated systems of work. Accident investigation team in accordance with rigorous, realistic and efficient principles of the day, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bclassic"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html&quot;&gt;classic</a> short uggs&lt;/a&gt;an orderly, to speed up the progress of the accident investigation. disclosed that the previous period, the scene of the accident investigation team has conducted a survey, investigation, and simulate the scene, the original data were collected, analyzed, including the interpretation of black box, but also related to the relevant units and personnel were asked made the necessary experts. &quot;Through these hard and meticulous work, we already have a lot of this accident cause analysis, responsibility for identification of valuable evidence and information.&quot;Huang Yi said through a preliminary analysis found that the accident exposed both signal system design flaws, resulting in failure problems caused by lightning, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Buggs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html&quot;&gt;uggs</a> bailey button&lt;/a&gt;but also reflects the failure, the emergency response and poor safety management loopholes. &quot;You could say that the accident was a really should not happen, and prevention of accidents can be avoided.&quot;He said the investigation team has completed a preliminary technical report on the accident and the direct cause of the accident report of the Group, the next step is about to enter the identification stage responsible for the accident. Responsible for the accident through accreditation, made responsible for the accident, the responsibility of handling the unit, so that the responsible person shall, in accordance with regulations subject to appropriate accountability.Huang Yi said that the direct cause of this accident, indirect causes, and identification of responsibility for the accident also need to go through further analysis, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> knightsbridge sale&lt;/a&gt;research, to arrive at scientific and accurate judgments of the conclusions. General plan in September, the accident investigation team will be formally submitted to the State Council handling the accident investigation report.According to reports, the State Council, high-speed rail safety inspection of the 12 inspection teams are already in place to work. In accordance with the unified arrangements of the State Council, the inspection drawn from 12 ministries and 286 staff, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> cardy boots&lt;/a&gt;including 175 experts, composed of 12 inspection groups in 10 railway bureaus of the 49 high-speed rail project under construction, 6000 km high-speed rail lines in operation to conduct a comprehensive inspection.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c3518729da8d793ac72ded968407eff4" url=""><![CDATA[Samsung said Apple iPad design back from 40 years ago, scien<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fa2f2ded4be493ec363a134695628b24" url=""><![CDATA[Samsung said Apple iPad design back from 40 years ago, scien<br/><br/>Beijing August 19, noon, according to documents released by Dutch Court in The Hague, Apple hopes throughout the EU for all the Galaxy series smart phones and tablet PCs issued an import ban.Apple's action will affect the Galaxy Ace, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> classic tall&lt;/a&gt;Galaxy S, Galaxy S II smartphones, and Galaxy Tab 7 and Galaxy Tab 10.1 Tablet PC.Apple sent a letter to Samsung in the indictment requires the dealer, within 14 days to return all inventory, and the cost borne by Samsung. The dealer does not return the inventory will also be regarded as infringing Apple's intellectual property rights.Samsung said in a statement: &quot;Samsung will continue to actively defend and protect our intellectual property rights to ensure that our mobile communications business can continue to innovate and grow.&quot;Apple spokesman was not immediately available for comment.Over the past few months, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bclassic"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html&quot;&gt;classic</a> short uggs&lt;/a&gt;Apple and Samsung Tablet PC's intellectual property rights between the legal battle began. Earlier this month, a German court in most countries of the European Union issued a preliminary injunction Galaxy Tab 10.1. But this week a German court lifted the ban in effect outside of Germany. This allows Samsung to continue to sell Galaxy products.With the growing Android users, and Apple gradually began to obstruct the proceedings through the development of this product. The case shows that Samsung and Apple in the three continents of the legal dispute is undermining the company's Tablet PC market competitiveness. It is predicted that the Tablet PC market by 2015 will reach $ 53 billion. Once out of the European market, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Buggs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html&quot;&gt;uggs</a> bailey button&lt;/a&gt;combined with HP and RIM from the competition, Samsung Galaxy Tab sales than previously expected this year, down 50 million units,Market research firm Ovum analyst Tim in Melbourne Reno Wendeng (Tim Renowden) said: &quot;This is the real thing that Samsung pain if these legal disputes continue, then it would affect the sales of Samsung products. The worst As a result, Samsung's channel partners found Samsung products will give them a risk. &quot;Düsseldorf District Court spokesman Peter Schultz (Tim Renowden) said that the court may after hearing three weeks make a final decision. Then, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> knightsbridge sale&lt;/a&gt;if dissatisfied with the award, either party can appeal.Days before the Federal Court of Australia ruled that Samsung may not sell in the U.S. version of the Galaxy Tab 10.1. Apple lawyer Steven Boer Li (Steven Burley) 8 1 at Sydney's Federal Court said that Samsung had Apple's products infringe 10 patents. Galaxy Tab 10.1 using the Google Android operating system, in June this year in the U.S. on sale next month in Korea market. IPad tablet is slightly thinner than the fuselage, but the larger screen, higher resolution camera.Market research firm Strategy Analytics in London analyst (Neil Mawston) said, compared to Apple's Tablet PC shipments this year may reach 35 million units. He said the first quarter of this year, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> cardy boots&lt;/a&gt;Samsung is the world's second-largest tablet PC makers, market share is about 16%, but far behind Apple iPad 69% share.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c490c8b3ed9e1591f3627f0c208d88f" url=""><![CDATA[Eastern consecutive five million hours of flight safety by F<br/><br/>As of July 2011, China Eastern Airlines Corporation Limited (hereinafter referred to as &quot;CEA&quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /> has achieved a continuous five million hours of flight safety, security, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> classic tall&lt;/a&gt;passenger transport 280 million passengers. According to &quot;China's civil aviation safety incentives,&quot; the Civil Aviation Authority decided to grant China Eastern Airlines, &quot;Star Flight Safety Award.&quot; August 25 morning, the Civil Aviation Authority of China Eastern Airlines in Shanghai officially awarded &quot;five-star China Civil Aviation Flight Safety Award&quot; medal. This is Eastern history and a landmark of the important moment, China Eastern Airlines is by virtue of excellent safety performance among the ranks of the advanced international airlines.&quot;Safety is the root, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bclassic"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html&quot;&gt;classic</a> short uggs&lt;/a&gt;the service is the soul.&quot; Over the years, Eastern has continued to seek safety as the biggest social responsibility has always been committed to achieve security and development, scientific development and sustainable development, conscientiously implement the scientific concept of development, adhere to the &quot;safety first, prevention, comprehensive, continuous improvement 'approach, committed to explore and establish a set of advanced international aviation safety management standards, but also for their own development needs, effective safety management concepts and methods. In 2010, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Buggs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html&quot;&gt;uggs</a> bailey button&lt;/a&gt;China Eastern Airlines as a pilot unit of the first by the Civil Aviation Authority SMS (Safety Management System) certification. Steady improvement in the quality of Eastern run SMS to SMS system as the starting point, the full application of SMS methods and standards, access and analyze all types of safety information, conduct timely risk management, reduce the security risk level, to achieve a secure closed-loop management.Year 2010, China Eastern Airlines 1.201 million hours of safe flight, landing 568,000 vehicles, up respectively 12.2%, 7.4% incident rate of less than full-million when the average level of civil aviation, unique in the industry; China Eastern Airlines has passed the IATA Operational Fourth review of security audit to obtain and maintain the IATA registration. Following in 2009, &quot;Flight Safety Award Samsung&quot; and by 2010, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> knightsbridge sale&lt;/a&gt;&quot;Four Star Flight Safety Award&quot;, this, China Eastern Airlines was awarded &quot;Five Star Flight Safety Award&quot; award. Safety performance continued to refresh, the level of safe operation to a new level every year.As the largest base of China Eastern Airlines Shanghai Airlines, passenger traffic has been ranked the world's top ten. Especially in the past two years, in the safe development, driven by China Eastern Airlines route network beginning to take shape, the layout of the market is increasingly clear, re-emerging effects of sustained, continuous profit, staff morale, work into a benign and healthy development track. Eastern Airlines said it would maintain the courage to explore, a pioneering spirit, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> cardy boots&lt;/a&gt;to build a solid operational safety shields, and striving for better safety performance, to the &quot;Blue Sky Diamond Flight Safety Award&quot; forward, to continue for the whole community to provide higher quality flight operation for the construction of air power and to promote Shanghai aviation hub and make greater contribution.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4f1d720b365778b3449bf5e3c0344ac1" url=""><![CDATA[State Oceanic Administration: ConocoPhillips oil spill will<br/><br/>August 25 afternoon, the State Oceanic Administration in Beijing video information meetings to inform Penglai 19-3 oil field disposal of the oil spill, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> classic tall&lt;/a&gt;and to propose follow-up measures. State Oceanic Administration official said, on August 31 will be a key node, any damage to our marine environment, companies are bound to pay the price.According to the briefing, the first time since June 4 oil spill since the Penglai 19-3 oil field cumulative oil spill polluted waters 5500 square kilometers, resulting in worse than Grade IV water about 870 square kilometers. Major oil spill oil spill polluted the surrounding waters and the northwest platform area, and has affected the Bohai Sea coast.Among them, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bclassic"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html&quot;&gt;classic</a> short uggs&lt;/a&gt;wearing Liaoning Suizhong East River along the beach, river beach at Repulse Bay in Hong Kong and Beijing Qinhuangdao Don Gold Coast and other areas affected, in whole or in part of the oil spill from the Penglai Oilfield.According to Wang Fei, deputy director of the State Oceanic Administration introduced the disposal of oil spills in the work, the North Sea Branch of State Oceanic Administration, and interviews with management of ConocoPhillips China 8; sends ConocoPhillips and fulfill the complete order Find oil spill points, sealing the requirements of class oil source fax 30; convene an expert consultation will be assessed five times, and 26 consultants.Surveillance to monitor the environmental impact of oil spills, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Buggs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html&quot;&gt;uggs</a> bailey button&lt;/a&gt;the State Oceanic Administration to satellite remote sensing, aerial remote sensing, ocean surveillance ship monitoring and on-site law enforcement and other means of three-dimensional oil spill monitoring the implementation of all-weather monitoring: monitoring has mobilized eight sea vessels, sailing 30000 nautical miles; two maritime surveillance aircraft, flying 29 sorties 112 hours, a range of about 24,800 km; interpretation of satellite remote sensing data were 73 King; sent onshore inspection staff 851 people, land and shore visits 140,000 km; 102 voyages to carry out emergency monitoring to monitor the sea area of ??about 68 square kilometers, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> knightsbridge sale&lt;/a&gt;to obtain various types of surveillance monitoring data set of nearly thousand; completed the 93 samples of the oil spill fingerprinting. Wang Fei also pointed out that the oil spill occurred after the State Oceanic Administration to initiate and launch eco-claims and is currently a lawyer in accordance with relevant regulations, while preparing for marine ecological damage assessment report for further evidence collection. On this basis, according to the &quot;ecology of marine oil spill damage assessment technical guidelines&quot; and other standards of scientific evaluation, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> cardy boots&lt;/a&gt;estimate the ecological damage caused by oil spill compensation, and ConocoPhillips on behalf of the State to make ecological damage claims.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1875053251bc54e54863bb8db423ab4e" url=""><![CDATA[New Democratic Party of Japan's ruling party today elected<br/><br/>Japan's ruling Democratic Party scheduled for 29 to elect a new representative of the party first, economy minister sea Eda Miles, finance minister Yoshihiko Noda,&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> classic tall&lt;/a&gt; Forestry and Fisheries Minister Kano Michihiko, former Foreign Minister Maehara and former Land and Transport Minister Sumio Mabuchi the five candidates among the sea Eda and the original odds before the higher. However, the Japanese media published more than 28 media survey, Hai Jiang Tian and set before the original may not be a victory, the party's first election very likely &quot;overtime.&quot;The reason why the Democratic Party's first election concern, because the winner will immediately become Japan's new prime minister. &quot;Immediately&quot; concept, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bclassic"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html&quot;&gt;classic</a> short uggs&lt;/a&gt;the 398 House of Representatives 29 Democrats voting the party selected first, the fastest all the members of the House of Representatives may vote on 30 new prime minister. Since the Democratic Party holds an absolute majority of seats in the House, the New Party also won the House of Representatives voted to take over as the new Prime Minister Naoto Kan is no suspense.&quot;Daily News&quot; 28 Democratic members of the public an intention by the survey, the party's first election, there are three possible echelon.Maehara, Noda, and Kano was undoubtedly the second tier, each have their own support team, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Buggs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html&quot;&gt;uggs</a> bailey button&lt;/a&gt;a total of 250 tickets may be equally or more votes;Mabuchi support rate is not too high, the top four candidates may be far behind. First round of elections, if no candidate can get more than half of House Democrats supported the high rate of support the first two candidates will then enter the second round of elections.Japanese media analysis, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> knightsbridge sale&lt;/a&gt;if the five World War II, before the original is no advantage, because Noda and Kano minutes to go a lot before the original source of votes; but if it is before the original and the sea Eda into the second round of elections, then the sea-Eda's advantage will be weakened, before the original's winning percentage will be Noda and get a lot for the support of members increased Kano.Eda and if it is the sea front of the original into the second round of elections, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> cardy boots&lt;/a&gt;the winning duo will be unpredictable.Many uncertainties, the sea-Eda, and before the original camp before the election have shown cautious attitude.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="392f0f8b122262248ad580f537d75303" url=""><![CDATA[Jiang determined as Acting Governor of Hainan Province<br/><br/>Should be invited President Hu Jintao, President of the Republic of the Philippines, Benigno S. Aquino III today until September 3 visit to China. &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-tall-boots-on-sale-c-240.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> classic tall&lt;/a&gt;This is the first visit after taking office, President Aquino, the Philippines will sign a series aimed at promoting bilateral trade and economic, cultural and media cooperation agreement. It is reported that during the visit, Aquino will follow the footprints to the mother's ancestral roots in Fujian Hongjian village.Foreign Ministry spokeswoman Jiang Yu said earlier, this is the first visit after taking office, President Aquino, Chinese leaders will hold talks with him, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bclassic"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-classic-short-boots-on-sale-c-243.html&quot;&gt;classic</a> short uggs&lt;/a&gt;meet on bilateral ties and promote cooperation in various fields, strengthen cooperation in international and regional affairs the coordination of exchange of views. The two sides will sign a series aimed at promoting bilateral trade and economic, cultural and media cooperation agreement. I believe this visit will further promote the further development of Sino-Philippine relations.Aquino told the Chinese media before his visit, said the joint interview, in China to achieve economic development, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Buggs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-bailey-button-boots-on-sale-c-270.html&quot;&gt;uggs</a> bailey button&lt;/a&gt;the Philippines also benefit, therefore, the development of relations between the Philippines and the interests of both sides. He hoped that the relations between the Philippines to mature, &quot;If we can work together to make the bilateral relationship is more mature, we will not just ordinary friends, and become friends, old friend.&quot;Relations between the Philippines will not be damaged Yin Nanhai problem, Philippine President Aquino 26, said he did not think relations between the Philippines will be Yin Nanhai problem damaged, &quot;disputes sometimes can consolidate and strengthen bilateral relations to provide an opportunity.&quot;August 26, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-knightsbridge-boots-sale-c-254.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> knightsbridge sale&lt;/a&gt;	President Aquino in the Philippines Malacanang presidential palace to accept the joint interview with Chinese media correspondents. When asked whether the deal between the Philippines and South China Sea in order to avoid harm to good bilateral relations? He gives an affirmative answer. He said the Philippines and both sides hope to resolve the problem through peaceful means, and the two of safeguarding national interests, it also clearly each other's interests, so both sides will explore the way out.Aquino stressed that the Philippines hopes to strengthen bilateral relations between the Philippines, efforts to eliminate any conflict between the two countries may lead to the situation. The Philippines have many in common, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salesuggbootsonline.com%2Fugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bugg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.salesuggbootsonline.com/ugg-cardy-boots-on-sale-c-267.html&quot;&gt;ugg</a> cardy boots&lt;/a&gt;&quot;for most Filipinos, the little people do not like Chinese food.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="80901a591ae7648fb4dd2d8c5f35c734" url=""><![CDATA[Philippine President Corazon Aquino to the ancestral roots i<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="10c0a90177f2df9daa47941ad380f1a0" url=""><![CDATA[the difficulties people have not been completely resolved do<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8c17098cd45ef86e5f1f97624769e893" url=""><![CDATA[Wen Jiabao said on intangible heritage protection should rea<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3287ff1a0c2b9ff16940ed64eb05778c" url=""><![CDATA[Ministry of Health issued guidelines that should aid falls i<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="55328410cf360b87dc431109d6894803" url=""><![CDATA[State: Bohai Bay, will strictly control new petrochemical pr<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4f02ac267b094733dabc5da803870ea0" url=""><![CDATA[Gaddafi's arsenal can be hundreds of missiles against moder<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="155c7ee584e12597053c35b11ad345ce" url=""><![CDATA[Jiangxi and Hubei 4.6 earthquake occurred at the junction<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a56547828cf9791d72b18f23c7b925d5" url=""><![CDATA[Reporters can observe the four-term CEO "for" wa<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2d570dcca0b22f914c014f86219814f7" url=""><![CDATA[CNOOC, ConocoPhillips agreed to block the program and superv<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d9cdc0bc57f7471cb0741aa30a564126" url=""><![CDATA[Republican history compilation of 30 published positive ro<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2cfee4b8ef9b74a2bae2cb02f041d33e" url=""><![CDATA[Wen: promoting the official property declaration system of<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="34a7cf42103a3e032945245065d8be30" url=""><![CDATA[Wen stressed that environmental protection in Dalian and the<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c975d360323bcb5ebb365002186283d4" url=""><![CDATA[Wen stressed that environmental protection in Dalian and the<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3e21e578340a61e66242aa317ebfb0b3" url=""><![CDATA[Media said the new U.S. arms sales to Taiwan could cause fur<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f20cb2decd25b5df79a60fa181130706" url=""><![CDATA[Yuan Luping: a teacher of life's ups and downs<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy10YWxsLWJvb3RzLW9uLXNhbGUtYy0yNDAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2xhc3NpYy1zaG9ydC1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjQzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">classic short uggs</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi1ib290cy1vbi1zYWxlLWMtMjcwLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">uggs bailey button</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2cta25pZ2h0c2JyaWRnZS1ib290cy1zYWxlLWMtMjU0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ugg knightsbridge sale</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3VnZ2Jvb3Rzb25saW5lLmNvbS91Z2ctY2FyZHktYm9vdHMtb24tc2FsZS1jLTI2Ny5odG1s" target="_blank">ugg cardy boots</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>