<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="17">
		<document id="bcf36cc4d7bcc13c2dbfc36becf05062" url=""><![CDATA[The Zoo Keeper<br/><br/>A bloke starts his new job at the zoo and is given three tasks.
<br /><br />First is to clear the exotic fish pool of weeds. As he does this a huge fish jumps out and bites him. To show who is boss, he beats it to death with a spade. Realising his employer won't be best pleased he disposes of the fish by feeding it to the lions, as lions will eat anything.
<br /><br />Moving on to the second job of clearing out the Chimp house, he is attacked by the chimps that pelt him with coconuts. He swipes at two chimps with a spade killing them both. What can he do?
<br /><br />Feed them to the lions, he says to himself, because lions eat anything. He hurls the corpses into the lion enclosure.
<br /><br />He moves on to the last job which is to collect honey from the South American Bees. As soon as he starts he is attacked by the bees. He grabs the spade and smashes the bees to a pulp. By now he knows what to do and throws them! into the lions cage because lions eat anything.
<br /><br />Later that day a new lion arrives at the zoo. He wanders up to another lion and says &quot;What's the food like here?&quot;
<br /><br />(Wait for it!!)....
<br /><br />The lions say: &quot;Absolutely brilliant, today we had Fish and Chimps with Mushy Bees.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6b430f68d829d2038a469c9b8e949fb" url=""><![CDATA[Poor Pirate<br/><br/>One day a Pirate and a bartender were talking to each other in a bar. The Bartender asked the pirate &quot;Where did ya get that peg leg from?&quot;
<br /><br />The Pirate responded &quot;We were sailing the seas when a big ol shark came up to me while I was swimmin and bit off me leg.&quot;
<br /><br />Later the Bartender asked &quot;Where did you get that hook then?&quot;
<br /><br />The pirate responded &quot;Well, me crew and I were in a battle and it got cut through the bone.&quot;
<br /><br />The bartender then asked &quot;Then where did ya get the eye patch from?&quot;
<br /><br />The pirate said &quot;In a harbor I looked at a gull flying over head and it took a dump right in me eye.&quot;
<br /><br />The bartender was puzzled and asked the pirate, &quot;How would that make you get an eye patch?&quot;
<br /><br />The pirate responded, &quot;First day with the hook.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="65dff7d91d65953fd217cec2f702ecc4" url=""><![CDATA[Some Quick Jokes<br/><br/>Q. Did you hear about the guy who lost his left arm and leg in a car crash?
<br />A. Hes all right now.
<br /><br />Q. Did you hear about the man who was tap dancing?
<br />A. He broke his ankle when he fell into the sink.
<br /><br />Q. What lies at the bottom of the ocean and twitches?
<br />A. A nervous wreck.
<br /><br />Q. Whats the difference between roast beef and pea soup?
<br />A. Anyone can roast beef.
<br /><br />Q. Where do you find a no legged dog?
<br />A. Right where you left him.
<br /><br />Q. Where do you get virgin wool from?
<br />A. Ugly sheep.
<br /><br />Q. Why do bagpipers walk when they play?
<br />A. Theyre trying to get away from the noise.
<br /><br />Q. What does Star Trek and toilet paper have in common?
<br />A. They both circle Uranus looking for Black Holes.
<br /><br />Q. How do you double the value of a Geo Metro?
<br />A. Fill it with gas.
<br /><br />Q. Whats the definition of mixed emotions?
<br />A. When you see your mother-in-law backing off a cliff in your new car.
<br /><br />Q. Why do chicken coops have two doors?
<br />A. Because if it had four doors its be a chicken sedan.
<br /><br />You should always give 100% at work...
<br />12% Monday; 23% Tuesday; 40% Wednesday; 20% Thursday; 5% Friday
<br /><br />Q. What do you call a cow with no legs?
<br />A. Ground beef.
<br /><br />Q. Whats the difference between an oral and a rectal thermometer?
<br />A. The taste
<br /><br />Q. Did you hear about the new divorced Barbie doll that theyre selling in stores now?
<br />A. It comes with all of Kens stuff.
<br /><br />Q. What does a skeleton get when he goes to a bar?
<br />A. A beer and a mop.
<br /><br />Q. What do you call Maoris on Prozac?
<br />A. Once were worriers.
<br /><br />Q. Whats a hindu?
<br />A. Lays eggs.
<br /><br />Q. How many men does it take to wallpaper a room?
<br />A. About two - if theyre thinly sliced.
<br /><br />Q. What do you call a man with no arms or legs that can swim across a pool?
<br />A. Clever Dick
<br /><br />Q. Whats the difference between a porcupine and a Porsche?
<br />A. The porcupine has the pricks on the outside.
<br /><br />Q. How many ears did Davy Crockett have?
<br />A. Three - his left ear, his right ear, and his wild front ear.
<br /><br />Q. Did you hear about the blind man who went bungee jumping?
<br />A. He loved it, but it scared the hell out of his dog.
<br /><br />Q. Why did the leper crash his car?
<br />A. He left his foot on the accelerator.
<br /><br />Q. What do you do if you come across a tiger in the jungle?
<br />A. Wipe him off, apologize and RUN
<br /><br />Q. What do you do if an elephant comes through your window?
<br />A. Swim
<br /><br />Q. Why did the koala fall out of the tree?
<br />A. Because it was dead.
<br /><br />Q. Why did the Leper go back into the shower?
<br />A. He forgot his Head and Shoulders.
<br /><br />Q. What do you get when a Leper takes a bath?
<br />A. Soup.
<br /><br />Q. Why did the ref call a penalty during the Leper Hockey game?
<br />A. Because there was a face off in the corner.
<br /><br />Q. Whats a Lepers favorite sport?
<br />A. Football.
<br /><br />Q. What is Osama bin Ladens idea of safe sex?
<br />A. Marking the camels that kick.
<br /><br />Q. What should Kabul get for its air defense system?
<br />A. A refund.
<br /><br />Q. Why did the tree fall down?
<br />A. The koala forgot to let go.
<br /><br />Q. How many male chauvinist pigs does it take to change a light bulb?
<br />A. None, let the bitch cook in the dark.
<br /><br />Q. What do you do if a bird shits on your car?
<br />A. Dont ask her out again.
<br /><br />Q. What do you call 100 men at the bottom of the ocean?
<br />A. A good start.
<br /><br />Q. Whats the difference between a woman and a computer?
<br />A. A computer only needs the information punched into it once.
<br /><br />Q. Why dont cannibals eat clowns?
<br />A. Because they taste funny.
<br /><br />Q. What do you call a deer with no eyes?
<br />A. No-Eye Deer. (sound like No Idea)
<br /><br />Q. What do you call a deer with no eyes and no legs?
<br />A. Still no eye deer.
<br /><br />Q. What do you call a deer with no eyes, no legs, and no sexual organs?
<br />A. Still no fucking eye deer.
<br /><br />Q. Why are women like condoms?
<br />A. They spend 90% of their time in your wallet, and 10% on your dick.
<br /><br />Q. What can a lifesaver do for a woman a man cant?
<br />A. Cum in five different flavours.
<br /><br />Q. Who is the poorest guy in West Virginia?
<br />A. The Tooth Fairy
<br /><br />Q. Did you hear that Fed Ex and UPS are going to merge?
<br />A. Yeah. Theyre going to call it FED UP
<br /><br />Q. Whats the difference between a car salesman and a computer salesman?
<br />A. The car salesman can probably drive
<br /><br />Q. Did you hear about the guy whos a dyslexic-bulimic?
<br />A. He eats, and then he sticks his finger up his ass.
<br /><br />Q. What do your boss and a slinky have in common?
<br />A. Theyre both fun to watch tumble down the stairs.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f6dadf4ac08010604bc2b85169feb2e9" url=""><![CDATA[Would You?<br/><br/>Would You....
<br />Kiss me:
<br />Hug me:
<br />Date me:
<br />Get tipsy with me:
<br />Kill me:
<br />Love me:
<br />Hate me:
<br />Hold me:
<br />Lie to me:
<br />Hurt me:
<br />Sing with me:
<br />Dance with me:
<br />Grind with me:
<br />Touch me:
<br />suck me
<br />Cuddle with me:
<br />Let me make a move on you:
<br />Make a move on me:
<br />Play with me:
<br />Watch a movie with me:
<br />Get me a B-day gift:
<br />Caress me:
<br />Let me borrow your car:
<br />Let me see you naked:
<br />Be there for me:
<br />Buy me a drink:
<br />Take a shower with me:
<br />Watch porn with me:
<br />Bring me around your friends:
<br />Give me a massage:
<br />Take me to the club:
<br />Go to sleep with me:
<br />Do me:
<br />Drink vodka with me:
<br />Look if i was naked:
<br />Take advantage of me:
<br />Let me take advantage of u:
<br />Hangout with me:
<br />Take care of me if I wasn't feeling good:
<br />Hold hands with me:
<br />Do something incredibly sweet for me:
<br />Give me a lap dance:
<br />Let me give you a lap dance:
<br />Tell me you love me:
<br />Let me call you:
<br />What would you do if you woke up next to me:
<br />Will you repost this so i can do the same for u:
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="59f27b7fd2e6aa163d1315df47309fec" url=""><![CDATA[go on i dare ya!!!!!!!!!!<br/><br/>Name:
<br /><br />Number: - - - - - - - - - - - -
<br /><br />Best time to text:
<br /><br />sheep
<br />xxxxxxxxx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="28c293c1991a4301c4585fd6289e3378" url=""><![CDATA[snickle rhinonose<br/><br/>MY NEW NAME IS IN THE SUBJECT.....DON'T LAUGH UNTIL YOU FIND OUT WHAT YOUR NEW NAME IS 
<br /><br />We all need a little stress-reliever! This only takes a minute.
<br /><br />Please don't be a bore &amp; ruin it. Send it on to everyone you know including the person that sent it to you.   Sometimes when you have a stressful day or week, you need some silliness to break up the day. If we are honest, we have a lot more stressful days than not.
<br /><br />Here is your dose of humor...
<br /><br />A. Follow the instructions to find your new name.
<br /><br />B. Once you have your new name, put it in the subject box and forward it to friends and family &amp; co-workers.   (I copied and pasted it, to leave out any unnecessary extras)
<br /><br />Don't forget to forward it back to the person who sent it to you 
<br /><br />And don't go all adult - a senior manager is now known far &amp; wide as Dorky Gizzardsniffer!
<br /><br />The following is excerpted from a children's book, Captain Underpants And the Perilous Plot Professor Poopypants, by Dave Pilkey, in which the evil Professor forces everyone to assume new names...
<br /><br />So:-
<br /><br />1. Use the third letter of your first name to determine your New first name:
<br /><br />a = snickle
<br />    b = doombah
<br />    c = goober
<br />    d = cheesey
<br />    e = crusty
<br />    f = greasy
<br />    g = dumbo
<br />    h = farcus
<br />    i = dorky
<br />    j = doofus
<br />    k = funky
<br />    l = boobie
<br />    m = sleezy
<br />    n = sloopy
<br />    o = fluffy
<br />    p = stinky
<br />    q = slimy
<br />    r = dorfus
<br />    s = snooty
<br />    t = tootsie
<br />    u = dipsy
<br />    v = sneezy
<br />    w = liver
<br />    x = skippy
<br />    y = dink y
<br />    z = zippy
<br /><br />2. Use the second letter of your last name to determine the first half of your new last name:
<br /><br />a = dippin
<br />    b = feather
<br />    c = batty
<br />    d = burger
<br />    e = chicken
<br />    f = barffy
<br />    g = lizard
<br />    h = waffle
<br />    i = farkle
<br />    j = monkey
<br />    k = flippin
<br />    l = fricken
<br />    m = bubble
<br />    n = rhino
<br />    o = potty
<br />    p = hamster
<br />    q = buckle
<br />    r = gizzard
<br />    s = lickin
<br />    t = snickle
<br />    u = chuckle
<br />    v = pickle
<br />    w = hubble
<br />    x = dingle
<br />    y = gorilla
<br />    z = girdl e
<br /><br />3. Use the third letter of your last name to determine the second half of your new last name:  
<br /><br />a = butt
<br />    b = boob
<br />    c = face
<br />    d = nose
<br />    e = hump
<br />    f = breath
<br />    g = pants
<br />    h = shorts
<br />    i = lips
<br />    j = honker
<br />    k = head
<br />    l = tush
<br />    m = chunks
<br />    n = dunkin
<br />    o = brains
<br />    p = biscuits
<br />    q = toes
<br />    r = doodle
<br />    s = fanny
<br />    t = sniffer
<br />    u = sprinkles
<br />    v = frack
<br />    w = squirt
<br />    x = humperdinck
<br />    y = hiney
<br />    z = juice
<br /><br />Thus, for example, George W. Bush's new name is: Fluffy Chucklefanny.
<br /><br />Now when you SEND THIS ON...use your new name as the subject.
<br /><br />And remember that children laugh an average of 146 times a day; adults laugh an average of 4 times a day.   
<br /><br />Put more laughter in your day.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3573d703898c8781abf5d5895bbeb19f" url=""><![CDATA[hi<br/><br/>well i am just chilling to him @ the mo and waiting for som1 to pop up &amp; say &quot;hello there&quot;
<br /><br />laters
<br />seanie the sheep
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="508fa4aaa7504f242e518c3f8657498b" url=""><![CDATA[wooooooooooooo hoooooooooo<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />the weekend has landed <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e726da51b261c68c3bb43766afed9a17" url=""><![CDATA[the prawn<br/><br/>One day, in the shark-infested waters of the Caribbean, teo prawns called Justin &amp; Christian are descussing the pressurs of being a preyed-upon prawn.
<br /><br />&quot;i hate being a prawn,&quot; says justin. &quot;i wish i were a shark.&quot;
<br /><br />Suddenly, a mysterious cod appears. &quot;your wish is granted,&quot; he says.
<br />instantly,justin becomes a shark. Horrified, Christian swims away, afraid his former friend might eat him.
<br /><br />As time passes, Christian continues to avoid justin, leaving the shrimp-turned maneater lonely &amp; frusrated. So when he bumps into the cod again, he begs him to Change him back. Lo &amp; behold, Justin is turned back into a prawn.
<br /><br />With tears of joy in is tiny little eyes,he swims back to the reef to seek out christian.
<br /><br />As he approches, he shouts out: &quot;Its's me Justin,your old friend. I've changed...... I've found Cod. I'm a prawn again Christan.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2d8c9754ec16a44cc399b81840bdd026" url=""><![CDATA[one to many<br/><br/>lets play a game!
<br />how many pills did i take to make my boobs this big? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ff4bddd91968637daa4696ad52ab66ee" url=""><![CDATA[goodnight<br/><br/>well good night all sweet dreams see you all in the morning <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/flowers.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f338ef39a1d335189fb3b1164cb588f" url=""><![CDATA[hello ppl<br/><br/>hi well it is the start of my one week hols and i don't know what to do!
<br />so can YOU tell me what to do?
<br />make me a list and i will see if i like it and if i do, i'll do it!
<br /><br />speek soon ppl
<br />love the sheep
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b717cd3567e0201b64d798b3e1b91f6f" url=""><![CDATA[a game<br/><br/>Hi people!!!!
<br /><br />Just found this random game and thought I would post it on here for a bit of fun have a go and see what your music says about your life. Its a bit random but you might like it have a go!!!! I
<br /><br />&quot;Rules&quot;
<br />* Put your music on shuffle.
<br />* Press forward for each question.
<br />* Use the song title as the answer to the question.
<br />* Don't cheat :
<br /><br />How am I feeling today?
<br /><br />Will i go far in life?
<br /><br />Will I get Married?
<br /><br />What is my best friend's theme song?
<br /><br />What is the story of my life?
<br /><br />What is the best thing about me?
<br /><br />What song describes my parents?
<br /><br />My grandparents?
<br /><br />How is my life going?
<br /><br />What song will they play at my funeral?
<br /><br />How does the world see me?
<br /><br />Will I have a happy life?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3bc264eb6d99ec30c67fe67717ae4b43" url=""><![CDATA[weeeeeeeeeeeekend!!!<br/><br/>woop woop woop woop
<br /><br />it is the weekend 
<br /><br />Bring it 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />love the sheep
<br />xxxx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="573d9507940eb5dce10b02dd11b8b11" url=""><![CDATA[1 q<br/><br/>i will let you ask one question and 1 question only i will only answer the truth go on i dare ya!!!!!
<br />love the sheep xxx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6227e50e446108320f6c7a730036623" url=""><![CDATA[hi<br/><br/>hello 
<br />just a note to say that i have some new pics
<br />why not pop in to say hello and leave a message!
<br /><br />o well
<br />see you all later
<br /><br />love from the 
<br />sheep
<br />xXxXxXx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="52e5b614fcf9e6dfd0db2bae6381e4b5" url=""><![CDATA[hi there<br/><br/>So then!
<br /><br />just finished working on my car &amp;
<br />what a hot day it has been, now i am sipping a sheepie sunrise (jealous Gav<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/4210//smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />So who would be up for a chat? 
<br /><br />love from the
<br />Sheep
<br />XxXxXxXxX
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>