<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="10">
		<document id="c10761e0686517caec8618b818afba75" url=""><![CDATA[Luxury goods: Fashion has also invested<br/><br/>Liu Yang favorite in all kinds of electronic products, but also each section I Phone's loyal supporters, in addition to the electronic collection of apple products, she also loves of luxury, &quot;a lot of people that luxury feel is superior to the masses and not touch, in fact, a luxury <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vbmxpbmVzdXByYXNob2Vzc2FsZS5jb20v" target="_blank">[color=#000080]supra shoes[/color]</a> far from the lives of ordinary people, many people buy a luxury but also from 'unintentional', to the last 'willow-lined'.” 
<br />Quotations one: a luxury is a state of mind, but not extravagant. 
<br />Liu Yang love in all kinds of brands of luxury bags, her first contact with the luxury brand Louis?? Vinton (Louis Vinton), she used his first paycheck to buy himself an entry-level bag. &quot;At that time is not particularly understand, just feel good to see, but also not <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vbmxpbmVzdXByYXNob2Vzc2FsZS5jb20vZGMtc2hvZXMtYy02OS5odG1s" target="_blank">dc skate shoes</a>
<br />The other bags, I feel out of date on the need.&quot; Bag from the to buy first a luxury, Liu Yang to have a special on the bag feelings, &quot;I started to pay attention the entire major brand new year of the most popular handbag, also began to enjoy the same hobbies with friends 
<br />Liu Yang had just graduated income is not very stable, this time, she had more to looking at, &quot;because can not afford, in fact, also learning a lot, if a bit of money at that time, some could not help but buy the . &quot; Two years in Hong Kong, Liu Yang's career very well, a lot of fee of the money for the filming of movies, &quot;as if that time demands on the quality of life high, but also have some understanding of luxury brands, because in Hong Kong working, shopping is also convenient.” Alone that <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vbmxpbmVzdXByYXNob2Vzc2FsZS5jb20vc3VwcmEtc2hvZXMtc3VwcmEtdmFpZGVyLWMtNjVfNjcuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">supra vaider</a> living in Hong Kong has not been easy,&quot; especially homesick, sometimes because their work did not &quot;She began going shopping and to see their favorite package buy, &quot;that I may not the same as with the other girls, they are particularly pleased to buy after the expiry, I do not have this feeling, but I bought something very like it.&quot; 
<br />Liu Yang now that luxury is a state of mind, &quot;it represents a refined and tasteful living conditions, although the association with the great wealth, but not extravagant.&quot; 
<br />Quotations II: selection of luxury goods, but also a way of managing money. 
<br />Liu Yang circle of contacts in the interpretation of some use to buy luxury goods like investment in the form of friends, &quot;the stock is now unstable and will haunt the property market in America, many friends around me have their money invested usury goods. &quot;&quot; One of my friends here likes wine. He felt that a good bottle of wine is unique, and the longer duration, the greater the appreciation of space, because as the age increases, the amount of red wine will survive in the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin</a> down. &quot;Liu Yang itself like watch, her collection of Cartier (Cartier), Dior (Dior), I have a brother like home to collect some designers, in fact, the highest of these is the appreciation of space, as are limited edition, the number itself is less, but also very memorable.&quot; 
<br />Most to heart is the art of luxury Liu Yang, &quot;This might be the direction of my future collections. Because does not yet have the strength.&quot; &quot;I'm particularly fond of realistic art paintings, and often to see some shows.&quot; Look at the Liu Yang, the contemporary art on the decline, the realistic art of the advantages to come out, &quot;one of my <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> often talk art gallery, art or very realistic appreciation of space, it is time-consuming, but also a great need for basic painting and realism the art of great artists in China only a few people, creative and very long period.” 
<br />Liu Yang's first luxury bag is Louis?? Vinton (Louis Vinton) an entry-level Speedy 30, &quot;I saw in Kong, LV store, and was particularly fond of to buy it, and until now there when I was back.” 
<br />Economic conditions in their case is not very abundant, particularly for luxury goods in this area new to the &quot;rookie&quot;, Liu Yang proposed to buy some classic big brands such as Louis Speedy 30 and the chain of Chanel's 2.55 package, &quot; These are enduring the 'war package'. &quot;After working for some time, can spend more money on their favorite <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> goods, you can buy some of the more popular seasonal bag,&quot; such as this year very bright colors, especially popular in the bag, Hermes (Hermes) this year, a silver crocodile skin bag, a limited edition in the future will certainly appreciate. &quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="709466ae07b2d5ce1b744c38eb27d00f" url=""><![CDATA[The Legend of shoes<br/><br/>Ancient legend, people have no shoes to wear, a large of foot all day long exposure to the sun. Only so-called slowly shoes, sandals, shoes, shoes, and now a variety / strange shoes. 
<br />I like to wear shoes a child, moving a bench in the sun, watching my grandmother is satisfied with the shoes; hemp rope child from the sole through, thick texture, sewing secrets, hidden inside is unable to express friendship. So every year my would certainly have made a few pairs of shoes, I was a kid will only like shoes, flower [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] face a variety of small little red shoes I remember the most, just do a good job of foot wear cloth shoes will be some pain, but more through the comfortable, in the end you will enjoy the shoes to your feet every day to bring the fun, simple, free, free, practical and safe. 
<br />Another big point, I had a pair of yellow shoes, that is, shoes, and shoes that I like, it's the end of a very solid, there are some small edge cartoons, but also comfortable to wear, the [url=dc-shoes-c-69.html]dc shoes online[/url] I feel good, wear very comfortable, I am happy to wear it for years, until the for my thumb up. 
<br />Mom bought me back a pair of red shoes, bright red, pointed cross in front of some tape, like it is quite avant-garde, with the words of that time, more foreign flavor, I like it because it is red, and cloth shoes The difference is that the people raised a grade. When the children to wear shoes which not many people, most feet are wrapped in cloth, do not know themselves, and asked fashionable, but I [url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]supra vaider[/url] very concerned about dress. So when I went a pair of red shoes only made me feels not normal. 
<br />Grow up, I have had many pairs of shoes, but the most memorable day or those who wear cloth shoes, deeply aware that give your feet the comfort and release, without the slightest stickle bound a smooth line. We grew up a child's shoes when my mother This away, and now <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">christian louboutin</a> of it maybe these things are worth, and after several generations of wear mill, its value is also reflected in the maxed out. 
<br />My shoes are now a lot of open space in the living room, according to the different clothes with different shoes, there are boots, high heels, with the end, there are shoes, as well as Mickey Mouse soft slippers, with different prices ranging from thin think about it, the more low price of shoes, the quality is not very good, long life, and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> very solid, very comfortable, affordable, recently bought a pair of high heels Ad Daphne, Although various aspects of texture are good, but I do not know why the high price of shoes is not fate, always the last dress is not the issue here where the problems. 
<br />    I got married last weekend, my colleagues went so far as to wear high-heeled foot Ad Daphne mill played a bubble, the former is the final feet to the toss could have actually the grinding of your shoes. 
<br /><br />I am aware: people must have a pair of shoes, whether it is cheap or expensive, a pair of good shoes, shoes for your feet can take you anywhere, but I have your shoes <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> I could not walk on the belt long way, only to meet the wedding such a formal occasion, other times I have double your comfortable shoes and relax, just like of mind, his feet, shoes do not fit together, only you know best. 
<br />African natives wear shoes 
<br />in a shoe factory in the United States. In order to expand the market, he sent a marketing manager for factory owners to survey the market on an island in Africa. Marketing Manager arrived that were found that local people have the habit of not wearing <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank">jimmy choo shoes sale</a> , back to the hotel; he immediately sent telegrams to tell the boss said: &quot;The here never wear shoes, no market here.&quot; 
<br />When the owner received the telegram, Marketing manager, ordered another to field surveys. When the name of the market manager to see the local people barefoot, wearing any shoes when extremely excited mind, a return to the hotel, immediately telegraphed the boss: &quot;This island residents without shoes to wear, the market potential is huge. Quick to send one pairs of shoes come here. “
<br />Inspiration 
<br />The same situation, there are different points of view and conclusions. In fact, when we often aspects to think about bad or if we will miss many of the &quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL21hbm9sby1ibGFobmlrLWMtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">manolo blahnik shoes sale</a> of success.&quot; Instead, we have been too good, positive aspects to think about it, we will tap the many surprising opportunities may be hidden even if the crisis line opportunities. 
<br />Heming shoe store ad 
<br />Put before the home Heming shoe store in Nanjing, signs, although old, no one cares. Many companies and the occasional boss found Hang was advertised brand-name stores to sell goods. He also wanted to advertise it. 
<br />But what the ads have effective? Back and forth wondering the store at this time, the clerk offered advice over Mr. said: &quot;Business competition and war as long as you are willing to spend in the city's largest newspaper ads set for three days. The first day of registration only big question mark, write the following line of fine print <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tc2FuZGFscy1jLTYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin shoes</a> more information, see Ming Boa Land Japan. The next day as usual, until the third day unlock secrets, advertising, write 'three from everyone, from everyone Heming shoes, leather shoes'. “
<br />Owner of one feels that this total is feasible to act in accordance with accounting, advertising, and a sign out to really attract the readers, Heming shoe store suddenly a household name, business red. Boss is very aware of feeling: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> not only to deepen the reader's impression of the ads, but also the reader to grasp the psychological knowledge. 
<br />This is especially commercial advertising, also shows the deep pockets of the famous old style. Since then, Heming shoe footwear industry will stand out in the Beijing and Shanghai. 
<br />  Inspiration 
<br />this story is Heming shoe ads. Although many ad people contacts, but have not thought about what to do to attract more people? Mr. Accountant described originality. His meticulous planning, advertising, although it brief, but the courage to create [url=]tory burch reva[/url] new, break through the traditional concept, which has achieved great success. We live in an era of rapid advancement in technology, rapid development, new thing after another, we must dare to think, say, daring to do, dare to innovate, to keep up with the times, also needs to have forward-thinking. These are the essential quality of successful
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbd98a33bc30aaf072fbe2e8307f6265" url=""><![CDATA[The story of a man to take care of backpack<br/><br/>I have not flown, but often planes only. &quot;In the cloud&quot; in the George Clooney is an aircraft control, in his own middle age, to complete the flight ten million miles of the target. I admire him [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] I often think is what it feels like to fly it, through the windows of aircraft, what strange sight to see it? Are not large clouds blowing in my body, and I close my eyes a little, you can think of me as the Monkey King? 
<br />George Clooney for the plane, it is already commonplace, and his imagination, boring flights because of shrinking, the plane has become a symbol of his alienation and the world, he in heaven, most of us on the ground, we busy with their own, the old [url=dc-shoes-c-69.html]dc shoes[/url]
<br />This life, happiness sadness, all does not matter. His empty backpack theory is probably out of the plane wondering. This theory is very strange, encouraging you to drop everything, traveling light. This is a typical individualism. He is a but any time an aircraft has landed, and when he landed to the earth, will find his backpack is not [url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]supra vaider[/url] , there is also a lot of things need to take care of him one by one. &quot;In the cloud&quot; is a person care about the story of backpack. 
<br />George Clooney's work is very strange, he was laid off experts. When a company wants to lay off some employees will find him, ask him or her employees to do work, to prevent the dismissal of employees to make these extreme things. I think there should be only the supremacy of the state of human rights can there be such a job. China has no such job security? Hopeless in our society, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">christian louboutin</a> wants to dismiss a person, just a word thing, even if you hanged himself on the spot, the boss who will not release a little bit of compassion. In the United States to have such a job happens, but George Clooney is not a person in combat, his company is mainly engaged in the. I think, to American eyes, work and life should be as important, lost his job, and is a very terrible thing. They dismissed employee's share of respect, so I was much moved. 
<br />And played opposite George Clooney is an old two women of a small, very beautiful. The two women have changed his life, but in different ways. Our lives are not all men by some women to change it? Little woman brought advanced ideas, to end the layoffs flying career experts, which makes George Clooney has a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> of the crash. The old woman is a moment of tenderness to George fell in love fog. The air bag called before the line of people, in fact, nothing fit. He eventually put the pick of the pick it up, and then throws all that away. 
<br />The disadvantage of this film is too concerned about George Clooney, on the little woman and the old woman to take care of poor planning. Little Women and the end of the work of George Clooney, her role will suddenly interrupted again when the account is hurried past her into her bag carrying something, they throw something, I do not see. Old woman, too, can even say that the whole film she is the most complex characters, families with husband and children, and George are playing night stand. Perhaps foreshadowing the front is not enough, when I see <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> home before exposure to George Clooney, I was a bit surprised. Perhaps the intelligence of the audience than I already guessed. Thus, the scenario described in terms of women is a weakness. 
<br />Film begins with some aerial shots, very beautiful; it is God's point of view overlooking the world. By the end part of the movie, the old captain appeared, he sat down and had just completed ten million miles flying George Clooney chats, and the sun he small window from his house shining, so he formed the whole body halo, and jimmy choom shoes <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.louboutinpumpssale.com%2Fjimmy-choo-c-12.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.louboutinpumpssale.com/jimmy-choo-c-12.html</a></a>
<br /><br />Together with his old face, as well as flamboyant beard, is simply coming of the Lord. So, this show can be understood as George Clooney met God, he, he should be on the elevation. 
<br />I like George Clooney when the period began to travel dazzling clips, and music combine perfectly. Editor called Dana E · Gray Berman, director Reitman’s up to the three films, all by his surgeon clip. Believe that every traveler, whether <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> and old, would like to return to his backpack when the bristle, there is in addition to their gifts, of course, be given to parents, relatives and friends. 
<br />As for me, or a collection of favorite local notes and coins (basically do not buy souvenirs in the country.) Money is a national card, fine money from the foundry industry, metal materials, printing, integrated manufacturing process, and so, the measure of country's overall strength. Each one (Zhang) coin has its unique [url=]tory burch reva[/url] significance. Local coin collection will enable us to better understand the local history and culture, experience the local culture.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ce8241eb89856a8bcb7f4f97f5c2bc6d" url=""><![CDATA[A boy with his backpack story<br/><br/>Adam recalls the first time, every time he walked by carrying a bag from the crowd, always found it strange that many people would fancy him for a moment. &amp;quot;I do not understand the beginning, thought it was what he wears fancy dress, and later at the same time telling myself to know.&amp;quot; Adam said, several colleagues cautioned, social security is very poor, both men and women, almost all [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] grabbed experience, if not robbed of it is really lucky. The Adam backpack so bold action, indeed, enviable one, but ah can not help but worry a bit. 
<br />&amp;quot;At first I really disagree, because in my appearance, I am afraid that most people can not get involved, now say really ashamed of it!&amp;quot; Said here, Adam laughed, sure enough, a few days to themselves in the Ishii Boulevard near robbed, documents, wallet, cell phone, etc. No one survived, but also since then started to put my in front of the chest or, no longer afraid &amp;quot;Even people like me were being robbed, showing that the security situation had deteriorated in Dungun, right!&amp;quot; Zhang [url=dc-shoes-c-69.html]dc shoes[/url]
<br />Said, &amp;quot;but starting in April 2006, Dungun Egan remediation and a few months, the change is very large.” 
<br />Zhang Costa recalls that time, the way the police very much, newspapers, on television almost every day on law and order matter, law and order quickly can feel a lot better, and in September 2006 after the motorcycle field after leaving Dungun, security is greatly changed. 
<br />Zhang Costa said with a smile, &amp;quot;for a long time, my backpack was back behind the position, not afraid, not only to be grabbed he did not even hear almost no side to have a friend who was robbed of the news.” Bag how to back, on the front or behind, this is entirely a personal preference, but this simple and habits are a [url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]supra vaider[/url] record of experience in Dungun: Dungun Municipal Government Sword law and order, in order to protect the public peace, and build &amp;quot;peace in Dungun,&amp;quot; a series of important initiatives. 
<br />Today, the streets of Dungun, shopping department stores, are people happy shopping, shopping, prosperity, there will not be before the tension face, the end of 2006, the authority of the media poll: In the 18,114 copies of the questionnaire, 86.19 % of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">christian louboutin</a> of the year expressed satisfaction with the social order. 
<br />I was born 80 years after the reform and opening up, though living in the forefront of reform opening up - Guangdong, but the home is located in the mountains of northern Guangdong, so the experience of change is a relatively deep experience. 
<br /><br />Play remembers every time out to see the fathers with a military green to be leaving for the package. Pack small, but there is just put some raw rice, a small bottle of pickles, addition is put one or two change of clothes. The bag away, it is very simple, but has taken away the best things at home. I remember meeting in Nanning, Guangxi to join the army of Uncle home to visit relatives, take the time, Grandma's off the New Year from the dark specially when he left a piece of bacon into <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> backpack. At that moment, Uncle imposing seven feet man, dressed in starched uniforms into tears at the grandmother cried in front of people: he will understand that a total of nine brothers and sisters, even though big brother big sister are married, but the big brother, brother's children gave the families make up the vacancies. Therefore, eating is a familiar problem in the family. Today, Grandma is secretly hidden in a piece of meat to him, called him how not to be moved? 
<br /><br />Eventually, Uncle, or take a piece of bacon. Father and uncle to send him, including his father had been thrown over your shoulder. Later, Uncle demobilized, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> Tang house, a house with a lot of things: eat, use..... There is several kind of backpack. Uncle to his father was one. 
<br /><br />Ever since the backpack after his father, who do not have time to go out the hard plastic skin wrapped things? As mother and grandmother, like to keep the best things at, when his father gave my father brought out. Every time I see myself and sister, father, this backpack, and my heart will be some private secretly pleased: because my father came back each time, there will be surprises, not the big red apple is the toys. However, there is some difficult times at home, young parents I saw a stormy night in the occasion, the father, brought back tobacco and alcohol from the outside to the plug when the backpack, and then hurried <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank">jimmy choo shoes sale</a> the door. Growing up, I realized it was a gift that is through the back door. Forced livelihoods, honest gifts parents can only go at night, and now think of all bitterness. Ever since then, my family would not have that backpack, and his mother hung it in the utility room. 
<br /><br />Later, my father came back out again, brought a large bag. However, their image of it running out, because then he started boarding school, and, not too concerned about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL21hbm9sby1ibGFobmlrLWMtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">manolo blahnik shoes sale</a> time his father would be filled with anything back there, we only care about his safe return. His mother washed clean each time the bag, and even a gift to each is also filled with grandma. It is for the mother, is a symbol of new life. Later, my 
<br />Worked, and she bought a stylish backpack, and she used to put a few back home. However, the use is not large, because the parents feel no need in this mountain town for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> a fancy thing, still go out with his father brought back the package. 
<br /><br />I graduated last year, the first paychecks they bought a bag, small, only enough to put down the phone with the keys, but that the price of a lifetime for the parents of is the price of meat a few months. So parents learn not stop shaking his head <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tc2FuZGFscy1jLTYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin shoes</a> a sigh: that I spend money. See me every time it was carrying out all, is very convenient, but also no the say. Today, my father brought back the bag with the tri backpack that went into the corner of history. While he looked at the bag, takes much: the backpack hidden in some of life's stories, but also hide some things that change our lives.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cc6c131142084561648a97031f8751f0" url=""><![CDATA[Backpack to go the UK<br/><br/>Think of how to go to England? Also go to Ireland? 
<br />Roaming is the first in several European Scheme ideas. Rabbit studies students in UK come to an end, so I want to take advantage of the rabbit with the students about her trip [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] returning, and I have a language of the stick. 
<br />Original plan was to buy an Aural Pass, the first stroll in London a week, then 3 weeks traveling the Scheme countries. Just as I was to design a number of lines on paper and took the train schedules of European countries is similar, the news that the serious &quot;bad news&quot;, the UK student visa rabbits less than 3 months, so may not apply for visa. After crying in the corner, only to modify travel plans change Scheme as UK. Always felt that visiting the UK a month too deep of it, think of the supra avider
<br />[url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html[/url]
<br />Years of Friends XM in Ireland for many years, and also try to do a visa to, which do Talia are close neighbors. 
<br />In fact, the Irish and did not open China's personal travel, a visa is a challenge. First, the Irish Consulate's website to search, find its type there is no tourist visa, then find the e-mail address, first write a letter sincerely, praise how beautiful this country, how do I look forward to traveling the country and so are some obvious Commitment to the visa office did not return e-mail, actually called the phone, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">christian louboutin</a> ask some questions, I heard that my passport was not a white of the children, there children say that you can try to do, it can give me a very the earth encouraged, it seems that one foot has set foot on Irish land. 
<br />Began to prepare travel plans, provide hotel booking air tickets, buy insurance, so these are the necessary visa documents, some busy, two countries, two visa, with a winning time of 2 , has not signed with the surface, very proud, fully thought behind <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> will be challenges, and immigration will be fine? This is something, the content and then Syria. 
<br />  Get to work 
<br />Raiders love to go out, take the family love to travel, read some of this out in front of other people's &quot;Raiders&quot;, are some real meaning, so in the last part, I am ready to sum up some &quot;Raiders&quot;, I hope to go after fewer people can go some detours. Preparation before departure or necessary are: Air ticket booking, ordering the rail passes, in order to save money is very tips of you; Chooses to visit sites to determine the optimal route, but also to determine the retention time for each location, a good combination of these factors is also a certain degree of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> Book accommodation, travel plans at the head, if you plan to have to change, you have to stay the order to immediately adjust, it is very important, they might have a direct economic loss; 
<br />Featured belongings can be brought to less with less, the back of the backpack with the and time, will become a big piece of iron; above all will be in the Raiders in the Detailed. 
<br />Later realized, in fact, far less how to do homework because there are accidents every day, and even from time to time there will be challenges. 
<br />Tenderness of the man is a steel frame, after the brilliant life of 2,500 years and remains passionate. Walking through this city known as the archives of Western culture, from Roman ruins to Renaissance treasures, from to modern fashion and cultural <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank">jimmy choo shoes sale</a> , each step is a charming landscape, every step of the exciting story. 
<br />We spent 5 days in Rome, walk for 5 days. Seven every morning, starting at eight, at seven, eight end, Baotou ten hours, it is only looked a little fur omissions. Commuting Rome, do not just look at his appearance, but also to see his character temper. The articles were introduced such as Rome, the stars, the story here is not superfluous. We would like to say that Rome &quot;police culture&quot; a little unique experience. Our Embassy in Italy, applied for a Scheme visa to enter Scheme in Athens, Greece. The provisions of this situation must be entered within 8 <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL21hbm9sby1ibGFobmlrLWMtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">manolo blahnik shoes sale</a> after the Italian border, to the local police station to report, or otherwise unlawful. Together with the visa issued to our &quot;Immigration Information&quot;, in Italian, English, Chinese, three languages, express this policy. 
<br />The third day we went to Rome, that is, the seventh day of entering the Italian territory, to find the police. Remember passing a sign of police units from the central railway station not far from our hotel near the Republic Square, not far. I wondered, to the police report on the line. Early in the morning, went to the police station, a middle-aged men and the police received us. Afraid to express clear, we directly to the “Information&quot; handed to him. A middle-aged policeman did not understand English or Italian <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tc2FuZGFscy1jLTYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin shoes</a> for a long time, meaning they will not be accepted in this business. 
<br />It seems there is only equivalent to a police station, level is not enough. Police asked the middle-aged men, we should go immigration report? I do not know is that we did not understand or he did not understand that for a long time, he confusedly, we sleepwalk. Had no choice but to take a map out of the police a place on the map, [url=]tory burch reva[/url] tell to get there. This time to understand and he indicated the place in the Roman suburbs, down 2 times to get to the bus. 
<br />Out from the police station, thinking Report to the agency receiving the entry of foreigners, common sense should be located where frequent entry and exit of foreigners, should be the central railway station is one such place. How it may be much in the suburbs? Toss a half-day, has more than 10 AM. How to do? Today, the original <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtaGFuZGJhZ3MtYy0yNS5odG1s" target="_blank">tory burch handbags</a> to visit the Roman 8 days left in the last 1 ½ days duration, from the heart a little anxious.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a1be453e4440071f050ddab3761ab4a5" url=""><![CDATA[The development of bag<br/><br/>from classic to modern, and both become the hearts of the ladies love. Interestingly, packages and clothing decorated with the rise of the evolution of closely linked. Since the eighteenth century, a wave-type dress with a belt she was replaced Slam’s [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] ; ladies will have to find the bag can hold personal items. The first fish mesh momentum into the sky, this beam on the long string pouch easily in your hand, become a veritable &amp;amp;quot;package decoration.&amp;amp;quot; For centuries, the trend of fashion accessories like fashion in general, with each passing day, keeps changing. The gradual increase of its status as the ladies dress in an integral part of, such based on the trend of different cultures, different [url=dc-shoes-c-69.html]dc shoes[/url]
<br />Of the times, on different, women's package decoration has evolved in the form of endless changes. 
<br /> The early nineteenth century, Europe to open its xxx, large travel bags out of Europe has become a necessity. Large bags conform to the students. Twentieth century, the rise of cigarettes, the small packets into the ladies attending the communication places an ornament, a small box-style package is heavily decorated therefore put into the market. In 1929, Hollywood stars heat that kept the foundation, lipstick of popular bags, all kinds of cosmetic bags, such as shells, football, locks, vases and decorative bird cage shaped packages, one by one [url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]supra vaider[/url] emerge. However, during the Second World War, shortage of materials, including decorative immediately become a luxury, ladies bags have adopted the rough canvas material, has forced designers to design at a series of shopping bags and bike bags. After the war, in the package decoration industry there are several brands: one is Coco Chanel (cocoa. Summer Nile) gold chain strap bag hanging decoration design became the symbol of taste. LV (Louis. Vinton) of the bucket type of package decoration Noël, to carry champagne, to Hermes, Highboy, after adoption by the Princess Grace Kelly, 
<br /><br />Gucci also joined the battle around the natural introduction of the bamboo handle handbag and drop type of package decoration. 
<br />Bags and women 
<br />the twentieth century, women are to brand-name command, package decoration has become a symbol of identity and powerful. After the middle of people's lives is the rise of laptops, so wide messenger bag, camera bag has become the darling of young people. Late, including the world more colorful decorated more than mining, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin</a> prevalence of minimalist, hot Chinese embroidery, more animal fur applications, such as snakeskin, leopard, crocodile skin, etc., when South Korea played St. hi Comb bloc developed at this time, access to the enthusiastic support of fashionable circles. Early 20th century, as the fashion representative of package decoration, as the prevalence of common items across Europe by the time the &amp;amp;quot;Oriental civilization,&amp;amp;quot; the impact of culture, including the decoration has become strange. But in that time, fashion is only the rich &amp;amp;quot;patent.&amp;amp;quot; Low income and heavy work to make the working class women and fashion for him, also decorated <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> the package missed. 
<br /> Until the 20's, the mass media increasingly developed, fashion is no longer the privilege of high society, and women in all walks of life have joined the ranks of fashion to catch up. The package is also beginning to show decorative features. Beaded bags swaying with the beat of the music sound occurs, and then plays the jazz song after another beautiful &amp;amp;quot;Concerto.&amp;amp;quot; 30 years, Hollywood movies spatial development, their <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> fashion has a huge impact. Bag decorated with sleek looks and a good cabinet, simple materials, simple and elegant. 
<br /> 40 years full of smoke, including decoration design the most emphasis on practicality, and pragmatism, the trend is more affected by the military design, collapse on the shoulder of the package all the rage, because can be used to install gas, ration card and other bills, and most practical outfit. Although the smoke swirling in the war years brought great suffering to the people, but it prompted package decoration and simplification to the civilian population, step forward greatly. End of the war, the economy's gradual recovery of 50, due to the war year’s imprisonment, after the war the people of sexual desire and competition, women dress jimmy choom shoes online<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.louboutinpumpssale.com%2Fjimmy-choo-c-12.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.louboutinpumpssale.com/jimmy-choo-c-12.html</a></a>
<br />The package is decorated with food, and without exception to sexy and charming. During this period, Rock and Pop music is not only a form of revolution, it formed a kind of acceptable for the majority of young people across the region and the culture of the new language. Youthful revolutionary style miniskirts and pants are with rock music was born. Mini is also calling for the emergence of new package decoration, so all small, with long <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL21hbm9sby1ibGFobmlrLWMtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">manolo blahnik shoes sale</a> strap, concise style shoulder bag to hang up the young man, so that passers-by it really envy. 
<br /> Rapid economic development in 70, 80, in a sense, package decoration has become a cultural symbol of status and identity. New materials and designs continue to be introduced to break the people &amp;amp;quot;invest to buy a good package&amp;amp;quot; of traditional values. With the late 70s a new concept of romantic and classical revival in fashion, some narrow-strap shoulder bag, fishing packages and other packages wig the a fresh <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tc2FuZGFscy1jLTYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">christian louboutin shoes</a> style decoration in one shoulder, also reflected in the economic tide in the Bay action, people asked the city to avoid congestion and clamor trouble will. 
<br /> In the 90's the fashion to be monopolized by young avant-garde seems to be synonymous with fashionable, high-top of the table after the order is designed to be a gimmick, without exception, those who are good at playing with avant-garde master handwriting. The &amp;amp;quot;Fashion today is the tomorrow of the past when&amp;amp;quot; the tide changes, people had to happen &amp;amp;quot;This world is changing fast,&amp;amp;quot; the deep feeling. Package decoration, without exception, by which shares are also <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> changing the trend of the impact of the arrival of 2000, retro wave will continue to prevail, beads, bags may be fever. As new century, women around you if you have thought about the package decorated to a few hundred years later can become a witness of history. In the twentieth century, mankind has created so many miracles, they are by their wisdom and positive initiative and creativity of mankind has left many valuable assets. Fly wheel still keep the clock running forward, we should firmly believe that hope for tomorrow, on our feet. 
<br />Some women in order to save time, use the same on different occasions are only the package, sometimes because it does not match with <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtc2hvZXMtYy0xOS5odG1s" target="_blank">tory burch shoes</a>
<br />Dress, it looks inconsistent. Are best several packages, one for work, leisure, and dinner and other occasions? To work with the package should be larger, so that essential supplies can be stored more, but style must be generous, consistent with the [url=]tory burch reva[/url] to go to work, such as briefcase-style package is the most suitable. But if that briefcase too tough, you can try both women carrying briefcases and reflect the style of the bag. This benefit is a more reasonable places your objects as much as possible, carrying plastic bags or paper bags than you much more to professional. Use back-type bag, women be back in the right shoulder, as when Ms. Habit of walking with the men's counterparts on the right. The use of a briefcase or handbag, because hands and looked confused. 
<br />Handbag 
<br />Female candidates to work or face, as when the examiner must not be placed in the bag on the table or hold in his chest, the most appropriate [url=]tory burch flats[/url]
<br />For general office workers, it is best not to use a more expensive purse than the boss, the young people just entering society with particular attention to this point. Dressed in civilian clothes, leisure and shopping time by the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtc2FuZGFscy1jLTI2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">tory burch sandals</a> choose style and lively, brightly colored bag or backpack, which is easy to match the mood and dress. Dinner and other formal occasions, should be used in relatively sophisticated bag, then it will match with the dress is courtesy of the owner, said. Best to use when attending the banquet-style hand-rolled or back-type bag, do not hand bags, so as not to take meals in the exchange of business cards or point, causing trouble. 
<br /> Gold and silver in the bag for use at the dinner, because the light will show its Men dressed in suits and ties his girlfriend or wife should not get a good impression while racing to take the bag for her, this is a indecent behavior. Because accessories, handbags, how well <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtaGFuZGJhZ3MtYy0yNS5odG1s" target="_blank">tory burch handbags</a>     back in men's to show the thoughtfulness and grace men can help women be raised by heavy items or shopping bags.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eab13c7a9a9b71e6608e7f528ef6ade" url=""><![CDATA[Titanium crystal bracelet story<br/><br/>50-70 years in the 16th century, the Spanish expedition along the track of Columbus, the Americas, from the hands of the Indians plundered countless treasures, and then loaded the cabin home. Among all the gold and silver jewelry, crystal [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] with a titanium the most expensive the most eye-catching, this bracelet bearing the Spanish life and Bracelet is given to Spain's fetish goddess Venus, the caretaker of the embezzlement, Po bracelet spread to the people. Goddess predicted that the Spanish treasure bracelet involves the survival of the King of Spain for this angry, people across the country to find treasure bracelet launched. By chance, they had learned from a foreign businessman whereabouts of a golden bracelet. King immediately ordered the minister to send his men [url=dc-shoes-c-69.html]dc shoes[/url]
<br />Retrieve the treasure bracelet, the Secretary of State when it starts to bring his daughter. As the Minister of greed, treasure bracelet in the back while they move the other Waning, pilfering looting property. Greedy acts of the Secretary of the Indians caused great anger. As a result, the Indians together to form a fleet in Los Halo ambush near Tokushima. When the minister's fleet to dale Halo Tokushima, when the Indians did give surrounded, defeated the Spanish fleet in one fell swoop. As Minister of the main boat ride too much jewelry installed, after a battle, can no longer sustain, the ship will be sunk. Minister and his daughter, and men's entourage also sank. 
<br />[url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]Supra vaider[/url] is gone; the remaining Spanish fleet fled back to Spain, the Indians are also driving the boat back. Smoke seems to mean that the post-war Spain, disaster is coming. 
<br />The second day in the sea, floating on the sea except a few broken wooden A way to this sea sailing ship, the distant glittering objects attract the ship's navigator, that the object is not only a dazzling light and in constant movement. Voyager find it very strange experience of decades of sailing, has never come across such a thing. To understand this mystery, to accelerate the speed of vessels, catch up with the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin</a> objects. That minister's daughter, and she was holding a beautiful dolphin, which is Philip Snow poetry, and shiny objects is set in the mouth of the titanium crystal dolphin treasure bracelet. 
<br />Navigator with a minister's daughter and the golden treasure of titanium crystal bracelet back to the Spanish king to reward the behavior of this name navigator, so he replaced the position of minister, and minister's daughter will be betrothed to the Spain saved, and Venus Po She’s under God to prosper. 
<br />These days, my <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> have brought to the silver bracelet, silver bracelet with a legend this year, well, small bees are the new money to buy more than four hundred Yuan, twenty years ago to buy a warm, red dragonfly is bought thirty years ago to see them worn on the wrist, I feel really very beautiful, I had a silver bracelet interest, but also buy a ready to wear in the hand around the neck, then start shopping from noon, European and Asian operators are on a buy, regardless <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> g, one needs ranging from 500-1000 Yuan. I think quite expensive, YOU, and good friends to Asian shopping malls, a silver bracelet that sold by the gram, eight dollars per gram, the price is very cheap. Gold and silver went to the Yu-tai jewelers, it's fine silver is eight dollars a gram, which posted a poster shop, generally means that this year is the Year of the Tiger Yin, and silver jewelry, good luck. I know that wearing a silver bracelet this year rumors coming out from the business Yeah. 
<br />Remember one is a pig, the rumors roll Dai Yen Chu, a mother to daughter have to buy, my <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank">jimmy choo shoes sale</a> bought her daughter, a time for every woman's finger roll are shipped with a gold bead, so as to fortune wishful. 
<br />Silver bracelet origin although this is considered as a decorative arm, is one of the earliest initiation of a vague sense of beauty, but there are many scientists believe that there is not entirely original bracelet is from the beauty and with the totem worship, witchcraft rituals related. There are also historians believe that, as men in economic life, an absolute dominance, making rings, bracelets and other accessories with a metaphorical leash on women, not to escape the barbarians of their customs. This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL21hbm9sby1ibGFobmlrLWMtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">manolo blahnik shoes sale</a> for a long period of time there has always been. 
<br />And earrings, necklaces, rings as bracelets as a jewelry, had been supporting as a clothing decoration to dress up as a work of art as a personal style, a dress-loving means being accepted by more and more people and use. Bracelet to wear, the aesthetic function is often the first. 
<br />    According to legend, the Republic of China, Shanghai, a famous jewelry store jade green arrayed a full round of the bracelet, although the kinds of good quality jade, head feet, Cuisse Yang Xiao, and the price is not too high, because there are <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tc2FuZGFscy1jLTYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">christian louboutin shoes</a> several points, &amp;quot;spots&amp;quot; (folk also called &amp;quot;fly feces&amp;quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />, but no one is interested, keeps a long time. 
<br />   The reason, people usually buy jade jewelry, jade there to see if the natural &amp;quot;black spot&amp;quot; impurities, not like, particularly taboo that people will pay attention to with a &amp;quot;black spot - feces spots, visible mold,&amp;quot; the jade jewelry, considered unlucky. 
<br />   Finally one day, have an uninvited guest to this &amp;quot;no one is interested,&amp;quot; the bracelet <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> to go. This bracelet is not to purchase their own needs, but to give his wife Miss Song Mailing bracelet. However, when he bought down the bracelet, we began to regret it, because one of his friends speak up carving master, this bracelet is not directly sent to shot, unless to have to find ways to remove the bracelet on the black classes. 
<br />The man listened reluctantly said: &amp;quot;Is there any way? Say there are ways, should be the master of your jade son.&amp;quot; That are not, the listener determined to. Remarks before, jade master returned, he was a mind for a long time, are wondering how to get rid of dark spots bracelet of friends only problem, and made the night he could not sleep, food is not sweet taste, World Hard work pays off. Jade master [url=]tory burch reva[/url] one day, with a rope tied item, a move suddenly PAA, inspiration came. On impulse, he left the hands of the living, and immediately went to a friend's house, friends come to watch bracelet. 
<br />   Friends at that time to talk about and do not care. Master jade bracelet suddenly looks so anxious to do a moment he was in the fog cloud. After observing the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtc2FuZGFscy1jLTI2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">tory burch sandals</a> jade bracelet smiled and said to him &amp;quot;into it! 
<br />    Friends puzzled as to ask how you? Jade master said to me before leaving! Three months later to find I prefer the bracelet, including your perfect, can be sent to Miss Song Mailing friend’s bracelet. When he took over from the master jade bracelet a look that he had purchased the only round of the bracelets have become a &amp;quot;braided&amp;quot; bracelet. Consider the original round of the Masters jade bracelet designed as a &amp;quot;rough Jimson&amp;quot; bracelet, jade happened on the dark spots can be Tory Burch flats
<br />[url=][/url]
<br />Friends finally got his wish, to buy their own bracelet given to Miss Song Mailing Jin. 
<br />     So history has left a talent, the story of the legendary jade!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a70bc38f6576e67878dd9700b146dc88" url=""><![CDATA[Processing of energy balance bracelet<br/><br/>Silicone bracelet (silicone wristbands, silicone wrist band) was first popular in the United States, the world's first silicone bracelet is yellow &quot;LIVESTRONG&quot;, all the people wearing the bracelet is resistant to diseases common goal of cancer, so life is more robust! Rubber hand with the trend of this stock is from the U.S. citizen cyclists Armstrong led the famous sports goods company Nike has produced the assistance of five [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] printed 'live STRONG' word yellow rubber strap to one dollar for each dollar the price sale is intended to Lance Armstrong Fund (LAF) to raise funds. 
<br /><br />Later a number of charitable organizations to follow the special LAF English words or words printed on the plastic bracelet, in addition to raising funds can be used in addition to the promotion of the organization's beliefs. This trend started by the [url=dc-shoes-c-69.html]dc shoes[/url]
<br />So far, plastic hand with Europe and America is still the most popular accessories. This new trend and the recent visit Georgia, and U.S. chain McDonald's fast food restaurant introduced in some Asian countries, with a redemption scheme rubber hand, greatly among young people, this trend towards greater heights. Thereafter, the silicone bracelet with green, non-toxic, tasteless and good elasticity, easy to wear advantage, and gradually developed into a popular jewelry, loved by young people, now the epidemic has spread to the world. Silicone bracelet more activities [url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]supra vaider[/url] various organizations, brand promotion, sports, and associated with, a good design can convey a very profound meaning. 
<br />Silicone bracelet (English silicone Environmental protection silicone material of high quality refined, is a green jewelry. Silicone bracelets jade bracelets with the traditional process would be similar; more jade bracelets wonderful beauty can not be compared. Engraving, printing, thousands of designs, thousands of colors, the trend 
<br /><br />Silica gel silica gel by dehydration mSiO2 · nH2O appropriate particle size different from the porous material. Has an open porous structure, specific surface area (surface area per unit mass) is very large, can absorb a lot of material, is a good desiccant, adsorbent and catalyst carrier. Silica gel adsorption is mainly physical adsorption, can be regenerated and used repeatedly. In the alkali <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin</a> silicates (egg sodium silicate) solution, adding acid to make it acidic, and then adding a certain amount of electrolyte stirring, the silica gel formation; or doctrinal adding acid or sodium silicate solution ammonium salt can also produce silica gel. Silica gel to put it aside for a few hours so that the aging, and then wash with hot water soluble salts, in the 60 ~ 70 ? oven-dried and activated at about 300 ?, can be silicone. The silica gel with cobalt chloride solution then dried and soaked in the activation of color silicone available. Use it as a desiccant, the water front is a blue to red after <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> water, the color change can be seen from water level, and the need for reclamation. Silicone is widely used in vapor recovery, oil refining and catalyst and so on. 
<br />1. Color, variety, style and diverse, environmentally friendly bracelets, non-toxic, tasteless, no side effects on the human body, material design and generous soft, simple, bright colors 
<br />2. Product Material: energy 100% hand-ring made of high-quality silicone material, the ratio of beneficial to human body a certain amount of nana-germanium, titanium, negative ions, far infrared health care until the functional materials, with new production and processing methods Cheng is a stylish health <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> . Long-term wear on the promotion of the human body's metabolism, regulate microcirculation have a good effect. 
<br />A soft, non-cracking, long life does not irritate skin, etc., 
<br />3. For various entertainment fields, but also can be used as gifts, souvenirs, promotional gifts with 
<br />Beautiful bright color, fashion and generous, do not fade, not afraid of water, afraid of wrinkles, inexpensive, the vast number of businesses as gifts, promotional items the best choice. 
<br />4. Product LOGO to screen printing, gravure printing, but also for Braille, the product itself can be made luminous hair. You can also customize according to customer, can be <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank">jimmy choo shoes sale</a> according to customer requirements, welcome customers to buy custom-made 
<br />to provide quality products and services to your satisfaction! EFX bracelet, energy bracelet, balance bracelet, PB bracelet EFX Wristband 
<br />Material: high quality imported silica gel produced by the complex forming process several times. 
<br />Usage: all kinds of activities, advertising, merchandise sales, charitable fund-raising promotion, identification, 
<br />Special <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL21hbm9sby1ibGFobmlrLWMtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">manolo blahnik shoes sale</a> purposes, is a stylish sport bracelet. 
<br />Proofing time: 3-5 days 
<br />Packing: OPP bag 
<br />Custom LOGO: LOGO can be customized according to customer requirements 
<br />Description: all kinds of color, blending, luminous, fluorescent, embossing, screen printing silicone bracelet 
<br />1. 
<br />2. Resistance to root penetration, ozone resistance, aging resistance, corrosion resistance, heat resistance and excellent low temperature flexibility. 
<br />3. A good diffusion of water vapor, condensate released easy to row, leaving the moisture easily <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tc2FuZGFscy1jLTYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">louboutin shoes</a> at the grassroots level. 
<br />4. The use of advanced hot air welding, seam sealing, reliable 
<br />5, activities, advertising, product promotions, charity fundraising promotion, identification, particularly 
<br />Special commemorative purposes, is a stylish sport bracelet. 
<br />Application of the second curing process difficult couplings, we need not glue bonding, can make a balanced functionality. 
<br />Can accept OEM, to undertake product development, mold design, tailor-made Welcome to call us for ordering, product design, development, production through-train service!! 
<br />Environmental protection silicone and has the energy balance can chip bonding, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> to create the perfect fashion bracelet, there are many colors for you choose, you can also color according to your requirements. 
<br />   Biological Engineering, Southeast University study shows that the use of modern technology: the human body itself produces temperature, magnetic field, electric field, so as to constitute a &quot;bio-information field.&quot; This &quot;bio-information field&quot; will produce a corresponding spectrum, known as &quot;bio-wave.&quot; &quot;Bio-wave&quot; can produce bio-electricity, it has a strange effect, that the photoelectric effect. 
<br />     Science Instrument Test: Jade also has this special &quot;photoelectric effect&quot; in a little pressure, cutting and finishing process of grinding effect will focus on storage ruined species form a &quot;electromagnetic field&quot;, and emits a can be absorbed into the body [url=]tory burch reva[/url] infrared waves, and then cells in the body of water molecules induced strong resonance, so that from a light massage, improve microcirculation system, so that the body improve blood circulation and metabolism, activate cells and tissues, regulate meridian quiz precision operation, enhance rapid response, improving the body's immune function. 
<br />Based on the above statement, jade bracelet worn on the wrist, long-term and wrist skin, points of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtaGFuZGJhZ3MtYy0yNS5odG1s" target="_blank">tory burch handbags</a> will naturally play a role in health care.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89c541c03e90aef00068ff79c07f4323" url=""><![CDATA[Water after skin becomes rosy.<br/><br/> China has proven gold reserves in the fourth in the world in recent years, China's gold production ranks fourth in the world; Asia has become an important producer of gold. After years of exploration and development and construction, at present, Shandong, western Henan, Heilongjiang, Shaanxi and Gansu Sichuan border, has become a major gold production base in China. Among them, Shandong has become the most proven reserves, the largest production scale, develop the best [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] -term gold production base, the region has proven gold reserves accounting for 1 / 4, the country's total gold output to 1 / 3, was hailed as China's &quot;Eldorado.&quot; Especially those with &quot;Inching Tearful,&quot; said the Shandong Zhao Yuan County, is China's current annual output of gold most of any county, the county's exquisite gold is China's largest gold mine. In addition, like Heilongjiang Jialing County and Human County, Xinxiang’s Altay and other places is the famous gold producer. 
<br />Thus, since ancient times gold is a symbol of wealth and power. Rapid development in technology today, it is increasingly wide range of applications. After years of [url=dc-shoes-c-69.html]dc shoes[/url]
<br />And development, have become the Crystal types and the benefits of the human body 
<br />The human body and the magnetic energy with rich, sometimes problems arise not because of the energy imbalance, as long as the increase or promote the power that the body's energy back to normal, will be able to grasp the key to health. Crystal itself is a pure high energy theory can be used to change the oscillation frequency of the body. Crystals of different colors, the different colors of crystal, on the [url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]supra vaider[/url] match of the human body, it will cause the energy integration, promote its role in removing the discomfort. Crystal display at home, you can front house, evil, changing magnetic field, it is Hong Kong called &quot;Fang Shum Stone&quot;, the Japanese called &quot;energy stone.&quot; 
<br />White crystals: pure and transparent, Kennedy really unwavering, fierce drive can be evil, strengthen the body magnetic field, and to self-cultivation, the raising of gas to purify the surrounding negative energy. Yellow Crystal: main side wealth, cohesion energy windfall strongest, corresponding to the sun gear to help the stomach, liver, digestive <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin</a> and so on. Rose Quartz: Also known as Crystal Lotus (love crystal), can be developed and help the pursuit of love, the heart chakra, improve interpersonal relations and many friends, develop contacts, so a good mood. Amethyst: top wheel and corresponding wheel eyebrow, the largest gathering strength to help sleep, rapid recovery. Evil, of body, life extension, Lack of Undisciplined, low learning ability have a very good conditioning effect. Emetine: also known as Valentine's stone, amethyst face the outside world to the different temperatures as a result of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> variation. With the harmonic, increase wisdom, 
<br />Smoky Quartz: a stable and balanced role in helping to enhance the analytical capacity of people to supplement the body heat to recuperate. Corresponding to sea round (will Shying), to promote sexual and regeneration. 
<br />The crystal: (a fat grain of Italy) who must successfully lead crystal, with plenty of energy, can enhance the courage, emotional stability, strengthen confidence and determination in dealing with things, and ability to make sound business grow day by day. Magnetic <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> than No hair and crystal to be strong and focused, can still be broken down into the following categories: 
<br />Titanium Crystal: Crystal King, the metal containing titanium dioxide, can enhance self-confidence, help gas, health, help wealth, corresponding to the sun gear of the liver, stomach, intestines and other organs with patients. 
<br />Cinnabar red hair crystal: the main reproductive round, promote blood circulation, improve the reproductive system. 
<br />Red Rabbit Crystal: Crystal Venus, also known as adjustable female physical, emotional comfort, beauty, and promote blood circulation and endocrine, and strengthen sea round. 
<br />Huang Faking: Treasure eats it, all communication, the nature of reconciliation, conditioning the digestive system. 
<br />Black crystal: eliminate karma, evil, prayer; eliminate symptoms of illness, all the characteristics of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank">jimmy choo shoes sale</a> and practical. 
<br />Bay Faking: peace, disaster information, improve luck, spiritual purification can, on behalf of the light. 
<br />Green hair crystal: as with the Phantom move is financial, travel and business trip can be a good opportunity to bring good luck, break through the bottleneck, to be creative, corresponding to the 
<br />Color Red Crystal: Crystal in the crystallization process, the internal cracks formed in the rainbow light irradiation. It is the wish of the crystal successful. 
<br />White Ghost Crystal: the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL21hbm9sby1ibGFobmlrLWMtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">manolo blahnik shoes sale</a> crown, on the efficacy of the brain, can cure headaches, depression, and drive away evil and change the fate of self-cultivation, the raising of gas. 
<br />Green Phantom Crystal: Changchow, corresponding to the heart chakra, and create business wealth to the wealth of Crystal Pyramid Crystal Phantom of the best, make people love and patience, the magnetic field Wensum Xiang and. 
<br />Vision Crystal: mineral elements with high energy, the potential can be developed, modified atmosphere of self-cultivation, smoking symptoms of illness, health and longevity, make <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tc2FuZGFscy1jLTYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">christian louboutin shoes</a> best. 
<br />Water tank Crystal: Crystal miserly with water features, people smart, flexible, and know how to advance and retreat strain of the Road, teach people to beats, smooth and slick. Can also increase the husband and wife, 
<br />Obsidian: a strong ability to ward off evil, and can strongly absorb the negative energy, avoid unclean things, the corresponding sea wheel, gas can cause the body under the three rounds of the kidney may be strong, absorption symptoms of illness, treatment of infertility, help sleep. 
<br />Crystal shape and ore 
<br />Seven Circle: two to seven as the base of the equilateral triangles, each side of the triangle must be a multiple of 7, the use of such a place, so that agitation among crystal frequency, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> in an invisible atmospheric column, after the start, the connection is more powerful force in the universe, be fulfilled. Fang Shum for display. 
<br />Pyramid: a collection of extremely powerful role in the universe can be directly introduced various types of energy for meditation. Crystal twin tip: for the treatment of diseases, air conductivity, with input and output to reach into me into the realm of 
<br />Large satellites: two equilateral triangles overlapping in the opposite direction after the formation of hexagonal with symbols, most of the nation, both initiatives are too deep religious significance, is the human symbol of the spiritual link with the universe <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtc2FuZGFscy1jLTI2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">tory burch sandals</a> called the Star of David or the seal of Solomon, representative of the lower triangular body, human vitality, but also represents the next three - the sun wheel, umbilical round, bottom round, a symbol of the spirit of the upper triangle, the human spirit, but also a symbol of the three, Throat , eyebrow round, top round, triangular overlap between the two is where the heart chakra. Use of such a totem, so that crystals produced stirring frequency, coupling is more powerful force in the universe, be fulfilled. 
<br />Five beads: press the corresponding color of the five elements, with five different color crystal beads are strung Shush or necklace can be worn by people who make up the missing element of that luck is better than smooth, the body, career, emotions also <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtaGFuZGJhZ3MtYy0yNS5odG1s" target="_blank">tory burch handbags</a> a help, and good fortune ... 
<br />Gold - White (available white crystal) 
<br />Wood - green or pink or light purple (or green hair can be quiet green amethyst powder) 
<br />Water - black or blue (or blue smoky quartz crystal can be black or natural onyx blue glass) 
<br />Fire - Red (Red hair crystal can be used) 
<br />Soil - soil yellow or brown (yellowish brown hair crystal citrine available) 
<br />Columnar Crystal: Laser column, firing particularly strong, with a focus on energy, point discharge characteristics. Anti-thief, villain, with the town house, so that subordinates obey. 
<br />Crystal ball: As the crystal has a dual focus on the characteristics of a town house defends the crystal ball performance, rich original crystal energy. Story rather than extra cash on behalf of the other, white crystal Ibo Buddhism, one of Buddha with a white crystal ball is an excellent choice. 
<br />White druses: Crystal [url=]tory burch flats[/url] group is the most natural beauty of the spar, it launched a number of boles to positive energy in all directions, can ward off evil and evil block, radiation protection and automation solutions and can automatically charged negative energy, also known as the White crystal matrix, the energy going. 
<br />Zip Dingdong: Zip Dingdong intensive internal boles, has a strong cohesive effect of resonance can be upright to improve the cohesion inside the house fang shut; fang shut is the best stone. On the financial position at home, you can ward off evil Fangs also embodies the wealth, also known as amethyst mother. 
<br />Cornucopia: a strong absorption sewage gas, stop evil enrichment functions, can concentrate and increase wisdom. 
<br />Crystal Block: Those into the water, the magnetic field can change the water; purify water, whether Tory Burch shoes <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tL3RvcnktYnVyY2gtc2hvZXMtYy0xOS5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.toryburchcenter.com%2Ftory-burch-shoes-c-19.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.toryburchcenter.com/tory-burch-shoes-c-19.html</a></a>
<br />Drinking, washing, bathing, beauty, fish, water the plants and so have very good results, many women face with a powder of 
<br /><br />Amethyst Pillow: insomnia, develop wisdom, to remove distractions, emotional stability, there are refreshing, the effect of modified atmosphere repose. 
<br />Crystal Carving: Crystal has high storage capacity of the message, so it is carved into an image of the crystal, that is, the image of the message will be there to make it more spiritual.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bf7420e6d1b7b64191cc9a273d48f478" url=""><![CDATA[The story bracelet<br/><br/>the first gift for mom is an agate bracelet. The results do not wear into the mother said, a gift that some of this failure. Therefore, there has been an idea in mind: get to be to buy one now! 
<br />This year came to Jiangxi, stopped in a small town. Small town, the market can not tell prosperity. Down in the street more than a dozen chipped silver shops, and seemed to be such a craft was popular. Hey! Bracelets on the back do not buy into, because the [url=][color=#000080]supra shoes[/color][/url] ID bracelet can be Jinzhou is open, you can adjust, and it should not have problems? Although each offer slightly different, but generally in the upper and lower 2.5 Yuan a gram, it is not expensive, I think probably this is the real price. Half a block away and saw the owner of an honest face, age about forty CSU, and went inside. Told him that wants to play a Jinzhou, ask him right? 
<br />&quot;OK, ah!&quot; The owner said. 
<br />&quot;Then a bracelet more than some of the General Assembly more appropriate? I asked. 
<br />That I hit one.&quot; I said, &quot;Hey, can you let me look at the raw materials?&quot; I suddenly remembered my mother once said to listen to some street hawkers will be playing the lead in silver, copper-nickel alloy metal to a class of replacement out of your [url=dc-shoes-c-69.html]dc shoes[/url] , good profit from it, have to prevent. 
<br />The store owner smiled. He may know what I was thinking. The thickness of a finger while out, Chi CSU-long trapezoidal cross-section for the silver bullion, she said to me: &quot;Our silver, are coming from the silver market, not false. Jiangxi itself is produced silver. &quot;. Having said Miao Lamiae eye on the silver bar, take a handful of bolt cutters, clip the finger length of a length. Section is a shiny silver color. 
<br />&quot;So this is the color of silver, did not appear so bright before.” 
<br />&quot;Of course, this is just the beginning. 
<br />He changed a pair of pliers, grips the silver bar on the anvil, and rattled the beat up. I'm told he does not need any color, looks like a natural and simple. He nodded. Little while, and looks to shape the general. Make a point and then changes in the corner, take [url=supra-shoes-supra-vaider-c-65_67.html]supra vaider[/url] lance baked, put into the water. &quot;Laugh&quot; is heard, jumping a mist. Grazed take a dry cloth, bright silver 
<br />I am very satisfied. 
<br />Bracelet, said the balance will be placed, and worse for at least fifty grams. Men quite accurate in it! Good to see him play the system, then let him call one. Not all people wearing a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Christian louboutin</a> of Jinzhou it! This time I let him slightly cut some more to play a little heavy. 
<br />Paid the owner 260 dollars, I have to do so for a pair of Jinzhou. Quickly send home, thinking: This will not have any problems? 
<br />Fortunately, my mother on the phone said fine. Also said the near cousin got married, she wore it out and make others see. 
<br />Do not mention how proud I am of the mind. 
<br />Branches in Guangzhou, recently launched the &quot;style of construction and standardization of services&quot; checks in place in Payne branch of a moving story: Leading up to the branch, down to the ordinary staff to strictly enforce the &quot;Style Construction of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tcHVtcHMtYy00Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin pumps</a> Development Bank and standardization of service standards &quot;in the provisions do not wear bracelets, conscious action, have tried off bracelets, can not shake off, and to reluctantly part, smashing! 
<br />Deputy Governor Wu Kaifeng Payne Branch has sent a mother in law has been ten years wearing a bracelet. May branch headquarters standardized services transmitted request, Wu Kaifeng immediately think of a way to take off bracelets, straining off the bracelet down, no; painted hands with soap off again, no good. Supposed to? Is a violation of discipline and continue to wear, or what disciplinary action will be <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2NocmlzdGlhbi1sb3Vib3V0aW4tYm9vdHMtYy01Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">louboutin boots</a> bracelet? Although not very expensive bracelets, but that is mother in law sent, there are elderly people inside the mind; while wearing such a long time, have also been feeling worn out, bracelets as part of the body as their own. But the thought of it is discipline, must be unconditional implementation! She said nothing, put the bracelet smashed. 
<br />Branch staff Xian Xinhua, her hand was her bird bracelet graduation of the first pieces of jewelry bought have been wearing for almost a decade. Four years ago when you were pregnant people fat, and bracelets out of hand Le printed, she was not willing to break it. Now, her conscious action, try soap, ice and other ways trying to take down the Smash hit in the choice or not, she thought only with his daughter to wife from doing, to do a full decade of his mother's bracelets, recalled <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL2ppbW15LWNob28tYy0xMi5odG1s" target="_blank">jimmy choo shoes sale</a> last time bit by bit, too hard feeling of dismay; But when she thought of the whole line for &quot;standardized management&quot; activities to contribute, each one of my colleagues are consciously abide by the rules and regulations, have a clear mind right decision. The next morning back to flat, she immediately invited his colleagues to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3Vib3V0aW5wdW1wc3NhbGUuY29tL21hbm9sby1ibGFobmlrLWMtMTMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">manolo blahnik shoes sale</a> the bracelets, and then broken bracelet, red velvet bag with a good collection of them carefully. 
<br />In Lucia Fang, Xian Xinhua that a small body, but the Guangzhou Branch of the strict regulations discipline, abide by the norms of the pledge on a little surf trip, but it reflects the employees a better mind. Bracelet off, smashing bracelet is a small matter, as the Payne branch employee said: &quot;This is normal ah! As a unit of employees, must submit to discipline, and obey the command!&quot; But it is a trivial thing in this fully reflects the majority of employees disciplined, curried, obeying the command, up and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J5YnVyY2hjZW50ZXIuY29tLw__" target="_blank">tory burch outlet</a> together, united in a good mental outlook, but also fully reflects the broad issue of management-level staff lead by example, self-discipline of good quality
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>