<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="20">
		<document id="dfb627ce834c37c0d36811f388766738" url=""><![CDATA[Chinese Medicine Device - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Reflexology Nervous System and Medicomat Chinese Medicine Device - Medicomat 2. Frequent use of our product will improve your immunity and delay the aging of each cell, thus make you stronger and more energetic, and keep you in a good health conditions. <br /><br />It is known that all the internal organs and body parts have their own acupuncture points on the ear lobe. Using special headphones placed over the ear shells LEKOMAT fully automatically finds all the diseased organs and automatically selects the necessary acupuncture points through which the treatment is done. When using LEKOMAT a tingling sensation is felt and heard the quiet music. It is used 2-3 times a day for 20-30 minutes. Usually 2-3 treatments are sufficient for 7 days, and treatment of chronic illness takes longer. <br /><br />According to the theory of traditional Chinese medicine, diseases are caused by block of meridian channels in the body. Block causes pain; no block, no pain. The human body is just like a river. If the river course is blocked, it will flood over. if it is cleared, it will run smoothly. Our product gives out 8 kinds of special audio frequency pulse which will open blockings in meridian channels in the human body. By stimulating the acupuncture points on the ear, a treatment can be given. <br /><br />The fifth acupuncture weight loss point is simply one of relaxation because after all, even acupuncture weight loss can't work if you're not relaxed. <br /><br />Why do most acupuncturists schedule 1½ hours or more for an initial acupuncture appointment? What exactly happens during the first visit that could possibly take that long? How long are the needles left in the patient? Do acupuncturists charge by the hour? <br /><br />When the patient feels an urge to eat in between meals or when it is unnecessary to eat, they apply a mild pressure on the ear staples; alternatively rub them back and forth for about 20 seconds. This results to a direct stimulation causing a mild endorphin release, relaxing the patient to regain control. <br /><br />Although these traditional Chinese hypertension treatments assure the hypertensive patients of a relief of up to 90%, they do require some lifestyle changes from the patient’s end such as lowered intake of salt, observance of well-balanced diet and restraining from harmful habits like smoking and alcoholism. These methods can be also practiced by people who have family history of hypertension and want to prevent this ailment from entering into their body. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicomat.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicomat.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="84274db2c3626a20a72d96867e7d1e7d" url=""><![CDATA[Electronic Body Massager - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Sensory Therapy Activities and Medicomat Electronic Body Massager - Apparatus Cures Medicobot. Acupuncture treatment  combined with electric stimulation, known as electro-acupuncture, can effectively lower high blood pressure. During this  treatment, sharp, fine needles are inserted into the trigger points or key points, including legs, forearms and wrists. In  electro-acupuncture method, low-frequency currents are passed through normal acupuncture needles. The needles are connected  to a device that continuously generates small electric pulses. <br /><br />As the tongue represents all the internal organs the ear represents the entire body. There are so many powerful healing  points in the ear that one can easily treat effectively many health conditions especially the  5 combo point for PTSD,  trauma, addictions (drugs, alcohol, nicotine, gambling), anxiety, BP issues, digestive, heart and lung, allergy conditions  to name a few. The Shenman point is such a beautiful point to relax, de-stress and diminish pain. Bleeding certain points in  the ear is often a great healing practice for many conditions. <br /><br />Lekomat apparatus lung disease, particularly effective in bronchitis, asthma, allergies, stress, diseases of the nervous  system. In a few minutes automatically reduces pain in the stomach, back, neck and legs. <br /><br />Tinnitus can arise in any of the four sections of the ear: the outer ear, the middle ear, the inner ear, and the brain.  Tinnitus is often accompanied by hearing loss. <br /><br />The lack of energy associated with tiredness can sometimes cause difficulty with normal daily activities, leading to  problems with attentiveness and concentration. Causes of tiredness range from lack of sleep and over exercise to medical and  surgical treatments. <br /><br />Shen nong was one of the greatest Chinese Emperors. He taught his people how to sow seeds and taught them which plants would  help them to get well. He invented the plough and he discovered ginsengs. His wife mastered the art of breeding silkworm.  She was the goddess of housecraft inventions. Herbal teas, ginseng, farming and cloth helped the Chinese civilization to be  one of the greatest civilizations. The Chinese people hailed Shen nong as the divine cultivator/farmer and as the founder of  Chinese medicine. <br /><br />Most of us are aware of the techniques involved in Acupuncture and while considering weight loss with this method, it  involves inserting hair-thin needles into particular spots on the skin that are believed to help the body function properly.  In general, the method of Acupuncture helps to stimulate the body and to discharge endorphins, which are nothing but body's  own pain-relieving chemicals which makes us feel good. This can be considered one of the ways in which Acupuncture helps us  in weight loss releasing endorphins and in turn control appetite. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and  disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a  href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href=''  target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d16dce4dbdd75af563bb2ce10d5488f9" url=""><![CDATA[Mini Tens Therapy Massager - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Acupuncture Knee Injury and Medicomat Mini Tens Therapy Massager - Lekomat Acupuncture Treatment. Points of the skin are  energetically connected to these specific organs, body structures and functional systems. If this energy circulation is  disrupted, optimal function is affected, resulting in pain or illness. <br /><br />All the internal organs and body parts have their own acupuncture points on the ear lobe. Probe / headphones placed over the  ear shells LEKOMAT alone, fully automatic, find all the diseased organs and automatically selects the appropriate  acupuncture points through which the treatment is done. When using LEKOMAT, a monitor for home treatment of acupuncture, a  tingling sensation is felt and heard the quiet music. It is used 2-3 times a day for 20-30 minutes. Usually 2-3 treatments  are sufficient for 7 days, and treatment of chronic illness takes longer. <br /><br />There are certain pathways within the body that can help to channel the energy in the body. These pathways can become  blocked at some point of time, unbalanced, or deficient in some way. Acupuncture and Chinese medicine can be used to bring  back the pathways to their proper balance. Occasionally herbs are burned and the properties of the herbs can help with the  acupuncture therapy to restore the balance of the body. <br /><br />Pain in the neck can be more than just a hassle. Neck pain can come from disorders and diseases of any structure in the  neck. There are seven vertebrae that are the bony building blocks of the spine in the neck (the cervical vertebrae) that  surround the spinal cord and canal. Between these vertebrae are discs and nearby pass the nerves of the neck. <br /><br />Pain can also occur in the knee from diseases or conditions that involve the knee joint, the soft tissues and bones  surrounding the knee, or the nerves that supply sensation to the knee area. In fact, the knee joint is the most commonly  involved joint in rheumatic diseases, immune diseases that affect various tissues of the body, including the joints to cause  arthritis. <br /><br />Many of us know about how acupuncture can relieve stress, deaden pain, and be used for other emotional or mental purposes.  It is also very useful for a number of problems that women face, from menstrual problems up to the problem of infertility.  We will look at a couple of examples to show that acupuncture can be an asset in each case. Of course, you will want to  consult your individual acupuncture professional to determine the specific treatment for an individual case. <br /><br />Is there any side-effect? No, there is not any side-effect. It uses skin electrodes to treat, no cross infection and avoids  acupuncture syncope. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and  disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a  href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href=''  target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="83c1d2804153f4401d9438d016a7caa4" url=""><![CDATA[Multi-Function Disease Device - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Neck Pain Management and Medicomat Multi-Function Disease Device - Causes, Triggers, Symptoms and Treatments. The term  acupuncture describes a family of procedures involving stimulation of anatomical points on the body by a variety of  techniques. American practices of acupuncture incorporate medical traditions from China, Japan, Korea, and other countries.  The acupuncture technique that has been most studied scientifically involves penetrating the skin with thin, solid, metallic  needles that are manipulated by the hands or by electrical stimulation. <br /><br />TCM cannot treat all lower back pain problems. Some are severe and need Western medical intervention. Nevertheless,  acupuncture has been effective at treating low back pain for most people, so it is worth checking out. If it does work for  you, you will at least get back to the activities you enjoy without all those anti-inflammatory drugs and back crackings! <br /><br />Cyanosis is the medical term for a bluish color of the skin and the mucous membranes due to an insufficient level of oxygen  in the blood. For example, the lips and fingernails may show cyanosis. Cyanosis can be evident at birth due to the presence  of a heart malformation that permits blood that is not fully oxygenated to enter the arterial circulation. <br /><br />Headache medicine is divided into four types: MIGRAINE - the most common and most painful, the most common is the so-called  tension - pain involves the whole head, EYE - the most intense pain in the eye cavity, sinus - pain above the eyebrow and  eye. Headaches accompanied by an illness in the acute phase: hepatitis, an infection of the lungs, interfere with digestion,  kidney disease ... Experience Lekomata big when it comes to diagnosing and treating headaches with acupuncture. This therapy  does not alleviate the symptoms (like most drugs), but goes to the root of the disease, cause, and it removes upešno. <br /><br />Depression is an illness that involves the body, mood, and thoughts and affects the way a person eats and sleeps, the way  one feels about oneself, and the way one thinks about things. Depressive disorders are characterized by pervasive mood  changes that affect all aspects of an individual's daily functioning. <br /><br />The type of symptoms and seizures depend on where the abnormal electrical activity takes place in the brain, what its cause  is, and such factors as the patient's age and general state of health. <br /><br />What is Acupuncture? Acupuncture is a system of holistic medicine that originated in China approximately 5,000 years ago.  Along with Chinese Herbal Medicine, Acupuncture is one the primary modalities of treatment in Oriental Medicine. During an  acupuncture treatment, fine sterile needles are inserted into the body at specific locations to provide a regulatory effect  on the body. These acupuncture points exist along energy pathways, called meridians, which connect the surface of the body  to the internal organs. As the body is needled, a mild propagated electric sensation can be felt along the course of the  corresponding meridian. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and  disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a  href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href=''  target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c992bfe95a46e4e0d4fce2587aa40876" url=""><![CDATA[Highly Effective Electronic Therapy Machine - Distributors W<br/><br/>Blood Pressure Cure Naturally and Medicomat Highly Effective Electronic Therapy Machine - Medicomat Tips. Acupuncture (Lekomat) successfully treat sinusitis. Sinusitis is a serious illness. Boring, because it does not go away easily. Curable if it becomes a chronic and become a curse for a lifetime. However, not all that bad. Acupuncture is effective in LekomatU, treating chronic sinusitis, but requires prolonged and persistent treatment, as well as the patience of the patient. <br /><br />Lekomat apparatus cures impotence and other disorders. The device is fully automatic all - examining and treating acupuncture to the ear. The list of diseases that monitor for home treatment is a long LEKOMAT treated and feel improvements after only a day or two. It is particularly effective in impotence, menstrual problems, insomnia, headaches, migraines, stress, bronchitis, asthma, allergies and obesity. Usually 2-3 treatments are sufficient for 7 days, and treatment of chronic illness takes longer. <br /><br />It is unclear how many people are affected with IBS. The incidence has been estimated anywhere between 5% and 65% of the general population. Women experience IBS far more than men. Acupuncture can assist in many of these cases. <br /><br />Loss of vision can occur suddenly or develop gradually over time. Vision loss may be complete (involving both eyes) or partial, involving only one eye or even certain parts of the visual field. Vision loss is different from blindness that was present at birth, and this article is concerned with causes of vision loss in an individual who previously had normal vision. <br /><br />Vertigo is a feeling that you are dizzily turning around or that your surroundings are dizzily turning about you. Vertigo is usually due to a problem with the inner ear but can also be caused by vision problems and other conditions. Vertigo is medically distinct from dizziness, lightheadedness, and unsteadiness in that vertigo involves the sensation of movement. <br /><br />The following are other conditions Acupuncture and Traditional Chinese Medicine can treat which are not classified using the above system: Acute sinusitis, Common Cold, Acute bronchitis, Acute conjunctivitis, Central retinitis, Myopia (in children), Cataract (without complications), Toothache, post-extraction pain, Gingivitis, Acute and chronic pharyngitis, Spasms of esophagus and cardia, Hiccough, Gastroptosis, Acute and chronic gastritis, Gastric hyperacidity, Chronic duodenal ulcer (pain relief), Acute duodenal ulcer (without complications), Acute and chronic colitis, Acute bacillary dysentery, Constipation, Diarrhea, Paralytic ileus, Trigeminal neuralgia, Frozen shoulder, Pareses following a stroke, Sequelae of poliomyelitis (early stage, i.e., within six months), Meniere's disease, Nocturnal enuresis, Intercostal neuralgia, Cervicobrachial syndrome. <br /><br />Oddly enough, they may also stick needles in the area around your ears. It doesn’t sound too pleasant but it gets results! The ears have points related to the large intestine, which can be the area of concern. There are also points connected to the anal region and spleen. Acupuncture here can really help. To treat hemorrhoids, you will have a few to several treatments of about 20 to 30 minutes. The doctor may also use moxibustion, or the burning of moxa leaves close to the skin. Treatment may also include herbal remedies such as bitter teas that help with digestion. They are not so tasty, but they will help! <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="424cda8721564efc83af4c64d4f3511a" url=""><![CDATA[EMS Massager Machine - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Apparatus Medikomat and Medicomat EMS Massager Machine - Acupuncture Without Needles. Jaundice, also referred to as icterus, is the yellow staining of the skin and sclerae by abnormally high blood levels of the bile pigment, bilirubin. The yellowing extends to other tissues and body fluids and also may turn the urine dark. Yellowing of only the skin also can be caused by eating too many carrots or drinking too much carrot juice. <br /><br />There are two different categories of headaches: primary and secondary. A primary headache is an actual clinical condition and not a symptom caused by another disorder. Primary headaches include tension-type headaches, migraines, and cluster headaches. Secondary headaches are caused by other medical conditions such as sinus disease, allergies, dental disorders, head injury, or brain tumors. <br /><br />A decreased desire to eat is a symptom that is common to numerous medical and psychological conditions. Almost any illness can lead to a decrease in appetite. When severe, decreased appetite can lead to unwanted weight loss and malnutrition. Medically, a decrease in appetite is referred to as anorexia. <br /><br />Tinnitus or ringing ears ailment may surface as a result of some serious underlying diseases such as tumors. Since tumors need to be operated upon, it is imperative that the patient undergoes a complete medical examination before opting for tinnitus acupuncture treatment. <br /><br />Swelling of the ankle on one side is often a result of sprains or strains. Sometimes diseases that affect the entire body, such as heart disease and kidney or liver failure, can result in excess fluid buildup (edema) that is often concentrated in the legs and feet, leading to swelling not only of the ankles but also of the feet and lower legs. This can also occur with obstruction of the venous system, as may occur with pregnancy and obesity. <br /><br />This device is simple and easy for home use. WARNING: Do not use if pregnant, have a pacemaker or suffer from malignant tumors, excessive bleeding or tuberculosis. Not to be used by children under the age of 3. <br /><br />Electro stimulation is the application of a pulsating electrical micro-current to the acupuncture needles as a means of stimulating the acupoints. It was developed in China around 1934. Good results are expected from electro-acupuncture treatments for a variety of diseases. Electro stim can be used for 10-20 or 30 minutes and in 1-3 pairs at a time, with the pairs usually on the same side of the body, with a certain frequency and voltage. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ef66fd5447c427b81c26d26f71b33f58" url=""><![CDATA[Disease Detecting And Curing Device - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Brain Tumor Acupuncture Treatments and Medicomat Disease Detecting And Curing Device - Lekomat Alternative Medicine. Common causes of pain in the heel include blisters and corns. Plantar fasciitis, inflammation of the bowstring-like tissue in the sole of the foot stretching from the heel to the front of the foot, is one condition commonly associated with heel pain. <br /><br />The treatment of the headache depends on the type and severity of the headache and on other factors such as the age of the patient. <br /><br />The list of diseases that monitor for home treatment is a long LEKOMAT treated and feel improvements after only a day or two. It is particularly effective in diseases of the nervous system, bronchitis, asthma, allergies, stress. He is successful in diseases of the heart, lungs, stomach and kidneys. The special value of this device is that it frees you of daily use of many drugs and medications. <br /><br />Cosmetic Acupuncture is a type of art that is perfected under Kinski Medicine for thousands of years, and which was initially only lady in the imperial court. Cosmetic acupuncture is a long time was not available to ordinary people. In the contemporary world is changing. It is safe, effective and virtually painless method that regenerates the skin of the face and neck, fine wrinkles can completely disappear, deeper wrinkles are reduced, returns to the freshness of the face and reduce bags under the eyes. <br /><br />Treating UTIs with Acupuncture. TCM sees the imbalance of qi in the lower abdomen as the cause of urinary tract infections. <br /><br />Acupuncture seeks its origin from China, and is based on the belief of Chinese people and their methods. The Chinese people immensely believe in energy concept and its relation with body, and assume a balanced flow of energy all through the body to remain healthy. They also believe that any obstacle in the flow of that energy leads to inflammations, and it consequently paves way to ruthless pains and numerous types of diseases in the body. <br /><br />Elbow pain is most often the result of tendinitis, which can affect the inner or outer elbow. Treatment includes ice, rest, and medication for inflammation. Elbow pain has many other causes including arthritis and bursitis. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca2e255bb19c0517b02f34bf4cf48733" url=""><![CDATA[Weight Loss Beauty Equipment - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Foot Massage Diabetes and Medicomat Weight Loss Beauty Equipment - Medicobot Care. Infertility is defined as the failure to become pregnant after one year of unprotected intercourse. There are two types of infertility; primary infertility, which is infertility without any previous pregnancy; and secondary infertility, when there has been a previous pregnancy. <br /><br />Hearing loss can be present at birth (congenital) or become evident later in life. The distinction between acquired and congenital deafness specifies only the time that the deafness appears. It does not specify whether the cause of the deafness is genetic. <br /><br />Acupuncture acupuncturist determines the point where the interruption of energy flow and diagnose disease originated. By stimulating these points individually identified points or more at a time gradually establishing energy re-circulation and therefore the patient returns to normal health condition and comes to a complete recovery. <br /><br />The common action of LFM intermediate frequency impulse wave and infrared heat treatment strap can ionize the message of the body to accomplish the double effectiveness of electrotherapeutics and TCM acupuncture point. <br /><br />Seeking treatment will banish acne forever. Acupuncture is a great way to fight acne, whether you are a troubled teen or an adult that hates to get pimples. <br /><br />Secondary headaches may result from innumerable conditions, ranging from life threatening ones such as brain tumors, strokes, meningitis, and subarachnoid hemorrhages to less serious but common conditions such as withdrawal from caffeine and discontinuation of analgesics (pain killing medication). Many people suffer from mixed headache disorders in which tension headaches or secondary headaches may trigger migraine. <br /><br />How many times to use per day? It is flexible according to the user's time. Three times per day is recommended. User who have enough time can also use much times. You can also use just once per day if you have scarce time, but should take longer time. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ed36e13ac76713fa20a61117382fe9dd" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Low Frequency Acupoint Stimulator<br/><br/>Foot Pain and Medicomat Low Frequency Acupoint Stimulator - Essential Advice Medicobot. Lekomat device for pain and to treat many diseases and ailments. In a few minutes automatically reduces pain in the stomach, back, neck and legs. List of diseases treated by the device is lengthy, and improvements are felt after only a day or two. It is particularly effective in diseases of the nervous system, bronchitis, asthma, allergies, stress. <br /><br />Find out if I am the right practitioner for you - USD125 initial session,  USD75  follow up sessions. OR, get unlimited sessions with Medicomat apparatus for USD175 including airmail shipping. Many users have referred their friends, relatives, neighbors and colleagues for our Medicomat apparatus. This is the best compliment any health provider can receive. <br /><br />Auriculotherapy involves the stimulation of specific acupuncture points of the external ear for diagnosis and treatment of health conditions. Ear Acupuncture from Seattle Health TherapiesStimulation of ear acu-points is accomplished by inserting several tiny needles into the ear points which are retained anywhere from 10 to 30 minutes. Occasionally several points may be stimulated with electro-acupuncture. Lasers, magnets, and electronic devices are also frequently used methods of stimulation. Taped products such as acubeads or seeds are often retained for long term use. <br /><br />LEKOMAT monitor for home treatment for rheumatism in the modern principle of acupuncture without needles without pain, and improve the feel, but after a day or two. It cures headaches, migraines, depression, high blood pressure, poor circulation, diabetes, dizziness, rheumatism, spondylosis, sciatica, stomach ulcers, obesity, insomnia, menstrual problems. In a few minutes automatically reduces pain in the stomach, back, neck and legs. <br /><br />All body parts have their main acupuncture points on the ear lobe, over the coffee-house treatment Lekomat fully automatic examining and treating acupuncture without needles. Use Lekomat is very simple, painless and without harmful effects. With Lekomatom will significantly reduce the use of drugs. Awarded a gold medal Eureka and Marconi. <br /><br />Insomnia is more likely to occur in females, people over 60 years of age, and people who have a history of depression, however, anyone can be affected by insomnia. Short-term insomnia may also occur as a side effect of certain medications. Chronic insomnia is more serious and may be caused or worsened by a variety of mental and physical problems. <br /><br />The Symptoms of Bell’s Palsy. This condition is caused by damage to nerves that paralyzes half of the face, meaning you’re unable to move your muscles. Other symptoms include tearing of the eyes since they can’t be closed, and possibly drooling from the side of the mouth that can’t be moved. It will also be accompanied by distortions of taste and a tingly feeling around the lips. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a72e5a778bfcc937d39dc66af01aed6b" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Low Frequency Stimulator<br/><br/>Bronchitis Symptoms and Medicomat Low Frequency Stimulator - Family Doctor Lekomat. A bruise is medically termed a contusion. Bruises are typically a result of some degree of injury to the blood vessels in the skin. Local leakage of blood into the skin from the capillaries that occurs spontaneously, without injury, results in a flat, purplish discolored area referred to as ecchymosis. <br /><br />An increase in appetite can be a normal physiological response that occurs, for example, in children and adolescents during periods of growth or following strenuous activity or excessive caloric demand. In some case, an increase in appetite can be a sign of an abnormal condition, such as some endocrinologic conditions. <br /><br />Less commonly, anatomical obstructions (e.g. a deviated nasal septum, foreign bodies) may lead to nasal congestion. Other causes of a stuffy or runny nose include environmental factors, hormonal changes, and some medications. Rarely, tumors of the nasal passages or chronic medical conditions may be the cause of a stuffy or runny nose. <br /><br />Cosmetic acupuncture is gaining in popularity in recent decades since the public and celebrities, especially in Hollywood, turning to these treatments as safe and natural alternative to surgical corrective methods. <br /><br />Infertility is the diminished ability or the inability to conceive and have offspring. Infertility is also defined in specific terms as the failure to conceive after a year of regular intercourse without contraception. Irreversible infertility is also referred to as sterility. <br /><br />The acupuncturist seeks to understand why your repetitive activity results in inflammation and elbow pain for you. In other words, why is it that others may take part in the same (or more extreme) activity without experiencing inflammation and pain? What makes you more susceptible to this condition than others? Determining this answer involves looking at more than just the elbow. <br /><br />Women are more likely than men to have anemia because of the loss of blood each month through menstruation. Iron deficiency anemia is common and in adults is most often due to chronic blood loss. This can be from menstruation or from small amounts of repeated bleeding and in children is due mainly to not enough iron in the diet. Anemia is also often due to gastrointestinal bleeding caused by medications including, such very common drugs as aspirin and ibuprofen. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3f5886424ab5fe28f52e947f6de294bf" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Acupoint Stimulator<br/><br/>Biofeedback Equipment and Medicomat Acupoint Stimulator - Lekomat No Pain. LEKOMAT monitor for home treatment of headaches all the work alone, fully automatic, finds all the disturbances and automatically treat headaches and other ailments. It is particularly effective in diseases of the nervous system, bronchitis, asthma, allergies, stress. <br /><br />Concentration problems, when present to an excessive degree, are also characteristic of certain physical and psychological conditions. The hallmark condition associated with difficulty concentrating is attention-deficit hyperactivity disorder, a condition that has been increasingly diagnosed in both children an adults in recent years. <br /><br />Insomnia may be classified by how long the symptoms are present. Temporary insomnia (transient insomnia) usually is due to situational changes, such as travel and stressful events. It lasts for less than a week or until the stressful event is resolved. Short-term insomnia lasts for one to three weeks, and long-term insomnia (chronic insomnia) continues for more than three weeks. <br /><br />Restless leg syndrome usually begins slowly. Over time, the legs become more affected. Less frequently, restless leg syndrome can affect the arms. <br /><br />Insomnia is the perception of inadequate or poor-quality sleep. It can be due to problems falling asleep, early wakening, waking frequently during the night, unrefreshing sleep, or a combination of these. Contrary to some popular beliefs, insomnia is not defined by the total amount of sleep one gets or how long it takes a person to fall asleep. Individuals can vary in their need for sleep, and in the time required to fall asleep. What is a refreshing night's sleep for one person might be insomnia for another person. <br /><br />The classic example is Tourette's syndrome, but other neurological disturbances can result in vocal outbursts as well. Psychiatric conditions such as schizophrenia may have vocal outbursts as a symptom, and some people suffering from dementia or other forms of damage to the brain may display vocal outbursts in the form of uncontrolled or dysregulated speech. Alcohol and drug use can also lead to impairment of behavior and control, leading sometimes to vocal outbursts. <br /><br />Auricular acupuncture is, simply put, applying acupuncture to only the ears of a person. By limiting acupuncture to the ears only, auricular acupuncturists can improve results and make patients feel more comfortable. For some people, using needles on other parts of their bodies is uncomfortable. Auricular acupuncture offers a pleasurable alternative to get the help that they need. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="392dfc601bdfd36c1881c4f39fd93ea2" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Blood Pressure Depressor<br/><br/>Disease Detecting And Curing Machine and Medicomat Blood Pressure Depressor - Lekomat Effective Health Care. Many medical conditions can affect the shape or texture of the fingernails. Brittleness of the nails, meaning that the nails easily become cracked or chipped, can be observed as a sign of aging or in response to the long-term use of nail polish or exposure to moist conditions. <br /><br />Vertigo is a feeling that you are dizzily turning around or that your surroundings are dizzily turning about you. Vertigo is usually due to a problem with the inner ear but can also be caused by vision problems and other conditions. Vertigo is medically distinct from dizziness, lightheadedness, and unsteadiness in that vertigo involves the sensation of movement. <br /><br />Weakness may be generalized or may affect one muscle or muscle group exclusively. Diseases of the neuromuscular system, injuries, metabolic diseases, and toxins can all cause of measurable muscle weakness. <br /><br />Health-keeping: Frequent use of our product will improve your immunity and delay the aging of each cell, thus make you stronger and more energetic, and keep you in a good health conditions. <br /><br />Daily treatment of 50-10 minutes can reduce pressure for 20-30/5-10 mmHg. Blood pressure will be controlled after 5-7 treatments. Two treatments of 10-20 minutes a day can stabilize blood pressure and hypertension in more pronounced. Therapy can be a supplement or alternative to medication for a gradual reduction in medication. <br /><br />The earliest use of ear acupuncture dates back to ancient China. Although much of the information on this subject was lost due to the historical burning of the books, the ancient Chinese stimulated many points on the auricle to rebalance the flow of energy and restore health. <br /><br />By using the monitor for home treatment LEKOMAT improvements are felt after only a day or two. In a few minutes automatically reduces pain in the stomach, back, neck and legs. The device runs on two 1.5V batteries, and can be used by multiple people. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="caaa1f6dfd4c205f73bfe4931908aa0" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Detecting And Curing Device<br/><br/>The Acupuncture Points and Medicomat Detecting And Curing Device - Help. Weakness may be generalized or may affect one muscle or muscle group exclusively. Diseases of the neuromuscular system, injuries, metabolic diseases, and toxins can all cause of measurable muscle weakness. <br /><br />Auricular mould is the first choice and the main stimulate method, the other two are supplementary. Use auricular mould first, and if time permits you can use the shoes, three times per day. Or use the ear treatment once per day. <br /><br />Swelling of the ankle on one side is often a result of sprains or strains. Sometimes diseases that affect the entire body, such as heart disease and kidney or liver failure, can result in excess fluid buildup that is often concentrated in the legs and feet, leading to swelling not only of the ankles but also of the feet and lower legs. <br /><br />Fever is part of the body's own disease-fighting arsenal. Rising body temperatures apparently are capable of killing off many disease-producing organisms. For that reason, low fevers should normally go untreated. Although, if the fever is accompanied by any other troubling symptoms, you may need to see your doctor to be certain. <br /><br />Scientific research into the mechanism of action of acupuncture have started about 30 years ago. To help understand the traditional and the modern theory, we need to know what actually happens during treatment. There are feelings of subjective and objective: subjective - pain (depending on skill acupuncture) and De Qi phenomenon (deep painful feeling of fullness, numbness or tingling); objective - analgesia, sedation, homeostasis, immune system and psychological effect. <br /><br />The acupuncturist will explain that unless a person is suffering some kind of harmful side effects, the patient should continue to follow their medical doctor's instructions. Also, the patient should not expect immediate or instant results. A number of treatments will be necessary before any benefits are likely to be seen. <br /><br />I'm A huge sceptic where complementary medicine is concerned. People are always running off to have wacky therapies because they need to stop smoking or give up sugar, but I've always been a great believer in the fact that if you really want to do something, you'll do it. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6bd3b2619ed09e6bae6d47a3cc557645" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Male Sexual Dysfunction Therapeutic Ap<br/><br/>Asthma Cure Research and Medicomat Male Sexual Dysfunction Therapeutic Apparatus - Tips to Cure. Trauma, including bone fracture, is also a cause of hip pain. Pain in the hip area may also originate from painful infections or other conditions of the skin, such as shingles. Hip pain may also occur because of a problem with the back or spine. Treatments for hip pain depend on the underlying cause. <br /><br />But the fact is that acupuncture weight loss is not only a possibility, acupuncture weight loss has become a workable option for many people who have struggled with the battle of the bulge. <br /><br />For ease of Use, Medicomat is equipped with only a dual channel and two alternatives on the frequency and the amplitude control. The user is allowed either to follow the doctor's indication or refer to the treatment setting on the user's manual. Only by choosing the most suitable treatment setting can one looks after both healing and health care. <br /><br />Blurred vision refers to a lack of sharpness of vision resulting in the inability to see fine detail. Blurred vision may result from abnormalities present at birth such as near- or farsightedness that require corrective lenses or it may signal the presence of eye disease. <br /><br />According to auricular acupuncture practitioners, the ear is a microcosm for your entire body. There are points in your ear that connect to each major organ. There are several other micro-systems in your body including your hands and feet. <br /><br />Indications: Gastric and Intestinal diseases, Headache and insomnia, neurasthenia, Diabetes, Syndrome of agedness, Tracheitis and asthma, Pseudo myopia of teen-ages, glaucoma, presbyopia, cataract, Arthritis, frozen shoulder, cervical vertebra diseases, lumbar diapophysis, Prostatic hyperplasia, prostatitis, pharyngitis, rhinitis, laryngitis, gum inflammation, Cardiovascular and cerebrovascular diseases, Coronary heart disease, hypertension, arteriosclerosis, cerebral blood shortage, apoplexy, cerebral thrombus, Toothache, lumbago, gall bladder pain, woman's dysmenorrhea, sciatica, trigeminal neuralgia, facial paralysis. <br /><br />Medium frequency apply to promote blood circulation, unclog meridian and regular channels. Help cure cardiovascular and cerebrovascular barrier, reduce blood pressure and sugar, prevent stroke hemiplegic and cerebral thrombus. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f48a1084e24365d073bc50c900509524" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Acupuncture Skin Beauty Equipment<br/><br/>Psoriasis Natural Remedies and Medicomat Acupuncture Skin Beauty Equipment - Strengthening The Body Resistance. The first case is a lady with painful and irregular menstrual periods. She gets depressed and irritable, and when she gets angry the pain increases. The first thing to notice about this case is the connection between the cause, menstruation, and the symptoms, which are both physical (pain), mental (irritability), and emotional (anger). <br /><br />Some diseases are also associated with changes in the nails, which can include brittleness. The term onychoschizia refers to splitting of the fingernails as well as brittle or soft nails. Taking biotin (a vitamin) supplements can help in some cases of brittle nails, and application of moisturizers after soaking in water can also be of benefit. <br /><br />Acupressure is one of the oldest forms of alternative treatment. It consists of pressing certain points on the body or on the feet and hands. The goal of acupressure is to improve the flow of positive life energy known as chi. The basis of acupressure is that the body uses its own potential drug possession. Acupressure is one of the few alternative method that is scientifically potvdjena in treating some conditions. <br /><br />A depressive disorder is not the same as a passing blue mood and is more than a case of persistent sadness. Symptoms of depression also include feelings of worthlessness, hopelessness, guilt, lack of interest in daily activities, and even thoughts of suicide. <br /><br />LEKOMAT device for treatment of high blood pressure works on the principle of traditional Chinese medicine and bio-electricity of the human body. The device works independently and not require external power sources. Improved functioning of the cell body and improved micro-circulation strengthens the immune system and thus achieve the goal of curing high blood pressure. <br /><br />Many of us know about how acupuncture can relieve stress, deaden pain, and be used for other emotional or mental purposes. It is also very useful for a number of problems that women face, from menstrual problems up to the problem of infertility. We will look at a couple of examples to show that acupuncture can be an asset in each case. Of course, you will want to consult your individual acupuncture professional to determine the specific treatment for an individual case. <br /><br />This device works on the principle of traditional Chinese medicine and bio-electricity of the human body. Balancing the positive and negative charges in the man's body, it is possible to regulate the functions of the body and normalize cell protein synthesis and transfer processes. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c5c7503a8b00d8212a78f5487e2a5b01" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Detecting And Curing Machine<br/><br/>Sports Medicine Products and Medicomat Detecting And Curing Machine - Treatment Clinic Medicobot. Stress generally tenses up the body such that your body systems are in a degree of fight or flee. The full extent of fight or flee status would for example be, the state of your body systems when you see a car speeding towards you to run you over. At such a state some of your body systems nearly shut down to facilitate others. Blood moves away from abdominal area to skeletal muscles, there is increased heart beat, all to put you in a position to fight or flee. <br /><br />Auriculotherapy is considered one form of alternative medicine, which also includes acupuncture, chiropractic manipulation, homeopathy, and biofeedback. All of these techniques are also referred to as Complementary Medicine, in that they are not only an alternative to conventional Western medical treatments, they can serve as an additional procedure which complements the practice conventional medicine. <br /><br />Swelling of the eye refers to the presence of excess fluid (edema) in the connective tissues around the eye, most commonly the eyelids. A swollen eye can result from trauma, infections, or other injuries to the eye area. Virtually any cause of inflammation to the eye area may manifest as eyelid swelling, although allergic reactions are likely the most common cause. Rarely, systemic conditions may result in fluid retention, including fluid retention in the tissues around the eyes. <br /><br />Acupuncture is a therapy based on ancient Chinese philosophy, and was first described in 90 BC in the text written by Shih-chi. Acupuncture in translation means needle piercing - it's actually a very fine practice of inserting needles into the skin to stimulate specific points on the body (called acupuncture points). At first they were used needles made of stone, and later those of bronze, gold and silver, electric impulses and lasers. The points are stimulated depends on the symptoms, season, weather conditions and results of pulse checks. <br /><br />A bruise can sometimes be associated with a temporary raised area in the skin. When a bruise fades, it becomes green and brown as the body metabolizes the blood cells and bilirubin pigment in the skin. A bruise is best treated with local application of a cold pack immediately after injury. <br /><br />Many medical conditions can affect the shape or texture of the fingernails. Brittleness of the nails, meaning that the nails easily become cracked or chipped, can be observed as a sign of aging or in response to the long-term use of nail polish or exposure to moist conditions. <br /><br />LEKOMAT monitor for home treatment of headaches all the work alone, fully automatic, finds all the disturbances and automatically treat headaches and other ailments. It is particularly effective in diseases of the nervous system, bronchitis, asthma, allergies, stress. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="544d522f870cf771d44b98bb23618751" url=""><![CDATA[Low Frequency Therapy<br/><br/>Natural Stimulators and Medicomat Low Frequency Therapy - Home Appliance Medicobot Detects And Cure Disease. Auricular acupuncture, or ear acupuncture as it is more commonly known, is similar to body acupuncture but with ear acupuncture stimulation is only to the external ear. It is a method of treating a variety of physiological and psychological health problems by the stimulation of certain acupuncture points on the external ear. <br /><br />LEKOMAT device which he won in Brussels Eureka and Markonijevu medal for innovation, detects and cures the disease completely automatically using the principles of Chinese acupuncture and Japanese computer techniques. In a few minutes automatically reduces pain in the stomach, back, neck and legs. Treating poor circulation, headaches, migraines, depression, high blood pressure, rheumatism, spondylosis, sciatica. <br /><br />The record of acupuncture begins in China. Acupuncture has been performed for thousands of years in Asian countries. This practice involves using needles at specifics points on the body to alleviate specific symptoms. But besides this, there is also a more spiritual side to the process. The idea of yin and yang, or two opposing and complementary forces that work simultaneously is a big part of the medicine as well. <br /><br />Hypertension is typically caused by a disharmony of the Liver organ in Oriental Medicine. It is important to understand that this refers to an energetic function of the Liver and not necessarily the physical liver in the body. The Liver is responsible for the smooth flow of energy, called Qi, in the body, and the regulation of the Blood.The most typical patterns causing hypertension include: Liver Yang Rising, Liver Qi Stagnation, and Liver and Kidney Yin Deficiency. <br /><br />LEKOMAT monitor for home treatment of diseases of the heart, lungs, stomach and kidneys. The device does everything I was totally automatic, finds all the disturbances and automatically treat anxiety and other disorders. It cures headaches, migraines, depression, high blood pressure, poor circulation, vertigo, rheumatism, spondylosis, sciatica. <br /><br />The most common cause of a toothache is a dental cavity. The second most common cause is gum disease. Toothache can be caused by a problem that does not originate from a tooth or the jaw. <br /><br />In some cases, pain that originates in other sources (such as cardiac angina or problems with the teeth and/or jaws) can be experienced in the tongue, even though the tongue itself is normal. This is known as referred pain. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dde01b08d1bba021595c20b25f8dd9d" url=""><![CDATA[Acupuncture Needle Stimulation Device<br/><br/>Neuralgia Treatment Natural and Medicomat Acupuncture Needle Stimulation Device - Online Pharmacy Medicomat. From a western perspective acupuncture increases blood flow to speed healing, and stimulates hormonal changes such as increasing the bodies natural pain modulators (endorphins). Patients who receive Naloxone (an anecdote to morphine like drugs) do not respond to acupuncture’s pain-reducing effects. <br /><br />Pain in the neck can be more than just a hassle. Neck pain can come from disorders and diseases of any structure in the neck. There are seven vertebrae that are the bony building blocks of the spine in the neck (the cervical vertebrae) that surround the spinal cord and canal. Between these vertebrae are discs and nearby pass the nerves of the neck. Within the neck, structures include the neck muscles, arteries, veins, lymph glands, thyroid gland, parathyroid glands, esophagus, larynx, and trachea. <br /><br />Confusion is a change in mental status in which a person is not able to think with his or her usual level of clarity. Frequently, confusion leads to the loss of ability to recognize people and or places, or tell time and the date. Feelings of disorientation are common in confusion, and decision-making ability is impaired. <br /><br />According to auricular acupuncture practitioners, the ear is a microcosm for your entire body. There are points in your ear that connect to each major organ. There are several other micro-systems in your body including your hands and feet. <br /><br />Acupuncture is a traditional Chinese medicine used for over 2,000 years to treat a wide range of diseases. It is believed that specific acupuncture points on the skin associated with internal roads of life energy, qi and to stimulate these points encourages the free flow above the energy throughout the body. <br /><br />Golfers elbow is quite similar to tennis elbow except the inflammation occurs on the inside of the elbow, around the bone called the medial epicondyle. It too can be treated with acupuncture. Golfers elbow is also referred to as medial epicondylitis. The inner part of the elbow becomes painful and tender as a result of damage or tearing of the tendons and muscles of this area. <br /><br />A bruise is medically termed a contusion. Bruises are typically a result of some degree of injury to the blood vessels in the skin. Local leakage of blood into the skin from the capillaries that occurs spontaneously, without injury, results in a flat, purplish discolored area referred to as ecchymosis. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c9c34b2f1f7ccda4dfcefe34e08d6026" url=""><![CDATA[Eye Massager<br/><br/>Home Healthcare Machine and Medicomat Eye Massager - Lekomat Apparatus Cures Almost All. This form of electronic acupuncture is most commonly used with pain management and healing. It’s been proven to be especially effective in treating musculoskeletal pain, trauma, back pain and shoulder pain. It can also be helpful with conditions that involve the nerves, like multiple sclerosis. <br /><br />All headaches are considered primary headaches or secondary headaches. Primary headaches are not associated with other diseases. Examples of primary headaches are migraine headaches, tension headaches, and cluster headaches. Secondary headaches are caused by other diseases. The associated disease may be minor or major. <br /><br />The full effects of cosmetic acupuncture are visible only after three months, because the maturation of skin cells for three months - a positive skin changes do not happen overnight or after 2 treatments of acupuncture or other methods, but only when the superficial layers of the skin begin to appear healthier and better nourished skin cells. <br /><br />Insomnia is more likely to occur in females, people over 60 years of age, and people who have a history of depression, however, anyone can be affected by insomnia. Short-term insomnia may also occur as a side effect of certain medications. Chronic insomnia is more serious and may be caused or worsened by a variety of mental and physical problems. <br /><br />Ear acupuncture, is an acupuncture technique similar to reflexology, and is speculated that the technique works because groups of pluripotent cells contain information from the whole organism and create regional organization centers representing different parts of the body, through recruitment of more cortex cells dedicated to specific areas of the body. Thus stimulation of a reflex point in the ear can relieve symptoms of distant pathology with a reliable duration. <br /><br />When it comes to fertility, therefore, acupuncture is most likely to help those people who have a structurally sound reproductive system. In other words, all of the parts of the system are there and structurally sound, but for some reason they have functional problems. <br /><br />Pseudocyanosis is the appearance of cyanosis that is not associated with reduced oxygen delivery to tissues. Most causes are related to the ingestion of metals (such as silver or lead) or drugs/toxins. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f5803de07cc0741005f3804a7bf6b1a7" url=""><![CDATA[Healthcare At Home Apparatus<br/><br/>Anxiety Treatment Without Medication and Medicomat Healthcare At Home Apparatus - No Pain Lekomat. According to the theory of traditional Chinese medicine, human ear is just like a reverse foetus. Each human organ has its corresponding acupuncture point on the ear. When certain organ has pathological changes, the bioelectric current of the corresponding acupuncture point on the ear will change at an early stage. By detecting the bioelectric current pathological change, an early diagnosis can be done. <br /><br />Symptoms of dyspepsia originate from the upper gastrointestinal tract, primarily the stomach and first part of the small intestine. The symptoms most often are provoked by eating, which is a time when many different gastrointestinal functions are called upon to work in concert. If function is not normal, the symptoms of dyspepsia occur. <br /><br />As the tongue represents all the internal organs the ear represents the entire body. There are so many powerful healing points in the ear that one can easily treat effectively many health conditions especially the  5 combo point for PTSD, trauma, addictions (drugs, alcohol, nicotine, gambling), anxiety, BP issues, digestive, heart and lung, allergy conditions to name a few. The Shenman point is such a beautiful point to relax, de-stress and diminish pain. Bleeding certain points in the ear is often a great healing practice for many conditions. <br /><br />It is unclear how many people are affected with IBS. The incidence has been estimated anywhere between 5% and 65% of the general population. Women experience IBS far more than men. Acupuncture can assist in many of these cases. <br /><br />Blurred vision can also be a symptom of numerous conditions that do not directly involve the eye, such as migraine or stroke. A number of medications may also lead to temporary blurring of vision as a side effect. <br /><br />Cluster headaches are a rare but important type of primary headache, affecting mainly men. The average age of cluster headache sufferers is 28-30 years, although headaches may begin in childhood. <br /><br />Pleurisy is frequently associated with the accumulation of extra fluid in the space between the two layers of pleura. This fluid is referred to as a pleural effusion. Pleurisy is also referred to as pleuritis. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>