<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="b12ba6dff17d05354192c2ee063049d1" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Bad Education, Football Match online stream 11 Sep, 20<br/><br/><strong>Watch Bad Education, Football Match online stream 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 00:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy9iYWQtZWR1Y2F0aW9uL3dhdGNoLWJhZC1lZHVjYXRpb24tZm9vdGJhbGwtbWF0Y2gtbGl2ZS0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Bad Education Football Match<br />&lt;h3&gt;Bad Education - Football Match&lt;/h3&gt;<br />Date: Tuesday, September 11, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />Air time: 05:00 PM&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: BBC Three&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch &lt;b&gt;Bad Education&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Football Match&lt;/b&gt; Season 1 Episode 5 online. This tv show will be shown on BBC Three at 13 Aug 2012 05:00 PM. You must see this episode. Starring Charlie Wernham, Ethan Lawrence, Jack Binstead, Jack Whitehall, Kae Alexander, Layton Williams, Leila Hoffman, Matt Horne, Michelle Gomez, Nikki Runeckles, Sarah Solemani. Duration of this tv show is only 30 minutes. Alfie reveals a hidden talent when the annual football match between Abbey Grove and the school he attended, Middleton House, approaches. Will the benefit scroungers pull it off, or Middleton's snooty toff boys who clinch the win? &lt;b&gt;Bad Education&lt;/b&gt;, written by and starring Jack Whitehall, follows Alfie, the worst teacher ever to grace the British education system, and a bigger kid than his students.<br /><br />Despite his obvious shortcomings, Alfie's position at the school is stable thanks to Fraser, the school's headmaster, who tragically longs to be as cool as Alfie. He's the teacher who just wants to be everyone's 'best mate' and is prone to massive and very public mishaps.<br /><br />There's also Miss Gulliver, the school biology teacher and the apple of Alfie's eye. She cares deeply about the school and the students.<br /><br />Deputy headmistress Pickwell is less easy-going. She is an 'old school' teacher and can't stand her younger colleagues. She's a disciplinarian who wants Creationism put back on the syllabus and would prefer a school without children at all! I hope you can watch &lt;b&gt;Bad Education&lt;/b&gt; here, don't worry.&lt;/p&gt;<br />bad education movie imdb, bad education bbc 3 trailer, bad education almodovar autobiographical, bad education bbc3 cast, bad education imdb jack whitehall, watch bad education, watch bad education online megavideo, bad education almodovar synopsis, bad education bbc trailer, pedro almodovar bad education trailer<br />Bad Education, Football Match, stream, stream Bad Education, watch Bad Education Football Match<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy9iYWQtZWR1Y2F0aW9uL3dhdGNoLWJhZC1lZHVjYXRpb24tZm9vdGJhbGwtbWF0Y2gtbGl2ZS0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Ftv-show%2Fbad-education%2Fwatch-bad-education-football-match-live-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/tv-show/bad-education/watch-bad-education-football-match-live-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e39c3d6a153ceb0dc0aae6cbf762f44b" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Portugal vs Azerbaijan online 11 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Watch Portugal vs Azerbaijan online 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-11 22:15:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vc29jY2VyL3dvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0LXdvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0L2xpdmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLXBvcnR1Z2FsLXZzLWF6ZXJiYWlqYW4uaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Portugal vs Azerbaijan<br />&lt;h3&gt;Watch Portugal vs Azerbaijan streaming&lt;/h3&gt;<br />&lt;h4&gt;World Cup 2014, World Cup 2014&lt;/h4&gt;<br />Date: Tuesday, Sep 11, 2012, Location: Estadio AXA&lt;br&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />Watch live &lt;b&gt;Portugal&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Azerbaijan&lt;/b&gt; stream. World Cup 2014 match start time Tuesday, September 11, 2012 10:15 PM. Location is Estadio AXA. Where to watch &lt;b&gt;Portugal&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Azerbaijan&lt;/b&gt; live stream TV online? Maybe this match will be available on justin tv or ustream, freedocast or veetle, veemi, or vshare tv. You can also try to watch free live TV &lt;b&gt;Portugal&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Azerbaijan&lt;/b&gt; online on MyP2P using sopcast or tvants in your PC. Enjoy football schedule in World Cup 2014 that will provide you the best sports broadcast TV online. Are you a fans ? Surely you don't want to miss to watch this football match between &lt;b&gt;Portugal&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Azerbaijan&lt;/b&gt;<br />Portugal VS Azerbaijan streaming, live Portugal VS Azerbaijan streaming, Portugal VS Azerbaijan live streaming, Portugal VS Azerbaijan live stream, streaming Portugal VS Azerbaijan<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vc29jY2VyL3dvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0LXdvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0L2xpdmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLXBvcnR1Z2FsLXZzLWF6ZXJiYWlqYW4uaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Fsoccer%2Fworld-cup-2014-world-cup-2014%2Flive-streaming-portugal-vs-azerbaijan.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/soccer/world-cup-2014-world-cup-2014/live-streaming-portugal-vs-azerbaijan.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5d1d44cf2bbdbd76db9e7f44511627da" url=""><![CDATA[Watch The Amazing World of Gumball, The Flower online stream<br/><br/><strong>Watch The Amazing World of Gumball, The Flower online streaming 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 02:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy90aGUtYW1hemluZy13b3JsZC1vZi1ndW1iYWxsL3N0cmVhbS1vbmxpbmUtdGhlLWFtYXppbmctd29ybGQtb2YtZ3VtYmFsbC10aGUtZmxvd2VyLTExLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />The Amazing World of Gumball The Flower<br />&lt;h3&gt;The Amazing World of Gumball - The Flower&lt;/h3&gt;<br />Date: 11 September, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />Air time: 07:00 PM&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: Cartoon Network&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch online &lt;b&gt;The Amazing World of Gumball&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;The Flower&lt;/b&gt; S2E5. Will be shown on Cartoon Network at Monday, May 02, 2011 05:00 PM. Remember the aired date guys. You must see this tv episode. Duration of this episode is 20 minutes. Gumball is jealous when he sees Leslie with Penny. Meet the Wattersons: Mom, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball! He's a twelve-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure. It's &lt;b&gt;The Amazing World of Gumball&lt;/b&gt;. Are you a fans? Surely you don't want to miss to watch this tv episode.&lt;/p&gt;<br />the amazing world of gumball episodes full, the amazing world of gumball episodes download, the amazing world of gumball full episodes, the amazing world of gumball episodes dailymotion, watch the amazing world of gumball episode 19, the amazing world of gumball the meddler, the amazing world of gumball season 2 promo, the amazing world of gumball live, the amazing world of gumball episodes the date, the amazing world of gumball full episodes the dvd<br />The Amazing World of Gumball, The Flower, watch, watch The Amazing World of Gumball, streaming The Amazing World of Gumball The Flower<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy90aGUtYW1hemluZy13b3JsZC1vZi1ndW1iYWxsL3N0cmVhbS1vbmxpbmUtdGhlLWFtYXppbmctd29ybGQtb2YtZ3VtYmFsbC10aGUtZmxvd2VyLTExLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Ftv-show%2Fthe-amazing-world-of-gumball%2Fstream-online-the-amazing-world-of-gumball-the-flower-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/tv-show/the-amazing-world-of-gumball/stream-online-the-amazing-world-of-gumball-the-flower-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7574e0f38070fc82752affedcd3a7106" url=""><![CDATA[Stream online Switzerland vs Albania<br/><br/><strong>Stream online Switzerland vs Albania</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-11 21:30:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3NvY2Nlci93b3JsZC1jdXAtMjAxNC13b3JsZC1jdXAtMjAxNC9saXZlLXN0cmVhbS1zd2l0emVybGFuZC12cy1hbGJhbmlhLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Switzerland vs Albania<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch Switzerland vs Albania&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Match date: Tuesday, Sep 11, 2012 , Location: Swissporarena Luzern Stadion&lt;br&gt;<br />World Cup 2014, World Cup 2014&lt;br&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />Watch &lt;b&gt;Switzerland&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Albania&lt;/b&gt; on local tv. World Cup 2014 match between &lt;b&gt;Switzerland&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Albania&lt;/b&gt; scheduled on Tuesday, September 11, 2012 09:30 PM and will be live at Swissporarena Luzern Stadion. Where to watch &lt;b&gt;Switzerland&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Albania&lt;/b&gt; World Cup 2014 football match TV online ? Maybe this match will be available on justin tv or ustream, freedocast or veetle, veemi, or vshare tv. Enjoy football schedule in World Cup 2014 that will provide you the best sports broadcast TV online. We will post results of this match, as soon as posible.. stay tuned.<br />Switzerland VS Albania streaming, live Switzerland VS Albania streaming, Switzerland VS Albania live streaming, Switzerland VS Albania live stream, streaming Switzerland VS Albania, Switzerland VS Albania stream, stream Switzerland VS Albania<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3NvY2Nlci93b3JsZC1jdXAtMjAxNC13b3JsZC1jdXAtMjAxNC9saXZlLXN0cmVhbS1zd2l0emVybGFuZC12cy1hbGJhbmlhLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fentrancemagazine.com%2Fsoccer%2Fworld-cup-2014-world-cup-2014%2Flive-stream-switzerland-vs-albania.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://entrancemagazine.com/soccer/world-cup-2014-world-cup-2014/live-stream-switzerland-vs-albania.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="41ba70fee53443f6ebb5fe7865c2f617" url=""><![CDATA[Watch CR Vasco da Gama vs Palmeiras live 12 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Watch CR Vasco da Gama vs Palmeiras live 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 04:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3NvY2Nlci9icmF6aWwtY2FtcGVvbmF0by1icmFzaWxlaXJvL3dhdGNoLXN0cmVhbS1jci12YXNjby1kYS1nYW1hLXZzLXBhbG1laXJhcy0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />CR Vasco da Gama vs Palmeiras<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch CR Vasco da Gama vs Palmeiras&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Match date: Wednesday, Sep 12, 2012 , Location: São Januário&lt;br&gt;<br />Campeonato Brasileiro, Brazil&lt;br&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />Watch Vasco da Gama vs &lt;b&gt;Palmeiras&lt;/b&gt; online stream. Campeonato Brasileiro match start time Wednesday, September 12, 2012 04:00 AM. Location is São Januário. In the last 15 home matches, Vasco da Gama has scored 31 points. Vasco da Gama won in 9 home matches, 4 home matches played in a draw, and 2 home matches has been losers. &lt;b&gt;Palmeiras&lt;/b&gt; has scored 26 points in the last 21 games. Average 0.87 points per game. Won in 6 matches, 8 matches played in a draw, and 16 matches &lt;b&gt;Palmeiras&lt;/b&gt; losers. It is difficult to predict the winner of this match. Maybe Vasco da Gama has a little chance to win this match. Where to watch Vasco da Gama vs &lt;b&gt;Palmeiras&lt;/b&gt; live stream TV online? Maybe this match will be available on justin tv or ustream. Enjoy football schedule in Campeonato Brasileiro that will provide you the best sports broadcast TV online. So guys, never miss it! Watch Vasco da Gama vs &lt;b&gt;Palmeiras&lt;/b&gt; according to the schedule mentioned impressions..<br />CR Vasco da Gama VS Palmeiras streaming, live CR Vasco da Gama VS Palmeiras streaming, CR Vasco da Gama VS Palmeiras live streaming, CR Vasco da Gama VS Palmeiras live stream, streaming CR Vasco da Gama VS Palmeiras, CR Vasco da Gama VS Palmeiras stream, <br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3NvY2Nlci9icmF6aWwtY2FtcGVvbmF0by1icmFzaWxlaXJvL3dhdGNoLXN0cmVhbS1jci12YXNjby1kYS1nYW1hLXZzLXBhbG1laXJhcy0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fentrancemagazine.com%2Fsoccer%2Fbrazil-campeonato-brasileiro%2Fwatch-stream-cr-vasco-da-gama-vs-palmeiras-12-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://entrancemagazine.com/soccer/brazil-campeonato-brasileiro/watch-stream-cr-vasco-da-gama-vs-palmeiras-12-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8afa637aec3ecc66756b93e991d4a3fd" url=""><![CDATA[Streaming online Teen Mom, Series Finale Special: Check Up W<br/><br/><strong>Streaming online Teen Mom, Series Finale Special: Check Up With Dr. Drew Part 2 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 05:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy90ZWVuLW1vbS93YXRjaC1vbmxpbmUtdGVlbi1tb20tc2VyaWVzLWZpbmFsZS1zcGVjaWFsLWNoZWNrLXVwLXdpdGgtZHItZHJldy1wYXJ0LTItMTEtc2VwLTIwMTIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Teen Mom Series Finale Special: Check Up With Dr. Drew Part 2<br />&lt;h3&gt;Teen Mom - Series Finale Special: Check Up With Dr. Drew Part 2&lt;/h3&gt;<br />Date: Tuesday, Sep 11, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />Air time: 10:00 PM&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: MTV&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch &lt;b&gt;Teen Mom&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Series Finale Special: Check Up With Dr. Drew Part 2&lt;/b&gt; Season 4 Episode 14. This tv show will be shown on MTV at Fri, March 12, 2010 05:00 PM. Duration of this tv show is 20 minutes. A spin-off of the MTV documentary series '16 and Pregnant'. The show follows the stories of four girls from the first season of '16 and Pregnant' and documents the challenges of their first years of motherhood. <br /><br />Each episode interweaves stories of four teenage girls who are navigating the bumpy terrain of adolescence, growing pains, and coming of age - all while facing the responsibility of being a young mother.<br /><br />Each story offers a unique look into the wide variety of challenges young mothers can face: marriage, relationships, family support, or lack thereof, adoption, finances, rumors among the community, graduating high school, starting college, getting (or losing) a job and the daunting and exciting step of moving out of the nest to create their own families Okay guys, don't miss this episode, because it will be very good and full of interesting entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;<br />watch teen mom season 4 episode 2, teen mom 2 season 3 trailer, teen mom season 4 episode 6, teen mom news amber, teen mom jenelle arrested, teen mom maci, teen mom 2 jenelle fight, teen mom season 4 episode 7, teen mom news farrah, teen mom jenelle evans<br />Teen Mom, Series Finale Special: Check Up With Dr. Drew Part 2, live, live Teen Mom, watch Teen Mom Series Finale Special: Check Up With Dr. Drew Part 2<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy90ZWVuLW1vbS93YXRjaC1vbmxpbmUtdGVlbi1tb20tc2VyaWVzLWZpbmFsZS1zcGVjaWFsLWNoZWNrLXVwLXdpdGgtZHItZHJldy1wYXJ0LTItMTEtc2VwLTIwMTIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Ftv-show%2Fteen-mom%2Fwatch-online-teen-mom-series-finale-special-check-up-with-dr-drew-part-2-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/tv-show/teen-mom/watch-online-teen-mom-series-finale-special-check-up-with-dr-drew-part-2-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d4fd7ba7b984d7d26149659f484a6d43" url=""><![CDATA[Stream online San Marino vs Montenegro 11 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Stream online San Marino vs Montenegro 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-11 21:30:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3NvY2Nlci93b3JsZC1jdXAtMjAxNC13b3JsZC1jdXAtMjAxNC93YXRjaC1saXZlLXNhbi1tYXJpbm8tdnMtbW9udGVuZWdyby5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />San Marino vs Montenegro<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch San Marino vs Montenegro&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Match date: 11 September, 2012 , Location: Stadio Olimpico Serravalle&lt;br&gt;<br />World Cup 2014, World Cup 2014&lt;br&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />Live streaming watch &lt;b&gt;San Marino&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Montenegro&lt;/b&gt;. World Cup 2014 - match start time Tuesday, Sep 11, 2012 09:30 PM at Stadio Olimpico Serravalle. Where to watch &lt;b&gt;San Marino&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Montenegro&lt;/b&gt; live stream TV online? Maybe this match will be available on justin tv or ustream, freedocast or veetle, veemi, or vshare tv. You can also try to watch free live TV &lt;b&gt;San Marino&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Montenegro&lt;/b&gt; online on MyP2P using sopcast or tvants in your PC. Enjoy football schedule in World Cup 2014 that will provide you the best sports broadcast TV online. We will try to get live video update early and absolutely no survey. Summary of the match &lt;b&gt;San Marino&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Montenegro&lt;/b&gt; will be on site soon..<br />San Marino VS Montenegro streaming, live San Marino VS Montenegro streaming, San Marino VS Montenegro live streaming, San Marino VS Montenegro live stream, streaming San Marino VS Montenegro, San Marino VS Montenegro stream, stream San Marino VS Montenegr<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3NvY2Nlci93b3JsZC1jdXAtMjAxNC13b3JsZC1jdXAtMjAxNC93YXRjaC1saXZlLXNhbi1tYXJpbm8tdnMtbW9udGVuZWdyby5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fentrancemagazine.com%2Fsoccer%2Fworld-cup-2014-world-cup-2014%2Fwatch-live-san-marino-vs-montenegro.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://entrancemagazine.com/soccer/world-cup-2014-world-cup-2014/watch-live-san-marino-vs-montenegro.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="caf974a752c2cd619ac340e0d6ec18be" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Toronto FC vs Chicago stream online 12 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Watch Toronto FC vs Chicago stream online 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 02:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L3VzYS1tYWpvci1sZWFndWUtc29jY2VyL3dhdGNoLWxpdmUtdG9yb250by1mYy12cy1jaGljYWdvLXN0cmVhbS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG0_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Toronto FC vs Chicago<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch Toronto FC vs Chicago&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Match date: Wednesday, Sep 12, 2012 , Location: BMO Field&lt;br&gt;<br />Major League Soccer, USA&lt;br&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />Watch stream &lt;b&gt;Toronto FC&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Chicago&lt;/b&gt; Fire on internet tv. Major League Soccer - match start time 12 September, 2012 02:00 AM. Location is BMO Field. In the last 15 home matches, &lt;b&gt;Toronto FC&lt;/b&gt; has scored 14 points. Won in 3 home matches, 5 home matches played in a draw, and 7 home matches &lt;b&gt;Toronto FC&lt;/b&gt; losers. &lt;b&gt;Chicago&lt;/b&gt; Fire has scored 51 points in the last 40 games. Average 1.70 points per game. Won in 15 matches, 6 matches played in a draw, and 9 matches &lt;b&gt;Chicago&lt;/b&gt; Fire losers. In our opinion &lt;b&gt;Chicago&lt;/b&gt; Fire has have a good chance of victory in this match. Unfortunately &lt;b&gt;Toronto FC&lt;/b&gt; maybe loser. Where to watch &lt;b&gt;Toronto FC&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Chicago&lt;/b&gt; Fire live stream TV online? Maybe this match will be available on justin tv or ustream. Enjoy football schedule in Major League Soccer that will provide you the best sports broadcast TV online. We will post live score and results of this match, as soon as posible.. stay tuned.<br />Toronto FC VS Chicago streaming, live Toronto FC VS Chicago streaming, Toronto FC VS Chicago live streaming, Toronto FC VS Chicago live stream, streaming Toronto FC VS Chicago, Toronto FC VS Chicago stream<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L3VzYS1tYWpvci1sZWFndWUtc29jY2VyL3dhdGNoLWxpdmUtdG9yb250by1mYy12cy1jaGljYWdvLXN0cmVhbS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG0_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdixiewitch.net%2Fusa-major-league-soccer%2Fwatch-live-toronto-fc-vs-chicago-stream-12-sep-2012.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dixiewitch.net/usa-major-league-soccer/watch-live-toronto-fc-vs-chicago-stream-12-sep-2012.htm</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4f521c966b3e40eda31a1d20a3cddafb" url=""><![CDATA[Watch stream Greece vs Lithuania 11 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Watch stream Greece vs Lithuania 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-11 21:45:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vc29jY2VyL3dvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0LXdvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0L3N0cmVhbS1vbmxpbmUtZ3JlZWNlLXZzLWxpdGh1YW5pYS0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Greece vs Lithuania<br />&lt;h3&gt;Watch Greece vs Lithuania streaming&lt;/h3&gt;<br />&lt;h4&gt;World Cup 2014, World Cup 2014&lt;/h4&gt;<br />Date: Tuesday, 11 September, 2012, Location: Karaiskakis Stadium&lt;br&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />Watch stream &lt;b&gt;Greece&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Lithuania&lt;/b&gt; on local tv. World Cup 2014 match between &lt;b&gt;Greece&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Lithuania&lt;/b&gt; scheduled on 11 September, 2012 09:45 PM and will be live at Karaiskakis Stadium. Where to watch &lt;b&gt;Greece&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Lithuania&lt;/b&gt; World Cup 2014 football match TV online ? Maybe this match will be available on justin tv or ustream, freedocast or veetle, veemi, or vshare tv.  We will try to get live video update early and absolutely no survey. Results and goal's highlights, will be available soon.. stay tuned.<br />Greece VS Lithuania streaming, live Greece VS Lithuania streaming, Greece VS Lithuania live streaming, Greece VS Lithuania live stream, streaming Greece VS Lithuania, Greece VS Lithuania stream, stream Greece VS Lithuania, live streaming Greece VS Lithuan<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vc29jY2VyL3dvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0LXdvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0L3N0cmVhbS1vbmxpbmUtZ3JlZWNlLXZzLWxpdGh1YW5pYS0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Fsoccer%2Fworld-cup-2014-world-cup-2014%2Fstream-online-greece-vs-lithuania-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/soccer/world-cup-2014-world-cup-2014/stream-online-greece-vs-lithuania-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5a9cfcdbe41263152a07fdf5dc8b1c48" url=""><![CDATA[Watch The Week the Women Went, Hug O' War live stream 11 S<br/><br/><strong>Watch The Week the Women Went, Hug O' War  live stream 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 05:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3R2LXNob3dzL3RoZS13ZWVrLXRoZS13b21lbi13ZW50L3N0cmVhbS1saXZlLXRoZS13ZWVrLXRoZS13b21lbi13ZW50LWh1Zy1vLXdhci0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />The Week the Women Went Hug O' War <br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch The Week the Women Went - Hug O' War &lt;/h2&gt;<br />Air date: 10:00 pm, Tuesday, September 11, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: Lifetime&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch &lt;b&gt;The Week the Women Went&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Hug O' War &lt;/b&gt; S1E5 online stream. This show will be aired on Lifetime at Monday, August 13, 2012 05:00 PM. Remember the aired date guys. You must see this episode. Only 60 is running time of this show. Can you imagine a world without women? Which gender is more capable of running society's day-to-day functions? What impact is today's shift in gender roles having on the world? Lifetime dives deep into the gender gap issue to answer these questions by bringing a daring social experiment to life by removing the women from one American town in the major program event, &quot;&lt;b&gt;The Week the Women Went&lt;/b&gt;&quot;. Originally scheduled to premiere on Lifetime on June 6, the unscripted series which explores modern gender roles and finds out what happens when all of the women leave town, leaving the remaining men to run their households, businesses and community on their own, will now air in August. Lifetime will announce a new airdate shortly. (Source: Lifetime TV)<br /> If you're one of &lt;b&gt;The Week the Women Went&lt;/b&gt; fans, don't miss it this episode. the week the women went 2012, live the week the women went, watch the week the women went season 2, the week the women went tatamagouche cast, the week the women went lifetime 2012, the week the women went away, watch the week the women went, the week the women went yemassee sc, the week the women went bbc, the week the women went&lt;/p&gt;<br />The Week the Women Went, Hug O' War , watch, watch The Week the Women Went, streaming The Week the Women Went Hug O' War<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3R2LXNob3dzL3RoZS13ZWVrLXRoZS13b21lbi13ZW50L3N0cmVhbS1saXZlLXRoZS13ZWVrLXRoZS13b21lbi13ZW50LWh1Zy1vLXdhci0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fentrancemagazine.com%2Ftv-shows%2Fthe-week-the-women-went%2Fstream-live-the-week-the-women-went-hug-o-war-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://entrancemagazine.com/tv-shows/the-week-the-women-went/stream-live-the-week-the-women-went-hug-o-war-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e882378f0fee4ff4611d6cb25fd14061" url=""><![CDATA[Live stream Bosnia-Herzegovina vs Latvia<br/><br/><strong>Live stream Bosnia-Herzegovina vs Latvia</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-11 21:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vc29jY2VyL3dvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0LXdvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0L2xpdmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLWJvc25pYS1oZXJ6ZWdvdmluYS12cy1sYXR2aWEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Bosnia-Herzegovina vs Latvia<br />&lt;h3&gt;Watch Bosnia-Herzegovina vs Latvia streaming&lt;/h3&gt;<br />&lt;h4&gt;World Cup 2014, World Cup 2014&lt;/h4&gt;<br />Date: Tue, September 11, 2012, Location: Bilino Polje&lt;br&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />Watch live &lt;b&gt;Bosnia-Herzegovina&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Latvia&lt;/b&gt;. World Cup 2014 - match start time 11 Sep 2012 09:00 PM. Location is Bilino Polje. Where to watch &lt;b&gt;Bosnia-Herzegovina&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Latvia&lt;/b&gt; live stream free TV online on 11 Sep 2012 09:00 PM ? The video live feed is available on justin tv or ustream, freedocast or veetle, veemi, or vshare tv. You can also watch free live TV &lt;b&gt;Bosnia-Herzegovina&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Latvia&lt;/b&gt; online on MyP2P using sopcast or tvants in your PC. Enjoy football schedule in World Cup 2014 that will provide you the best sports broadcast TV online. We will try to get live video update early and absolutely no survey. Okay guys, don't miss this football match between &lt;b&gt;Bosnia-Herzegovina&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Latvia&lt;/b&gt;<br />Bosnia-Herzegovina VS Latvia streaming, live Bosnia-Herzegovina VS Latvia streaming, Bosnia-Herzegovina VS Latvia live streaming, Bosnia-Herzegovina VS Latvia live stream, streaming Bosnia-Herzegovina VS Latvia<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vc29jY2VyL3dvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0LXdvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0L2xpdmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLWJvc25pYS1oZXJ6ZWdvdmluYS12cy1sYXR2aWEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Fsoccer%2Fworld-cup-2014-world-cup-2014%2Flive-streaming-bosnia-herzegovina-vs-latvia.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/soccer/world-cup-2014-world-cup-2014/live-streaming-bosnia-herzegovina-vs-latvia.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="def8c0e0141345085f427c1d71cf0a2" url=""><![CDATA[Watch live Collection Intervention, Yabba Dabba Don't! 11 S<br/><br/><strong>Watch live Collection Intervention, Yabba Dabba Don't! 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 05:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3R2LXNob3dzL2NvbGxlY3Rpb24taW50ZXJ2ZW50aW9uL3dhdGNoLWNvbGxlY3Rpb24taW50ZXJ2ZW50aW9uLXlhYmJhLWRhYmJhLWRvbnQtb25saW5lLXN0cmVhbWluZy0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Collection Intervention Yabba Dabba Don't!<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch Collection Intervention - Yabba Dabba Don't!&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Air date: 10:00 pm, Tuesday, Sep 11, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: Syfy&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch stream &lt;b&gt;Collection Intervention&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Yabba Dabba Don't!&lt;/b&gt; Season 1 Episode 6 on local tv. Will be shown on Syfy at Mon, August 13, 2012 05:00 PM. You must see this episode. Remember the aired date guys. Duration of this tv show is only 60 minutes. In Syfy's newest reality series, &lt;b&gt;Collection Intervention&lt;/b&gt;, premiering Tuesday, August 14 at 10PM (ET/PT), former Head of Special Collections at Christie's Elyse Luray helps couples, families and individuals whose pop-culture memorabilia collections - from Star Wars and Battlestar Galactica to Catwoman and Barbie - have become damaging obsessions, creating financial strife and a huge strain on their lives. In each of the six hour-long episodes, Elyse will create a strategy that helps these collectors curate and showcase their collection by assessing where the true value lies and then allow them to decide what's worth keeping and what they can sell. These massive collections include dining rooms stuffed with 30,000 comic books, a garage filled to the rafters with Catwoman memorabilia, and an almost uninhabitable house filled with Transformers. For each collector, parting with some of their collection may free up some much needed space in their home, provide a cash windfall to get out of debt, or even just allow a couple to become more focused on their relationship. Okay guys, don't miss this Reality episode, because it will be very good and full of interesting entertainment. live collection intervention, collection intervention tv show, watch collection intervention, collection intervention preview, collection intervention, collection intervention host, collection intervention wiki, collection intervention syfy host, collection intervention on syfy, collection intervention syfy trailer&lt;/p&gt;<br />Collection Intervention, Yabba Dabba Don't!, streaming, streaming Collection Intervention, watch Collection Intervention Yabba Dabba Don't!<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3R2LXNob3dzL2NvbGxlY3Rpb24taW50ZXJ2ZW50aW9uL3dhdGNoLWNvbGxlY3Rpb24taW50ZXJ2ZW50aW9uLXlhYmJhLWRhYmJhLWRvbnQtb25saW5lLXN0cmVhbWluZy0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fentrancemagazine.com%2Ftv-shows%2Fcollection-intervention%2Fwatch-collection-intervention-yabba-dabba-dont-online-streaming-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://entrancemagazine.com/tv-shows/collection-intervention/watch-collection-intervention-yabba-dabba-dont-online-streaming-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8eeb1d39222331962d0e6a02190fcaa7" url=""><![CDATA[Stream Italy vs Malta 11 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Stream Italy vs Malta 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-11 21:45:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vc29jY2VyL3dvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0LXdvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0L3dhdGNoLWl0YWx5LXZzLW1hbHRhLXN0cmVhbS0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Italy vs Malta<br />&lt;h3&gt;Watch Italy vs Malta streaming&lt;/h3&gt;<br />&lt;h4&gt;World Cup 2014, World Cup 2014&lt;/h4&gt;<br />Date: Tuesday, 11 September, 2012, Location: Alberto Braglia&lt;br&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />Watch online &lt;b&gt;Italy&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Malta&lt;/b&gt;. World Cup 2014 match between &lt;b&gt;Italy&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Malta&lt;/b&gt; scheduled on Tuesday, 11 September, 2012 09:45 PM and will be live at Alberto Braglia. Where to watch &lt;b&gt;Italy&lt;/b&gt; vs &lt;b&gt;Malta&lt;/b&gt; World Cup 2014 football match TV online ? Maybe this match will be available on justin tv or ustream, freedocast or veetle, veemi, or vshare tv. Enjoy football schedule in World Cup 2014 that will provide you the best sports broadcast TV online. Results and goal's highlights, will be available soon.. stay tuned.<br />Italy VS Malta streaming, live Italy VS Malta streaming, Italy VS Malta live streaming, Italy VS Malta live stream, streaming Italy VS Malta, Italy VS Malta stream<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vc29jY2VyL3dvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0LXdvcmxkLWN1cC0yMDE0L3dhdGNoLWl0YWx5LXZzLW1hbHRhLXN0cmVhbS0xMS1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Fsoccer%2Fworld-cup-2014-world-cup-2014%2Fwatch-italy-vs-malta-stream-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/soccer/world-cup-2014-world-cup-2014/watch-italy-vs-malta-stream-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="873b68e722a337c939219371b041381a" url=""><![CDATA[Watch online The New Normal, Pilot 11 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Watch online The New Normal, Pilot 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 04:30:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy90aGUtbmV3LW5vcm1hbC93YXRjaC10aGUtbmV3LW5vcm1hbC1waWxvdC1saXZlLXR2LTExLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />The New Normal Pilot<br />&lt;h3&gt;The New Normal - Pilot&lt;/h3&gt;<br />Date: Tuesday, 11 September, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />Air time: 09:30 PM&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: NBC&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch stream &lt;b&gt;The New Normal&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Pilot&lt;/b&gt; S1E1 on internet tv. This show will be aired on NBC at Sun, September 09, 2012 05:00 PM. Only 30 is running time of this tv serie. Starring Andrew Rannells, Bebe Wood, Ellen Barkin, Georgia King, Justin Bartha, NeNe Leakes. A gay couple start a family with the help of a young single mother who becomes their surrogate. These days, families come in all forms - single dads, double moms, sperm donors, egg donors, one-night-stand donors... It's 2012 and anything goes.<br /><br />Bryan and David are a Beverly Hills couple and they have it all. Well, almost. With successful careers and a committed and loving partnership, the one thing missing is a baby. And just when they think the stars will never align, enter Goldie, an extraordinary young woman with a checkered past. A Midwestern waitress and single mother looking to escape her dead-end life and small-minded grandmother, Goldie decides to change everything and move to L.A. with her precocious eight-year-old daughter. Desperate and broke - but also fertile - Goldie quickly becomes the guys' surrogate and quite possibly the girl of their dreams. Surrogate mother, surrogate family. Okay guys, don't miss this Comedy tv episode, because it will be very good and full of interesting entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;<br />the new normal extended trailer, live the new normal, the new normal pilot, the new normal show cast, the new normal pilot cast, the new normal trailer youtube, watch the new normal pilot, the new normal tv show nene leakes, watch the new normal megavideo, watch different is the new normal online<br />The New Normal, Pilot, live, live The New Normal, streaming The New Normal Pilot<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy90aGUtbmV3LW5vcm1hbC93YXRjaC10aGUtbmV3LW5vcm1hbC1waWxvdC1saXZlLXR2LTExLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Ftv-show%2Fthe-new-normal%2Fwatch-the-new-normal-pilot-live-tv-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/tv-show/the-new-normal/watch-the-new-normal-pilot-live-tv-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e57142c55a96e43b1b6494cadcba59ea" url=""><![CDATA[Streaming online Chopped, A Bunny Thing Happened 11 Sep, 201<br/><br/><strong>Streaming online Chopped, A Bunny Thing Happened 11 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 05:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy9jaG9wcGVkL3dhdGNoLWNob3BwZWQtYS1idW5ueS10aGluZy1oYXBwZW5lZC1vbmxpbmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLTExLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Chopped A Bunny Thing Happened<br />&lt;h3&gt;Chopped - A Bunny Thing Happened&lt;/h3&gt;<br />Date: Tuesday, 11 September, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />Air time: 10:00 pm&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: Food Network&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch stream &lt;b&gt;Chopped&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;A Bunny Thing Happened&lt;/b&gt; Season 13 Episode 2 on tv. Will be shown on Food Network at 12 January, 2009 05:00 PM. Remember the aired date guys. You must see this tv episode. Only 45 is running time of this tv episode. Starring Aaron Sanchez, Alex Guarnaschelli, Amanda Freitag, Chris Santos, Geoffrey Zakarian, Marc Murphy, Scott Conant, Ted Allen. A pink candy surprise in the appetizer basket prompts the chefs to make some very creative choices. Then in the entree round, the chefs have to hop to it with a chocolate bunny and an imposing cut of meat as ingredients. A sweet baked good seems like a good start for some delicious desserts, but will the chefs' final dishes be inventive enough to impress the judges? Hosted by Ted Allen, &lt;b&gt;Chopped&lt;/b&gt; is a high energy, fast paced cooking competition that challenges four up-and-coming chefs to turn a selection of everyday ingredients into an extraordinary three-course meal. After each course, a contestant gets &quot;chopped&quot; by our panel of esteemed culinary luminaries until the last man or woman left standing claims victory. This is going to be an exciting episode. Never miss it!&lt;/p&gt;<br />mercy chopped and screwed mp3, chopped and screwed mp3 downloads, watch chopped grill masters part 3, chopped all stars season 1, chopped salad nyc, chopped salad portillos, chopped and screwed lyrics ft ludacris, chopped salad calories, chopped salad ingredients, watch full episodes chopped online free<br />&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;<br />Chopped, A Bunny Thing Happened, live, live Chopped, stream Chopped A Bunny Thing Happened<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy9jaG9wcGVkL3dhdGNoLWNob3BwZWQtYS1idW5ueS10aGluZy1oYXBwZW5lZC1vbmxpbmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLTExLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Ftv-show%2Fchopped%2Fwatch-chopped-a-bunny-thing-happened-online-streaming-11-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/tv-show/chopped/watch-chopped-a-bunny-thing-happened-online-streaming-11-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dc6899e2dd4f1afc44cbf84738f5704b" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Class of 3000, The Hunt for Red Blobtober live 12 Sep,<br/><br/><strong>Watch Class of 3000, The Hunt for Red Blobtober live 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 14:30:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3R2LXNob3dzL2NsYXNzLW9mLTMwMDAvd2F0Y2gtY2xhc3Mtb2YtMzAwMC10aGUtaHVudC1mb3ItcmVkLWJsb2J0b2Jlci1vbmxpbmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLTEyLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Class of 3000 The Hunt for Red Blobtober<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch Class of 3000 - The Hunt for Red Blobtober&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Air date: 07:30 am, Wednesday, Sep 12, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: Cartoon Network&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch &lt;b&gt;Class of 3000&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;The Hunt for Red Blobtober&lt;/b&gt; Season 1 Episode 5 on local tv. Will be aired on Cartoon Network at Thu, November 02, 2006 05:00 PM. Remember the aired date guys. Only 25 is running time of this tv serie. The Westley kids stumble upon Sunny's old school yearbook and mistake his years in a funk band for a tour of duty as a pirate. They find a treasure map that leads to a cave where they awaken and unleash a toxic Sloppy Joe blob. Sunny himself has a connection to the blob and he and the kids must work together to save the day. &lt;b&gt;Class of 3000&lt;/b&gt; is an American animated television series on Cartoon Network that was created by, was executively produced by, and starred André 3000 of the Hip Hop group OutKast as superstar and music teacher Sunny Bridges, set at Atlanta, Georgia's Westley School of Performing Arts. Are you a fans? Surely you don't want to miss to watch this tv show. watch class of 3000 episodes online free, live class of 3000, class of 3000 episode 1 free, watch full episodes of class of 3000 online, class of 3000 cartoon network games, watch class of 3000 online free, list of class of 3000 songs, class of 3000 episode 1 english, class of 3000 episode 1 megavideo, class of 3000 music volume one&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;<br />Class of 3000, The Hunt for Red Blobtober, streaming, streaming Class of 3000, watch Class of 3000 The Hunt for Red Blobtober<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3R2LXNob3dzL2NsYXNzLW9mLTMwMDAvd2F0Y2gtY2xhc3Mtb2YtMzAwMC10aGUtaHVudC1mb3ItcmVkLWJsb2J0b2Jlci1vbmxpbmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLTEyLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fentrancemagazine.com%2Ftv-shows%2Fclass-of-3000%2Fwatch-class-of-3000-the-hunt-for-red-blobtober-online-streaming-12-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://entrancemagazine.com/tv-shows/class-of-3000/watch-class-of-3000-the-hunt-for-red-blobtober-online-streaming-12-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="416c117367cc0a952c32604c4349c89" url=""><![CDATA[Watch live Philadelphia Phillies vs Miami Marlins streaming<br/><br/><strong>Watch live Philadelphia Phillies vs Miami Marlins streaming 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-12 23:05:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpdmViYXNlYmFsbGhkdHYuY29tL3BoaWxhZGVscGhpYS1waGlsbGllcy12cy1taWFtaS1tYXJsaW5zLXdhdGNoLWxpdmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLTEyLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Philadelphia Phillies vs Miami Marlins<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch baseball - Philadelphia Phillies vs Miami Marlins&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Location: Citizens Bank Park<br />&lt;center&gt;Date: 12 Sep 2012, Time: 04:05 pm&lt;/center&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br /><br />marlins at philadelphia, watch philies vs marlins, stream miami at philies, stream marlins at philadelphia, philadelphia at miami, philadelphia vs miami, live philadelphia vs marlins, philies vs miami, miami vs philadelphia, stream marlins at philies<br />Philadelphia Phillies, Miami Marlins, live, live Philadelphia Phillies vs Miami Marlins, streaming Philadelphia Phillies vs Miami Marlins<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpdmViYXNlYmFsbGhkdHYuY29tL3BoaWxhZGVscGhpYS1waGlsbGllcy12cy1taWFtaS1tYXJsaW5zLXdhdGNoLWxpdmUtc3RyZWFtaW5nLTEyLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flivebaseballhdtv.com%2Fphiladelphia-phillies-vs-miami-marlins-watch-live-streaming-12-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://livebaseballhdtv.com/philadelphia-phillies-vs-miami-marlins-watch-live-streaming-12-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="10425c91e8fca59b2e2aa41b254551b9" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Abandoned, Oil City, Pennsylvania Bank online stream 1<br/><br/><strong>Watch Abandoned, Oil City, Pennsylvania Bank online stream 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-13 04:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3R2LXNob3dzL2FiYW5kb25lZC93YXRjaC1hYmFuZG9uZWQtb2lsLWNpdHktcGVubnN5bHZhbmlhLWJhbmstb25saW5lLXN0cmVhbS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Abandoned Oil City, Pennsylvania Bank<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch Abandoned - Oil City, Pennsylvania Bank&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Air date: 09:00 PM, Wed, September 12, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: National Geographic&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch stream &lt;b&gt;Abandoned&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Oil City, Pennsylvania Bank&lt;/b&gt; Season 1 Episode 7 on internet tv. Will be shown on National Geographic at 21 Aug 2012 05:00 PM. You must see this tv episode. Remember the aired date guys. Only 30 is running time of this tv episode. The saying goes, “one man’s junk is another man’s treasure” and that is certainly the case for expert carpenter and collector Jay Chaikin. He makes a living scouring the nation for abandoned buildings that may hold unexpected “gems” of history with shockingly high values. Follow Jay and his buddies Dan and Mark across the country on their ongoing quest to find their next big paycheck. Along the way, they’ll find classic items like Coca Cola memorabilia, an Edison phonograph, and a Zenith radio, as well as surprising discoveries like an early microwave oven and a top secret manual for a Boeing B-52 bomber. If you like &lt;b&gt;Oil City, Pennsylvania Bank&lt;/b&gt;, don't miss this Reality tv show. live abandoned house, abandoned towns missouri, abandoned prison skyrim, live abandoned, watch the abandoned online putlocker, skyrim abandoned prison ghost, abandoned property florida, abandoned property texas, abandoned property, live abandoned missile silo&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;<br />Abandoned, Oil City, Pennsylvania Bank, watch, watch Abandoned, stream Abandoned Oil City, Pennsylvania Bank<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VudHJhbmNlbWFnYXppbmUuY29tL3R2LXNob3dzL2FiYW5kb25lZC93YXRjaC1hYmFuZG9uZWQtb2lsLWNpdHktcGVubnN5bHZhbmlhLWJhbmstb25saW5lLXN0cmVhbS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fentrancemagazine.com%2Ftv-shows%2Fabandoned%2Fwatch-abandoned-oil-city-pennsylvania-bank-online-stream-12-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://entrancemagazine.com/tv-shows/abandoned/watch-abandoned-oil-city-pennsylvania-bank-online-stream-12-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2142bc618b559458da45dd0f3818d3db" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Houston Astros vs Chicago Cubs online streaming 12 Sep<br/><br/><strong>Watch Houston Astros vs Chicago Cubs online streaming 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-13 03:05:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vbWxiL2hvdXN0b24tYXN0cm9zLXZzLWNoaWNhZ28tY3Vicy13YXRjaC1saXZlLXN0cmVhbS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Houston Astros vs Chicago Cubs<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch baseball - Houston Astros vs Chicago Cubs&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Location: Minute Maid Park<br />&lt;center&gt;Date: Wednesday, Sep 12, 2012, Time: 08:05 pm&lt;/center&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br /><br />astros vs chicago cubs, houston vs chicago cubs, live cubs at houston, stream cubs at houston, astros vs cubs tickets, astros vs cubs game, astros vs cubs 2012, live astros vs chicago cubs, live houston vs cubs, live astros vs cubs<br />Houston Astros, Chicago Cubs, live, live Houston Astros vs Chicago Cubs, streaming Houston Astros vs Chicago Cubs<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vbWxiL2hvdXN0b24tYXN0cm9zLXZzLWNoaWNhZ28tY3Vicy13YXRjaC1saXZlLXN0cmVhbS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Fmlb%2Fhouston-astros-vs-chicago-cubs-watch-live-stream-12-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/mlb/houston-astros-vs-chicago-cubs-watch-live-stream-12-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e40381420f78cb744701e46b2bddb46" url=""><![CDATA[Cincinnati Reds vs Pittsburgh Pirates online broadcast 12 Se<br/><br/><strong>Cincinnati Reds vs Pittsburgh Pirates online broadcast 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-13 02:10:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L21sYi93YXRjaC1jaW5jaW5uYXRpLXJlZHMtdnMtcGl0dHNidXJnaC1waXJhdGVzLW9ubGluZS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG0_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Cincinnati Reds vs Pittsburgh Pirates<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch baseball - Cincinnati Reds vs Pittsburgh Pirates&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Location: Great American Ball Park<br />&lt;center&gt;Date: 12 Sep 2012, Time: 07:10 PM&lt;/center&gt;<br /><br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br /><br />stream cincinnati vs pirates, stream pittsburgh at reds, watch reds vs pittsburgh, live cincinnati vs pittsburgh, pittsburgh at reds, watch pirates at reds, watch cincinnati vs pittsburgh, live pirates at reds, stream reds vs pittsburgh, cincinnati at pirates<br />Cincinnati Reds, Pittsburgh Pirates, live, live Cincinnati Reds vs Pittsburgh Pirates, watch Cincinnati Reds vs Pittsburgh Pirates<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L21sYi93YXRjaC1jaW5jaW5uYXRpLXJlZHMtdnMtcGl0dHNidXJnaC1waXJhdGVzLW9ubGluZS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG0_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdixiewitch.net%2Fmlb%2Fwatch-cincinnati-reds-vs-pittsburgh-pirates-online-12-sep-2012.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dixiewitch.net/mlb/watch-cincinnati-reds-vs-pittsburgh-pirates-online-12-sep-2012.htm</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b99e2d22de95d27f33f86d56294b51f5" url=""><![CDATA[Watch The Soup, September 12 online 12 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Watch The Soup, September 12 online 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-13 05:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L3R2LXNob3dzL3RoZS1zb3VwL3N0cmVhbS1saXZlLXRoZS1zb3VwLXNlcHRlbWJlci0xMi0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG0_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />The Soup September 12<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch The Soup - September 12&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Air date: 10:00 pm, 12 September, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: E!&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch stream &lt;b&gt;The Soup&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;September 12&lt;/b&gt; Season 9 Episode 37 on internet tv. This show will be aired on E! at 30 June, 2004 05:00 PM. Remember the aired date guys. You must see this tv serie. Duration of this tv show is 30 minutes. Starring Joel McHale, Lou the Chihuahua. With this new satirical series, the E! Entertainment Network returns to a format they helped create with the popular '90s show Talk Soup. Only this time instead of just poking fun at talk shows, they're setting their sights on all things in entertainment, reality TV, pop culture, and politics Okay guys, don't miss this Comedy tv show, because it will be very good and full of interesting entertainment. the soup nazi, the soup full episodes free, watch the soup nazi free online, watch the soup full episodes online, watch the soup sidereel, the soup nazi recipes, the soup full episodes online, watch the soup episodes, the soup nazi full episode, the soup nazi imdb&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;<br />The Soup, September 12, stream, stream The Soup, watch The Soup September 12<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L3R2LXNob3dzL3RoZS1zb3VwL3N0cmVhbS1saXZlLXRoZS1zb3VwLXNlcHRlbWJlci0xMi0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG0_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdixiewitch.net%2Ftv-shows%2Fthe-soup%2Fstream-live-the-soup-september-12-12-sep-2012.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dixiewitch.net/tv-shows/the-soup/stream-live-the-soup-september-12-12-sep-2012.htm</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="450d28592b81507a5a9dff7f9603f47c" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Storage Wars Texas, Night of the Pondering Dead online<br/><br/><strong>Watch Storage Wars Texas, Night of the Pondering Dead online stream 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-13 04:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy9zdG9yYWdlLXdhcnMtdGV4YXMtdHYtc2hvdy93YXRjaC1zdG9yYWdlLXdhcnMtdGV4YXMtbmlnaHQtb2YtdGhlLXBvbmRlcmluZy1kZWFkLW9ubGluZS1zdHJlYW1pbmctMTItc2VwLTIwMTIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Storage Wars Texas Night of the Pondering Dead<br />&lt;h3&gt;Storage Wars Texas - Night of the Pondering Dead&lt;/h3&gt;<br />Date: 12 Sep 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />Air time: 09:00 pm&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: A&amp;E&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch stream &lt;b&gt;Storage Wars Texas&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Night of the Pondering Dead&lt;/b&gt; S2E8 on internet tv. This tv show will be shown on A&amp;E at Mon, December 05, 2011 05:00 PM. Remember the aired date guys. You must see this episode. Only 30 is running time of this tv serie. In the small town of Ponder, a dark secret looms; the townspeople pounce on lockers like hordes of zombies. Ricky and Bubba score some intimate objects for cattle. Jenny Grumbles scrambles for antique furniture. Victor hears the voice of doom when appraising motorcycle gear, while Moe and Mary uncover an object that may have been built by Benjamin Franklin. As the buyers quickly learn--in the town of Ponder, the rabid citizens are quite fond of brains. A&amp;E's top-rated nonfiction franchise is heading to Dallas, Texas where the units, bankrolls, and buyers are bigger. Following four Dallas storage unit hunters, this series has all the intrigue of the original &quot;Storage Wars&quot; in a landscape chock-full of cowboys and oil tycoons. This is going to be an exciting Reality tv episode to watch.&lt;/p&gt;<br />storage wars texas lesa leaving, storage wars texas lesa and jerry new season, storage wars texas cast moe, storage wars texas lesa lewis leaves, storage wars texas episodes wiki, watch storage wars texas season 2, storage wars texas lesa gone, storage wars texas season 1 episode 2, storage wars texas cast 2012, storage wars texas cast change<br />Storage Wars Texas, Night of the Pondering Dead, live, live Storage Wars Texas, watch Storage Wars Texas Night of the Pondering Dead<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtYXhhbGl2ZS5jb20vdHYtc2hvdy9zdG9yYWdlLXdhcnMtdGV4YXMtdHYtc2hvdy93YXRjaC1zdG9yYWdlLXdhcnMtdGV4YXMtbmlnaHQtb2YtdGhlLXBvbmRlcmluZy1kZWFkLW9ubGluZS1zdHJlYW1pbmctMTItc2VwLTIwMTIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femaxalive.com%2Ftv-show%2Fstorage-wars-texas-tv-show%2Fwatch-storage-wars-texas-night-of-the-pondering-dead-online-streaming-12-sep-2012.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://emaxalive.com/tv-show/storage-wars-texas-tv-show/watch-storage-wars-texas-night-of-the-pondering-dead-online-streaming-12-sep-2012.html</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e6d890b3c7fc6702e64f8dfe0d57a33" url=""><![CDATA[Watch The X Factor (US), Auditions No. 1 online tv 12 Sep, 2<br/><br/><strong>Watch The X Factor (US), Auditions No. 1 online tv 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-13 03:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L3R2LXNob3dzL3RoZS14LWZhY3Rvci11cy9zdHJlYW1pbmctb25saW5lLXRoZS14LWZhY3Rvci11cy1hdWRpdGlvbnMtbm8tMS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG0_" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />The X Factor (US) Auditions No. 1<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch The X Factor (US) - Auditions No. 1&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Air date: 08:00 pm, Wednesday, 12 September, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: FOX&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch stream &lt;b&gt;The X Factor (US)&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Auditions No. 1&lt;/b&gt; Season 2 Episode 1 on local tv. This tv serie will be aired on FOX at Tuesday, September 20, 2011 05:00 PM. You must see this tv serie. Remember the aired date guys. Starring Britney Spears, Demi Lovato, L.A. Reid, Nicole Scherzinger, Paula Abdul, Simon Cowell, Steve Jones. Running time is only 120 minutes. The X Factor is Simon Cowell’s brand new singing competition on a mission to find America’s next undiscovered superstar.<br /><br />The X Factor, on FOX is going to give someone like you the chance to win a $5 million recording contract with Sony Music.<br /><br />What’s great about The X Factor is that it is open to anyone – vocal groups and solo singers, over the age of 12 – and there’s absolutely no upper age limit. If you like &lt;b&gt;The X Factor (US)&lt;/b&gt;, don't miss this episode. the x factor usa sidereel, watch the x factor usa online free megavideo, x factor usa wikipedia season 1, watch the x factor usa, watch the x factor usa project free tv, wikipedia the x factor usa season 1, the x factor usa ratings wiki, the x factor usa ratings wikipedia, the x factor usa 2011 wiki, watch the x factor uk online&lt;/p&gt;<br />&lt;center&gt;&lt;/center&gt;<br />The X Factor (US), Auditions No. 1, live, live The X Factor (US), streaming The X Factor (US) Auditions No. 1<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L3R2LXNob3dzL3RoZS14LWZhY3Rvci11cy9zdHJlYW1pbmctb25saW5lLXRoZS14LWZhY3Rvci11cy1hdWRpdGlvbnMtbm8tMS0xMi1zZXAtMjAxMi5odG0_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdixiewitch.net%2Ftv-shows%2Fthe-x-factor-us%2Fstreaming-online-the-x-factor-us-auditions-no-1-12-sep-2012.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dixiewitch.net/tv-shows/the-x-factor-us/streaming-online-the-x-factor-us-auditions-no-1-12-sep-2012.htm</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="72bf8810b6555a7783864d798e0958ba" url=""><![CDATA[Watch Oh Sit!, Episode 7 online stream 12 Sep, 2012<br/><br/><strong>Watch Oh Sit!, Episode 7 online stream 12 Sep, 2012</strong><br />Air date: 2012-09-13 03:00:00<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L3R2LXNob3dzL29oLXNpdC9zdHJlYW0tbGl2ZS1vaC1zaXQtZXBpc29kZS03LTEyLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bQ__" target="_blank">Watch live streaming</a><br />Oh Sit! Episode 7<br />&lt;h2&gt;Watch Oh Sit! - Episode 7&lt;/h2&gt;<br />Air date: 08:00 PM, Wednesday, September 12, 2012&lt;br&gt;<br />TV Network: The CW&lt;br&gt;<br />&lt;!--more--&gt;<br />&lt;p&gt;Watch &lt;b&gt;Oh Sit!&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;Episode 7&lt;/b&gt; S1E7 online stream. This episode will be shown on The CW at Tue, August 14, 2012 05:00 PM. Remember the aired date guys. You must see this tv episode. Only 60 is running time of this show. OH SIT! will see 12 thrill-seeking daredevils racing head to head through five physically demanding, obstacle course-style eliminations as they each compete to claim a chair, to the sounds of a live band. At the end of the hour, only one contestant will be left sitting triumphant to seize the cash prize. Adding to the fun, Tanika Ray (&quot;Extra&quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /> will be in the trenches with the contestants both on and off the track and will add color commentary from the sidelines as the action unfolds. Every series is very interesting to watch, so don't forget to watch this episode. oh sit tv show, oh she loved sit watch you, oh sit game show commercial, oh sit!, cwtv oh sit, oh sit trailer, watch oh sit!, oh sit game show, oh sit cw premiere, oh sit premiere date&lt;/p&gt;<br />Oh Sit!, Episode 7, watch, watch Oh Sit!, live Oh Sit! Episode 7<br />Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RpeGlld2l0Y2gubmV0L3R2LXNob3dzL29oLXNpdC9zdHJlYW0tbGl2ZS1vaC1zaXQtZXBpc29kZS03LTEyLXNlcC0yMDEyLmh0bQ__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdixiewitch.net%2Ftv-shows%2Foh-sit%2Fstream-live-oh-sit-episode-7-12-sep-2012.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dixiewitch.net/tv-shows/oh-sit/stream-live-oh-sit-episode-7-12-sep-2012.htm</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>