<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="c71024031ab56e4d2e7590abaa96fdc1" url=""><![CDATA[Organize Ur desk<br/><br/>Ah today i had to do the wrost thing, i had to clean up my DESK!
<br /><br />God i  hate this job, werent be some1 like he can put all my papers in my files?
<br /><br />What to do ?? i have to wait for 1 month, my assistant is in vocation and i am tired already of putting all the papers back to their folder which i don't know any 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />i hear the sound of ZzzZz??
<br /><br />if u r getting sleepy of reading this, i don't care, i write this for my own reference
<br /><br />so my boss saw my desk and he told me to clean it up in 2 hours
<br /><br />but hey, it's very lil for me
<br /><br />and the time is up and i had to go out of theoffice la??!!
<br /><br />before i run away, he saw me and told me to come early 2moro one hour earlier just to clean up 
<br /><br />i don't know if this is his right or not
<br /><br />but i'll leave one hour earlier <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2acfcf8ccae2f116f43f219662ff5c6" url=""><![CDATA[The Holiday<br/><br/>Today i am extreeeeemlly happy!!
<br /><br />I FOUND IT!
<br /><br />Yes i did found it,
<br /><br />this sweeet gentle soundtrack that i have been looking for since this movie was released in bahrain!
<br /><br />have i mentioned the name of the movie??!
<br /><br />The Holiday!
<br /><br />one of two best movie of 2006 for me
<br />&quot;Click&quot; &amp; &quot;The Holiday&quot;
<br /><br />they tought me valuable lessons to move on in this life 
<br /><br />and i found the soundtrack that remindes me of this movie, since i am always sayina bout myself that i am ugly fat etc..
<br /><br />somehow, it helped.. 
<br /><br />i am blessed by this Day as it's Friday and finding the soundtrack
<br /><br />again.. did i mention that this soundtrack is by Hans Zimmer?
<br /><br />that exmplains <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6a94adf5cf737ddaf30be930dd2164b0" url=""><![CDATA[Gumption<br/><br/>The word of the day is GUMPTION!
<br /><br />if u hesitate, have the GUMPTION to say it or do it
<br /><br />as long as you know
<br /><br />YOU ARE RIGHT! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31984df134f43087762c2f5844d4231d" url=""><![CDATA[Try it!<br/><br/>Mighty Zinger
<br /><br />that's it
<br /><br />try it!
<br /><br />it's soo tasty !
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7b4c62c853beee053aa96362d93eb35c" url=""><![CDATA[Others<br/><br/>We always feel depressed because of the things we're facing in our life...
<br /><br />what about others??
<br /><br />have you ever felt depressed because of the bad things happening to people &quot;you just know&quot;?
<br /><br />can we be once not selfish in our life?
<br /><br />I did yesterday, I was very sad for the un-happy event happened to my friend (friend), very far from me, yet I felt that if this happened to me, I won't be happy for the rest of day and I would be so lonely in this feeling.
<br /><br />For that, I have decided for this person not to feel lonely, weather she know it or not, I should share the feeling. @ least I would find out what does it feel like if this happened to me…
<br /><br />Hope all your problems will be solved
<br /><br />&quot;we all have problems, we all feel sad about it, so there what worst could happen if we share it once in a while, and what could happen if we bare other's problem for 5 min&quot;?
<br /><br />Others shouldn't be others all the time, others should have people like us <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Written by ME! do not COPY <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e6760510c8c7d17c71e6e368a5dff26" url=""><![CDATA[Gilling the gap<br/><br/>Today is the most boring day of this week! 
<br /><br />i know it's the start of it but i know it's booooooooooring
<br /><br />The Boss didn't come! i though it would be YABADEBADOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />but no.. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />i feel boring!
<br /><br />i had to eat just to fill the gap <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />me fatso <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aa55d9c2756498f696f83491f9327b06" url=""><![CDATA[i wrote a warning letter for myself :D<br/><br/>Hey no need to know the details 3aib,
<br /><br />fashiliiiiiiiiiiii <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c30122ceadc84a7669d8792462d09112" url=""><![CDATA[BUT NO!<br/><br/>hey! i'm sorry my blog that i didn't write for y ou yesterday 
<br /><br />first, i was soooooooo happy that i will go to movies
<br /><br />i was planning for it for days!  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />BUT NO!
<br /><br />my friends had turned me down in the las tmin, and i don't have a BF ! so should i wait for my friend or the BF to go to movies with??
<br /><br />Na! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />so i decided to go ALONE!
<br /><br />and i did, i went to pay for the ticket 
<br />it was 3 BD! God everything in Bahrain is becoming expensive
<br /><br />and i choosed the movie &quot;Notes of a Scandle&quot; because it won something bla bla bla
<br /><br />so when i checked in the movies, everybody were looking @ me cause they think that the BF will come later on (as it's usual in bahrain hehe)
<br /><br />but no, i was alone, i sat in the threate and i noticed that those security guys came 3 times during the movie checking if some1 is with me
<br /><br />but NO! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />  iwas alone
<br /><br />in fact i though that i would be despressed or something 
<br /><br />BUT NO <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />i was happy, you know sometimes when you go to a movie that you picked up with some1 but the movie is not as good as you though
<br />so all the time you will be thinking
<br />&quot; oh! i am afraid that he/she didn't like it, they will kill me, i hope they like the movie&quot;
<br /><br />it happens to you isn't?
<br /><br />BUT NO <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />not this time, it didn't happen to me cause i was ALONE!
<br />and i wasn't depressed or anything <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />i watched the whole movie, it wasn't that good, they acted well but the story is repeated and it's a known story &quot;not recommended movie&quot;
<br /><br />so i went out of the movies, and still the security people were looking @ me desbelieving that i came alone and NO BF AFTER ME <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />in facnt, in yesterdays' experience, i learned that i shouldn't wait just because it's common that i should go with others, 
<br /><br />i just, simply do it <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9e22e5339764f8f216b21042e5ebc4e9" url=""><![CDATA[You're not WRONG!<br/><br/>Few days ago @ work, I was discussing this issue with my co-worker, of course we were gossiping about one of our colleges… girls u know <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />Anyway, we were saying that his person is always wrong and stupid, and she knows nothing.
<br /><br />But the way she speaks is like SHE IS RIGHT! Which makes us think that we are WRONG?
<br /><br />On the other hand, there is this nice girl she is ALWAYS right but because of hesitation she shows, we think that she is WRONG!
<br /><br />So in conclusion, we come to know that, no matter if you’re right or wrong
<br /><br />Act as you are SURE and 100% SURE that there is NO way that you are WRONG!
<br /><br />And people will say that YOU ARE RIGHT!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5b213e76c9a33268178d43a2bf6a950f" url=""><![CDATA[BUT NO - part II<br/><br/>i went to movies alone AGAAAAAIN  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />this time i have choose &quot;the last king of scotland&quot;
<br /><br />so as i walked into the movies, there was only two seats are taken, and between them it was the walkway
<br /><br />so, i was surprice, who will take two seperate seats in a total empty movie that the total attendance was only 3 !!!! including me
<br /><br />but as i walked into the movie, a boy and a girl were in those seperated seats, and as soon th girl saw me SHE RUN TO THE BACK OF THE MOVIE! just to hide from me!!!
<br /><br />NO KIDDING! it was a side movie for me there hehehehe
<br /><br />and my seat was in the same line as these fellows hehe
<br /><br />so i decided to SIT on my chair!
<br /><br />then i though, you know what? <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />  lemme go infront and give those fellow a bit of privacy, since i have destroyed it
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />BUT NO !! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />it's my seat, and if those fellow wanna do something, let them do anywhere, NOT IN PUBLIC! so i stick to my seat <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />then i though, well it's not enough,,, i will go and sit in the back of the movie with th girl <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />7ashrah ma3a al nas yeboooooooooooooooo....
<br /><br />so i ruled the movies that day
<br /><br />About the movie
<br /><br />The actor really deserve the oscarrs, he was a very good actor,
<br /><br />The movie: it's a political movie and action so it's not recommended for girls. but not girls like me, i like political and war movies
<br /><br />so in conclusion, if u like those kind, its a good one, but u have to wait patiently, cause the best is in the last 
<br /><br />Bless you all..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a84a2f9cfb31c58220db85e37d4329c2" url=""><![CDATA[I'm FAT but..<br/><br/>Ya  i am fat, something that u don't know dear blog
<br /><br />i am crazy about being fat, i always make fun of this part in me, i dislike being a fat, however...
<br /><br />I'm fat <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />Two days ago, i went To Chillis in Seef mall,
<br /><br />This time NOT ALONE! but with my friend
<br /><br />so as we walked in, the waitress said to me &quot; Table for two&quot;?
<br /><br />I Said: &quot;Yes&quot;
<br /><br />There was another Bahraini waiter standing next to us, and he said:
<br />&quot; No! Table for Three&quot;!
<br /><br />And he started Laughing Out LOUD!
<br /><br />As he was like making fun of me being FAT!
<br /><br />….
<br /><br />No comments
<br /><br />I didn't say anything, he really hurt my feeling, 
<br /><br />But
<br /><br />I deserve it, I am fat, so I must get those comments all the time
<br /><br />So I walked into the restaurant, and I told my friend about what happened
<br /><br />My friend, she became very mad about this
<br /><br />And she noticed that this Bahraini waiter was rooming around and making fun, so he sounded like a naughty guy anyway 
<br /><br />I sat sadly, disbelieving that this guy would say that to me, 
<br /><br />But hey! I am fat
<br /><br />We finished our meal and we walked out of the restaurant
<br /><br />But before I walk out
<br /><br />I took the business card of the restaurant
<br /><br />I went home, I called the restaurant and I asked for the Manager
<br /><br />And I complained…
<br /><br />Yes I did, that the least thing I could have done for a person who makes fun of me JUST BECAUSE I LOVE FOOD
<br /><br />The Manager told me that he would take care of this matter etc
<br /><br />And he thanked me for being calm regarding this mater
<br /><br />But I don’t know, I feel like that I have to do something more, cause this guy was thin and everything, which made him better than me, he is better than me in terms of looks and that
<br /><br />As a result, it gave him the authority to make &quot;Funny&quot; comments about me
<br /><br />So what I shall do? I loose weight to avoid such comments?
<br /><br />No, I want to loose weight, it's the dream for every fat and ugly girl like me
<br /><br />That's it for today, I can't write more, or else I'll cry
<br /><br />Yes I have feeling, fat and ugly people cry sometimes
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="80f7692902a204545a3add7005b88505" url=""><![CDATA[When they don't gather<br/><br/>When you like your family soooooooooo much
<br /><br />and you know that they don't gather a lot
<br /><br />or they don't, @ all
<br /><br />------------------
<br /><br />my brothers and sister are very friendly people, very funny, i like them so much, and id on't have problem with any of them
<br /><br />but we never in our life had a day out together
<br /><br />NEVER!
<br /><br />this month, i got the JAM3EYA <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />so i though? WHY NOT?
<br /><br />i called them up, and invite all of them to a dinner in a lovely quiet restaurant
<br /><br />they were very surpriced &quot;What's wrong with u lil sis? r u tellin bad news&quot;?
<br /><br />&quot;No&quot;, i said &quot;why we just go out? let's all talk together as brothers and sisters&quot;
<br /><br />why not? and we did
<br /><br />we have such a lovely time, chatting, laughing, we even shared our bad experience and good one, and we all talked about our career, what's next, and what is our problems @ work, and we helped each other
<br /><br />Never in our life we had a gathring like that
<br /><br />gr8!
<br /><br />a refreshment in our life, sometimes spouses, kids, co-workers are too heavy
<br /><br />and u JUST need time with ur family
<br /><br />Ur childhood mates @ home
<br /><br />sharing memories and hopes of what will it be for next time
<br /><br />what we will EAT for our next gathering <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>