<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="b0552c41f77116a44c11a5b16d936291" url=""><![CDATA[welcome one and all......<br/><br/>wow another one of these online bolgs...
<br /><br />this one seems really wikid though... heaps better than melo and myspace... wikid!!!
<br /><br />well i havent really spoken to anyone for awhile... those back up in darrwin and those down here in  bunbury w.a. 
<br /><br />my bf is kinda .... lets just say hes really protec`tive.... to the point where hes really controlling... which isnt that bad coz its stopped me taking pills and shooting up n stuff... so really its a blessing!! 
<br /><br />ive been so bored lately...
<br /><br />i just found out that i have to go back up to darwin to go to court in feb.... FUCK!!!! thats really bad!!! dean wont let me go all the way up there by myself again... last time i went up there for court, i was raped by two american soldiers.... so hes kinda freeakin out bout me goin back up there... n dun worry im not in trouble... i was just a witness to something... 
<br /><br />so anyways... do ppl actually read these or nah????? coz ppl used to think melo and myspace wee wikid.. then they kinda just...... you know stopped goin on an stuff...
<br /><br />well i guess ill catcha on the flipside..
<br /><br />luv thomi  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wub.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31736017f573e0b3bf821ae0ba9e59c4" url=""><![CDATA[A lil Miracle<br/><br/>A little girl went to her bedroom and pulled a glass jelly jar from 
<br />its hiding place in the closet. 
<br /><br />She poured the change out on the floor and counted it carefully. 
<br />Three times, even. The total had to be exactly perfect. No chance 
<br />here for mistakes. 
<br /><br />Carefully placing the coins back in the jar and twisting on the cap, 
<br />she slipped out the back door and made her way 6 blocks to Rexall's 
<br />Drug Store with the big red Indian Chief sign above the door. 
<br /><br />She waited patiently for the pharmacist to give her some attention 
<br />but he was too busy at this moment. 
<br />Tess twisted her feet to make a scuffing noise. 
<br />Nothing. She cleared her throat with the most disgusting sound she 
<br />could muster. No good. Finally she took a quarter from her jar and 
<br />banged it on the glass counter. 
<br />That did it! 
<br /><br />&quot;And what do you want?&quot; the pharmacist asked in an annoyed tone of 
<br />voice. I'm talking to my brother from Chicago whom I haven't seen in 
<br />ages,&quot; he said without waiting for a reply to his question. 
<br /><br />&quot;Well, I want to talk to you about my brother,&quot; Tess answered back in 
<br />the same annoyed tone. 
<br />&quot;He's really, really sick...and I want to buy a miracle.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;I beg your pardon?&quot; said the pharmacist. 
<br /><br />&quot; His name is Andrew and he has something bad growing inside his head and my Daddy says only a miracle can save him now. So how much does a miracle cost?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;We don't sell miracles here, little girl. I'm sorry but I can't 
<br />help you,&quot; the pharmacist said, softening a little. 
<br /><br />&quot;Listen, I have the money to pay for it. If it isn't enough, I will 
<br />get the rest. Just tell me how much it costs.&quot; 
<br /><br />The pharmacist's brother was a well dressed man. He stooped down and asked the little girl, &quot;What kind of a miracle does your brother 
<br />need?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot; I don't know,&quot; Tess replied with her eyes welling up. 
<br />&quot; I just know he's really sick and Mommy says he needs an operation. 
<br />But my Daddy can't pay for it, so I want to use my money.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot; How much do you have?&quot; asked the man from Chicago. 
<br /><br />&quot;One dollar and eleven cents,&quot; Tess answered barely 
<br />audibly. 
<br /><br />&quot;And it's all the money I have, but I can get some more if I need 
<br />to.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Well, what a coincidence,&quot; smiled the man. &quot;A dollar and eleven 
<br />cents---the exact price of a miracle for little brothers. &quot; 
<br /><br />He took her money in one hand and with the other hand he grasped her 
<br />mitten and said &quot;Take me to where you live. I want to see your 
<br />brother and meet your parents. Let's see if I have the 
<br />miracle you need.&quot; 
<br /><br />That well dressed man was Dr. Carlton Armstrong, a surgeon, 
<br />specializing in neuro-surgery. The operation was completed free of 
<br />charge and it wasn't long until Andrew was home again and doing well. 
<br /><br />Mom and Dad were happily talking about the chain of 
<br />events that had led them to this place. 
<br /><br />That surgery,&quot; her Mom whispered. &quot;was a real miracle. 
<br />I wonder how much it would have cost?&quot; 
<br /><br />Tess smiled. She knew exactly how much 
<br />a miracle cost...one dollar and eleven cents, 
<br />plus the faith of a little child.. 
<br /><br />In our lives, we never know how many 
<br />miracles we will need.. 
<br /><br />A miracle is not the suspension of natural law, 
<br />but the operation of a higher law.. 
<br />I know you'll keep the ball moving!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="992ebc797746fecef653fe36195ae31f" url=""><![CDATA[25 Prayers from kids<br/><br/>1. Dear God, 
<br />please put another holiday 
<br />between Christmas and Easter. 
<br />There is nothing good in there now. 
<br />Amanda 
<br /><br />2. Dear God, 
<br />Thank you for the baby brother 
<br />but what I asked for was a puppy. 
<br />I never asked for anything before. 
<br />You can look it up. 
<br />Joyce 
<br /><br />3. Dear Mr. 
<br />God, I wish you would not make it so easy 
<br />for people to come apart 
<br />I had to have 3 stitches and a shot. 
<br />Janet 
<br /><br />4. God, 
<br />I read the bible. 
<br />What does beget mean? 
<br />Nobody will tell me. 
<br />Love Alison 
<br /><br />5. Dear God, 
<br />how did you know you were God? 
<br />Who told you? 
<br />Charlene 
<br /><br />6. Dear God, 
<br />is it true my father 
<br />won't get in Heaven 
<br />if he uses his golf words in the house? 
<br />Anita 
<br /><br />7. Dear God, 
<br />I bet it's very hard for you 
<br />to love all of everybody in the whole world. 
<br />There are only 4 people in our family 
<br />and I can never do it. 
<br />Nancy 
<br /><br />8. Dear God, 
<br />I like the story about Noah 
<br />the best of all of them. 
<br />You really made up some good ones. 
<br />I like walking on water, too. 
<br />Glenn 
<br /><br />9. Dear God, 
<br />my Grandpa says you were around 
<br />when he was a little boy. 
<br />How far back do you go? 
<br />Love, Dennis 
<br /><br />10. Dear God, 
<br />do you draw the lines around the countries? 
<br />If you don't, who does? 
<br />Nathan 
<br /><br />11. Dear God, 
<br />did you mean for giraffes 
<br />to look like that or was it an accident? 
<br />Norma 
<br /><br />12. Dear God, 
<br />in bible times, 
<br />did they really talk that fancy? 
<br />Jennifer 
<br /><br />13. Dear God, 
<br />how come you did all those miracles 
<br />in the old days and don't do any now? 
<br />Billy 
<br /><br />14. Dear God, 
<br />please send Dennis Clark 
<br />to a different summer camp this year. 
<br />Peter 
<br /><br />15. Dear God, 
<br />maybe Cain and Abel 
<br />would not kill each other so much 
<br />if they each had their own rooms. 
<br />It works out OK with me and my brother. 
<br />Larry 
<br /><br />16. Dear God, 
<br />I keep waiting for spring, 
<br />but it never did come yet. 
<br />What's up? Don't forget. 
<br />Mark 
<br /><br />17 Dear God, 
<br />my brother told me about 
<br />how you are born 
<br />but it just doesn't sound right. 
<br />What do you say? 
<br />Marsha 
<br /><br />18. Dear God, 
<br />if you watch in Church on Sunday 
<br />I will show you my new shoes. 
<br />Barbara 
<br /><br />19. Dear God, 
<br />is Reverend Coe a friend of yours, 
<br />or do you just know him through the business? 
<br />Donny 
<br /><br />20. Dear God, 
<br />I do not think anybody 
<br />could be a better God than you. 
<br />Well, I just want you to know that. 
<br />I am not just saying that because 
<br />you are already God. 
<br />Charles 
<br /><br />21. Dear God, 
<br />it is great the way you always 
<br />get the stars in the right place. 
<br />Why can't you do that with the moon? 
<br />Jeff 
<br /><br />22. Dear God, 
<br />I am doing the best I can. 
<br />Really !!!! 
<br />Frank 
<br /><br />And, saving the best for last . . 
<br /><br />23. Dear God, 
<br />I didn't think orange went with purple 
<br />until I saw the sunset 
<br />you made on Tuesday night. 
<br />That was really cool. 
<br />Thomas
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8fb531577276877b1d27861780757f3a" url=""><![CDATA[drink driving<br/><br/>Jenny was so happy about the house they had found. 
<br />For once in her life 'twas on the right side of town. 
<br />She unpacked her things with such great ease. 
<br />As she watched her new curtains blow in the breeze. 
<br /><br />How wonderful it was to have her own room. 
<br />School would be starting; she'd have friends over soon. 
<br />There'd be sleep-overs, and parties; she was so happy 
<br />It's just the way she wanted her life to be. 
<br /><br />On the first day of school, everything went great. 
<br />She made new friends and even got a date! 
<br />She thought, &quot;I want to be popular and I'm going to be, 
<br />Because I just got a date with the star of the team!&quot; 
<br /><br />To be known in this school you had to have clout, 
<br />And dating this guy would sure help her out. 
<br />There was only one problem stopping her fate. 
<br />Her parents had said she was too young to date. 
<br /><br />&quot;Well I just won't tell them the entire truth. 
<br />They won't know the difference; what's there to lose?&quot; 
<br />Jenny asked to stay with her friends that night. 
<br />Her parents frowned but said, &quot;All right.&quot; 
<br /><br />Excited, she got ready for the big event 
<br />But as she rushed around like she had no sense, 
<br />She began to feel guilty about all the lies, 
<br />But what's a pizza, a party, and a moonlight ride? 
<br /><br />Well the pizza was good, and the party was great, 
<br />But the moonlight ride would have to wait. 
<br />For Dan was half drunk by this time. 
<br />But he kissed her and said that he was just fine. 
<br /><br />Then the room filled with smoked and Dan took a puff. 
<br />Jenny couldn't believe he was smoking that stuff. 
<br />Now Dan was ready to ride to the point 
<br />But only after he'd smoked another joint. 
<br /><br />They jumped in the car for the moonlight ride, 
<br />Not thinking that he was too drunk to drive. 
<br />They finally made it to the point at last, And Dan started trying to make a pass. 
<br /><br />A pass is not what Jenny wanted at all 
<br />(and by a pass, I don't mean playing football.) 
<br />&quot;Perhaps my parents were right....maybe I am too young. 
<br />Boy, how could I ever, ever be so dumb.&quot; 
<br /><br />With all of her might, she pushed Dan away: 
<br />&quot;Please take me home, I don't want to stay.&quot; 
<br />Dan cranked up the engine and floored the gas. 
<br />In a matter of seconds they were going too fast. 
<br /><br />As Dan drove on in a fit of wild anger, 
<br />Jenny knew that her life was in &gt;danger. 
<br />She begged and pleaded for him to slow down, 
<br />But he just got faster as they neared the town. 
<br /><br />&quot;Just let me get home! I'll confess that I lied. 
<br />I really went out for a moonlight ride.&quot; 
<br />Then all of a sudden, she saw a big flash. 
<br />&quot;Oh God, Please help us! We're going to crash!&quot; 
<br /><br />She doesn't remember the force of impact. 
<br />Just that everything all of a sudden went black. 
<br />She felt someone remove her from the twisted rubble, 
<br />And heard, &quot;call an ambulance! These kids are in trouble! 
<br /><br />Voices she heard...a few words at best. 
<br />But she knew there were two cars involved in the wreck. 
<br />Then wondered to herself if Dan was all right, 
<br />And if the people in the other car was alive. 
<br /><br />She awoke in the hospital to faces so sad. 
<br />&quot;You've been in a wreck and it looks pretty bad.&quot; 
<br />These voices echoed inside her head, 
<br />As they gently told her that Dan was dead. 
<br /><br />They said &quot;Jenny, we've done all we can do. 
<br />But it looks as if we'll lose you too.&quot; 
<br />&quot;But the people in the other car!?&quot; Jenny cried. 
<br />&quot;We're sorry, Jenny, they also died.&quot; 
<br /><br />Jenny prayed, &quot;God, forgive me for what I've done 
<br />I only wanted to have just one night of fun.&quot; 
<br />&quot;Tell those people's family, I've made their lives dim, 
<br />And wish I could return their families to them.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Tell Mom and Dad I'm sorry I lied, 
<br />And that it's my fault so many have died. 
<br />Oh, nurse, won't you please tell them that for me?&quot; 
<br />The nurse just stood there-she never agreed. 
<br /><br />But took Jenny's hand with tears in her eyes. 
<br />And a few moments later Jenny died. 
<br />A man asked the nurse, &quot;Why didn't you do your best 
<br />To bid that girl her one last request?&quot; 
<br /><br />She looked at the man with eyes so sad. 
<br />&quot;Because the people in the other car were her mom and dad.&quot; 
<br />This story is sad and unpleasant but true, 
<br />So young people take heed, it could have been you.
<br /><br />please dont drink and drive.... my aunty was killed in a car crash with her boyfriend when she was just 16yrs old!! you might think that your not pissed... but if youve been drinking... please PLEASE dont drive!!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e2c590c862bb65f5f1c3154f99971ecf" url=""><![CDATA[abortion...<br/><br/>Dear Mommy, 
<br />I am in Heaven now, sitting on Jesus' lap. 
<br />He loves me and cries with me; 
<br />for my heart has been broken. 
<br />I so wanted to be your little girl. 
<br />I don't quite understand what has happened. 
<br />I was so excited when I began realizing my existance. 
<br />I was in a dark, yet comfortable place. 
<br />I saw I had fingers and toes. 
<br />I was pretty far along in my developing, yet not near ready to leave my surroundings. 
<br />I spent most of my time thinking or sleeping. 
<br />Even from my earliest days, I felt a special bonding between you and me. 
<br />Sometimes I heard you crying and I cried with you. 
<br />Sometimes you would yell or scream, then cry. 
<br />I heard Daddy yelling back. 
<br />I was sad, and hoped you would be better soon. 
<br />I wondered why you cried so much. 
<br />One day you cried almost all of the day. 
<br />I hurt for you. 
<br />I couldn't imagine why you were so unhappy. 
<br />That same day, the most horrible thing happened. 
<br />A very mean monster came into that warm, comfortable place I was in. 
<br />I was so scared, I began screaming, but you never once tried to help me. 
<br />Maybe you never heard me. 
<br />The monster got closer and closer as I was screaming and screaming, &quot;Mommy, Mommy, help me please; Mommy, help me&quot;; 
<br />Complete terror is all I felt. 
<br />I screamed and screamed until I thought I couldn't anymore. 
<br />Then the monster started ripping my arms off. 
<br />It hurt so bad; the pain I can never explain. 
<br />It didn't stop. 
<br />Oh, how I begged it to stop. 
<br />I screamed in horror as it ripped my leg off. 
<br />Though I was in such complete pain, I was dying. 
<br />I knew I would never see your face or hear you say how much you love me. 
<br />I wanted to make all your tears go away. 
<br />I had so many plans to make you happy. 
<br />Now I couldn't; all my dreams were shattered. 
<br />Though I was in utter pain and horror, I felt the pain of my heart breaking, above all. 
<br />I wanted more than anything to be your daughter. 
<br />No use now, for I was dying a painful death. 
<br />I could only imagine the terrible things that they had done to you. 
<br />I wanted to tell you that I love you before I was gone, but I didn't know the words you could understand. 
<br />And soon, I no longer had the breath to say them; I was dead. 
<br />I felt myself rising. 
<br />I was being carried by a huge angel into a big beautiful place. 
<br />I was still crying, but the physical pain was gone. 
<br />The angel took me to Jesus and set me on His lap. 
<br />He said He loved me, and He was my Father. 
<br />Then I was happy. 
<br />I asked Him what the thing was that killed me. 
<br />He answered;Abortion. 
<br />I am sorry my child; for I know how it feels; 
<br />I don't know what abortion is; I guess that's the name of the monster. 
<br />I'm writing to say that I love you and to tell you how much I wanted to be your little girl. 
<br />I tried very hard to live. 
<br />I wanted to live. 
<br />I had the will, but I couldn't; the monster was too powerful. 
<br />It sucked my arms and legs off and finally got all of me. 
<br />It was impossible to live. 
<br />I just wanted you to know I tried to stay with you. 
<br />I didn't want to die. 
<br />Also, Mommy, please watch out for that abortion monster. 
<br />Mommy, I love you and I would hate for you to go through the kind of pain I did. 
<br />Please be careful. 
<br /><br />Love,Your Baby Girl
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="121722642145f2deff879c167155cfdb" url=""><![CDATA[in loving memory of the Colombine Students<br/><br/>Mommy... Johnny brought a gun to school, 
<br />He told his friends that it was cool, 
<br />And when he pulled the trigger back, 
<br />It shot with a great&gt;crack. 
<br /><br />Mommy, I was a good girl,I 
<br />did what I was told, 
<br />I went to school, I got straight A's, 
<br />I even got the gold! 
<br /><br />But Mommy, when I went school that day, 
<br />I never said good-bye, 
<br />I'm sorry Mommy, I had to go, 
<br />But Mommy, please don't cry. 
<br /><br />When Johnny shot the gun, 
<br />He hit me and another, 
<br />And all because Johnny, 
<br />Got the gun from his older brother. 
<br /><br />Mommy, please tell Daddy; 
<br />That I love him very much, 
<br />And please tell Chris; my boyfriend; 
<br />That it wasn't just a crush. 
<br /><br />And tell my little sister; 
<br />That she is the only one now, 
<br />And tell my dear sweet grandmother; 
<br />I'll be waiting for her now, 
<br /><br />And ell my wnderful friends; 
<br />That they always were the best; 
<br />Mommy, I'm not the first, 
<br />I'm no better than the rest. 
<br /><br />Mommy, tell my teachers; 
<br />I won't show up for class, 
<br />And never to forget this, 
<br />And please don't let this pass. 
<br /><br />Mommy, why'd it have to be me? 
<br />No&gt;one deserves this, 
<br />Mommy, warn the others, 
<br />Mommy I left without a kiss. 
<br /><br />And Mommy tell the doctors; 
<br />I know they really did try, 
<br />I think I even saw a doctor, 
<br />Trying not to cry. 
<br /><br />Mommy, I'm slowly dying, 
<br />With a bullet in my chest, 
<br />But Mommy please remember, 
<br />I'm in heaven with the rest. 
<br /><br />When I heard that crack, 
<br />I ran as fast as i could, 
<br />Mommy, listen to me 
<br />please if you would, 
<br /><br />I wanted to go to college 
<br />I wanted to try things that were new, 
<br />I guess I'm not going with Daddy, 
<br />On that trip to the new zoo. 
<br /><br />I wanted to get married, 
<br />I wanted to have a kid, 
<br />I wanted to be an actress, 
<br />Mommy, I wanted to live. 
<br /><br />But Mommy I must go now, 
<br />The time is getting late, 
<br />Mommy, tell my Chris, 
<br />I'm sorry but I had to cancel the date. 
<br /><br />I love you Mommy, I always have, 
<br />I know; you know it's true, &gt;&gt; 
<br />And Mommy all I wanted to say 
<br />is, &quot;Mommy, I love you.&quot; 
<br /><br />*~* In Memory of The Columbine Students Who Were Lost *~*
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5bf1330fb2670d532c412dcddd30a00" url=""><![CDATA[Broken Promises<br/><br/>A guy and a girl, both best friends, chatting online : 
<br /><br />Girl- hey 
<br />Guy- hey 
<br />Girl- what's up? 
<br />Guy- nothing, I have some really bad news... 
<br />Girl- what is it? 
<br />Guy- I'm moving. 
<br />Girl- you can't move! 
<br />Guy- I am, my parents are making me. We're moving out of state. 
<br />Girl- you can?t go! I'll miss you too much. 
<br />Guy- I know, I'll miss you too 
<br />Girl- I love you 
<br />Guy- I know, I love you to 
<br />Guy- I g2g now 
<br />Guy- later 
<br /><br />The girl was sad - not only because he was moving, but because he didn't love her the way that she loved him. She had been in love with him since the day they met. 
<br /><br />They meet for pizza the day before he leaves. They talk, and the girl is worried that she won't ever see him again, or that he won't remember her; but the guy promises that he would never forget her and that he would come and visit. They were about to leave when the girl said 'I love you' again. The guy said 'I know I love you too. We'll be friends forever'. Although the girl was glad they were friends she was torn up inside that he didn't love her the way she loved him. 
<br /><br />He moved the next day. When he got to his new place he got online : 
<br /><br />Girl- hey 
<br />Girl- I want to tell you something 
<br />Guy- can it wait, I don?t feel like talking now 
<br /><br />It went on like that for a few weeks. Then he stopped talking to her completely. She never got to tell him what she wanted. 
<br /><br />The guy came back to visit a year later. The girl ran up and gave him a hug 
<br /><br />Girl- I missed you so much! 
<br />Guy- do I know you? 
<br />Girl- funny, I'm your best friend 
<br />Guy- I don?t think I know you. Please get away from me now... 
<br /><br />This destroyed her. She decided to leave. Just then, a car came around the corner. It was about to hit the guy. The girl ran and jumped in front of the car, pushing the guy out of the way. The girl was killed. The guy was invited to her funeral not knowing why he was there - since he thought he didn't know her. Just then her dad read the last entry out of her diary : 
<br /><br />'My best friend has moved away. He has stopped talking to me online. I am very sad. I fell in love with him the day we met, but he did not love me the way that I love him. I tried to tell him how I really felt, but he didn't want to talk to me. He finally quit talking to me altogether. I haven't heard from him in months. I miss him dearly. I never got to tell him that I really do love him and that I would do anything for him - even die for him.' 
<br /><br />Just then, the guy remembered who she was. He felt horrible. He had forgotten her. He had broken his promise.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fa467b52e43c806305ac255d430d5d45" url=""><![CDATA[a lovely lil message<br/><br/>As we grow up, we learn that even the one person that wasn't supposed to ever let you down probably will. 
<br /><br />You will have your heart broken probably more than once and it's harder every time. 
<br /><br />You'll break hearts too, so remember how it felt when yours was broken. 
<br /><br />You'll fight with your best friend. 
<br /><br />You'll blame a new love for things an old one did. 
<br /><br />You'll cry because time is passing too fast, and you'll eventually lose someone you love. 
<br /><br />So take too many pictures, laugh too much, and love like you've never been hurt because every sixty seconds you spend upset is a minute of happiness you'll never get back.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="56f2f490d2ced35cdc847fbe8012303d" url=""><![CDATA[12 Signs Of Love<br/><br/>12 signs of love
<br /><br />2006-01-04 00:57:35.419222-08   edit  Title: 
<br /><br />Body: 
<br /><br />Format this entry for me. (Adds &lt;br&gt;'s to your line endings.)
<br /> Do not format this entry for me.
<br /><br />These are 12 signs that you are falling in love.... 
<br /><br />12. You'll read his/her IMS over and over again... 
<br /><br />11. You'll walk really really slow while you're with him/her... 
<br /><br />10. You'll feel shy whenever you're with him/her... 
<br /><br />9. While thinking bout him/her...your heart will beat faster and faster... 
<br /><br />8. By listening to his/her voice...you'll smile for no reason. 
<br /><br />7. While looking at him/her..you cant see the other people around you...you can only see that person... 
<br /><br />6. You'll start listening to SLOW songs. 
<br /><br />5. He/She becomes all you think about. 
<br /><br />4. You'll get high just by their smell... 
<br /><br />3. You'll realize that you're always smiling to yourself when you think about them.. 
<br /><br />2. You'll do anything for him/her... 
<br /><br />1. While reading this, there was one person on your mind the whole time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7b380eb85414781926cd8c81374a2bda" url=""><![CDATA[the last two<br/><br/>Daniel and Jasmine are sitting alone in the park one 
<br />night.... 
<br />Daniel: I guess we are the left overs in this world 
<br /><br />Jasmine: I think so... All of my friends have boyfriends and we are 
<br />only the 
<br />2 people left in this world without a special person in our lives 
<br /><br />Daniel: Yup, I don't know what to do 
<br /><br />Jasmine: I know! We'll play a game 
<br /><br />Daniel: What game? 
<br /><br />Jasmine: i'll be your girlfriend for 30 days and you will be my 
<br />boyfriend 
<br /><br />Daniel: That's a great plan. In fact, i don't have anything to do 
<br />for the following weeks... 
<br /><br />DAY 1: 
<br />They watched their first movie and they both touched in a romantic 
<br />film 
<br /><br />DAY 4: 
<br /><br />They went to the beach and had a picnic...Daniel and Jasmine have their 
<br />quality time together 
<br /><br />DAY 12: 
<br /><br />Daniel invited Jasmine to a circus and they rode on a Horror 
<br />House....Jasmine was scared and she tried to touched Daniel's hand but she 
<br />touched someone else's hand and they both laughed... 
<br /><br />DAY 15: 
<br /><br />They saw a fortune teller down the road and they asked for their future 
<br />advice and the fortune teller said: &quot;My darling, Please don't waste the time 
<br />of your life... Spend the rest of your time together happily&quot; Then tears 
<br />flow out from the teller's eyes 
<br /><br />DAY 20: 
<br /><br />Jasmine invited Daniel to go to the hill and they saw a meteor...Jasmine 
<br />mumbled something 
<br /><br />DAY 28: 
<br /><br />They sat on the bus and because of a bumpy road, Jasmine gave her first 
<br />kiss to Daniel by accident 
<br /><br />DAY 29: 
<br /><br />11:37pm 
<br /><br />Jasmine and Daniel sat in the park where they first decided to play this 
<br />game... 
<br /><br />Daniel: I'm thirsty Jasmine...Do you want any drinks? I'll buy you one.. 
<br />I'll just go down the road 
<br /><br />Jasmine: Apple juice, that's all 
<br /><br />Daniel: Wait for me.... 
<br /><br />20mins later... a stranger approached Jasmine 
<br /><br />Stranger: Are you a friend of Daniels? 
<br /><br />Jasmine: Why yes? What happened? 
<br /><br />Stranger: A reckless drunk driver ran over Daniel and he is critical 
<br />condition in the hospital 
<br /><br />11:57pm 
<br /><br />The doctor came out of the emergency room and he handed Jasmine an apple 
<br />juice and a letter 
<br /><br />Doctor: We found this in daniel's pocket 
<br /><br />Jasmine reads the letter and it says: 
<br /><br />Jasmine, This past few days, i realized you are a really cute girl and i am 
<br />really falling for you..Your cherished smile your everything when we 
<br />played this game..... 
<br /><br />Before this game would end...I would like you to be 
<br />my girl friend for the rest of my life.... I love you Jasmine.... 
<br /><br />Jasmine crumples the paper and shouts: 
<br /><br />&quot;Daniel ! i don't want you to die... I love you...Remember that night when 
<br />we saw a meteor, I mumbled something... I mumbled that I wish we would be 
<br />together forever and never end this game. Please don't leave me Daniel.... 
<br />I love you! You cannot do this to me!&quot; 
<br /><br />Then the clock strikes 12 
<br /><br />Daniel's heart stopped pumping 
<br /><br />THEN IT WAS THE 30TH DAY........ 
<br /><br />************************************************* 
<br /><br />Always love your loved ones and show them how you feel before it is too 
<br />late... You will never know when they will be gone ... If you were given a 
<br />time to bestow petals of everlasting compassion and love to your loved 
<br />ones? 
<br />Today is the day.... Love them while they are still here...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c9d30b503e7c43a0f9f612093af16fc8" url=""><![CDATA[Because you are my friend<br/><br/>When you are sad 
<br />I will dry your tears. 
<br /><br />When you are scared 
<br />I will comfort your fears. 
<br /><br />When you are worried 
<br />I will give you hope. 
<br /><br />When you are confused 
<br />I will help you cope. 
<br /><br />And when you are lost 
<br />and can't see the light. 
<br /><br />I shall be your beacon 
<br />shining ever so bright. 
<br /><br />This is my oath 
<br />I pledge till the end. 
<br /><br />Why you may ask 
<br />because you're my friend.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="50673d41de04fe02360da454cb095094" url=""><![CDATA[i asked you a question<br/><br/>I asked u if u liked me, 
<br />u said no. 
<br />i asked u if i was pretty, 
<br />u said no. 
<br /><br />i asked u if i was in ur heart 
<br />u said no, 
<br />i asked u if u would cry if i walked away, 
<br />u said no. 
<br /><br />So i walked away.. 
<br />u grabbed my arm and said... 
<br /><br />i dont like u 
<br />i love u .. 
<br />ur not pretty 
<br />ur beautiful.. 
<br /><br />ur not in my heart, 
<br />u r my heart... 
<br />and i wouldnt cry if u walked 
<br />away i would die.....
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>