<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="64f3699bc76dc2f9bc37985f1195467c" url=""><![CDATA[Oro Verde Shipwreck<br/><br/>The Oro Verde (meaning Green Gold) shipwreck in Grand Cayman has been a favorite site for divers since she was sunk on May 31, 1980 by the Caymanian government.  The vessel a 131-foot 692-ton freighter lies in about 50 feet of water just off Grand Cayman's famous Seven Mile Beach.  The wreck has deteriorated a lot since her reefing, mainly as a result of several hurricanes that have hit the island in the last 30 years.  The debris field today is scattered over a wide area with only the bow section still intact.
<br />The following is an article from the Sarasota Herald-Tribune dated Sunday, August 10, 1980 three months after the Oro Verde was reefed.
<br />New Target Found For Cayman Divers
<br />N.Y. Times News Service
<br />Scuba divers on Grand Cayman Island in the Caribbean have a new target to examine:  A 692-ton Panamanian cargo ship that has been deliberately sunk in 60 feet of water off the island's Seven Mile Beach.
<br />The vessel, the 131-foot Oro Verde, had been stuck on a sandbar after it ran aground off the 17-mile long island's North Sound four years ago.  A group of Grand Cayman divers then hit on the idea of stimulating diving interest by salvaging the freighter and sinking it 300 yards offshore from the beach and hotel area.
<br />The divers sought contributions to the project from hotels, airlines and other tourist organizations and purchased the salvage rights from the Caymanian government.  Then, before towing the Oro Verde to its new site, they cleaned it and removed the watches, doors, glass and rough edges to make it as safe as possible.
<br />&quot;The removal of the doors and hatches also created a lovelier site by allowing more sunlight to filter through to the ship's interior,&quot; said Horace DuQuesnay, a tour company representative who lives on the island and participated in the salvage.  &quot;The wreck will become more beautiful over the years as the colored coral becomes an integral part of the ship.&quot;
<br />The story of the Oro Verde is a rather interesting one.  She was originally built as a &quot;liberty ship&quot; to carry cargo for the US Navy.  Once the ship was retired from the Navy, she was registered in Nassau and ran freight to and from North America, Latin America and the Caribbean.
<br />The ship was once almost blown up in Miami with a homemade bomb in a cigar box.  See the following story from the Miami Herald dated October 19, 1966.
<br />Cigar Box Bomb Attached to Ship
<br />By Gene Miller
<br />Herald Staff Writer
<br />A homemade bomb in a cigar box, attached by a magnet to the hull of a British cargo ship, failed to explode at the Miami City Docks Tuesday - apparently because an undersea bomber didn't set it correctly.  &quot;It should have gone off,&quot; said Capt. Tom Brodie, chief of the Sheriff's office bomb squad.  The ship the 180-foot 692-ton Oro Verde, was due to sail late in the day for a five-day trip to Cristobal, Panama. From there, after unloading, its normal route takes it through the Panama Canal to Ecuador.
<br />&quot;We don't have the slightest idea why anyone would want to blow up our ship,&quot; said Robert Trost, operations manager for Chester, Blackburn &amp; Roder Inc., Miami agents.  Horace Barron, a crane operator loading general cargo, first noticed something peculiar attached to the hull several feet below the water line.  &quot;He'd looked at it for a couple of hours and didn't know what to think,&quot; said Bob Kretzschmar, a sheriff's deputy assigned to docks.  The ship was on the north side of Pier C, berth three.  But before it arrived there at 7 a.m., it had unloaded bananas at the parking lot dock of the Banana Supply Co. on the river. The ship reached Miami Sunday.
<br />&quot;The crane operator started talking to the crew and someone finally decided to call the Coast Guard,&quot; said Kretzschmar.  &quot;The Coast Guard took one look and said 'Call the bomb squad.'&quot; This was at 11:28 a.m.  Capt. Brodie, accustomed to frequent false reports, also needed but a single glance. He took off his shoes and shirt, jumped in, and deactivated it.  The time-bomb, put inside a wooden Cuban cigar box consisted of a cast-made explosive, pentalite, and weighed about two pounds.  Attached to it was an acid pellet triggering device floating underwater in a prophylactic. It looked like a ping-pong ball in a balloon from the surface.  When the pellet or ampule is crushed, the acid begins to eat at the wire. When the wire gives, a spring releases a hammer which strikes the primmer of the cap.  &quot;Someone didn't set it right,&quot; said Capt. Brodie. &quot;It should have gone off.&quot;
<br />Pentalite, he said, is a &quot;very high order explosive, a step above TNT or the normal plastic explosives. It would have blown quite a hole in the hull.&quot;  Investigators said they didn't know whether or not the ship would have sunk.  Capt. Brodie said that pentalite is often used by militant Cuban exiles here. There was one unverified report that the CIA once had an interest in the ship.  Trost, the agency manager, discounted thoughts of anyone trying to blow up the ship in the Panama Canal. &quot;The detonating device was of much too short duration for that,&quot; he said. &quot;It sure is odd.&quot;
<br />The ship, registered as British, is managed by a crew of 17. Wendell Phillips, a U.S. citizen, is the captain.  Trost, as well as police, believed that the bomb was attached to the ship in the Miami River sometime prior to loading at Pier C.  Yet police said they couldn't tell how long it had been there.  Sheriff skindiver Ed Zender explored the underside of the hull for other bombs and Deputies J. K. Russell and James Askew searched the ship.  Neither Capt. Phillips nor John. W. Tatcher, owner of the vessel, could offer any possible motive for sabotage.  The ship, built in 1942, once was an Army cargo vessel, Phillips said.  &quot;All we do is carry bananas from Ecuador and general cargo from Miami to the Canal Zone,&quot; said Thatcher.
<br />The Oro Verde is supposedly a sistership to the infamous USS Pueblo (although documentation is very shaky). The ship was sold by the Navy and began operations as a merchant cargo ship sailing in the Caribbean and South America and is thought to mainly carry bananas on a regular basis.  She became a drug smuggling ship late in her life and ran aground in Grand Cayman in 1976.  She was on the reef several years until a consortium of local diver operators got together with the local government to turn the ship into an artificial reef.  Local dive lore tells that the Captain of the ship hoped to make one last large deal to retire more comfortably and had a large amount of marijuana on board the Oro Verde.  While on route to Grand Cayman the crew of the ship found out about the Marijuana and confronted the captain, seeking a share of the profits since they would be prosecuted if caught with the ship and the drugs.  The Captain is said to have refused and the crew killed him and threw him overboard.  The crew then not knowing the local waters ran the ship aground.  When the authorities were notified the crew had abandoned ship and the marijuana was confiscated and burned on the south end of the island.  The story also goes on to say that the prevailing winds were blowing from the southeast to the northwest and everyone on the islands was reportedly quite happy for  several days.
<br />The Dive
<br />The ship wreckage and surrounding reefs are home to many species of sea animals, fish and corals, making this one of the most popular shallow dives in Grand Cayman, often frequented after a deeper wall dive or on a night dive.  Though it was in pristine condition when it was sunk and lying on her starboard in the sand next door to a patch of reef, the wreck's finer details have since given way to the force of time; passing hurricanes have broken, rolled and scattered the vessel across a wide debris field closer to the reef. Still, the Oro Verde remains a great example of a thriving artificial reef.
<br />The buoy is attached to the bow section which is the only remaining intact part of the wreck.  There are no longer any ways to penetrate the wreck but you can look into the bow section through a couple of port holes.  The debris field flows primarily from the bow section to the north along several coral fingers.  The diver can choose to spend all or part of the dive on the wreck and part of the dive on the reef. There is a wide variety of reef fish such as parrotfish, sergeant majors, angelfish, silversides (seasonally), schoolmasters, large groupers and moray eels as well as crustaceans such as the arrow crab and rough file clam
<br />This is a very worthwhile dive still and I especially like it as a night dive for the variety of marine species that are present.  The Oro Verde lies about 100 yards off shore so advanced divers in good physical condition could reach it as a shore dive but with the long swim and requisite dive flags and floats due to offshore boat traffic, why bother? All of the local dive operators will be happy to take you to the Oro Verde as your second half of a two tank west side boat dive, an afternoon dive or on a night dive.  I would urge you to dive the wreck whether it is the first time or it you have dove on the wreck before.  The site is constantly changing and the marine species always make for an interesting dive.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2f9a24e16a906db684c91c8ee536628c" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Andes Wall<br/><br/>When you are on your next scuba diving trip to Grand Cayman make a point to dive on &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F2012%2F01%2F16%2Fdiving-andes-wall%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/2012/01/16/diving-andes-wall/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Andes Wall&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Andes Wall&lt;/a&gt;, you will certainly not regret it. It is certainly one of my favorite sites on the island and is accessible from the West Side dive boat operators or out of Rum Point. This is a great wall dive and is a premium spot for underwater photography. Andes Wall is located just past Rum Point on the North Wall. Typical conditions are 100+ feet of visibility and there is a sheer drop along the wall of several thousand feet. On this dive you will see Spotted Eagle Rays on almost every dive. There are also other pelagics that can be found here from the elusive Tiger Shark to White Tips, Hammerheads and more.
<br /><br />I went with Red Sail Sports on my last dive at Andes Wall and the day was absolutely perfect for underwater photography. It was one of those extremely rare days when the north wall was absolutely flat. The visibility was over 150, no current, very little particulates in the water and there were only 8 divers on the boat. This must be paradise. Andes Wall is just about 10 to 15 minutes past Rum Point on the North Side and one of my two favorite dive sites on the North Wall.
<br />You can dive this site on top of the wall or as a wall dive and I would highly recommend the wall dive. When we descended to the mooring the first thing I noticed on this dive was a Spotted Eagle Ray in the distance and a Great Barracuda cruising by. This was one of seven that I saw on this dive. After meeting at the mooring pin, we head to the wall notch, the visibility is absolutely phenomenal. We then made our way through the &quot;notch&quot; to the wall and immediately on my left was another Spotted Eagle Ray. This is going to be a great dive.
<br /><br />As we move past the 90 foot level out to the wall I notice a number of Blackcap Basslets swimming upside down in a small indentation in the wall. There are a great variety of fish usually on this dive. Today we see Schoolmasters, numerous types of Basslets, Princess Parrotfish, Bermuda Chub, Blue Chromis, Trumpetfish, Gray Angelfish, Spiny Lobsters, Spotted Eagle Rays and much, much more. The soft corals are amazing on this part of the island and they are especially plentiful around the mooring ball on this dive. You will find several great places to get photos of sea fans, or sea rods, sea whips and of course many colorful stony corals as well. Then I got one of my better shots of the trip. I was setting up to take a shot of a Giant Slit-Pore Sea Rod and looking up towards the sun to frame the soft coral I noticed one of the Spotted EagleRays that had been following us throughout the dive and repositioned slightly and the rest...well I will leave it up to the photo to speak for itself. Needless to say I think I found a great image....
<br /><br />This place is magic and as a scuba diver this is a must dive when you come to Grand Cayman and if you are an &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving and Underwater Photography&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photographer&lt;/a&gt;, perhaps you can make a little magic of your own.
<br /><br />The pool is open.....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7e3bdc2dec70a90ef11c57fc42537214" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Maui - Carthaginian II<br/><br/>Carthaginian  II Background
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCarthiginian-Shipwreck%2FG0000uhmxfmGxkic%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Carthiginian-Shipwreck/G0000uhmxfmGxkic/&quot</a>; title=&quot;The Carthaginian II Gallery&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Carthaginian II&lt;/a&gt;, once used as a whaling museum, is a replica of a 19th century brig similar to the ships that first brought commerce to the Hawaiian Islands. The ship was a cement carrier built in Germany in 1920 and rechristened the Carthaginian II. It sailed to Lahaina in 1973 where it took seven years for the historically accurate 18th century whaling ship rigging to be assembled. The ship served as a reminder of Lahaina's nautical heritage and was docked for many years at Lahaina Harbor. The ship was owned by the Lahaina Carthaginian Restoration Foundation which operated the museum on board that displayed relics of Lahaina's historic whaling days.
<br /><br />Although it had no true historical value, the Carthaginian II was one of Lahaina's most recognizable attractions, featured in thousands of artworks and visitor photographs for over the 30 years.
<br /><br />The ship belonged to the nonprofit Lahaina Restoration Foundation, which was spending $50,000 a year to maintain the rusting hulk. When marine engineers advised against further repairs because of the increasing costs, Atlantis was approached to claim the vessel and use it as an artificial reef which would in turn enhance the existing Atlantis submarine tours in Lahaina.
<br /><br />On December 13, 2005, following two years of preparation, Atlantis Adventures sank the Carthaginian off Lahaina, Maui, creating an artificial reef that will have lasting marine life benefits. The reefing took place off Puamana which is just outside the Lahaina harbor. The 97-foot, steel-hulled vessel, sank in 95 feet of water where it will serve as an artificial reef.
<br /><br />The first Carthaginian was a replica of a whaling supply vessel used for the 1966 movie &quot;Hawaii,&quot; based on the James Michener novel. The Lahaina Restoration Foundation purchased the wooden boat, but it sank in 1972 on its way to O'ahu for dry dock. The German vessel was acquired and was rechristened the Carthaginian II and after extensive work served the city as a floating museum for many years.
<br /><br />Atlantis spent approximately $350,000 on the Carthaginian project, including preparation of environmental studies. American Marine Services was hired to handle reefing operation. Before the Carthaginian II was towed from Lahaina Harbor, entertainers from the Old Lahaina Lu'au performed &quot;Aloha 'Oe&quot; and members of the Lahaina Restoration Foundation placed lei on the vessel and held signs bidding it aloha.
<br /><br />To prepare for the sinking, 10 tons of concrete had been loaded on board, adding to the 35 tons of material the boat already was carrying. Atlantis' small tugboat Roxie pulled the Carthaginian II out of the harbor before transferring the operation to the larger American Islander tugboat.
<br /><br />A flotilla of about 20 boats was waiting when the Carthaginian II arrived at Puamana, and spectators lined the shore or pulled over on Honoapi'ilani Highway to watch the spectacle. Kahu Charles Kaupu offered a Hawaiian blessing, and after a 3-ton anchor was secured to the bow and the boat was in position, patches were removed from two sets of holes that had been cut into the hull about 18 inches above the water line. Seawater was pumped into the hull, and 27 minutes later the Carthaginian was headed to the sandy bottom.
<br /><br />Observers let loose with applause and whoops of appreciation as the ship quietly slipped beneath the surface. Aboard the Atlantis shuttle boat three air-shattering blasts were fired from miniature brass cannon to mark the occasion.
<br /><br />The Dive
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-maui-carthaginian-ii%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/scuba-diving-maui-carthaginian-ii/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui - Carthaginian II&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Carthaginian&lt;/a&gt; lies in about 90 feet of water of the coast of Lahina. It is about a 10 to 15 minute trip from the harbor to the dive site. The ship was sunk approximately 6 years ago and now supports a wide variety of marine life. When you begin to descend from the mooring ball you will normally be able to see the outline of the ship quite easily. The visibility is usually 80+ feet and much of the time over 100+ feet.  This is a great diven for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Underwater Photography&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt; for both wide angle and macro shots.  There can be some current on this site so some divers may want to descend using the mooring line. As you descend you will begin to notice more details regarding the ship and the impacts of being on the reef for about 6 years. The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCarthiginian-Shipwreck%2FG0000uhmxfmGxkic%2FI0000Lbr_z2vb55I%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Carthiginian-Shipwreck/G0000uhmxfmGxkic/I0000Lbr_z2vb55I&quot</a>; title=&quot;Collapsed Main Mast&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;main mast collapsed&lt;/a&gt; in mid-summer 2011 and can now be seen sitting on the deck. The main cabin roof and walls have deteriorated to some degree and there are numerous holes into the hold. The access to the hold itself is quite large and easily accessible. The engine room and forward compartment is blocked by a gate but you can still get a good variety of photos in this area. The rear area of the cargo hold is fairly clear and at the present time will contain various fish species or crustaceans as they are moving about the ship.
<br /><br />There are a number of frogfish on the wreck. I was able to photograph five different &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2FI0000HjGaAvCVJg8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/I0000HjGaAvCVJg8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Commerson's Frogfish&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;frogfish&lt;/a&gt; on my last dive. These fish are extremely well placed for macro photos and can consume a lot of bottom time, but it is well worth the effort. Two frogfish were on the main deck to the rear of the main cabin and three were on the starboard side about the midships area.
<br /><br />You will also find a wide variety of fish including,&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Pictures of Hawaiian Fish&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Pacific Trumpetfish, Sergeant Majors, Dascyllus, Orangespine Unicornfish, Rainbow Cleaner Wrasse,&lt;/a&gt; and many more.
<br /><br />This dive is best when there are less than ten divers in the water since the ship itself is not very large. It is a very worthwhile dive and I highly recommend it for your next trip to Maui.
<br /><br />Check out images of other wrecks on my website at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.stevenwsmeltzer.com</a> or visit my blog blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com or follow me on Twitter at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitter.com%2Fimages2inspire"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.twitter.com/images2inspire</a>   
<br /><br />The pool is open...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ab1e670a766080f0f285cf0828cb946a" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Maui - Mala Pier<br/><br/>&lt;h3&gt;Description&lt;/h3&gt;
<br />&lt;a title=&quot;Mala Pier Gallery&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FMala-Pier%2FG0000QHG5zSrvxC0%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Mala-Pier/G0000QHG5zSrvxC0&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mala Pier&lt;/a&gt; is without a doubt one of the top if not the top shore dive on Maui and especially on the leeward side of the island near Kaanapali. The pier is in the middle of Lahina near the Canary Mall. When you are driving along the highway from Kaanapali back towards Kahului you can see the pier on the right just as you start into Lahina. This is an extremely easy boat dive and a moderately easy shore dive (only difficulty is the entry if you go over the reef on the side of the pier). The dive itself is between 15 to 35 feet and you can spend well over an hourwith no problems depending upon your air consumption. This site is loaded with all kinds of &lt;a title=&quot;Pictures of Hawaiian Fish&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bschooling"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot;&gt;schooling</a> fish, White-tip Reef Sharks, lots of Butterflyfishes&lt;/a&gt;, Green Sea Turtles and Hawksbill Turtles and much more making it an excellent site for underwater photography.
<br />The pier was built in the early 1900's by the Dole Pineapple company to be able to offload pineapples from Lanai and have them processed at the Pineapple Cannery in Lahina which is now the Cannery Mall. The pier for a variety of reasons was never used by the Dole Company but did see service in WWII for loading and unloading supplies. The concrete pier stood until 1992 when it was destroyed in hurricane Iniki. However, the destruction of the pier has been a boon for scuba divers in Maui.
<br />&lt;h3&gt;The Dive&lt;/h3&gt;
<br />This site makes a great morning or afternoon dive and is spectacular as a night dive, but I would recommend that you dive the site first during the day before attempting a night dive. Visibility is usually quite good, from 60 feet and up. There is no current to speak of and the site is quite easy to navigate. You swim out with the remains of the pier and then turn around and follow them back to shore. No worries. There are a few coral mounds in the sand surrounding the pier which are also quite interesting and make for great macro photography but you should be a reasonable navigator to investigate these other sites.
<br />To enter the site, there is ample parking found at the pier and there is also a place to rinse your gear after the dive at the top of the boat ramp. The dive site can be entered in one of two ways, entering via the beach on the west side of the pier that is still standing or walking down the boat ramp but don't tell anyone I recommended the second option….
<br />If you enter from the beach this is best done when there is a high tide as you will have to cross a veryshallow reef and will most likely have to walk part of the way out. One suggestion is to float your gear and not put on your fins or BC until you reach deeper water. To understand the tides you can check with Google or go to tides.info and search for tidal information for Lahina.
<br />Once you are past the reef you will quickly get to about 15 feet of water and can begin your dive. You will notice many &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FMala-Pier%2FG0000QHG5zSrvxC0%2FI00004HlDTqPzU1M%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Mala-Pier/G0000QHG5zSrvxC0/I00004HlDTqPzU1M&quot</a>; title=&quot;Mala Pier Gallery&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Keetail Needlefish &lt;/a&gt;around the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FMala-Pier%2FG0000QHG5zSrvxC0%2FI0000pkq9LbvEcNI%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Mala-Pier/G0000QHG5zSrvxC0/I0000pkq9LbvEcNI&quot</a>; title=&quot;Mala Pier&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;standing and fallen columns&lt;/a&gt; of the pier. You will also see a number of juvenile fish of a variety of species in this same area. As you move further along the pier you will encounter a variety of corals attached to the pier and a number of different types of Butterflyfishes, Bird Wrasses, Goatfishes, Green Sea Turtles and much more.If you are looking for sharks you can almost guarantee that you will see several &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FMala-Pier%2FG0000QHG5zSrvxC0%2FI0000dw2XVQPbwv0%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Mala-Pier/G0000QHG5zSrvxC0/I0000dw2XVQPbwv0&quot</a>; title=&quot;White-tip Reef Shark&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;White-tip reef sharks&lt;/a&gt; on this dive. There is usually one or more resting under the fallen columns towards the far end of the pier. You will also see sharks resting on the bottom typically on the western side of the pier usually about mid-way down. You can also encounter these sharks as they are cruising around the ruble in search of their next meal. Don't worry they won't bother divers unless they are significantly provoked. So approach slowly and then take time to appreciate these marvelous creatures.
<br />This is a great dive site so take your time to truly appreciate it. If you need to rent tanks check out Lahina Divers, they are my favorite dive operation on Maui, but you can also rent from a number of other locations.
<br />You can see the complete photo gallery for Mala Pier at &lt;a title=&quot;Mala Pier Photo Gallery&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FMala-Pier%2FG0000QHG5zSrvxC0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Mala-Pier/G0000QHG5zSrvxC0/&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;stevenwsmeltzer.com&lt;/a&gt; as well as more on &lt;a title=&quot;Underwater and Landscape Photogaphy&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-list%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bunderwater"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-list&quot;&gt;underwater</a> photography&lt;/a&gt; and landscape photography or you can follow me on Twitter at &lt;a title=&quot;Images2Inspire&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fimages2inspire%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://twitter.com/images2inspire&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Images2Inspire&lt;/a&gt;.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="39271bbc646b968edfa16f3fcf6c71bf" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - USS Kittiwake<br/><br/>This is a great &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; site that just past the one year anniversary of the reefing of the ship.  The following is an overview of the dive,  some history and information regarding the ship and an overview of what you will find on the wreck.  I have also just added over two dozen new photos to the gallery in honor of the one year anniversary of the reefing.  View the complete &lt;a title=&quot;USS Kittiwake Photo Gallery&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FKittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bphoto"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/&quot;&gt;photo</a> gallery&lt;/a&gt;  on my website and see my blog entry for the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-uss-kittiwake-shipwreck%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-uss-kittiwake-shipwreck/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman &quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; USS Kittiwake&lt;/a&gt; for more information on the wreck and a history of the ship.
<br /><br />The Dive:
<br /><br />The ship was  sunk January 5, 2011 off the north end of Seven Mile Beach in Grand Cayman.
<br /><br />There are 5 decks on the 47 foot tall &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUSS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000Wcb0w0RopvI%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/USS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000Wcb0w0RopvI&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USS Kittiwake&lt;/a&gt;. Externally, the crow's nest, mast and large stern a-frame have been cut down and remounted to make her height suitable for Cayman waters. The upper decks accommodate the 2 bridges (both an external and internal bridge to allow operations in heavy seas) along with the radio and navigation room. The sonar has been removed. The Captain and XO's quarters are also on the upper decks.
<br /><br />On the main deck, from bow to stern, internally you will find the rec room, mess hall, ironing room, small tool workshop and recompression chambers. You will note the large &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUSS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000nrOSPnFJRtU%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/USS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000nrOSPnFJRtU&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving USS Kittiwake&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a-frame structure&lt;/a&gt; on the stern that supported submarines and hard hat divers, as well as the diving bell where divers would enter to return to the ship from the ocean and then be placed in the chambers for decompression.
<br /><br />Below the main deck, 2 decks exist that include the crews quarter, medic/hospital station, engine and propulsion rooms,&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUSS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000QmV9jUuDJyQ%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/USS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000QmV9jUuDJyQ&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving USS Kittiwake&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; air bank storage&lt;/a&gt; and compressors, as well as the steering gear, shaft, gyro, ammunition lockers, cold storage and barber shop to name a few areas. While the USS Kittiwake has been opened up with large&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUSS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000evHtkg3GaYQ%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/USS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000evHtkg3GaYQ&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving USS Kittiwake&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; access holes&lt;/a&gt; both vertically and horizontally, every space on the ship was used while in service.
<br /><br />Be sure to plan your dive adequately. I would recommend heading to the stern before entry into the ship to get photographs around the&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUSS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000MlfKl.47lgI%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/USS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000MlfKl.47lgI&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving USS Kittiwake&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &quot;USS Kittiwake&quot; logo&lt;/a&gt; on the stern and also get photographs by the screw (propeller) and rudder.  For Scuba Divers that plan on penetrating the wreck, you can then make your way to the top of the ship and enter via the main funnel which is located on the Bridge Deck.  If you do not plan on penetrating the wreck you can start your exploration on the main deck just above the Screw.
<br /><br />The main &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUSS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000ndu7PcxF.bM%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/USS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000ndu7PcxF.bM&quot</a>; title=&quot;Underwater Photography USS Kittiwake&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;funnel entry makes an excellent underwater photograph&lt;/a&gt; and I would suggest taking the photo looking up from the bottom of the funnel to the top of the funnel.  I would suggest silhouetting one of your dive buddies diving down into the wreck.  You can then exit the shaft on the first platform or in the hold.  Note the hold deck does not have any exterior exit points and is not recommended for divers that do not have an advanced certification and prior wreck experience.  When you exit to the first platform you will be able to see the Engineering logo in the Motor Room area/engineering section.  This area is easily accessible and makes for a very good underwater photograph near the &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUSS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000Y0UeUwX5JJc%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/USS-Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000Y0UeUwX5JJc&quot</a>; title=&quot;USS Kittiwake Shipwreck&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Engineering Mural&lt;/a&gt;&quot;.  The silt can be heavy here so you need to move slowly to prevent clouding up the water.  For advanced divers/wreck divers, you can also check out shaft alley and the forward hold areas of the ship.  For others you can explore the various compartments on the first platform and then begin making your way up deck by deck and then finally arriving at the Bridge (Pilot House) where you can do you safety stop as it is at about 5 to 6 meters or 15 to 18 feet.
<br /><br />Check out images of other &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FShipwrecks%2FG0000OtMyTETA74I%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Shipwrecks/G0000OtMyTETA74I/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;shipwrecks&lt;/a&gt; on my website or visit my &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-uss-kittiwake-shipwreck%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-uss-kittiwake-shipwreck/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; for reviews of specific shipwrecks or follow me on Twitter:@Images2Inspire.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24f746c0bde584771f70b1b42256b6ab" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Big Tunnels<br/><br/>&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-big-tunnels%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-big-tunnels/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Big Tunnels&lt;/a&gt; is one of the better dives on the west side of Grand Cayman.  It has a large passageway, &quot;tunnel&quot; that is wide enough for a couple of buses to pass side by side and dumps out to the wall at about 100 feet.  There are a number of spiral routes up through the coral where you can find a wide variety of marine life including a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2FI0000A_K0nSjL98Y%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/I0000A_K0nSjL98Y&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scub Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;number of Tarpon&lt;/a&gt;, usually congregated in one of the passages ways just down from the top of the wall.  
<br /><br />You will find &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FSponges%2FG0000AUYkLv.mB8M%2FI0000_fqiiufDMLQ%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Sponges/G0000AUYkLv.mB8M/I0000_fqiiufDMLQ&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Yellow Tube sponges&lt;/a&gt;, Spiny Lobsters, several small Bubble-tip Annenome colonies, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2FI0000ggGjV7ysqyk%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/I0000ggGjV7ysqyk&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Schoolmasters&lt;/a&gt;, Green Sea turtles as well as &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI0000hCUIZEWd99o%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I0000hCUIZEWd99o&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Hawksbill&lt;/a&gt; in the area and much more. You may also see a Spotted Eagle Ray off the wall, so make sure you take the chance to &quot;peer into the blue&quot; as you are swimming along the wall.  The site can have current as it is close to the west end of the island and it can also be fairly turbid at times.  However, most of the time you will find good to excellent visibility and a good spot for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt;.  
<br /><br />As you exit the tunnel on the wall you can usually get a great shot of the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUnderwater-World%2FG0000rThUYFy4ACc%2FI0000Ev8xFEgwv8E%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Underwater-World/G0000rThUYFy4ACc/I0000Ev8xFEgwv8E&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wall&lt;/a&gt; with the sun backlighting the tope of the wall.  When taking wide angel shots at&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI0000Ev8xFEgwv8E%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I0000Ev8xFEgwv8E&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Big Tunnerls&lt;/a&gt;, and other places along the wall remember to have your strobes are aimed &quot;out&quot; as as much as possible to avoid picking unwanted back scatter.  
<br /><br />As you come up to the top of the wall you will find a good variety of health soft and hard corals, including rope sponges, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2FI0000s7H79t5AxsI%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/I0000s7H79t5AxsI&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;brain corals&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2FI0000Ew.e6H2x5_0%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/I0000Ew.e6H2x5_0&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;star corals&lt;/a&gt;, barrel sponges, sea whips as well as a variety of crustaceans.  This is a very relaxed dive with good variety typical of the west wall.  Overall I rate this site highly, but I tend to prefer Bonnie's Arch and Northwest Point (if the current is not bad) and Orange Canyon.
<br />  View other underwater photography images on my website at &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&lt;/a&gt</a>; or visit my blog &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com&lt;/a&gt; or follow me on Twitter @ &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.twitter.com%2Fimages2inspire%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.twitter.com/images2inspire&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;images2inspire&lt;/a&gt;
<br />  The pool is open...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="60644d913c42e8e5aa3f8d954d33aa8c" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Oro Verde<br/><br/>The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oro Verde shipwreck&lt;/a&gt; in Grand Cayman has been a favorite site for divers since she was sunk on May 31, 1980 by the Cayman government.  The vessel a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FOro-Verde%2FG0000oIFpDg4SWto%2FI0000I55grfjXZj0%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Oro-Verde/G0000oIFpDg4SWto/I0000I55grfjXZj0&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;131-foot 692-ton freighte&lt;/a&gt;r lies in about 50 feet of water just off Grand Cayman's famous Seven Mile Beach.  The wreck has deteriorated a lot since her reefing, mainly as a result of several hurricanes that have hit the island in the last 30 years. &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FOro-Verde%2FG0000oIFpDg4SWto%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Oro-Verde/G0000oIFpDg4SWto/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The debris field&lt;/a&gt; today is scattered over a wide area with only the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FOro-Verde%2FG0000oIFpDg4SWto%2FI0000I.h2e7kuj2s%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Oro-Verde/G0000oIFpDg4SWto/I0000I.h2e7kuj2s&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Oro Verde&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;bow section &lt;/a&gt; still intact.
<br /><br />You can read about the history and background of the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-oro-verde-shipwreck%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-oro-verde-shipwreck/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oro Verde&lt;/a&gt; on my &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; and view the complete &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FOro-Verde%2FG0000oIFpDg4SWto%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Oro-Verde/G0000oIFpDg4SWto&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photo gallery&lt;/a&gt; on my website.
<br />&lt;h3&gt;The Dive&lt;/h3&gt;
<br />The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FOro-Verde%2FG0000oIFpDg4SWto%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Oro-Verde/G0000oIFpDg4SWto/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;shipwreck&lt;/a&gt; and surrounding reefs are home to a variety of marine life including, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fish&lt;/a&gt;, turtles, custaceans and corals, making this one of the most popular shallow &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dives in Grand Cayman&lt;/a&gt;, often frequented after a deeper wall dive or on a night dive.  Though it was in pristine condition when it was sunk and lying on her starboard in the sand next door to a patch of reef, the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wreck's&lt;/a&gt; finer details have since given way to the force of time; passing hurricanes have broken, rolled and scattered the vessel across a wide debris field closer to the reef. Still, the&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Oro Verde&lt;/a&gt;remains a great example of a thriving&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FOro-Verde%2FG0000oIFpDg4SWto%2FI0000egxo.Zip33U%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Oro-Verde/G0000oIFpDg4SWto/I0000egxo.Zip33U&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; artificial reef.&lt;/a&gt; The buoy is attached to the bow section which is the only remaining intact part of the wreck.  There are no longer any ways to penetrate the wreck but you can look into the bow section through a couple of port holes.  &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FShipwrecks%2FG0000OtMyTETA74I%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Shipwrecks/G0000OtMyTETA74I/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The debris field&lt;/a&gt; flows primarily from the bow section to the north along several coral fingers.  The diver can choose to spend all or part of the dive on the wreck and part of the dive on the reef. There is a wide variety of reef fish such as &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Parrotfish, Sergeant Majors, Angelfish, Silversides&lt;/a&gt; (seasonally), schoolmasters, large groupers and moray eels as well as crustaceans such as the arrow crab and rough file clam
<br /><br />This is a very worthwhile dive  and I especially like it as a night dive for the variety of marine species that are present.  &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-oro-verde-shipwreck%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-oro-verde-shipwreck/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Oro Verde&lt;/a&gt; lies about 100 yards off shore so advanced divers in good physical condition could reach it as a shore dive but with the long swim and requisite dive flags and floats due to offshore boat traffic, why bother? All of the local dive operators will be happy to take you to the Oro Verde as your second half of a two tank west side boat dive, an afternoon dive or on a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2FI00005Ta8Y0MP5DE%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/I00005Ta8Y0MP5DE&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;night dive&lt;/a&gt;.  I would urge you to dive the wreck whether it is the first time or it you have dove on the wreck before.  The site is constantly changing and the marine species always make for an interesting dive.
<br /><br />Check out images of other wrecks in Grand Cayman the &lt;a title=&quot;Doc Poulson Gallery&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FDoc-Paulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BDoc"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Doc-Paulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/&quot;&gt;Doc</a> Poulson&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a title=&quot;USS Kittiwake Galery&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FKittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BUSS"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/&quot;&gt;USS</a> Kittiwake&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1dfe6449365631c3b7a0c8a7fd8c786b" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Doc Poulson<br/><br/>There are other interesting &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wrecks&lt;/a&gt; in Grand Cayman besides the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FKittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000bmvsFN.fJCU%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000bmvsFN.fJCU&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USS Kittiwake&lt;/a&gt;.The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doc Poulson&lt;/a&gt; is a purpose sunk &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FShipwrecks%2FG0000OtMyTETA74I%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Shipwrecks/G0000OtMyTETA74I/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;shipwreck&lt;/a&gt; on the western part of Grand Cayman.  The ship was originally a Japanese cable laying ship and was sunk in Grand Cayman in 1981 to create an &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FDoc-Poulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2FI0000WBgjSdIBrM0%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Doc-Poulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/I0000WBgjSdIBrM0&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;artificial reef&lt;/a&gt; on Seven Mile beach.  The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FDoc-Poulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Doc-Poulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wreck&lt;/a&gt; site is named for Doc Poulson who helped set up the first hyperbaric chamber on Grand Cayman for the treatment of decompression sickness.
<br /><br />The wreck sits upright in about 50 to 60 feet of water and can be easily explored. However, given the age of the wreck there are many exposed surfaces that can cause harm to a diver.  The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FDoc-Poulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2FI0000jFCzaI21Xf4%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Doc-Poulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/I0000jFCzaI21Xf4&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ship&lt;/a&gt; is about 70 feet in length and the cable wenches can still be seen on deck but are heavily encrusted with corals.  There are a variety of fish in and around the ship from Goliath grouper, to &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FDoc-Poulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2FI0000KWKpgND7DkA%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Doc-Poulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/I0000KWKpgND7DkA&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Queen Conch&lt;/a&gt;, to cleaner shrimp, blue tang and many more.
<br /><br />The wreck sits on a sand flatand is about a 5 minute swim away from the reef.  The clarity of the water in Grand Cayman, along with the upright position of the boat makes it a great place for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt; from the novice to the professional.
<br /><br />The hatches have been removed to make penetration diving easy and safe allowing a diver to explore the decks and the hold of the ship.  The interior of the ship is filled with a good bit of sand, but working your way through the ship is still quite easy even after 30 years on the reef.  As a day dive the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doc Poulson&lt;/a&gt; is a rather small site and is usually combined with diving the reef nearby which is about a 5 minute swim away.  If you take your time however, you can spend most of your dive time at the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wreck&lt;/a&gt;.  However, this is a better &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wreck dive&lt;/a&gt; when there are no more than 5 to 6 divers on the site and great when there are only two.  It can be a good night-dive spot especially for an&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI0000XxEMIuA0TBY%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I0000XxEMIuA0TBY&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; underwater photographer &lt;/a&gt;as you have awide variety of marine life around the wreck including a number of small creatures great for macro shots. There are many sponges, brain corals, Christmastree worms and a nice Social Feather Duster on the stern rail.
<br /><br />For other underwater photographs of the Doc Poulson just click on one of the photographs or go to my &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FDoc-Paulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Doc-Paulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doc Poulson Gallery&lt;/a&gt;.  If you want to find information on other wrecks in Grand Cayman such as the USS Kittiwake you can check out my &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt; and/or view more underwater photographs on my &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-list%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-list&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;website &lt;/a&gt;and/or follow me on Twitter @ Images2Inspire
<br /><br />The pool is open...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a0da880773a108052089049408180c5a" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Doc Poulson<br/><br/>There are other interesting &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wrecks&lt;/a&gt; in Grand Cayman besides the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FKittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2FI0000bmvsFN.fJCU%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/I0000bmvsFN.fJCU&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USS Kittiwake&lt;/a&gt;.The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doc Poulson&lt;/a&gt; is a purpose sunk &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FShipwrecks%2FG0000OtMyTETA74I%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Shipwrecks/G0000OtMyTETA74I/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;shipwreck&lt;/a&gt; on the western part of Grand Cayman.  The ship was originally a Japanese cable laying ship and was sunk in Grand Cayman in 1981 to create an &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FDoc-Poulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2FI0000WBgjSdIBrM0%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Doc-Poulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/I0000WBgjSdIBrM0&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;artificial reef&lt;/a&gt; on Seven Mile beach.  The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FDoc-Poulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Doc-Poulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wreck&lt;/a&gt; site is named for Doc Poulson who helped set up the first hyperbaric chamber on Grand Cayman for the treatment of decompression sickness.
<br /><br />The wreck sits upright in about 50 to 60 feet of water and can be easily explored. However, given the age of the wreck there are many exposed surfaces that can cause harm to a diver.  The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FDoc-Poulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2FI0000jFCzaI21Xf4%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Doc-Poulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/I0000jFCzaI21Xf4&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ship&lt;/a&gt; is about 70 feet in length and the cable wenches can still be seen on deck but are heavily encrusted with corals.  There are a variety of fish in and around the ship from Goliath grouper, to &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FDoc-Poulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2FI0000KWKpgND7DkA%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Doc-Poulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/I0000KWKpgND7DkA&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Queen Conch&lt;/a&gt;, to cleaner shrimp, blue tang and many more.
<br /><br />The wreck sits on a sand flatand is about a 5 minute swim away from the reef.  The clarity of the water in Grand Cayman, along with the upright position of the boat makes it a great place for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt; from the novice to the professional.
<br /><br />The hatches have been removed to make penetration diving easy and safe allowing a diver to explore the decks and the hold of the ship.  The interior of the ship is filled with a good bit of sand, but working your way through the ship is still quite easy even after 30 years on the reef.  As a day dive the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doc Poulson&lt;/a&gt; is a rather small site and is usually combined with diving the reef nearby which is about a 5 minute swim away.  If you take your time however, you can spend most of your dive time at the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wreck&lt;/a&gt;.  However, this is a better &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wreck dive&lt;/a&gt; when there are no more than 5 to 6 divers on the site and great when there are only two.  It can be a good night-dive spot especially for an&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI0000XxEMIuA0TBY%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I0000XxEMIuA0TBY&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; underwater photographer &lt;/a&gt;as you have awide variety of marine life around the wreck including a number of small creatures great for macro shots. There are many sponges, brain corals, Christmastree worms and a nice Social Feather Duster on the stern rail.
<br /><br />For other underwater photographs of the Doc Poulson just click on one of the photographs or go to my &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FDoc-Paulson%2FG0000TGXE_MiE3nA%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Doc-Paulson/G0000TGXE_MiE3nA/&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Doc Poulson Gallery&lt;/a&gt;.  If you want to find information on other wrecks in Grand Cayman such as the USS Kittiwake you can check out my &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blog&lt;/a&gt; and/or view more underwater photographs on my &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-list%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-list&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;website &lt;/a&gt;and/or follow me on Twitter @ Images2Inspire
<br /><br />The pool is open...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a9cf319b62cbfd25be1fe0942db67936" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Orange Canyon<br/><br/>Overall Rating = 3.5 out of 5&lt;/p&gt;
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Orange Canyon&lt;/a&gt; is one of the more well known and visited scuba diving sites on the west side of Grand Cayman.  The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-orange-canyon%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-orange-canyon/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Dive Site Review&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive site&lt;/a&gt; is near the west end of the island and is very close to several other well know sites, such as Big Tunnels.  This &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; site is typical of thebetter sites on the west side.  You start on the mooring ball and descend through a break in the coral and emerge on the wall around 100 feet.  The dive moves along the wall where you can look out into the blue for large pelagic species such as sharks and &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2FI0000bNZffh9EAjQ%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/I0000bNZffh9EAjQ&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Spotted Eagle Rays&lt;/a&gt; and then finishes at the top of the wall where you can explore various coral, sponges, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fish&lt;/a&gt;, eels and turtles.
<br /><br />Depth to 105+
<br />Visibility - good to excellent
<br />Current - variable
<br />Marine Species variety - Moderate to high
<br />Reef health - Moderate to healthy
<br /><br />This site compares very well with other west side dive sites, but I admit my favorite (non-wreck) &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive sites&lt;/a&gt; are on the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;north wall&lt;/a&gt;.  However, I definitely like this site and I dive it regularly.  It is especially good when there are large &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;swarms&lt;/a&gt;&quot; of Silversides on this site.  There are also likely to be several Tarpon in the canyons as you explore the site.  This site gets its name from the spectacular &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FSponges%2FG0000AUYkLv.mB8M%2FI0000AgtpwRIBGBg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Sponges/G0000AUYkLv.mB8M/I0000AgtpwRIBGBg&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Elephant Ear Sponges&lt;/a&gt;.  These colorful sponges make a great backdrop for photos and if you explore closely you will likely find various cleaner shrimps and blennys on the sponges.  You will also likely find a cleaningstation with a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI0000RjmnShBmZYg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I0000RjmnShBmZYg&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;grouper &lt;/a&gt;exposing his gills for servicing.  The site can have a current and can have a good bit of turbidity but normally the visibility is quite good and the diver operator should check this before you enter the water.
<br /><br />I recommend taking this dive very slowly and actively looking around at the wide&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; variety of life&lt;/a&gt; that can be found here.
<br /><br />The pool is open...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c878676756816d0adbba2f892680dd99" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Maui - Black Rock<br/><br/>Black rock or Sheraton Reef rates average for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; Maui during the day, but is a bit above average when compared to other shore diving locations in the Kaanapali area. I do rate it a bit better as a night dive site. However, when&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Scuba Diving Maui &lt;/a&gt;near Kaanapali, I would recommend Mala Pier as a much better shore dive either during the day or at night if transportation is not a problem.
<br />&lt;ul&gt;
<br />  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ffff00;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Access - Moderate difficulty to reach the site; Easy entry into the water&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
<br />	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ffff00;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Depth to 45ft&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
<br />	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ffff00;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visibility - average to good&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
<br />	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ffff00;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current - moderate to quite strong&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
<br />	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ffff00;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marine Species variety - Moderate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
<br />	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ffff00;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reef health - Moderate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
<br />&lt;/ul&gt;
<br />The dive at Black Rock is quite shallow allowing for a dive that can run 60 minutes or more depending upon your air consumption. The current can be quite strong after you pass the rocky point for which the dive site receives its name, so inexperienced divers should only dive this site with a local guide. The dive shop at the Sheraton, In 2 Scuba, is ok but the staff that I have used tends to be younger and inexperienced and I tend to brief them on how I will dive the site. So if you are an experienced diver, there is no reason you cannot do this dive on your own, but you will have to bring your own equipment or rent gear and bring it in.
<br /><br />You enter the site in the beach area of the Sheraton Maui Resort and Spa. You can access the beach whether you are staying at the hotel or not, but getting your gear to the beach can be an adventure. You have to park in a parking garage near the front of the hotel and then haul your gear a good distance to the beach probably about 200 meters The local dive operator on the beach, &quot;In 2 Scuba&quot;, does not &quot;rent tanks&quot; or at least they have not in the past, so you need to rent these off site, I rent typically at Lahaina Divers, and/or sign up for a guided dive from the onsite dive shop. I have been able to get the valet to sometimes take my equipment down to the beach but that usually involves a nice tip. There is a place to rinse your gear by the Scuba Diving shack and ample places to gear up prior to the dive.
<br /><br />Once you are geared up, the entry is quite easy, the beach is a little steep just before entering the water, but the waves are typically very small due to the protection from the cliff. During the day, there tends to be a number of snorkelers above you on this site and you need to be careful on the entry and exit.
<br /><br />The dive is quite easy if the current is not too strong. You swim out about 20 to 30 meters from the beach and thensubmerge and swim out and around the rocky promontory, from which you can watch &quot;cliff diving&quot; during the day. If there is a current you will feel it immediately as you go around the point and it will get stronger for about the next 50 meters or so and then taper off a bit. The variety of&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; marine life&lt;/a&gt; is reasonable and you will almost always see several sea turtles once you round the point. This is a favorite site for many large turtles to come in for a nap. Typically you can see a large number of eels including &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2FI0000pkbDx6dCFoo%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/I0000pkbDx6dCFoo&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Yellow Margin Eels&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2FI0000gVHxHBipFCk%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/I0000gVHxHBipFCk&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Undulated Moray Eels&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2FI0000n5XqIatwp_U%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/I0000n5XqIatwp_U&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Whitemouth Moray Eels&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2FI0000jE1X53Vtjuo%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/I0000jE1X53Vtjuo&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zebra Moray Eels&lt;/a&gt; and others. As you head away from the beach the cliff will be to your right and open ocean on your left. The cliff has a number of crevices as you round the point that are well worth exploring as you will sometimes find a variety of shrimp, such as the rare &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCrustaceans-and-Echinoderms%2FG0000OLcModvF7w4%2FI0000IZs3Rh3LCys%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Crustaceans-and-Echinoderms/G0000OLcModvF7w4/I0000IZs3Rh3LCys&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candy Cane Shrimp&lt;/a&gt;, and various types of cleaners. There also tend to be a number of Goatfish just away from the wall along with variouspuffer fishes, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2FI0000OandS1Heqp8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/I0000OandS1Heqp8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;butterflyfishes&lt;/a&gt; and parrotfishes staying fairly close to the cliff.. The water tends to have a good bit of sand and other debris which makes photography a bit challenging so remember to keep your strobes pointed away from your subject to eliminate backscatter and shoot as close as possible. However, if the current is not too strong you can get reasonable visibility and clarity. As you round the point make sure you look out away from the cliff about 10 meters to 25 meters, you will sometimes find one or more rays staying virtually motionless in the current and feeding. You have to approach them very, very slowly and close to the bottom or you will cause them to move away. If they are present stop and watch them a bit before you begin the approach. I had a dive in 2011 in the spring where three Manta Rays were hovering and feeding and another diver sprinted to get a closer look and needless to say that was the last that we saw of them. So again go slow, and approach very cautiously and you will tend to see more.  You will be diving against the current so continue swimming out beside the cliff until you reach about 1500 PSI and then simply turn around and follow the same path back in.  If for some reason you do run short on air this site is very forgiving and you can simply surface and then swim back around to where you entered, just make sure you stay wide of the point.  The wave action here can be quite strong and the rocks can do a lot of damage if you were to get pushed up against them.
<br /><br />Overall a fun dive and I usually make it once or twice when I am in &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Maui&lt;/a&gt; and usually at night.
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The pool is open&lt;/a&gt;...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d602612f13bb32635d9f6dc9f14c73d" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Divng Lanai - First Cathedral<br/><br/>&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-lanai-first-cathedrals%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/scuba-diving-lanai-first-cathedrals/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;First Cathedral&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most visited &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI0000WWBe3UNlNZU%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I0000WWBe3UNlNZU&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving &lt;/a&gt;sites on Lanai and in Maui County.  It is a dual pinnacle site and is also one of the largest &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving sites&lt;/a&gt; in Maui County.   The mooring at the pinnacle is about 35 feet deep on the shallow portion and has a large arch on the west side.  The northern side of the site has a wall with lava caves, crevices to explore and a swim through arch.  A sand channel separates this from the wash rock pinnacle that comprises FirstCathedral.  The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI00004c9NGcDmqbI%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I00004c9NGcDmqbI&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;large cavern&lt;/a&gt;, of the Cathedral, has a maximum depth of 45'-50' deep and a ceiling overhead which is approximately 20' high.  It has a lace work of openings in the lava on the east wall that allows light in, in a manner suggesting a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI00003lZYA_8YqU8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I00003lZYA_8YqU8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;stained glass window&lt;/a&gt; within a church or cathedral, from which this scuba diving site derives its name.
<br /><br />Access - Moderate; boat only and 45 minutes from Lahaina.  If you tend to get sea sick take your Bonine or ginger before this trip.  
<br />Depth to 60+ ft
<br />Visibility - good to very good
<br />Current - variable, minimal to strong
<br />Marine Species variety - Good
<br />Reef health - Good
<br /><br />When you enter the water on the mooring you you will swim first toward the Pinnacle containing the lava tube known as First Cathedral and then after exploring the &quot;Chapel&quot; as I like to call it, you exit rather quickly, or as some like to say, you are flushed from the First Cathedral to reef outside.  There is an opening on the inside of the Cathedral which has water rushing in and out with the actions of the waves.  You swim to the exit &quot;portal&quot; and then hold on as the water rushes into the Cathedral and then when the flow reverses you enter the portal and are rather quickly deposited on the outside of the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI0000LcwpwkXkcQ8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I0000LcwpwkXkcQ8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;coral reef.&lt;/a&gt; This is not as intimidating as it might first seem as the opening is fairly large and you only travel a short distance before exiting on the reef.  That said, if you have a camera, please bring the strobes in before entering the portal and you should not have any trouble.  If this is too much excitement you can exit the Cathedral the same way you entered and simply swim around to the other side.
<br /><br />The Cathedral itself is an ancient lava tube that has several openings on the upper portion and side of the cavern.  These openings allow light to pass through them and provide some great opportunities for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt;.  I especially like black and white images of the cathedral as they seem to provide the most dramatic effects with the light.  The ceiling &quot;window&quot; provides very good lighting (assuming sunny skies) on a rocky outcrop in the middle of the room and you can see &quot;rays of light&quot; shining in from the top of the dome making for some interesting underwater photography.   The opening to enter the cathedral is very large and should not cause anyone concern.  First Cathedral can hold many scuba divers at one time but I find it best, especially when trying to take &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-lanai-first-cathedrals%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/scuba-diving-lanai-first-cathedrals/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photographs&lt;/a&gt;, to be in a small group or be first.  Having a larger number of scuba divers will stir up a good bit of sediment making it especially difficult to take good shots.  It is also better to be in &quot;group 1&quot; verses &quot;group 2&quot; if you have a large number of divers on the boat as the silt in the Cathedral will tend to get stirred up as more divers are going through the cavern.
<br /><br />Once inside the lava tube, you will find a number of different fish species and more than likely a school of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2FI0000Yn8uYwpoKr4%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/I0000Yn8uYwpoKr4&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Brick Soldierfish&lt;/a&gt; up towards the ceiling.  When you exit the cavern you will be on a portion of the reef that usually has a nice diversity of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2FI0000OandS1Heqp8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/I0000OandS1Heqp8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;marine life&lt;/a&gt;.  You will head towards a swim through where you will find a number of different butterflyfishes, moray eels, frogfishes, nudibranches, goatfishes, and much more.
<br /><br />There are several archways to swim thru and the coral gardens are great places to look for eels, shrimps, and small crustaceans.  So take your time when scuba diving on this site and you will be well rewarded.
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Lanai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The pool is open...&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="914ca2fa07c25980701c88371646c8e8" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman<br/><br/>&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Cayman Islands&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Scuba Diving&lt;/a&gt; in the Cayman Islands is something special.  The magnificent walls, spectacular soft and hard corals, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FKittiwake-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000JtpXOPWAQac%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Kittiwake-Grand-Cayman/G0000JtpXOPWAQac/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;great wrecks&lt;/a&gt;, easy access and warm water makes this a marvelous place for scuba diving.  Whether you are an experienced technical diver or a recreational diver or an &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Underwater Photography&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;undewater photographer&lt;/a&gt;, there is something for you in the Cayman Islands.  The variety of marine species and topography provides every type of scuba diver with what they want.  With boat rides of 10 to 30 minutes to the dive site you can become easily spoiled to the warm, friendly and inviting waters of this Caribbean paradise.
<br /><br />There are  a number of&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; great scuba diving sites&lt;/a&gt; in the Cayman Islands such as &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fbabylon%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/babylon/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Babylon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-andes-wall%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-andes-wall/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Andes Wall&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-uss-kittiwake-shipwreck%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-uss-kittiwake-shipwreck/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USS Kittiwake,&lt;/a&gt; MV Capt. Keith Tibbetts, Bloody Bay Wall and much, much more. With water temperatures requiring only shorts and t-shirt almost year around and abundant marine life, the Cayman Islands are hard to beat. Whether you prefer the slightly higher pace of life in Grand Cayman or the laid back atmosphere of Little Cayman and Cayman Brac the scuba diving here is marvelous. As an &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FOro-Verde%2FG0000oIFpDg4SWto%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Oro-Verde/G0000oIFpDg4SWto/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photographer&lt;/a&gt;, I find this one of the most ideal places on the planet to see and interact with an extremely wide variety of marine life in a very relaxed and easy going environment. The conditions are rarely challenging, although the swell on some parts of the islands can be interesting if you tend to have sea sickness, these scuba diving sithes offer easy to access snd numerous high quality scuba diving for novices to professional divers.
<br /><br />I love to dive in Grand Cayman, as the variety of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;marine life&lt;/a&gt; and  of diving sites around the entire island provides any scuba diver with dozens of high-quality scuba diving sites from which to choose. There are a number of reputable scuba diving operators in Grand Cayman, from very large such as &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.redsailcayman.com%2Fen%2Findex.html%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.redsailcayman.com/en/index.html&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Operators&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Red Sail Sports&lt;/a&gt; or  specialtiy scuba diving operators like &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcathychurch.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://cathychurch.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Operator&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Cathy Church&lt;/a&gt; (who is the queen of underwater photography). Most of these dive operations are of a high quality, but do use seasonal / short-term staff that will from time to time cause problems for individual divers. 
<br /><br />My recommendation are:
<br /><br />1. Book as early as possible before you arrive at the island (you can usually get a discount if you book before you arrive and make sure you check the &amp;quot;rules&amp;quot; for the discount)
<br />2. Think about what you want to accomplish on your dives such as going for a higher certification, taking amazing &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2FI0000U0AWVAvo9kI%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/I0000U0AWVAvo9kI&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;macro shots&lt;/a&gt;, night diving, wreck diving, just relaxing, etc., and make sure that those in your group have the same objectives
<br />3. When you arrive on the island spend some time to review your itinerary with the dive shop and make sure that what they have on their schedule is what you want.&lt;/li&gt;
<br />4. Inspect and check all of your gear before it is time to go to the boat&lt;/li&gt;
<br />5. Bring extra straps, masks, etc., in case of problems and do not forget the sunscreen&lt;/li&gt;
<br />6. Listen to  the instructions from the dive master and boat captain&lt;/li&gt;
<br />7. Adequately tip the crew for their work. These people are professionals, and they are professionals at what they do, they work by the hour and it is not a highly paid profession. 
<br />8. When the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FShipwrecks%2FG0000OtMyTETA74I%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Shipwrecks/G0000OtMyTETA74I/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; is done, review the bill and charges a day or two before you leave the island so you can sort out any issues. It is always a good idea to review and validate any charges being made to a credit card or room charge before you have to leave.
<br /><br />If you follow these simple guidelines, then 99 times out of 100 you will have a great time and a great scuba diving experience and if you do not then.....
<br /><br />The pool is open...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="651612ee1a2d8f6f57f60989bf5d7837" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Molokai - Fish Rain<br/><br/>Overall Rating = 4.1 out of 5
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-molokai-fish-rain%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/scuba-diving-molokai-fish-rain/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fish Rain&lt;/a&gt; is a great scuba diving site and probably has one of the highest densities of marine species that you will find while &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Hawaii&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; in Maui County.  This &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive site&lt;/a&gt; would rate even higher  if it was easier to access. Scuba diving in Moloki is challenging, this is not a dive for the novice.  In fact any time you have to cross the Pailolo Channel you are in for an interesting ride.  Seas can regularly be between 6 and 10 feet with strong gust or steady winds.  The Pailolo Channel is one of the windiest and roughest of the Hawaiian Island channels.  Seas of 4 to 6 feet should be considered calm water and it takes about 45 minutes to get to the dive site.  So do not attempt this &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuab Diving Hawaii&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive&lt;/a&gt; unless you do not have a problem with motion sickness, you are not intimidated by rough seas, and you are not concerned about exiting or reentering the boat while it is moving. But.... what a great dive.
<br /><br />Access - Difficult to reach the site; Complex entry and exit; Advanced level only
<br />Depth to 120ft
<br />Visibility - very good to excellent
<br />Current - variable - moderate to quite strong
<br />Marine Species variety - Wonderful diversity and high number of species; large pelagic species
<br />Reef health - Very good
<br /><br />There are no buoys on the north east side of Molokai, no place for a boat to tie up and the high seas mean the boats must stay in constant motion when dropping or picking up divers.  There will be rigid instructions given for entry and reentry into the boat and these must be followed.  The dive masters and captains regularly take ginger before making this trip.  So again, this trip is not for novice divers.
<br /><br />Now….to the good stuff….
<br /><br />Fish Rain is a really cool scuba diving site.  It is on the far eastern side of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Molokai&lt;/a&gt; near Mokuhooniki Rock.  You go to this site for Hammerheads and you get the bonus of amazing diversity and quantity of marine life.  The site depth is to about 110 feet around the pinnacle / &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mokuhooniki Rock&lt;/a&gt; and there are sea grass beds along the bottom.  You will a good amount of coral on the lava slopes of the pinnacle and such a great variety of fish surrounding  that will make you think it is literally &quot;raining&quot; fish, hence the name of this site.  If the weather is good and there is adequate sunlight this site makes a really nice place for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt; and the opportunity to see large pelagic species.  If you do not encounter sharks or other pelagic species, do not worry this dive site will not disappoint.
<br /><br />You will need to exit the boat as it is moving.  The seas are typically 2 to 4 feet as you enter the water.  You will be given precise instructions on how to get into a ready position for entry into the water and you need to follow these closely.  You will typically gear up and wait at your station until signaled by your dive master.  You will then queue up in groups and when the dive master says &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&quot;Dive, Dive, Dive&quot;&lt;/a&gt; you enter the water, whith your camera or other gear and swim quickly away from the boat as all divers in yourgroup will be entering one right after the other.  Your inner &quot;navy seal&quot; will love this.  So enjoy.
<br /><br />Once in the water you will descend as a group quickly as you do not want to stay on the surface here for an extended period of time.  As you descend you will notice immediately the large number of fish surrounding you and the pinnacle.  You will see hundreds of fish including various Butterflyfishes such as the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pennant Butterflyfish&lt;/a&gt; and Milletseed Butterflyfish.  You will also see Eels, Unicornfishes, all types of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2FI0000_8ENRhqXu9U%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/I0000_8ENRhqXu9U&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wrasses&lt;/a&gt; and much more.  A camera of some type is a must for this location if you can.  The lava pinnacle has lots of very healthy hard corals covering the slope down to the sea floor which tends to be covered in sea grass.  You will more than likely go to around 100 to 115 feet just off the pinnacle on your first dive and &quot;hang out&quot; waiting to for the Hammerhead sharks.  You will more than likely at least get a view of the sharks in the distance and if you are patient and do not frighten them away they may come in to investigate your dive group.   The Hammerheads are easily frightened or chased away so do not chase them as soon as you see them.  Be patient and wait for them to approach your group, they are basically curious and you may be rewarded to see them up close.
<br /><br />This is more or less a drift dive and you will follow your instructor and then surface and wait forthe boat to come and pick you up.  You must have a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;safety sausage&lt;/a&gt; or signaling device when on this dive.  It is extremely difficult to see a diver in calm waters from a distance and in these seas without a signaling device you can easily be missed.  When you surface, have one or more of the people in your group inflate their safety sausage and then wait until the ship spots you.  You could be on the surface for 15 minutes before you are picked up, especially if you have more than one group in the water.  The boat will typically have a line in the water and all divers will need to use the rope for reentry.  As the boat comes by simply grab and hold onto the line and then wait your turn to approach and enter the boat.  Be prepared and be patient.  This is certainly one of my favorite scuba diving sites and highly recommended to very experienced divers.
<br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The pool is open&lt;/a&gt;…
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2cf1b6d33eb44b7778a9ca156834ab" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Molokai - Fish Rain<br/><br/>Overall Rating = 4.1 out of 5
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-molokai-fish-rain%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/scuba-diving-molokai-fish-rain/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fish Rain&lt;/a&gt; is a great scuba diving site and probably has one of the highest densities of marine species that you will find while &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Hawaii&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; in Maui County.  This &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive site&lt;/a&gt; would rate even higher  if it was easier to access. Scuba diving in Moloki is challenging, this is not a dive for the novice.  In fact any time you have to cross the Pailolo Channel you are in for an interesting ride.  Seas can regularly be between 6 and 10 feet with strong gust or steady winds.  The Pailolo Channel is one of the windiest and roughest of the Hawaiian Island channels.  Seas of 4 to 6 feet should be considered calm water and it takes about 45 minutes to get to the dive site.  So do not attempt this &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuab Diving Hawaii&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive&lt;/a&gt; unless you do not have a problem with motion sickness, you are not intimidated by rough seas, and you are not concerned about exiting or reentering the boat while it is moving. But.... what a great dive.
<br /><br />Access - Difficult to reach the site; Complex entry and exit; Advanced level only
<br />Depth to 120ft
<br />Visibility - very good to excellent
<br />Current - variable - moderate to quite strong
<br />Marine Species variety - Wonderful diversity and high number of species; large pelagic species
<br />Reef health - Very good
<br /><br />There are no buoys on the north east side of Molokai, no place for a boat to tie up and the high seas mean the boats must stay in constant motion when dropping or picking up divers.  There will be rigid instructions given for entry and reentry into the boat and these must be followed.  The dive masters and captains regularly take ginger before making this trip.  So again, this trip is not for novice divers.
<br /><br />Now….to the good stuff….
<br /><br />Fish Rain is a really cool scuba diving site.  It is on the far eastern side of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Molokai&lt;/a&gt; near Mokuhooniki Rock.  You go to this site for Hammerheads and you get the bonus of amazing diversity and quantity of marine life.  The site depth is to about 110 feet around the pinnacle / &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mokuhooniki Rock&lt;/a&gt; and there are sea grass beds along the bottom.  You will a good amount of coral on the lava slopes of the pinnacle and such a great variety of fish surrounding  that will make you think it is literally &quot;raining&quot; fish, hence the name of this site.  If the weather is good and there is adequate sunlight this site makes a really nice place for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt; and the opportunity to see large pelagic species.  If you do not encounter sharks or other pelagic species, do not worry this dive site will not disappoint.
<br /><br />You will need to exit the boat as it is moving.  The seas are typically 2 to 4 feet as you enter the water.  You will be given precise instructions on how to get into a ready position for entry into the water and you need to follow these closely.  You will typically gear up and wait at your station until signaled by your dive master.  You will then queue up in groups and when the dive master says &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&quot;Dive, Dive, Dive&quot;&lt;/a&gt; you enter the water, whith your camera or other gear and swim quickly away from the boat as all divers in yourgroup will be entering one right after the other.  Your inner &quot;navy seal&quot; will love this.  So enjoy.
<br /><br />Once in the water you will descend as a group quickly as you do not want to stay on the surface here for an extended period of time.  As you descend you will notice immediately the large number of fish surrounding you and the pinnacle.  You will see hundreds of fish including various Butterflyfishes such as the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pennant Butterflyfish&lt;/a&gt; and Milletseed Butterflyfish.  You will also see Eels, Unicornfishes, all types of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2FI0000_8ENRhqXu9U%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/I0000_8ENRhqXu9U&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wrasses&lt;/a&gt; and much more.  A camera of some type is a must for this location if you can.  The lava pinnacle has lots of very healthy hard corals covering the slope down to the sea floor which tends to be covered in sea grass.  You will more than likely go to around 100 to 115 feet just off the pinnacle on your first dive and &quot;hang out&quot; waiting to for the Hammerhead sharks.  You will more than likely at least get a view of the sharks in the distance and if you are patient and do not frighten them away they may come in to investigate your dive group.   The Hammerheads are easily frightened or chased away so do not chase them as soon as you see them.  Be patient and wait for them to approach your group, they are basically curious and you may be rewarded to see them up close.
<br /><br />This is more or less a drift dive and you will follow your instructor and then surface and wait forthe boat to come and pick you up.  You must have a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;safety sausage&lt;/a&gt; or signaling device when on this dive.  It is extremely difficult to see a diver in calm waters from a distance and in these seas without a signaling device you can easily be missed.  When you surface, have one or more of the people in your group inflate their safety sausage and then wait until the ship spots you.  You could be on the surface for 15 minutes before you are picked up, especially if you have more than one group in the water.  The boat will typically have a line in the water and all divers will need to use the rope for reentry.  As the boat comes by simply grab and hold onto the line and then wait your turn to approach and enter the boat.  Be prepared and be patient.  This is certainly one of my favorite scuba diving sites and highly recommended to very experienced divers.
<br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The pool is open&lt;/a&gt;…
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bcd5aacf1925e6c01cf369affdac26e8" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Molokai - Fish Rain<br/><br/>Overall Rating = 4.1 out of 5
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-molokai-fish-rain%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/scuba-diving-molokai-fish-rain/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fish Rain&lt;/a&gt; is a great scuba diving site and probably has one of the highest densities of marine species that you will find while &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Hawaii&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; in Maui County.  This &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive site&lt;/a&gt; would rate even higher  if it was easier to access. Scuba diving in Moloki is challenging, this is not a dive for the novice.  In fact any time you have to cross the Pailolo Channel you are in for an interesting ride.  Seas can regularly be between 6 and 10 feet with strong gust or steady winds.  The Pailolo Channel is one of the windiest and roughest of the Hawaiian Island channels.  Seas of 4 to 6 feet should be considered calm water and it takes about 45 minutes to get to the dive site.  So do not attempt this &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuab Diving Hawaii&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive&lt;/a&gt; unless you do not have a problem with motion sickness, you are not intimidated by rough seas, and you are not concerned about exiting or reentering the boat while it is moving. But.... what a great dive.
<br /><br />Access - Difficult to reach the site; Complex entry and exit; Advanced level only
<br />Depth to 120ft
<br />Visibility - very good to excellent
<br />Current - variable - moderate to quite strong
<br />Marine Species variety - Wonderful diversity and high number of species; large pelagic species
<br />Reef health - Very good
<br /><br />There are no buoys on the north east side of Molokai, no place for a boat to tie up and the high seas mean the boats must stay in constant motion when dropping or picking up divers.  There will be rigid instructions given for entry and reentry into the boat and these must be followed.  The dive masters and captains regularly take ginger before making this trip.  So again, this trip is not for novice divers.
<br /><br />Now….to the good stuff….
<br /><br />Fish Rain is a really cool scuba diving site.  It is on the far eastern side of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Molokai&lt;/a&gt; near Mokuhooniki Rock.  You go to this site for Hammerheads and you get the bonus of amazing diversity and quantity of marine life.  The site depth is to about 110 feet around the pinnacle / &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mokuhooniki Rock&lt;/a&gt; and there are sea grass beds along the bottom.  You will a good amount of coral on the lava slopes of the pinnacle and such a great variety of fish surrounding  that will make you think it is literally &quot;raining&quot; fish, hence the name of this site.  If the weather is good and there is adequate sunlight this site makes a really nice place for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt; and the opportunity to see large pelagic species.  If you do not encounter sharks or other pelagic species, do not worry this dive site will not disappoint.
<br /><br />You will need to exit the boat as it is moving.  The seas are typically 2 to 4 feet as you enter the water.  You will be given precise instructions on how to get into a ready position for entry into the water and you need to follow these closely.  You will typically gear up and wait at your station until signaled by your dive master.  You will then queue up in groups and when the dive master says &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&quot;Dive, Dive, Dive&quot;&lt;/a&gt; you enter the water, whith your camera or other gear and swim quickly away from the boat as all divers in yourgroup will be entering one right after the other.  Your inner &quot;navy seal&quot; will love this.  So enjoy.
<br /><br />Once in the water you will descend as a group quickly as you do not want to stay on the surface here for an extended period of time.  As you descend you will notice immediately the large number of fish surrounding you and the pinnacle.  You will see hundreds of fish including various Butterflyfishes such as the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pennant Butterflyfish&lt;/a&gt; and Milletseed Butterflyfish.  You will also see Eels, Unicornfishes, all types of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2FI0000_8ENRhqXu9U%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/I0000_8ENRhqXu9U&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wrasses&lt;/a&gt; and much more.  A camera of some type is a must for this location if you can.  The lava pinnacle has lots of very healthy hard corals covering the slope down to the sea floor which tends to be covered in sea grass.  You will more than likely go to around 100 to 115 feet just off the pinnacle on your first dive and &quot;hang out&quot; waiting to for the Hammerhead sharks.  You will more than likely at least get a view of the sharks in the distance and if you are patient and do not frighten them away they may come in to investigate your dive group.   The Hammerheads are easily frightened or chased away so do not chase them as soon as you see them.  Be patient and wait for them to approach your group, they are basically curious and you may be rewarded to see them up close.
<br /><br />This is more or less a drift dive and you will follow your instructor and then surface and wait forthe boat to come and pick you up.  You must have a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Molokai&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;safety sausage&lt;/a&gt; or signaling device when on this dive.  It is extremely difficult to see a diver in calm waters from a distance and in these seas without a signaling device you can easily be missed.  When you surface, have one or more of the people in your group inflate their safety sausage and then wait until the ship spots you.  You could be on the surface for 15 minutes before you are picked up, especially if you have more than one group in the water.  The boat will typically have a line in the water and all divers will need to use the rope for reentry.  As the boat comes by simply grab and hold onto the line and then wait your turn to approach and enter the boat.  Be prepared and be patient.  This is certainly one of my favorite scuba diving sites and highly recommended to very experienced divers.
<br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The pool is open&lt;/a&gt;…
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d71c9c9f09558a366669d04b3790391c" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Maui - Molokini Crater<br/><br/>Overall Rating = 3.75 out of 5
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fhawaiian-dive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-maui-molokini-crater%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/hawaiian-dive-sites/scuba-diving-maui-molokini-crater/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Molokini Crater&lt;/a&gt; is one of the best dives if not the best dive on Maui.  This scuba diving site is only accessible via boat and is at the remnants of an extinct volcano.  The crescent of the volcano &quot;cone&quot; rises above the sea some 165 feet.  The small island lies in the Alalakeiki Channel between the islands of Kahoolawe and Maui.  The opening side of the crater faces the northwest and only a short boat ride from the Wailea side of Maui.  If you are interested in some of the history around Molokini Crater there is a short article written by Edward L Caum, Geology of Molokini and published in 1930.  There are a couple of &quot;plate&quot; photographs included in the article and it is interesting to compare to the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Hawaii%2FG00003HdAnUezgNU%2FI0000d0E1OHeDAwo%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Hawaii/G00003HdAnUezgNU/I0000d0E1OHeDAwo&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;crater today&lt;/a&gt;.  Molokini Crater has been a Marine Preserve(MLCD) since the summer of 1977 and features one of the most pristine hard coral reefs in Hawaii and is a great spot for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt;.
<br /><br />The ride from the Lahina side of the island takes about 45 minutes and if you tend to get sea sick, I would recommend driving about 45 minutes or an hour to the Wailea area where you can take a very easy boat ride to the crater.
<br /><br />I prefer scuba diving with Lahina Divers but you must take about a 45 minute boat ride to the Molokini crater.  If you want you can use a scuba diving operator that leaves from the Wailea side of Maui.  If you are staying in Wailea I would certainly recommend this, although the boats tend to be smaller and there is one operator on that side that I simply refer to as the &quot;Scuba Nazi&quot;.  So be careful of the operator that you choose.  Make sure you check out the reviews and the equipment used by each of the dive operators.  The v-hull boats that leave the Wailea area can be quite cramped if the number of divers is more than 10 on the boat and on many of these there is little if any room to move around.  
<br /><br />The Dive 
<br /><br />Access - Moderate to Moderately Difficult to reach the site; boat only (You should not take a boat from Lahaina if you get seasick - 45 minute boat ride); Much easier ride from Wailea side.
<br />Depth to 125+ft
<br />Visibility - good to excellent&lt;
<br />Current - mild to extremely strong at the edges of the crater
<br />Marine Species variety - good; normally White-tip Reef Sharks at about 110 feet on the eastern side of the volcano
<br />Reef health - good to very good
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Scuba Diving Molokini Crater&lt;/a&gt; is certainly the best boat dive on the island of Maui.  You have to go to Lanai or Molokai to find better deep water scuba diving sites.  The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FUnderwater-World%2FG0000rThUYFy4ACc%2FI0000bmrvadYC5xg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Underwater-World/G0000rThUYFy4ACc/I0000bmrvadYC5xg&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;clarity&lt;/a&gt; of the water is usually quite good at Molokini and there are a several dive sites on the volcano on the outside of the crescent shape crater and on the inside of the crater.  
<br /><br />Enenue - Inside eastern tip of the crescent
<br />Middle Reef - Inside just to the east of the middle of the crescent and closer to the cone
<br />Tako Flats - Inside on the western side of the crescent
<br />Reef's End - Far western end of the crescent
<br />The Back Side - Outside or on the back of the crescent
<br /><br />When &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; inside the crater I like the Eastern edge - Enenue.  At about 120 feet there is a series of overhangs that tend to house several &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2FI0000bUBzsxvhb5Y%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/I0000bUBzsxvhb5Y&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;White-tip Reef Sharks&lt;/a&gt;.  As you are swimming down and back up after visiting the &quot;condos&quot; there is a good variety of marine species.  You will find typical butterflyfishes, wrasses, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2FI0000DK4GQMxbnhg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/I0000DK4GQMxbnhg&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;damselfishes&lt;/a&gt;, eels, and crustaceans all around the crater.  You will also find sea turtles on a regular basis and on a very rare occasion humpback whales have been seen by scuba divers at Molokini crater.  
<br /><br />The current can be quite strong on the outside edges of the crater, so do not go outside the crater for any reason if your group is scuba diving the &quot;inside&quot;.  The current at the edges can take a diver quite a distance in a very short period of time.  For this reason you must take a safety sausage with you on this dive and know how to use it.  If you are scuba diving the inside of the crater you will rarely have much if any current and even if the seas are choppy the cone of the volcano protects the inner dive sites quite well.  
<br /><br />In the sand flats of the crater you will often find &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2FI0000xqI9VkrFyUE%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/I0000xqI9VkrFyUE&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Freckled Snake Eels&lt;/a&gt;, so take your time on this dive and also make sure you &quot;look&quot; into the distance often as you can see various types of sharks and on especially amazing dives you may even see a Humpback Whale.  If you are diving in whale season (December to April/May) make sure you listen for the whale song.  In February to early April I have heard literally dozens of whales singing to each other.  It certainly makes the dive a lot more interesting.  
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Maui&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The pool is open&lt;/a&gt;...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9498b8b306a760237ee3194829083a7a" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Lonestar Ledges<br/><br/>Overall Rating = 2.9 out of 5 
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-lonestar-ledges%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-lonestar-ledges/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lonestar Ledges&lt;/a&gt; is located just off Seven Mile Beach on the west side of Grand Cayman. This &lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving Site Reviews&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bscuba"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/&quot;&gt;scuba</a> diving site&lt;/a&gt; is a frequent &quot;second dive&quot; site after a deep wall dive on the west side. The scuba diving site is named for the restaurant/bar of the same name that lies almost due east of the dive site and where it is rumored that local scuba diving instructors and dive masters consume copious amounts beer and sorted adult beverages. However, you will have to confirm this rumor on your own.
<br /><br />Access - Easy; boat only; 10 to 25 minutes from beach depending on where you are staying
<br />Depth to 60 ft
<br />Visibility - good
<br />Current – negligible
<br />Marine Species variety – average; reef sharks are frequently seen at the &quot;fresh water&quot; vent on the southern part of this dive site&lt;/span&gt;Reef health - average
<br /><br />Lonestar Ledges is typical of shallow dive sites (60t and under) on the west side of Grand Cayman. There are fingers of coral separated by sandy flats. This scuba diving site has several long &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2FI0000wOyzfM2JfNM%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/I0000wOyzfM2JfNM&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ledges or overhangs&lt;/a&gt; that can be explored and which are navigable. Under these ledges scuba divers will be able to frequently find turtles, crabs, and various types of &lt;a title=&quot;Underwater Photography&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bfish%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot;&gt;fish&lt;/a&gt;</a>. Several of these ledges make a nice swim through with the coral reef on both sides and the ledge overhanging above and almost but not quite creating a fully enclosed &quot;tube&quot; through which you can swim. These ledges are wide and should pose no problems as long as you have fairly good buoyancy control. Go slowly and carefully through each &quot;swim threw&quot; or you will stir up a significant amount of sediment making the dive significantly less enjoyable to those divers behind you. Make sure you are checking out the crevices for various types of eels and crustaceans and also check out the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FSponges%2FG0000AUYkLv.mB8M%2FI0000QlLC8fNG7y8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Sponges/G0000AUYkLv.mB8M/I0000QlLC8fNG7y8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;large barrel sponges&lt;/a&gt; that tend to be around this dive site. You can find numerous
<br />types of shrimp and &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCrustaceans-and-Echinoderms%2FG0000OLcModvF7w4%2FI0000QmdyYSdXNWE%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Crustaceans-and-Echinoderms/G0000OLcModvF7w4/I0000QmdyYSdXNWE&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;small marine species&lt;/a&gt; that are great for macro photography.
<br /><br />The Dive
<br /><br />When you are planning your dive you will usually have the opportunity to follow a dive master around the dive site or you can do this dive site on your own in a buddy team. No solo diving. The dive master will usually take the group to the southern part of the dive site where a fresh water outlet from the island flows into the sea. This is an interesting overhang and &quot;cave&quot; that often has a Nurse Shark or Reef Shark resting inside. This fresh water outlet is an underground stream that flows from the island to the ocean and where the sharks tend to gather on a regular basis, especially at night.  This is a good second dive site as long as the water is not too turbid and it is almost always a good night dive site. I have been scuba diving on this site more times that I can count and always enjoy &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;exploring the reef,&lt;/a&gt; the ledges and keeping an eye out for a shark or two.  You will find the typical &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;variety of fish&lt;/a&gt; from parrotfishes, to angelfishes, to damsels, eels and much more.  You will very often find sea
<br /><br />turtles swimming around the site or resting under one of the ledges at night.  If you do find a sea turtle resting at night, make sure to not disturb it.  Do not shine your light directly at the turtle and after watching it for a minute or two leave it alone and allow it to rest.  If you wake the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FSea-Turtles%2FG0000sfq3MVhBuZM%2FI0000Ma6qGmx872w%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Sea-Turtles/G0000sfq3MVhBuZM/I0000Ma6qGmx872w&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;turtle&lt;/a&gt; it will have to return to the surface to &quot;hyperventilate&quot; again which takes a substantial amount of time for the turtle on the surface where it is very vulnerable to predators.
<br /><br />With any marine life, especially at night, do not aim your light directly at the eel or fish you are trying to watch.  Use indirect light and be considerate, just as you do not want another scuba diver to shine a light in your eyes.  On this site you will find a number of large barrel sponges and a good amount of health soft corals on top of the reef above the fresh water inlet and back towards the mooring ball for the dive site.  Take your time and I am sure you will also enjoy this site as much as I do.
<br /><br />&lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BThe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot;&gt;The</a> pool is open…&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="652006ee6e367e0d822d99fc3020aa09" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Eagle Ray Pass<br/><br/>Overall Rating = 2.9 out of 5 
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-lonestar-ledges%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-lonestar-ledges/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lonestar Ledges&lt;/a&gt; is located just off Seven Mile Beach on the west side of Grand Cayman. This &lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving Site Reviews&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bscuba"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/&quot;&gt;scuba</a> diving site&lt;/a&gt; is a frequent &quot;second dive&quot; site after a deep wall dive on the west side. The scuba diving site is named for the restaurant/bar of the same name that lies almost due east of the dive site and where it is rumored that local scuba diving instructors and dive masters consume copious amounts beer and sorted adult beverages. However, you will have to confirm this rumor on your own.
<br /><br />Access - Easy; boat only; 10 to 25 minutes from beach depending on where you are staying
<br />Depth to 60 ft
<br />Visibility - good
<br />Current – negligible
<br />Marine Species variety – average; reef sharks are frequently seen at the &quot;fresh water&quot; vent on the southern part of this dive site&lt;/span&gt;Reef health - average
<br /><br />Lonestar Ledges is typical of shallow dive sites (60t and under) on the west side of Grand Cayman. There are fingers of coral separated by sandy flats. This scuba diving site has several long &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2FI0000wOyzfM2JfNM%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/I0000wOyzfM2JfNM&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ledges or overhangs&lt;/a&gt; that can be explored and which are navigable. Under these ledges scuba divers will be able to frequently find turtles, crabs, and various types of &lt;a title=&quot;Underwater Photography&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bfish%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot;&gt;fish&lt;/a&gt;</a>. Several of these ledges make a nice swim through with the coral reef on both sides and the ledge overhanging above and almost but not quite creating a fully enclosed &quot;tube&quot; through which you can swim. These ledges are wide and should pose no problems as long as you have fairly good buoyancy control. Go slowly and carefully through each &quot;swim threw&quot; or you will stir up a significant amount of sediment making the dive significantly less enjoyable to those divers behind you. Make sure you are checking out the crevices for various types of eels and crustaceans and also check out the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FSponges%2FG0000AUYkLv.mB8M%2FI0000QlLC8fNG7y8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Sponges/G0000AUYkLv.mB8M/I0000QlLC8fNG7y8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;large barrel sponges&lt;/a&gt; that tend to be around this dive site. You can find numerous
<br />types of shrimp and &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCrustaceans-and-Echinoderms%2FG0000OLcModvF7w4%2FI0000QmdyYSdXNWE%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Crustaceans-and-Echinoderms/G0000OLcModvF7w4/I0000QmdyYSdXNWE&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;small marine species&lt;/a&gt; that are great for macro photography.
<br /><br />The Dive
<br /><br />When you are planning your dive you will usually have the opportunity to follow a dive master around the dive site or you can do this dive site on your own in a buddy team. No solo diving. The dive master will usually take the group to the southern part of the dive site where a fresh water outlet from the island flows into the sea. This is an interesting overhang and &quot;cave&quot; that often has a Nurse Shark or Reef Shark resting inside. This fresh water outlet is an underground stream that flows from the island to the ocean and where the sharks tend to gather on a regular basis, especially at night.  This is a good second dive site as long as the water is not too turbid and it is almost always a good night dive site. I have been scuba diving on this site more times that I can count and always enjoy &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;exploring the reef,&lt;/a&gt; the ledges and keeping an eye out for a shark or two.  You will find the typical &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;variety of fish&lt;/a&gt; from parrotfishes, to angelfishes, to damsels, eels and much more.  You will very often find sea
<br /><br />turtles swimming around the site or resting under one of the ledges at night.  If you do find a sea turtle resting at night, make sure to not disturb it.  Do not shine your light directly at the turtle and after watching it for a minute or two leave it alone and allow it to rest.  If you wake the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FSea-Turtles%2FG0000sfq3MVhBuZM%2FI0000Ma6qGmx872w%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Sea-Turtles/G0000sfq3MVhBuZM/I0000Ma6qGmx872w&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;turtle&lt;/a&gt; it will have to return to the surface to &quot;hyperventilate&quot; again which takes a substantial amount of time for the turtle on the surface where it is very vulnerable to predators.
<br /><br />With any marine life, especially at night, do not aim your light directly at the eel or fish you are trying to watch.  Use indirect light and be considerate, just as you do not want another scuba diver to shine a light in your eyes.  On this site you will find a number of large barrel sponges and a good amount of health soft corals on top of the reef above the fresh water inlet and back towards the mooring ball for the dive site.  Take your time and I am sure you will also enjoy this site as much as I do.
<br /><br />&lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BThe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot;&gt;The</a> pool is open…&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13e09c985b4e7b906191e0721829009a" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Roundabout<br/><br/>Overall Rating 3.9
<br />&lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BRoundabout%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/&quot;&gt;Roundabout&lt;/a&gt</a>; can be either a first/deep dive or many times I have been on this site as a second /shallow dive site on the north wall in Grand Cayman.  It can be quite good as it has a very good variety of soft and hard corals and normally has an abundant variety of marine species.  The downside of the site is that it can also be a bit turbid after hard rains due to the close proximity to the cuts in the reef from the North Sound to the Caribbean Sea that allow &quot;runoff&quot; to cloud the dive site.
<br /><br />Access - Relatively easy; boat only;  Typically fairly easy entry into the water but rougher seas can make this a bit of an adventure on re-boarding the boat which is typical to any north wall dive in &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Grand Cayman&lt;/a&gt;; 
<br />Depth to 60+ft (on top of the wall); 
<br />Visibility - average to excellent; 
<br />Current - moderate to quite strong; 
<br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Marine Species variety&lt;/a&gt; - Good; 
<br />Reef health - Good to very good; 
<br /><br />This scuba diving typically has sea turtles, such as the Hawksbill, or Green Sea Turtle.   You can distinguish the &lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FSea-Turtles%2FG0000sfq3MVhBuZM%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BHawksbill"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Sea-Turtles/G0000sfq3MVhBuZM/&quot;&gt;Hawksbill</a> &lt;/a&gt;from the Green Sea Turtle by looking at its head and the plates between its eyes.  If you see 2 sets of plates - 2 between the eyes and 2 just about its beak/bill, then it is a Hawksbill.  The Green Sea Turtle just has two plates between its eyes.  You will also see a variety of parrotfishes, such as the &lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BPrinces"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot;&gt;Princes</a> Parrotfish&lt;/a&gt; or Stoplight Parrotfish, a variety of of small oval type fishes such as the Barred Hamlet, and if you look closely in the crevices within the coral reef you will find a variety of &lt;a href=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;crustaceans&lt;/a&gt; and juvenile fish species.
<br /><br />This is usually a very relaxing and interesting dive, since it is done on top of the wall you have plenty of time to explore.  You will occasionally see a nurse shark or ray cruising the sand channels between the reef and there are always a good number of lobsters about, you just have to go slowly and look diligently.  I was trying to take a shot of an Eagle Ray that was &quot;flying around the site&quot; when I turned around and this &lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BGreen"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/&quot;&gt;Green</a> Moray&lt;/a&gt; had just about jumped into my lap.  It just shows that it is a good idea to continually look around or have your dive buddy let you know when something interesting happens to swim nearby.  Just don't use pulling your hair as the signal, but that is a story for another time.... Typically you can do this dive as a dive buddy and your only responsibility is to monitor your air and your computer to make sure you don't get into &quot;deco&quot; time.  You can also follow the dive master around to see what they can help find.  Either way, I like to cruise the&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; top of the wall&lt;/a&gt; for a bit and look out into the &quot;blue&quot; to see if anything interesting is around.  I then usually swim very slowly over the top of the reef and enjoy the variety of&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; soft corals&lt;/a&gt; that are on this site and also look for smaller marine animals that might make a good shot.
<br /><br />&lt;a title=&quot;StevenWSmeltzer.com&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BThe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot;&gt;The</a> pool is open.....&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7bf946f897a9a530a8f2e66c9262f947" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Chinese Wall<br/><br/>Overall Rating - 3.1 out of 5
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Scuba Diving Chinese Wall&lt;/a&gt; can be done as a first / deep dive on the wall or as a shallow / second dive.  This site is a better &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wall dive&lt;/a&gt;, but diving as a second dive is usually ok, but it can be a bit &quot;cloudy&quot; if there have been recent / continual rains. It is located fairly close to one of the cuts in the coral reef near Stingray City and can get a good bit of &quot;run-off&quot; from the mangroves after a rain. The boat captain should check the visibility on the site before the dive so this will usually not be too much of a problem. However, if it has been raining a good bit I would be sure and suggest another site if you have the opportunity. Typically go to the sites towards Rumpoint and beyond if possible as they will tend to be out of the &quot;run-off&quot; area.
<br /><br />This site is typical for &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive sites&lt;/a&gt; on the north wall. As a deep dive you will head down close to the buoy and then swim as a group down towards the wall. You will descend through a channel in the coral reef and exit at about 100 ft on the wall. Then you will swim along the wall for a few minutes and gradually make your way back to the top of the wall. Scuba divers will sometimes be treated to a &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Spotted Eagle Ray&lt;/a&gt; or even more rarely a Hammerhead Shark as you swim along the wall. You will often find sea turtles on the site and as with all north wall sites there is a good variety and number of fish on the site. Also due to its proximity to Stingray City you can often find Stingrays cruising at the top of the wall or resting in one of the sand channels on top of the wall.
<br /><br />There is a good variety of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;hard and soft corals&lt;/a&gt; on the site although the sites from Rum Point and past tend to have much better soft corals.  The varieties of coral range from Knobby Cactus Corals to the Slimy Sea Plumes to encrusting Lettuce Coral and much more. You will also typically find a number of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Moray Eels&lt;/a&gt; on this site along with Princess Parottfish, Black Durgon, Blue Chromis, Yellowhead Wrasse and a variety of other fish. You can also find &lt;a href=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Spiny Lobsters&lt;/a&gt; and a variety of other crustaceans if you take your time on the dive.
<br /><br />If I am &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving&lt;/a&gt; this site as a deep dive, after enjoying the wall, I will usually take one section or area near the buoy and examine it very carefully for small creatures. It is usually time well spent. See my &lt;a title=&quot;Scuba Diving Site Reviews&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bdive"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/&quot;&gt;dive</a> site reviews&lt;/a&gt; for information on other Grand Cayman scuba diving sites.
<br /><br />&lt;a title=&quot;StevenWSmeltzer.com&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BThe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot;&gt;The</a> pool is open.....&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="37a49f18cdd1c85ef08bb549d9906303" url=""><![CDATA[What Are Coral Reefs - Introduction<br/><br/>What do you think of when you hear the term &quot;coral reef&quot; or when someone asks &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fwhat-are-coral-reefs%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/what-are-coral-reefs/&quot</a>; title=&quot;What are Coral Reefs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;What are coral reefs&lt;/a&gt;?&quot;..  Some may think of the Great Barrier Reef in Australia while others may think of the reefs surrounding the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving the Caribbean&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Caribbean islands&lt;/a&gt; or yet someone else may think of aqua-blue water and long sandy beaches surrounding their favorite island or tropical get away.
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/&quot</a>; title=&quot;What Are Coral Reefs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Coral reefs&lt;/a&gt; are definitely related to each of these but they are much, much more.  Coral reefs are estimated to cover 284,300 km (109,800 sq mi), just under 0.1% of the oceans' surface area. The Indo-Pacific region (including the Red Sea, Indian Ocean, Southeast Asia and the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FHawaiian-Fish-Pictures%2FG0000nEnP4ApIAak%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Hawaiian-Fish-Pictures/G0000nEnP4ApIAak/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Pictures of Fish&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pacific&lt;/a&gt<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /> account for 91.9% of this total. Southeast Asia accounts for 32.3% of that figure, while the Pacific including Australia accounts for 40.8%. Atlantic and &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Pictures of Fish&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Caribbean coral reefs&lt;/a&gt; account for 7.6%.
<br /><br />This series of articles will focus on what are coral reefs and try to understand the importance of coral reefs to our environment.  Some of the items that we will review includes:
<br /><br />Types of Coral Reefs
<br />Benefits of Coral Reefs
<br />Dangers to the Reefs
<br />Economics impacts of Coral Reefs
<br /><br />Overview
<br /><br />Coral reefs form a critical part of the earth's overall ecosystem.  While Coral reefs cover less than one tenth of one percent of the earth's oceans these same reefs are estimated to contain one quarter of known marine fish species. Scientists estimate that there could be anywhere from one to eight million undiscovered species living in and around the coral reefs (&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Focean.si.edu%2Focean-life-ecosystems%2Fcoral-reefs%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://ocean.si.edu/ocean-life-ecosystems/coral-reefs&quot</a>; title=&quot;Smithsonian Ocean Portal&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Smithsonian Institute&lt;/a&gt<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />.
<br /><br />The importance of this precious resource can not be &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;underestimated.  Coral Reefs are critical to not only our ecosystem but also the world's financial system, through fishing and harvesting of marine plants and animals, the ability of the reefs to protect land masses from dangerous storms, providing moisture that in turn provides rain to all &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;of the earth's land masses, and much more.  Without these reef systems our world would look much different than it does today.  
<br /><br />Corals are tiny animals which belong to the group &lt;em&gt;cnidaria&lt;/em&gt; (the &quot;c&quot; is silent). Other cnidarians include hydras, jellyfish, and &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCrustaceans-and-Echinoderms%2FG0000OLcModvF7w4%2FI00000v7PLoc5Ld8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Crustaceans-and-Echinoderms/G0000OLcModvF7w4/I00000v7PLoc5Ld8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Picture of Sea Anemone&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sea anemones&lt;/a&gt;. Corals are &lt;em&gt;sessile&lt;/em&gt; animals, meaning they are not mobile but stay fixed in one place.  As corals grow and expand, they will form one three reef types:
<br /><br />Fringing
<br />Barrier or
<br />Atoll
<br /><br />Fringing reefs:  These are the most common types of coral reefs and they project seaward directly from the shore, forming borders along the shoreline and surrounding islands. 
<br />Barrier reefs:  These reefs also border shorelines, but at a greater distance. They are separated from their adjacent land mass by a lagoon of open, often relatively deep stretch of water. 
<br />Atoll:  These reefs form when a fringing reef forms around a volcanic island and continues to grow upward while the volcanic island subsides completely below sea level.  Atolls are usually circular or oval, with a central lagoon. Parts of the reef platform may emerge as one or more islands, and breaks in the reef provide access to the central lagoon
<br /><br />All three reef types of coral reefs—&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2FI0000OYLGxeWpsD0%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/I0000OYLGxeWpsD0&quot</a>; title=&quot;Lagoon Zone&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fringing, barrier and atoll&lt;/a&gt;—share similarities in their biogeographic profiles.  Their bottom topography, depth, wave, current strength, light, temperature, and amount of suspended sediments act to create horizontal and vertical zones of corals, algae and other species. While these zones vary according to the location and type of reef, there are a number of major divisions which are common to most reefs, as they move seaward from the shore, including the reef flat, reef crest or algal ridge, buttress zone, and seaward slope.
<br /><br />Through this series of articles we will answer the following questions:
<br /><br />What are Coral Reefs?
<br />Where are Coral Reefs located and How were they formed?
<br />What are the different types of Coral Reefs?
<br />What types of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Underwater Photography and Marine Species Information&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;creatures inhabit coral reefs&lt;/a&gt;?
<br />What are the threats to Coral Reefs?
<br />What are the potential impacts of these threats on us from the impacts to our economy, to food supplies, to medicines and more
<br />What if anything should we be doing to help the coral reefs?
<br />How can you help?
<br /><br />So come join in the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Pictures of Coral Reefs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;discovery of our coral reefs&lt;/a&gt; and the&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FUnderwater-World-StevenWSmeltzer-com%2FG0000rThUYFy4ACc%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Underwater-World-StevenWSmeltzer-com/G0000rThUYFy4ACc/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Underwater World Pictures&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; underwater world &lt;/a&gt;that is so amazing and important to each and everyone one of us. 
<br /><br />Educators, send your schools name, address, the title to your class, and your grade level and I will provide you with an invitation only access to special galleries where you can download images to share with your classrooms.  When you send your request make sure to send a copy of your logo and also contact information for your school including email address and phone number. 
<br />Next week...What are Coral Reefs - Introduction to the Underwater World
<br /><br />Resources:
<br /><br />Marine Species Galleries:
<br /><br />&lt;a title=&quot;Coral Reef Photographs&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BCoral"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/&quot;&gt;Coral</a> Reef Images&lt;/a&gt;
<br />&lt;a title=&quot;Pictures of Fish&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FPictures-of-Fish%2FG0000XW6Lrw5i7Jw%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BPictures"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Pictures-of-Fish/G0000XW6Lrw5i7Jw/&quot;&gt;Pictures</a> of Fish&lt;/a&gt;
<br />&lt;a title=&quot;Sea Turtles&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FSea-Turtles%2FG0000sfq3MVhBuZM%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSea"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Sea-Turtles/G0000sfq3MVhBuZM/&quot;&gt;Sea</a> Turtles&lt;/a&gt;
<br />&lt;a title=&quot;Crustaceans and Echinoderms&quot; href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Crustaceans and Echinoderms&lt;/a&gt;
<br />&lt;a title=&quot;Moray Eels&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FMoray-Eels%2FG0000lAjRNX9s.XM%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BMoray"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Moray-Eels/G0000lAjRNX9s.XM/&quot;&gt;Moray</a> Eels&lt;/a&gt;
<br /><br />Detailed Information on select Marine Species:
<br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fmarine-organisms%2Fcaribbean-fish%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BCaribbean"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/marine-organisms/caribbean-fish/&quot;&gt;Caribbean</a> Fish&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title=&quot;Hawaiian Fish Pictures&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fmarine-organisms%2Fhawaiian-fish%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BHawaiian"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/marine-organisms/hawaiian-fish/&quot;&gt;Hawaiian</a> Fish&lt;/a&gt;
<br />&lt;a title=&quot;Sponges&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fmarine-organisms%2Fsponges%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSponges%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/marine-organisms/sponges/&quot;&gt;Sponges&lt;/a&gt</a>;
<br />&lt;a title=&quot;Crustaceans, Invertebrates, Mollusks, Echinoderms&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fmarine-organisms%2Fcrustaceans-invertabrates-molusks-echinoderms%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BCrustaceans"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/marine-organisms/crustaceans-invertabrates-molusks-echinoderms/&quot;&gt;Crustaceans</a>, Invertebrates, Mollusks, Echinoderms&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9cd384594cdd125fb1648f4ab3b17f4e" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Dragon's Hole<br/><br/>Overall Rating - 2.7 out of 5
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-dragons-hole%2F%3Fpreview%3Dtrue%26amp%3Bpreview_id%3D2556%26amp%3Bpreview_nonce%3D4a2598423b%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-dragons-hole/?preview=true&amp;preview_id=2556&amp;preview_nonce=4a2598423b&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Scuba diving Dragon's Hole&lt;/a&gt; can be quite a varied experience.  I don't dive on this site very often and  on most dives it is  average at best when compared with the other &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;wall dives&lt;/a&gt; on the west side. I much prefer, Hepp's Wall, Northwest Point, &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-orange-canyon%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-orange-canyon/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Orange Canyon&lt;/a&gt;, Bonnie's Arch, or even &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-big-tunnels%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-big-tunnels/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Big Tunnels&lt;/a&gt;. If you cannot dive one of these scuba diving sites there, I would recommend asking the boat captain to head back to Round Rock or Trinity Caves. I have found over a number of years that these sites tend to be the best on the west side. The current is always a consideration but Hepp's Wall, Bonnie's Arch and Northwest Point are some of the &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;best dives on Grand Cayman&lt;/a&gt; so don't miss them if you get a chance.
<br /><br />That said Dragon's Hole can still be a very good dive depending upon the current and the amount of particulates in the water. This dive site tends to be a bit more &quot;cloudy&quot; than other wall dive sites on the west end of Grand Cayman but still has a lot of good features. Backscatter can be a real problem so if you are an underwater photographer or if you are just trying to get a few photos to show friends back home, remember to keep your strobes very wide on this scuba diving site or you could end up with a lot of photos that are not worth printing. This is definitely better as a &quot;first/deep&quot; &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dive&lt;/a&gt; and is typical of other scuba diving sites on the west side. You will find a number of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FSponges%2FG0000AUYkLv.mB8M%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Sponges/G0000AUYkLv.mB8M/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Orange Elephant Ear&lt;/a&gt; sponges along with Roe Pore Rope sponges, brain corals and numerous other soft and hard corals along with a good variety of fish. The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;coral condition&lt;/a&gt; on the site is fair to average but on top of the wall the condition of the coral would be a bit less than average especially if compared with the scuba diving sites on the north side of the island.
<br /><br />On our last dive we found several &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2FI00004r6Kk2jcPkA%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/I00004r6Kk2jcPkA&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lionfish&lt;/a&gt; and one of the dive masters promptly dispatched them. While some people may feel some angst about killing these fish, it is something that must be done. Lionfish are definitely a danger to the Caribbean and other areas since these fish have few if any &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2FI0000Rp.i4F6rXf8%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/I0000Rp.i4F6rXf8&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;natural predators&lt;/a&gt; in the Caribbean. These fish are voracious hunters and could significantly impact the reefs if not dealt with now. So if you do not like this, please do not hinder the work of the divers. It is important.
<br /><br />I have gotten some amazing shots on this sites including this &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2FI00005Ta8Y0MP5DE%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/I00005Ta8Y0MP5DE&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Green Moray Eel&lt;/a&gt;. So my advice is to take this site as a second or third choice, but if you do dive on this site, please enjoy it as you never know quite what you may find. 
<br /><br />&lt;a title=&quot;StevenWSmeltzer.com&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BThe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot;&gt;The</a> pool is open.....&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="54fbeadb84d35eb4c039e95f5c7d07fb" url=""><![CDATA[Scuba Diving Grand Cayman - Penny's Arch<br/><br/>Overall Rating 4.2 out of 5
<br /><br />&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Scuba Diving&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblog.stevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fdive-site-reviews-and-listings%2Fdive-sites%2Fscuba-diving-grand-cayman-pennys-arch%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blog.stevenwsmeltzer.com/dive-site-reviews-and-listings/dive-sites/scuba-diving-grand-cayman-pennys-arch/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Penny's Arch&lt;/a&gt; is usually great dive.  It is almost directly across from Rum Point and in a place that does not get high traffic, but is still within the typical &quot;west side&quot; dive operators range.  This &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman%2FG0000DLsGbyx7U5k%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Grand-Cayman/G0000DLsGbyx7U5k/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;scuba diving site&lt;/a&gt; has a nice archway, hence the name, and has a very nice coral garden at the top of the reef.  The dive site is typical for those on the north wall and this far to the east the coral reef really looks good.  When the water is clear, which is most of the time, this site can be really great.  The wall is spectacular as usual and you have a great chance to sea Spotted Eagle Rays, turtles, numerous &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Caribbean fish&lt;/a&gt; and maybe even sharks on this site.
<br /><br />You will start down by the buoy and then start making you will down through a cut in the coral and then swim down and through Penny's Arch.  Do not worry it is very wide.  You will then be emerge on the wall and swim along the wall for a bit before returning to the top of the wall to explore the coral gardens. If you are into &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FScuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography%2FG0000BWCcQG1I0II%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Scuba-Diving-Underwater-Photography/G0000BWCcQG1I0II/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;underwater photography&lt;/a&gt; look back and up as you emerge from the arch and you can typically get some very nice wall shots looking up at towards the sun (assuming the sun is shinning).  You can get a great sense of the deep trench that surrounds Grand Cayman as you gaze downward into the blue for literally hundreds of feet.  The sense is surreal and I love this view.
<br /><br />The &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;coral reef &lt;/a&gt;is quite good on this dive site.  It gets plenty of nutrients and is far enough away from the cuts in the reef by the North Sound that you don't usually have a problem with visibility even after a rain.  It can get cloudy like any other site, but the visibility here is usually excellent.
<br /><br />When finishing up your dive in the coral, make sure to look carefully, usually you will find a good number of spiny lobsters, moray eels, quite a variety of fish, as well as a large variety of &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2FI0000G5qZzU0DX7k%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery-image/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/I0000G5qZzU0DX7k&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;soft and hard corals&lt;/a&gt;.  The Slimy Sea Plumes, Bent Sea Rods, Common Sea fans, Giant Slit-pore Sea Rods, and much more.  On the&lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.com%2Fgallery%2FCoral-Reefs%2FG00007HdqcXifCa4%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.com/gallery/Coral-Reefs/G00007HdqcXifCa4/&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Gorgonian fans&lt;/a&gt;, you will usually find the colorful Flamingo Tongue snails, but be careful to leave them alone as the color on the shell is from a membrane that can be extended and retracted.  When taken from the water these shells are just basic white with no color at all.  You can find a great variety of &lt;a href=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;crustaceans&lt;/a&gt; on the site, you just need to go slowly.
<br /><br />We found several &lt;a href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com%2Fgallery-image%2FCaribbean-Fish%2FG0000l7UPDDuOGA0%2FI0000dlv7fuoJCBw%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenwsmeltzer.photoshelter.com/gallery-image/Caribbean-Fish/G0000l7UPDDuOGA0/I0000dlv7fuoJCBw&quot</a>; title=&quot;Scuba Diving Grand Cayman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Lionfish&lt;/a&gt; on the site, reminding everyone of the need to cull these fish so that they do not cause anymore damage to the local environment. &lt;a title=&quot;StevenWSmeltzer.com&quot; href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stevenwsmeltzer.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BThe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stevenwsmeltzer.com&quot;&gt;The</a> pool is open.....&lt;/a&gt;
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>