<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="fad4f1d3eea4bdf72d36b15a13259b51" url=""><![CDATA[Superman Custom Nike Dunk<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rdGhlYm9vay5jb20vc3VwZXJtYW4tY3VzdG9tLW5pa2UtZHVuaw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_11593317_50226858.jpg" /></a>
<br />Superman, also known as the Man of Steel, is one of the most powerful superheroes in the DC Universe. His abilities include incredible super-strength, super-speed, invulnerability, freezing breath, flight, and heat-vision. Born as Kal-El on the dying planet Krypton, his parents Jor-El and Lara sent him in a rocket to the planet Earth where he would be the last surviving member of his race. His rocket was discovered by the kindly Jonathan and Martha Kent, who raised him as their son Clark Kent in the town of Smallville, Kansas. His upbringing provided him with strong moral values, and life-long friends Lana Lang and Pete Ross. In his secret identity he works as a reporter at the Daily Planet in the city of Metropolis. This is where he interacts with his love interest Lois Lane, and his co-workers Perry White and Jimmy Olsen. His greatest nemesis is the brilliant super-villain Lex Luthor.  
<br /><br />An influence on early Superman stories is the context of the Great Depression. The left-leaning perspective of creators Shuster and Siegel is reflected in early storylines. Superman took on the role of social activist, fighting crooked businessmen and politicians and demolishing run-down tenements. This is seen by comics scholar Roger Sabin as a reflection of &amp;amp;quot;the liberal idealism of Franklin Roosevelt's New Deal&amp;amp;quot;, with Shuster and Siegel initially portraying Superman as champion to a variety of social causes. In later Superman radio programs the character continued to take on such issues, tackling a version of the KKK in a 1946 broadcast. Siegel and Shuster's status as children of Jewish immigrants is also thought to have influenced their work. Timothy Aaron Pevey has argued that they crafted &amp;amp;quot;an immigrant figure whose desire was to fit into American culture as an American&amp;amp;quot;, something which Pevey feels taps into an important aspect of American identity.
<br /><br />Nike Dunk High shoes is a lifestyle sneaker shoes in the market. They are comfortable to wear. This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rdGhlYm9vay5jb20v" target="_blank"><strong>Custom Nike Dunk</strong></a> Superman  Shoes by Brass Monki, which is my favorite and it is the most popular shoes. The design of Brass Monki Shoes was derived from super hero Superman. The Nikes superman Premium ID Blue Red Yellow sneaker is completed off with yellow added to the midsole, shoelaces along with other areas. Additionally, the Custom Dunks ID Superman Shoes is customizable by customers and allows excellent cushioning to your technique full-length EVA midsole.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="301d17fc6e6c20fcc0c8fdd36efdeac9" url=""><![CDATA[Air Jordan 1 Retro High Premier (LS) Pewter / Black Max Oran<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci1scy1wZXd0ZXItYmxhY2stbWF4LW9yYW5nZS1wLTE1MjYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_12530195_30742434.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vbmlrZS1haXItam9yZGFuLXNob2VzLWFpci1qb3JkYW4tMS1jLTFfMi5odG1s" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1</a>    was designed by Peter Moore and marked a new era in basketball shoewear design. There has been multiple color of this shoe and also other shoe brands made models where you could see lots of similarities with <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vbmlrZS1haXItam9yZGFuLXNob2VzLWMtMS5odG1s" target="_blank">Air Jordan</a>  .
<br /><br />Most of us already know the the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci1scy1wZXd0ZXItYmxhY2stbWF4LW9yYW5nZS1wLTE1MjYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1 Retro High Premier</a>   will make a comeback in the Spring 2009 season from Jordan Brand, what we didn’t expect was this new Blue Sapphire pair to be included into the mix that already includes a Black and Infared pair  as well as a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci1scy1wZXd0ZXItYmxhY2stbWF4LW9yYW5nZS1wLTE1MjYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Pewter Black  Max Orange Jordans</a>   that comes at a Premier level. It’s safe to say that with these three <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci1scy1wZXd0ZXItYmxhY2stbWF4LW9yYW5nZS1wLTE1MjYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Retro Air Jordan 1 High Premier</a>   pairs being released in Spring 2009, Jordan fans will definitely be pleased with the assortment from JB. This shoe features a dark pewter colorway along with a foil-like finish on the upper and max orange accents, including the inner lining. The ankle area features the Jordan Wings logo in black which goes well with the black sole.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="95a4b213090a391346644463f4d0dac4" url=""><![CDATA[Nike 6.0 Dunk High Plaid Trace Blue Orange Whip<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC9uaWtlLTYuMC1kdW5rLWhpZ2gtcGxhaWQtdHJhY2UtYmx1ZS1vcmFuZ2Utd2hpcA__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_9822548_30769942.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />High profile, high style, high horsepower—the immortal <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High</a>   is got it all. Score serious points with your slick moves in the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Shoes</a>  , featuring comfort and support in a vintage-inspired profile. Considered Design for high performance and low environmental impact Leather, suede and nubuck upper High profile for ankle support Full-length EVA midsole for cushioning Flexible rubber outsole with a full cupsole stitch for durability.
<br /><br />The Nike 6.0 division has been running at full speed in 2010 with a ton of great colorways of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC9uaWtlLTYuMC1kdW5rLWhpZ2gtcGxhaWQtdHJhY2UtYmx1ZS1vcmFuZ2Utd2hpcA__" target="_blank">Nike 6.0 Dunk High</a>  , but its the materials used that have us impressed. We’ve already seen denim and a fleece/sweatpant material used already, and this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC9uaWtlLTYuMC1kdW5rLWhpZ2gtcGxhaWQtdHJhY2UtYmx1ZS1vcmFuZ2Utd2hpcA__" target="_blank">High Plaid Trace Dunk Shoes</a>  , appears to have a nylon/twill in use. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC9uaWtlLTYuMC1kdW5rLWhpZ2gtcGxhaWQtdHJhY2UtYmx1ZS1vcmFuZ2Utd2hpcA__" target="_blank">Nike 6.0 Dunk High Plaid Trace</a>   textile in contrasting colors also make these pop but are united with a neutral beige swoosh, and a white mesh lining should make for easy and cool walking.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a060e55a28c6e32fbf32c3cc6a19f371" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Wmns Air Max 1 Safari Pack Red Plum<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3L25pa2Utd21ucy1haXItbWF4LTEtc2FmYXJpLXBhY2stcmVkLXBsdW0_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_15714200_30770041.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Nike Air Max</a>    uppers was made of nylon mesh and synthetic suede, but the first leather edition Air Max 1 was released in 1988. For a while now, we have been giving you some looks at the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3" target="_blank">Nike Women’s Air Max 1</a>   Safari pack  and now they are finally starting to pop up for sale. For a while now, we have been giving you some looks at the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3L25pa2Utd21ucy1haXItbWF4LTEtc2FmYXJpLXBhY2stcmVkLXBsdW0_" target="_blank">Nike Women’s Air Max 1</a>   pack and now they are finally starting to pop up for sale.Now that they have begun to make their way onto ebay, we have some great detailed images for you to check out. This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3L25pa2Utd21ucy1haXItbWF4LTEtc2FmYXJpLXBhY2stcmVkLXBsdW0_" target="_blank">Nike Air Max 1 Red Plum</a>    sports a red plum upper and midsole with several sections covered by Nike’s beloved Safari print. Aside from the Red Plum overload, some minimal accents are provided by a touch of white and some tangerine orange on the lining and the upper eyelet holes.Very nice this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3L25pa2Utd21ucy1haXItbWF4LTEtc2FmYXJpLXBhY2stcmVkLXBsdW0_" target="_blank">Red Plum Air Max 1 Safari</a>  with the red plum theme all around the shoe. Don't sleep ladies because these will not be around for long!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8bc1b26065bd2e7e62ea59a67d501877" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Kids Air Max 90 White / White<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWtpZHMtYWlyLW1heC05MC13aGl0ZS13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_4346651_30780973.jpg" /></a>
<br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Nike Air Max 90</a>  was first named the Nike Air Max III until it was reissued and renamed in 2000. Its current name comes from the year this iconic sneaker was launched, 1990. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MA__" target="_blank">Air Max 90</a>    was originally constructed with a Duromesh upper, synthetic suede, and synthetic leather. Striking color combos, comfort and clean lines made this model an instant hit, and the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWtpZHMtYWlyLW1heC05MC13aGl0ZS13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank">Nike Air Max 90 White</a>   is still extremely popular today.The next shoe <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWtpZHMtYWlyLW1heC05MC13aGl0ZS13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank">Air Max 90 Kids</a>   sneaker rocks virgin white. All parts – outsole, midsole, upper and inner lining come in white, reminding of the famous Air Force 1 from 1982. The visible Air unit comes clear translucent. The shoe will drop at the beginning of 2011 in January.The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWtpZHMtYWlyLW1heC05MC13aGl0ZS13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank">Nike Kids Air Max 90</a>    is a good running shoe.Polyurethane midsole with visible Max Air cushioning in the heel;leather/mesh upper for light-weight and breath.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="923556b226d663c6c8cfd751c7afc329" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Air Max 90 APFC World Expo 2010 Shanghai Red Black<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtYXBmYy13b3JsZC1leHBvLTIwMTAtc2hhbmdoYWktcmVkLWJsYWNr" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_1087546_30781011.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />The second shoe that is a part of the 2010 World Expo pack that Nike Sportswear has released exclusively in Asia is this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Nike Air Max 90</a>  , taking the same inspiration as the Blazer Mid, this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MA__" target="_blank">Air Max 90</a>    looked to the Chinese National Pavilion as it’s main source of inspiration. Using a Challenge Red, White, and Black colorway this AM90 uses a graphic print leather on the upper, hits of patent leather, ballistic nylon on the toe box, and jersey mesh lining on the inside of the shoe for added comfort. These <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtYXBmYy13b3JsZC1leHBvLTIwMTAtc2hhbmdoYWktcmVkLWJsYWNr" target="_blank">Air Max 90 APFC World Expo 2010</a>   shoes are available at our online shop.
<br /><br />Joining the Nike Blazer Mid, this special colorway of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtYXBmYy13b3JsZC1leHBvLTIwMTAtc2hhbmdoYWktcmVkLWJsYWNr" target="_blank">World Expo 2010 Air Max 90</a>   featrures a 3M polygonal graphic representative of the Chinese Pavilion, placed on the upper mudguard and heel liner. A black Nike Air heel badge and swoosh off-set the bright red. Patent leather is visible on the toeguard and center panel with crease camouflaging mesh on the toe. Quite an interesting mix of materials on this Asia-Exclusive pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtOTAtYXBmYy13b3JsZC1leHBvLTIwMTAtc2hhbmdoYWktcmVkLWJsYWNr" target="_blank">Air Max 90 Shanghai World Expo</a>  , so check out the extra detailed images after the jump and stick with Sneaker News for more release info.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="211a2a39952babfadff46229e3286d0f" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk High SB FA08 Studio<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXNiLWZhMDgtc3R1ZGlv" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_1997741_30830154.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2N1c3RvbS1uaWtlLWR1bmtz" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High  SB</a>    shoes was released March 2002, in an effort to enter the fast growing skateboarding market after Nike’s two previous ventures at the skate market fizzled out. Today <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunks</a>    Skateboarding has become one of Nike hottest products with its full line of shoes, skate team and royal following of sneaker heads and skaters.Nike SB low shoe has a full team of riders lead by their signature athlete Paul Rodriguez or P-Rod. The rest of the team include Brian Anderson, Daniel Shimizu, Danny Supa, Chet Childress, Paul Rodriguez, Gino Iannucci, Reese Forbes, Stefan Janoski, Omar Salazar, Lance Mountain, Wieger Van Wageningen and Todd Jordan. A smaller team of Amateur riders include Grant Taylor, Lewis Marnell, Dan Murphy, Clark Hassler and Glenn Thomas Camba.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXNiLWZhMDgtc3R1ZGlv" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High SB FA08</a>   is Nike's most popular skateboarding shoe, has all the high quality design features. Since the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXNiLWZhMDgtc3R1ZGlv" target="_blank">FA08 Nike Dunk High SB</a>   evolution into a skateboarding shoe, the letters 'SB' have been added to signify their link to Skateboarding. It’s apprehensive at first about Nike skate shoes, people like the way they've gone about it. Instead of making cheap crap skateboarding shoes and trying to undercut the skate shoe market, Nike has taken the high road. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXNiLWZhMDgtc3R1ZGlv" target="_blank">Custom FA08 Studio Nike Dunks High</a>   have their own unique style, and while some of their shoes look like a pack of crayons left on a stove burner, some of them look pretty cool. This Studio Nike now available at shoe-page.com with the limit quantity,taking acting, don't miss it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ef44128546310afe78b3e022e351cbf6" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk High Do The Dew Green Label Art Event<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_13085594_30830155.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />These <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a>   sneakers are so fresh and so clean. Artist Dez created these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2N1c3RvbS1uaWtlLWR1bmtz" target="_blank">Custom Dunk High</a>    with a Mountain Dew theme to go along with his Mountain Dew Green Label  Art tundra bottle. The fading between the 2 shades of Green is mint, and the splatter effect on the back gives it a nice little touch that you may not notice at first. One of the sneakers says ‘Do The Dew’ and the other sneaker says <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank">Custom Nike Do The Dew Shoes</a>   and both are done in a stylish graffiti font.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Do The Dew Green Label</a>   Art Event DK-247,Mountain Dew &amp;quot;Green Label Art&amp;quot; where famous artists got the chance to infuse art into the citrus beverage. Some of the names on the list of artists include jeffstaple, Methamphibian, Haze, and our good friend from Houston, Dez.Mountain Dew and Seed Gives Life is putting on a special event to celebrate Dezs work. For the special event, Dez put together a pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank">Custom Do The Dew Dunks</a>   that match the bottle.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8610b9682504e9d0da6c821d18935e4b" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk High Do The Dew Green Label Art Event<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_13085594_30830155.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />These <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a>   sneakers are so fresh and so clean. Artist Dez created these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2N1c3RvbS1uaWtlLWR1bmtz" target="_blank">Custom Dunk High</a>    with a Mountain Dew theme to go along with his Mountain Dew Green Label  Art tundra bottle. The fading between the 2 shades of Green is mint, and the splatter effect on the back gives it a nice little touch that you may not notice at first. One of the sneakers says ‘Do The Dew’ is done in a stylish graffiti font.
<br /><br />Artist Dez created these custom dunks with a Mountain Dew theme to go along with his Mountain tundra bottle <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Do The Dew Green Label</a>   . Thats right, Dez is one of the six lucky artists who were able to catch the eye of the people at Mountain Dew during the Green Label Art design contest. An award of this nature is more then enough to celebrate seeing how Dez was added to the list with legendary artists such as Haze. So to take things one step further, and to celebrate the award, Dez went ahead and put together the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank">Custom Do The Dew Dunks</a>  . The fading between the 2 shades of green is mint, and the splatter effect on the back gives it a nice little touch that you may not notice at first. One of the sneakers says 'Do The Dew' and the other sneaker says ‘Dunk The Dew’ and both are done in a stylish graffiti font. These <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank">Custom Nike Do The Dew Shoes</a>   are so fresh and so clean that you would believe they were straight from the factory with a paint job like that.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca8f74292d337630e6da9912e553fc" url=""><![CDATA[Nike SB Dunk Mid Beijing - Triumvir x Fly<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1taWQtYmVpamluZy10cml1bXZpci14LWZseQ__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_15013390_30932620.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Nike Dunks</a>   Mid Shoes has been a very well liked sneakers for decades currently and they're unique through the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtbWlk" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Shoes</a>  . They'd provide you with an unanticipated styles feeling. The brand new design type of traditional type of Nike Skateboarding  are developed for great males.
<br /><br />Back in November 2008, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1taWQtYmVpamluZy10cml1bXZpci14LWZseQ__" target="_blank">Nike SB  Triumvir x Fly</a>   – Dunk Mid Beijing was officially introduced to the public. Triumvir, an Orange County based lifestyle company, flystreetwear, a Beijing and Shanghai based skate shop, and this <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1taWQtYmVpamluZy10cml1bXZpci14LWZseQ__" target="_blank">Triumvir x Fly Nike SB</a>  got together to design a Dunk Mid inspired by Beijing. Many around the world have taken notice to the Chinese culture since the 2008 Summer Olympic Games in Beijing.  This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1taWQtYmVpamluZy10cml1bXZpci14LWZseQ__" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Mid Beijing</a>  pays tribute to some aspects of this very intriguing and unique country.  For those knowledgeable of this area, one can immediately see the Beijing high-rise/ highway gray-toned heel, red and gold accents to represent fortune, prosperity and Chinese flag, and even the white dust mask worn by many inhabitants on the toe and laces of the shoe.  The slogan “skate towards Tienanmen square” is embedded in the sockliner, while the sole fuses Fly’s Chinese coin logo and Triumvir’s “3? logo.  Definitely a special shoe for a special culture.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="38f83e99f819fb5db54978dc30ec1df6" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk SB Mid Premium - TV Cappuccino Silver<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1zYi1taWQtcHJlbWl1bS10di1jYXBwdWNjaW5vLXNpbHZlcg__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_7706996_30932678.jpg" /></a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a>    is a global leader in designing, engineering and marketing premium-quality skateboard shoes for skateboarders. Dunksb.net online store is a Professional store which supply Nike dunk shoes only.We offer great products from Nike Dunks Low,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtbWlk" target="_blank">Nike Dunks Mid</a>  ,Nike Dunks High,Women Nike Dunks,New Dunks,Nike Air Dunk,Nike Custom Dunks and many more. Our purpose is to let every customers can pick their favourite Nike dunks shoes at a low price.
<br /><br />You might not immediately realize it by looking at them, but a look at the insole reveals that these <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1zYi1taWQtcHJlbWl1bS10di1jYXBwdWNjaW5vLXNpbHZlcg__" target="_blank">TV Cappuccino Silver Dunks</a>   are inspired by the almighty boob tube. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1zYi1taWQtcHJlbWl1bS10di1jYXBwdWNjaW5vLXNpbHZlcg__" target="_blank">Mid TV Cappuccino Silver Dunks</a>   insole is decorated with pixel boxes and the rainbow striped no-signal bars that appeared on old television sets. The outer part of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1zYi1taWQtcHJlbWl1bS10di1jYXBwdWNjaW5vLXNpbHZlcg__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk SB Mid Shoes</a>   looks pretty basic, with a suede cappuccino/silver upper accented by a textured material on the side panel and toebox and a silver Swoosh.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f46b1b0808a2cd4a9e19e03116c3f19" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk High 0.44 Sticky Rubber Custom<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLTAuNDQtc3RpY2t5LXJ1YmJlci1jdXN0b20_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_1946634_31010068.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunks</a> are mostly used by sports personalities all over the world with varieties of Nike Dunk models.The popular Nike dunks models includes Nike Dunk High, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2N1c3RvbS1uaWtlLWR1bmtz" target="_blank">Custom Nike Dunk</a> and more.In conclusion, nike dunks can become your closest friend.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLTAuNDQtc3RpY2t5LXJ1YmJlci1jdXN0b20_" target="_blank">0.44 Sticky Rubber Nike Dunks</a> should bring back some memories for its closely resemblence to the Curry Dunk High Premium from a few years back. This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLTAuNDQtc3RpY2t5LXJ1YmJlci1jdXN0b20_" target="_blank">Custom Nike 0.44 Sticky Rubber</a> new version is part of the Spark Pack which includes two other colorways using the same color and material blocking. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLTAuNDQtc3RpY2t5LXJ1YmJlci1jdXN0b20_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High 0.44 Sticky Rubber</a> upper features premium brown leather on the toe guard, heel, eye stay and the swoosh. The rest of the upper include brown suede on the toebox and brown wool on the side panels and upper heel. On the entire sole is 0.44 Sticky Rubber which is generally used in Nike’s.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c99c2af56259521daee2d404c7798c8c" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Air Force 1 Holiday 2010<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLWZvcmNlLTEtbG93LWhvbGlkYXktMjAxMC1ibGFjay13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_9206307_31010139.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />One of the great well-known products of Nike is the Air Force 1. It is recognized to be the first basketball footwear to work with the Nike Air technologies. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLWZvcmNlLTEtaGlnaA__" target="_blank">Nike Air Force 1 High</a>  is certainly referred to as just after the plane which is certainly applied by the President of the United States. That special shoe style has got previously retained a large quantity of customers as well as we desire to display our aid for this dedicated purchasers along with moreover for those who are usually merely looking all around.
<br /><br />It’s been a superb year for the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Air Force 1</a> and it looks like we’ll be finishing 2010 on a strong note.  Keeping with the trend of simply colorblocked AF1s, here are three new pairs for the Holiday 2010 season, likely to hit retail in November.  The one pair of AF1 Highs is all black leather, and draws a nice subtle contrast from the gum rubber outsole.  The two pairs of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLWZvcmNlLTEtbG93" target="_blank">Nike Air Force 1 Lows</a> are also two-toned, the one is white on the black The&lt;em&gt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLWZvcmNlLTEtbG93LWhvbGlkYXktMjAxMC1ibGFjay13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank">Nike Air Force 1 Low Holiday 2010 Black White</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLWZvcmNlLTEtbG93" target="_blank">&lt;em&gt;</a> ,and the other one is <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLWZvcmNlLTEtbG93LWhvbGlkYXktMjAxMC13aGl0ZS1yZWQ_" target="_blank">Nike Air Force 1 Low Holiday 2010 White Red</a>, they are surely great sneaker pair that you would love to see as Nike release.  Click the jump below for images of all three and stick with Sneaker News for updates.
<br /><br />One of the most popular goods of Nike is actually the Air Force Ones. It is well-known to be the first basketball footwear to work with the Nike Air technology. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL0FpciUyMEZvcmNlJTIwMSUyMEhpZ2glMjBTaGVlZCUyMFBhdGVudCUyMEJsYWNrJTIwV2hpdGU_" target="_blank">Air Force 1 High Sheed Patent Black White</a>  is definitely branded since the aircraft which is employed by the President of the United States.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="57dd6b2b4cc51e999494d92310db6d3d" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk High Custom Brass Monki Black White Green<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbS1icmFzcy1tb25raS1ibGFjay13aGl0ZS1ncmVlbg__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_16154828_31023403.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunks</a> are mostly used by sports personalities all over the world with varieties of Nike Dunk models.The popular Nike dunks models includes Nike Dunk High, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2N1c3RvbS1uaWtlLWR1bmtz" target="_blank">Custom Nike Dunk</a> and more.In conclusion, nike dunks can become your closest friend.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbS1icmFzcy1tb25raS1ibGFjay13aGl0ZS1ncmVlbg__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Custom Brass Monki Black White Green</a> features a black, white and green colorway on the upper. The green inner lining is made to match well with the outsole and swoosh.Brass Monki Nikes is design by the genius artist Brass monki. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbS1icmFzcy1tb25raS1ibGFjay13aGl0ZS1ncmVlbg__" target="_blank">Nike Brass Nonki Custom</a> is so cool and we've seen few enough colorways that pretty much all it takes to make a fresh Nike Dunk High is to add an accent color to the otherwise monochromatic upper. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbS1icmFzcy1tb25raS1ibGFjay13aGl0ZS1ncmVlbg__" target="_blank">Brass Monki Nike Dunk High</a> feature a white upper and black accents with a green swoosh and green laces. I' m always excited to see what a creative mind can produce using any medium other than the norm. Reese specializes in commission work so contact Brass Monki for a personalized pair of sneakers.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank">[img]<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shoe-page.com%2Fshoes%2FNike-Dunks%2Fnike-dunk-high-do-the-dew-green-label-art-event.JPG"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.shoe-page.com/shoes/Nike-Dunks/nike-dunk-high-do-the-dew-green-label-art-event.JPG</a>[/img]</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWRvLXRoZS1kZXctZ3JlZW4tbGFiZWwtYXJ0LWV2ZW50" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Do The Dew Green Label Art Event</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbS1mYXQtcmFiYml0LWNhcnJvdA__" target="_blank">[img]<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shoe-page.com%2Fshoes%2FNike-Dunks%2Fnike-dunk-high-custom-fat-rabbit-carrot.JPG"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.shoe-page.com/shoes/Nike-Dunks/nike-dunk-high-custom-fat-rabbit-carrot.JPG</a>[/img]</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbS1mYXQtcmFiYml0LWNhcnJvdA__" target="_blank">Don't Sweat It Nike Dunk High Custom Fat Rabbit Carrot</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbS1raWNrcy1lY2VudHJpay1sZXR0ZXJz" target="_blank">[img]<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shoe-page.com%2Fshoes%2FNike-Dunks%2Fnike-dunk-high-custom-kicks-ecentrik-letters.JPG"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.shoe-page.com/shoes/Nike-Dunks/nike-dunk-high-custom-kicks-ecentrik-letters.JPG</a>[/img]</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbS1raWNrcy1lY2VudHJpay1sZXR0ZXJz" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Custom Kicks Ecentrik Letters</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbXMtYmFjay10by10aGUtZnV0dXJlLTI_" target="_blank">[img]<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shoe-page.com%2Fshoes%2FNike-Dunks%2Fnike-dunk-high-customs-back-to-the-future-2.JPG"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.shoe-page.com/shoes/Nike-Dunks/nike-dunk-high-customs-back-to-the-future-2.JPG</a>[/img]</a>
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLWN1c3RvbXMtYmFjay10by10aGUtZnV0dXJlLTI_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Customs Back to the Future 2</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="20f44668765c1c93e023b954f65339f4" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Zoom Kobe VI (6) Mamba Snake Yellow Black<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLXZpLTYtbWFtYmEteWVsbG93LWJsYWNr" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_7533654_31023468.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />From the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunks</a>, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLWJhc2tldGJhbGwtc2hvZXM_" target="_blank">Zoom Kobe 6</a> completely followed starting from the 4th generation of the shoe body Bryant signature shoe design, shoe side of the fabric is too thin has been unsafe in the visual sense of this seems to be well resolved, thickening of the leather Zoom Kobe  shoes, body, looks lot thicker, there is a visible change in the design followed by the TPU material is no longer block before being wrapped in style, but by the two put together, In addition, Bryant elegant signature was replaced by the KB does the word appear in the heel striking.
<br /><br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLXZpLTYtbWFtYmEteWVsbG93LWJsYWNr" target="_blank">Nike Zoom Kobe VI (6) Black Mamba Yellow</a>, Kobe is a champion as long as the TCS were the neckline, so it looks like they keep this trend going in the direction of the bars for the final structure monitoring. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLXZpLTYtbWFtYmEteWVsbG93LWJsYWNr" target="_blank">Mamba Yellow Black Nike Zoom Kobe VI</a> is probably the most highly structured basketball sneakers for the use of performance of all time. In this new teasers, you can use a pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utem9vbS1rb2JlLXZpLTYtbWFtYmEteWVsbG93LWJsYWNr" target="_blank">Black Yellow Nike Kobe VI</a>, which is fully textured with a scaleY that, although quite different than the Black Mamba to see come true, Kobe pseudo fits quite well.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cbaa26fbaa21de67951d5bd0f8d69f61" url=""><![CDATA[Adidas Originals Mastermind Japan MMJ Hardland Consortium Bl<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2FkaWRhcy1vcmlnaW5hbHMtbWFzdGVybWluZC1qYXBhbi1tbWotaGFyZGxhbmQtY29uc29ydGl1bS1ibGFjaw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_7419476_31057595.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Mastermind Japan and Adidas have teamed up to bring a highly polished hightop into the mix. The basketball inspired <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2FkaWRhcy1vcmlnaW5hbHMtbWFzdGVybWluZC1qYXBhbi1tbWotaGFyZGxhbmQtY29uc29ydGl1bS1ibGFjaw__" target="_blank">Hardland Consortium Adidas</a> model is a perfect canvas for MMJ’s use of clean black leather uppers with contrasting outsole and skeleton logos. Not everything is black and white with this shoe though – if you look a little closer you’ll see some more subtle design choices like intricately arranged laces, looped eyelets, and of course, a bright red sole. This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2FkaWRhcy1vcmlnaW5hbHMtbWFzdGVybWluZC1qYXBhbi1tbWotaGFyZGxhbmQtY29uc29ydGl1bS1ibGFjaw__" target="_blank">Mastermind Japan MMJ Adiadas</a> and more will see the light of day June 16th at ISETAN Shinjuku in Tokyo.
<br /><br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2FkaWRhcy1zaG9lcw__" target="_blank">Adidas Shoes</a> really make people love and hate,Yes, the MMJ and adidas together to design a series of sports shoes <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2FkaWRhcy1vcmlnaW5hbHMtbWFzdGVybWluZC1qYXBhbi1tbWotaGFyZGxhbmQtY29uc29ydGl1bS1ibGFjaw__" target="_blank">Adidas Hardland Consortium</a>, oil skin fight bizarre set of shoelace while eye-catching, but the most striking of course, the super-huge tongue skeleton LOGO, with red soles, absolutely fatal lethal as a limited version, it's naturally expensive, more than 450 usd on ebay,but sneakerfans still need chance to get this shoe, and not easy at all since most <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL2FkaWRhcy1vcmlnaW5hbHMtbWFzdGVybWluZC1qYXBhbi1tbWotaGFyZGxhbmQtY29uc29ydGl1bS1ibGFjaw__" target="_blank">Adidas Originals Mastermind Japan (MMJ) Hardland Consortium</a> are sold out at first day selling,but from Humorshoes.com you can easily get MMJ design, Welcome to order this sneaker with excellent design!More discount in shoe-page.com!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f2efb2a29928bce5959b6ba5a99fb1" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk High Women Olympic Pack White Tour Yellow Berry<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXdvbWVuLW9seW1waWMtcGFjay13aGl0ZS10b3VyLXllbGxvdy1iZXJyeQ__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_10932093_31057596.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a> is definitely getting ready for the 2008 Beijing Olympics, and they want to get the kids involved too. This new release is being called the Olympic “5 Rings” Pack. All the shoes within the pack, which include an Air Max 90, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High</a>, and Blazer Low, are available in grade school (GS) sizes and feature the colors of the five Olympic rings. The black, blue, red, green and yellow accents colors are contrasted nicely with white for a great inspirational design.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXdvbWVuLW9seW1waWMtcGFjay13aGl0ZS10b3VyLXllbGxvdy1iZXJyeQ__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Women Olympic Pack</a> , guarantee the lowest prices on the world nike dunks shoes.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXdvbWVuLW9seW1waWMtcGFjay13aGl0ZS10b3VyLXllbGxvdy1iZXJyeQ__" target="_blank">Olympic Pack Nike Dunk High</a> is most popular skateboarding shoe all the high quality design features that Nike offers. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXdvbWVuLW9seW1waWMtcGFjay13aGl0ZS10b3VyLXllbGxvdy1iZXJyeQ__" target="_blank">Olympic Pack High Nike Dunk</a>  have been available for over many years now, and come in over 65 different color variations and styles now. Since the Dunk's evolution into a skateboarding shoe,  have been added to signify their link to Skateboarding.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="67ecdef8d420894c0ff226abc79dfd1b" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunks High Premium SB Dinosaur Jr<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLWRpbm9zYXVyLWpy" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_1926738_31085601.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Back to basics. Now popular with skaters, basketball players, and the fashionable alike, the first ever production of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a> shoe was in 1985. Before the Nike Air Jordan I, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High</a>, which later influenced the Jordan I, was the team basketball shoe of choice.
<br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLWRpbm9zYXVyLWpy" target="_blank">Nike Dunks High Premium SB Dinosaur Jr</a> is inspired after the 80s band Dinosaur Jr consisting of J Mascis, Lou Barlow, and Murph. It had been nearly 18 years since the original three members of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLWRpbm9zYXVyLWpy" target="_blank">Nike SB Dinosaur Jr</a> released an album together. The original three members rejoined together in 2005 to put out a come back album. Nike SB decided to grant them a pair of Nike Dunk SB Dinosaur Jr  to commemorate the group’s return and their comeback back album. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLWRpbm9zYXVyLWpy" target="_blank">Dinosaur Jr Nike Dunks</a> features a metallic silver color-way with purple accents, including purple stitching, outsole, and laces. It also features a small figure holding up a peace symbol on the heel of the shoe.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9b9ef67bc78e346863bfc0c6fb37b1ef" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk High Undefeated NL<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXVuZGVmZWF0ZWQtbmw_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_1977130_31085622.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXVuZGVmZWF0ZWQtbmw_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Undefeated NL</a>
<br />The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a> is a highly sought-after collectors item and due to consumer demand, the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High</a> line was reissued in 1998 and numerous colorways have been made available on a regular basis since then. Nike released the skate Dunk in 1999 featuring a padded tongue and ankle collar. In 2002, they collaborated withe the Supreme Skate brand to produce the Supreme Dunks, and in 2004, Nike released the new, never-before-seen Nike Dunk Mid.
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXVuZGVmZWF0ZWQtbmw_" target="_blank">Undefeated Nike Dunk High</a> has always been known as one of the top retailers for sneakers, but really made its mark in 2005 appearing in the Clerks Pack alongside its neighbors, Stussy and Union. The colorful <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXVuZGVmZWF0ZWQtbmw_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High  NL Undefeated </a>created for the boutique consists of blue reef, cotton candy, black in addition to the other colors not listed on the box, brown and green. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1oaWdoLXVuZGVmZWF0ZWQtbmw_" target="_blank">High Undefeated Nike Dunks</a> were No Linen Edition originally released in 2005.
<br />The Nike Dunk High – NL Undefeated  is a No Linen Edition shoe.It was inspired by Undefeated, and features an interesting colorway.The large variety of colors would clash on most shoes, but on this Nike Dunk, it seems to blend well together.These Dunks are colorful, vibrant, and eye catching.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6eda5ffc676d791bd4f243e7c48ef20c" url=""><![CDATA[Nike SB Dunk High Send Help Edition<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1oaWdoLXNlbmQtaGVscC1lZGl0aW9u" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_10998047_31155407.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />As we stated before,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk SB</a> was born in 2002. They introduced their 1st footwear line up which was made up fof the classic Nike Dunk. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">High Nike Dunk</a> made it's debut in 1985-1986 coming in all leather. The simple silhouette is easy to work with, and the designs are endless when talking about the Dunk. With that said, Nike SB put out several SB Dunks in 2002.
<br /><br />The<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1oaWdoLXNlbmQtaGVscC1lZGl0aW9u" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Pro SB Send Help</a> Consolidated black white blue reef feature a black white blue reef colorway, and are highly adored by Nike Dunk SB fanatics. They are sometimes referred to as the Nike Dunk High Pro SB Todd, as they were designed by Consolidated Skateboards art director Todd Bratrud. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1oaWdoLXNlbmQtaGVscC1lZGl0aW9u" target="_blank">Send Help High Nike Dunk SB</a> inner sole features artwork of a skeleton and is brilliantly designed. They are definitely limited and hard to come by in deadstock condition.Now cop one of your nike send help now.
<br /><br />Another Version Nike Dunk Mid SB send help.These <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1oaWdoLXNlbmQtaGVscC1lZGl0aW9u" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High SB Shoes</a>, dubbed &quot;Send Help&quot;, feature a blue reef leather upper that is acccented with black suede in the toe box and quarter panels. Grey is also used around the laces, as well as on the heel tab and the strap. It's a fresh colorway that's great to finish off the sumer.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e71af7fce88324accab59251240680e4" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Womens Air Force 1 Custom Kanye West 808s Heartbreak<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utd29tZW5zLWFpci1mb3JjZS0xLWN1c3RvbS1rYW55ZS13ZXN0LTgwOHMtaGVhcnRicmVhaw__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_2074342_31155421.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />Kanye West’s new album <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utd29tZW5zLWFpci1mb3JjZS0xLWN1c3RvbS1rYW55ZS13ZXN0LTgwOHMtaGVhcnRicmVhaw__" target="_blank">808s Hearbreak Nike Air Force 1 Womens</a> released not long ago and has enjoyed much success and the album cover art is definitely a great piece as well.  Taking inspiration from the album art, which features art from Kaws as well, he’s created a pair of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLWZvcmNlLTEtd29tZW5z" target="_blank">Nike Air Force 1 Womens </a>that almost matches the cover exactly even down to the broken heart on Kanye’s suit. Each section is attached at an angle that forms a bigger pattern. The&lt;strong <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunk</a> swoosh is given a totally new look with the colorful graphic print. This is coordinated with the heel’s segment. The two sections blend in well.The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utd29tZW5zLWFpci1mb3JjZS0xLWN1c3RvbS1rYW55ZS13ZXN0LTgwOHMtaGVhcnRicmVhaw__" target="_blank">Nike Air Force 1 Womens Kanye</a> uses white to tone down its gaudy graphics and checks. White is a good idea for the lace, inner lining and midsole. The pair of lace locks completes the symmetry of the shoe.
<br />With much success since its release a few weeks ago, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utd29tZW5zLWFpci1mb3JjZS0xLWN1c3RvbS1rYW55ZS13ZXN0LTgwOHMtaGVhcnRicmVhaw__" target="_blank">Kanye Nike Air Force 1 Womens</a> has inspired East coast sneaker customizer MACHE to design a special pair of Nike Air Force Ones. They take inspiratio from artwork on the alum cover, which includes art from Kaws as well. They feature a old skool plaid like upper along with a colorful back half, which pretty much matches the album cover down to the smallest details.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8eb14761f18b2cb2bb9df22bdaa5fa45" url=""><![CDATA[Nike SB Dunk High Urban Haze Huang black<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1oaWdoLXVyYmFuLWhhemUtaHVhbmctYmxhY2s_" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_12661726_31301369.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike Dunks</a> are mostly used by sports personalities all over the world with varieties of Nike Dunk models.Our website includes <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High</a>, Custom Nike Dunk and more.In conclusion, nike dunks can become your closest friend.
<br />This <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1oaWdoLXVyYmFuLWhhemUtaHVhbmctYmxhY2s_" target="_blank">Urban Haze Nike SB Dunks</a> design is a bit strange compared to other Nike Dunks, and it takes a lot of symbols. One of the characteristics of this would be the image of the scissors into the back quarter of the shoe. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1oaWdoLXVyYmFuLWhhemUtaHVhbmctYmxhY2s_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk SB Urban Haze</a> is at the top of the seam area set with some of the impressions on the heel. Its upper part is a subtle combination of yellow and brown suede.Swoosh is mixed with black lace detail and a delicate new bolder. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2Utc2ItZHVuay1oaWdoLXVyYmFuLWhhemUtaHVhbmctYmxhY2s_" target="_blank">High Nike Dunk Urban Haze</a> also has some black lining and a black device. So if you are a candidate for urban fashion, then you are really looking for the colors of these shoes too big to add to your collection.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c1adefafc02eff8abdf97235b50432f" url=""><![CDATA[Nike Dunk Premium hip-hop II Girl<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1wcmVtaXVtLWhpcC1ob3AtaWktZ2lybA__" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_12287553_31301381.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29t" target="_blank">Nike dunk SB</a> is a global leader in designing, engineering and marketing premium-quality skateboard <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3Mtd29tZW5z" target="_blank">Nike Dunks Womens</a> for skateboarders. Now, the street dance is commonly used specifically for the many hip hop dances and funk dance styles that began appearing in the United States in the 1970s and are still alive and evolving within hip hop culture today.
<br />These impressive kill <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1wcmVtaXVtLWhpcC1ob3AtaWktZ2lybA__" target="_blank">Hip-hop Nike Dunks</a> has a pink / black / white colorway and our beloved dancer painted on the central part of the pin. There is a dancing girl in <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1wcmVtaXVtLWhpcC1ob3AtaWktZ2lybA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunks Hip-Hop</a>. Street Dance is a general term used to describe dance styles that evolved outside of dance studios at more everyday spaces such as streets, school yards and nightclubs.These shoes look awesome hip-hop. As impressive, in fact, that could pass for a factory product. The <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1wcmVtaXVtLWhpcC1ob3AtaWktZ2lybA__" target="_blank">Hip-Hop II Girl Nike Dunks</a> is the kind of shoes you really want to have!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="10412d0b39f02a5ea3b0fe4e9fdf07e5" url=""><![CDATA[My links<br/><br/>   Sale[/url]
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci13aGl0ZS1tZXRhbGxpYy1wbGF0aW51bS1wLTE4OTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1 Retro High Premier - White / Metallic Platinum On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWFybWVkLWZvcmNlcy1taWxpdGFyeS1wZWFybC13aGl0ZS1oYXktd2FsbnV0LXAtMTUzMS5odG1s" target="_blank">Nike Air Jordan 1 Retro Armed Forces Military Pearl White Hay Walnut On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXBoYXQtbG93LXdoaXRlLWNlcmFtaWMtY291cnQtcHVycGxlLXN0ZWFsdGgtcC0yMzIxLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1 Phat Low - White / Ceramic - Court Purple - Stealth On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXBoYXQtbG93LXBvcnRsYW5kLXRyYWlsYmxhemVycy13aGl0ZS12YXJzaXR5LXJlZC1ibGFjay1wLTIzMTkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1 Phat Low - Portland Trailblazers - White / Varsity Red - Black On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXBoYXQtbG93LWJsYWNrLXZhcnNpdHktcmVkLXdoaXRlLXAtMTg3Ni5odG1s" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1 Phat Low - Black / Varsity Red / White On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLWhpZ2gtc3RyYXAtZ3JhbmQtcHVycGxlLW1haXplLXdoaXRlLXAtMjMwNC5odG1s" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1 High Strap - Grand Purple - Maize - White On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci12YXJzaXR5LXJlZC1kYXJrLWFybXktcC0xODc0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1 High Premier - Varsity Red / Dark Army On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLWktZG1wLXJldHJvLXNwbGl0LXdoaXRlLWdyZWVuLWJsYWNrLXAtMTgzMS5odG1s" target="_blank">Air Jordan 1 (I) DMP Retro Split (White / Green / Black) For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstbG93LXByby1zYi1iYWJ5LWJlYXItMy10aHJlZS1iZWFycy1lZGl0aW9uLWxpZ2h0LXVtYmVyLWdyYXNzLWhvcHBlcg__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low Pro SB - Baby Bear - (3) Three Bears Edition (light umber grass hopper) For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstbG93LXByZW1pdW0tcXVpY2tzdHJpa2UtZGF5LW9mLXRoZS1kZWFkLW1leGljbw__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low Premium Quickstrike Day Of The Dead Mexico For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstbG93LXByZW1pdW0tYmxhY2stdmFyc2l0eS1wdXJwbGUtYW50aHJhY2l0ZQ__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low Premium (black varsity purple anthracite) For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstbG93LWNsLWJsYWNrLWJsYWNrLXZhcnNpdHktcmVkLWFudGhyYWNpdGU_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low CL black black varsity red anthracite For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstbG93LWJpcmNoLWRlc2VydC1ibG9vbS1icm9uemVkLW9saXZl" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low Birch Desert Bloom Bronzed Olive For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstbG93LXdoaXRlLWJhcm9xdWUtYnJvd24tZGFyay1vYnNpZGlhbi1wb3dkZXItYmx1ZQ__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low (white baroque brown dark obsidian powder blue) For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS93b21lbnMtbmlrZS1kdW5rLWxvdy1waG90by1ibHVlLXdoaXRlLXBvbGthLWRvdHM_" target="_blank">Womens Nike Dunk Low Photo Blue White Polka Dots On sale [317813-400] : Nike Dunks,Nike Dunk High,Nike Dunk For Sale,Custom Nike Dunk,Nike Air Force Ones, Online Footwear Boutique</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstbG93LXByby1zYi1jbGFzc2ljLWdyZWVuLWJsYWNrLXdoaXRlLXJlZA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Low Pro SB classic green black white red For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLXNiLWR1bmstbG93LXByZW1pdW0tY29uY2VwdHMtYmx1ZS1sb2JzdGVy" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk Low Premium Concepts Blue Lobster For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLXRvZGQtYnJhdHJ1ZC1icmFpbi13cmVjaw__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Premium SB Todd Bratrud Brain Wreck For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLWdvb2RmZWxsYXMtbWFmaWEtZWRpdGlvbg__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Premium SB Goodfellas Mafia Edition On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXFrLXVsdGltYXRlLWdsb3J5LS1kZS1sYS1ob3lhLWNoYXZlenZhcnNpdHktcmVkdmFyc2l0eS1yZWQ_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Premium QK Ultimate Glory -De La Hoya - Chavez(varsity red/varsity red) For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLWxpZ2h0LWphZGUtYmxhY2stZ3JleQ__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Premium Light Jade Black Grey For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLWRxbS1pY2Utd2hpdGU_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Premium DQM (ice white) For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1sZS0zbS1yZWZsZWN0aXZlLWNyb2M_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High LE 3M Reflective Croc For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1oZWFydGJyZWFrLXdoaXRlLWJhYnktYmx1ZQ__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Heartbreak White Baby Blue For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1jdXN0b20tc2J0Zy1kcnMtbXItc2stYWMtYmxpenphcmQ_" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Custom SBTG DRS MR SK AC Blizzard For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaG9ub3Jpbmctcm9iZXJ0by1jbGVtZW50LWN1c3RvbXM_" target="_blank">Discount Nike Dunk Honoring Roberto Clement Customs For Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGktd2hpdGV2YXJzaXR5LXJlZC1ibGFjaw__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk Hi WhiteVarsity Red Black For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1jdXN0b21zLWhvbWVyLXRoZS1zaW1wc29u" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Customs Homer The Simpson For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hZGR0aGlzLmNvbS9ib29rbWFyay5waHA_" target="_blank">Nike SB Dunk High Skunk Go Green</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcm8tc2ItcXMtdG9kZC1icmF0cnVkP3plbmlkPW1kYjlybDFrY2pxdmlpYmVnaXA1Z3F1a2wx" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High Pro SB (QS) Todd Bratrud On Sale</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaA__" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High For Sale 30%-70% Off</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2R1bmstc2hvcC5jb20v" target="_blank">Nike Dunk High | Custom Nike Dunks | Nike Dunk Women | Save: 30%-70%, Dunk-Shop.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>