<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="ad6c3d2a8bdfae3df4d2680a6445a6c0" url=""><![CDATA[A TIME FOR RESTORATION IS HERE WITH US!!<br/><br/>&quot; 'Nevertheless, I will bring health and healing to it; I will heal my people and will let them enjoy abundant peace and security.  I will bring Judah and Israel back from captivity and will rebuild them as they were before. I will cleanse them from all the sin they have committed against me and will forgive all their sins of rebellion against me. Then this city will bring me renown, joy, praise and honour before all nations on earth that hear of all the good things I do for it ; and they will be in awe and will tremble at the abundant prosperity and peace I provide for it.<strong>( Jeremiah 33: 6-9)</strong><strong></strong><strong></strong><strong></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6185e7f7eb4fd847fb38dae08572d301" url=""><![CDATA[ABUDANCE RE-ASSURED<br/><br/>&quot;I will repay you for the years the locusts have eaten- the great locust and the young locust, the other locusts and the locust swarm- my great army that that i sent among you. You will have plenty toe at, until you are full, and you will praise the name of the LORD your God, who has worked wonders for you; never again will my people be shamed. Then you will know that  I am in Israel, that  I am the LORD your God, and that there is no other; never again will my people be shamed&quot;.<strong> (Joel 2: 25-27)</strong><strong></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d877bc50c58c863efd3ad20b16827e19" url=""><![CDATA[A TIME OF LAUGHTER<br/><br/>When the LORD brought back the captives to Zion, we were like men who dreamed. Our mouths were filled with laughter, our tongues with songs of joy. Then it was said among the nations, &quot;The Lord has done great things for them.&quot; The LORD has done great things for us, and we are filled with joy. Restore our fortunes, O LORD, like streams in the Negev. Those who sow in tears will reap with songs of joy. He who goes out weeping, carrying seed to sow, will return with songs of joy, carrying<strong></strong> sheaves with him.<strong> (PSALMS 126:1-6)</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="655db1ef2897ecf2bc4d554aa09aff38" url=""><![CDATA[HE'S FULL OF SUPRISES<br/><br/>When the Lord brought back the captives to Zion, we were like men who dreamed. Our mouths were filled with laughter,our tongues with songs of joy. Then it was said among the nations, &quot;the Lord has done great things for them. &quot; The Lord has done great things for us, and we are filled with joy. Restore our fortunes o Lord, like the streams in the Negev. Those who sow in tears will reap with songs of joy. He who goes out weeping, carrying seed to sow, will return with songs of joy, carrying sheaves with him.  AMEN. Psalms 126
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9e24564f42e608d394534b79dc4fc00" url=""><![CDATA[A WORTHY PRAYER<br/><br/>May my cry come before you, O Lord; give me understanding according to your word. May my supplication come before you; deliver me according to your promise. May my lips overflow with praise, for you teach me your decrees. May my tongue sing of your word, for all your commands are righteous. May you hand be ready to help me, for i have chosen your precepts. I long for your salvation, o Lord, and your law is my delight. Let me live that i may praise you, and may your laws sustain me. I have strayed like a lost sheep. Seek your servant, for i have not forgotten your commands.  Psalmwww.9:169-176.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="44ecc648fa94f2d3a3a818ac89530925" url=""><![CDATA[THE BENEFITS OF WISDOM<br/><br/>Blessed is the man who finds wisdom, the man who gains understanding, for she(wisdom) is more profitable  than silver and yields better returns than gold. She is more precious than rubies; nothing you desire can compare with her. Long life is in her right hand; in her left hand are riches and honor.  Her ways are pleasant ways, and all her paths are peace. She is a tree of life to those who embrace her; those who lay hold of her will be blessed. AMEN; Proverbs 2:13-18
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31891bacb48f49dd70da8a4f2e40c3a4" url=""><![CDATA[HIS PROMISE TO YOU.<br/><br/>But now, this is what the Lord says-He who created you, &quot;Fear not, for I have redeemed you; I have summoned you by name; you are mine. When you pass through the waters, I will be with you; and when you pass through the rivers, they will not sweep over you. When you walk through the fire, you will not be burned; the flames will not set you ablaze. For I am the Lord, your God, the Holy One of Israel, your Savior; I give Egypt for your ransom, Cush and Seba in your stead. Since you are precious and honoured in my sight, and because I love you, I will give men in exchange for you, and people in exchange for your life. Don not be afraid, for I am with you....ISAIAH 43:1-4
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f537f443ab34afad9eb99f3a533286e" url=""><![CDATA[CALL TO REPENTANCE.<br/><br/>Submit yourselves , then, to God. Resist the devil, and he will flee from you. Come near to God and he will come near to you. Wash your hands, you sinners, and purify your hearts, you double minded. Grieve, mourn and wail,. Change your laughter to mourning and your joy to gloom. Humble yourselves before the Lord, and He will lift you up.  Brothers, do not slander one another. Anyone who speaks against his brother or judges him speaks against the law and judges it. When you judge the law, you are not keeping it, but sitting in judgement on it. There is only one Lawgiver and Judge, the one who is able to save and destroy. But you- who are you to judge your neighbour? <strong>James 4:7-12</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="859928117c7c0f5b08e3e9ce666cf481" url=""><![CDATA[CHANGE YOUR WAYS!<br/><br/>&quot;....You have rejected me&quot;, declares the Lord. &quot;You keep on backsliding. So i will lay hands on you and destroy you; I can no longer show compassion. I will winnow them with a winnowing fork at the city gates of the land. I will bring bereavement and destruction on my people, for they have not changed their ways. I will make their widows more numerous than the sand of the sea. At midday i will bring a destroyer against the mothers of their young men; suddenly I will bring down on them anguish and terror. The mother of seven will grow faint and breath her last. Her sun will set while it is still day; she will be disgraced and humiliated. I will put the survivors to the sword before their enemies.&quot; declares the Lord. [b]Jeremiah 15:6-9[b]
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7522b5d92b1c9904a8ea7365faf36232" url=""><![CDATA[WE'RE NOT FORSAKEN<br/><br/>The Lord is with you when you are with Him. If you forsake Him, he will forsake you. For a long time Israel was without the true God, without a priest to teach and without the law.But in their distress they turned to the LORD, the God of Israel, and sought Him, and He was found by them. V7b. As for you, be strong and do not give up for your work will be rewarded!<strong> 2Chronicles 15:2b-4;7b</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="94550e42af8efca2342868fadd4432f3" url=""><![CDATA[BLESSINGS FOR OBEDIENCE<br/><br/>If you fully obey the Lord your God and carefully follow all his commands............................all these blessings will come upon you and accompany you....
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />You will be blessed in the city and blessed in the country. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />The fruit of your womb will be blessed, and the crops of your land and the young of your livestock-the     calves of your herds and the lambs of your flocks. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />Your basket and your kneading trough will be blessed. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />Your will be blessed when you come in and blessed when you go out. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />The Lord will grant that the enemies who rise up against you will be defeated before you. They will come at you from one direction but flee from you in seven. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />The Lord will send a blessing on your barns and on everything you put your hands to.
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />The Lord will open the havens, the storehouse of his bounty, to send rain on your land in season and to bless all the work of your hands.
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />You will lend to many nations but will borrow from none. 
<br /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />The Lord will make you the head, not the tail
<br /><strong>Deuteronomy 28:1-13</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7fc01a8ddb65e9474f52a6bb936cc212" url=""><![CDATA[NO SITUATION IS HARD FOR HIM<br/><br/>This is what the Lord says- He who made a way through the sea, a path through the mighty waters, who drew out the chariots and horses, the army and reinforcements together, and they lay there, never to rise again, extinguished, snuffed out like a Wick <strong>&quot;Forget the former things; do not dwell on the past. See, I am doing a new thing! Now it springs ; do you not perceive it? I am making a way in the desert and streams in the wasteland. The wild animals honor me, the jackals and the owls, because I provide water in The desert and steams int he wasteland, to give drink to my people, my chosen, the people I formed for myself that they may proclaim my praise.</strong> Isaiah 43:16-21
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="60ad25e5b318d353afe54a3b527fa821" url=""><![CDATA[GOD, OUR STRENGH<br/><br/>Why do you say and complain,....&quot;my way is hidden from the Lord; my cause is disregarded by my God&quot;? Do you not know? Have you not heard? The Lord is the everlasting God, the creator of the ends of the earth. He will not grow tired or weary, and His understanding no-one can fathom. He gives strength to the weary and increases the power of the weak. Even youths grow tired and  weary, and young men stumble and fall; but those who hope in the Lord will renew their strength. They will soar on wings like eagles; they will run and not grow weary, they will walk and not be faint. (Isaiah 40:27-31)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="808c0c202bab6d06bf303dda84e6a3f7" url=""><![CDATA[HE'S WORTHY OF OUR PRAISE<br/><br/>Praise the Lord, O servants of the LORD, Praise the name of the LORD. Let the name of the Lord be praised, both now and for evermore. From the rising of the Sun to the place where it sets, the name of the Lord is to be praised. The Lord is exalted over all the nations, his glory above the heavens. <strong>WHO IS LIKE THE LORD OUR GOD</strong>, the One who sits enthroned on high, who stoops down to look on heavens and the earth?  He raises the poor from the dust and lifts the needy from the ash heap; he seats them with princes, with the princes of their people. He settles the barren woman in her home as a happy mother of children. <strong>PRAISE THE LORD. Psalms 113</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31c3f392e2242355b0733c9e62f3dc66" url=""><![CDATA[THE COUNSEL OF GOD<br/><br/>My son, do not forget my teaching, but keep my commands in your heart, for they will prolong your life many years and bring you prosperity.  Let love and faithfulness never leave you; bind them around you neck, write them on the tablets of your heart. Then you will win favor and a good name in the sight of God and man.  Trust in the LORD with all your heart and lean not on your own understanding; in all your ways acknowledge him, and he will make your paths straight. Do not be wise in your own eyes; fear the Lord and sun evil. This will bring health to your body and nourishment to your bones.. Honor the Lord with your wealth, with the first fruits of all your crops; then your barns will be filled to overflowing and your vats will brim over with new wine. <strong>Proverbs 3:1-9</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4011048af7552fa31f5a2190aaa3e13b" url=""><![CDATA[THE POWER OF BELIEVING<br/><br/>He said to them, &quot;Go into all the world and preach the good news to all creation. <strong>Whoever believes and is baptized will be saved, but whoever does not believe will be condemned. And these signs will accompany those who believe: In my name they will drive out demons; they will speak in new tongues; they will pick up snakes with their hands; and when they drink deadly poison, it will not hurt them at all; they will place their hands on sick people, and they will get well.&quot;</strong> After the Lord Jesus had spoken to them, he was taken up into heaven and he sat at the right hand of God. Then the disciples went out and preached everywhere, and the Lord worked with them and confirmed his word by the signs that accompanied it. <strong>Mark 16: 15-20</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="64ad4b4b9b9e1694c01196fea33fe31d" url=""><![CDATA[LEARN TO TRUST IN GOD ALONE!<br/><br/>This is what the Lord says: &quot;Cursed is the one who trusts in man, who depends on flesh for his strength and whose heart turns away from the Lord. He will be like a bush in the wastelands; he will not see prosperity when it comes. He will dwell in the parched places of the desert, in a salt land where no-one lives.&quot; <strong>&quot;BUT BLESSED</strong>  is the man who trusts in the Lord, whose confidence is in him. He will be like a tree planted by the water that sends out its roots by the stream. It does not fear when heat comes; its leaves are always green. It has not worries in a year of drought and never fails to bear fruit.<strong> Jeremiah 17:5-8</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a2b4ae29462bf796121669f63dd907a" url=""><![CDATA[HIS RIGHTEOUSNESS SPRINGS UP!!<br/><br/>I delight greatly in the Lord; my soul rejoices in my God. For He has clothed me with garments of salvation and arrayed me in a robe of righteousness, as a bridegroom adorns his head like a priest, and as a bride adorns herself with her jewels. For as the soil makes the young plant to come up, and a garden causes seeds to grow, so the Sovereign Lord will make righteousness and praise spring up before all nations. <strong>Isaiah 61:10-11. I</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="181819cf0dd742fa2c1c7c9379e2ba57" url=""><![CDATA[HIS WORD IS TRUE! BELIEVE IT!!<br/><br/>&quot;For  my thoughts are not your thoughts, neither are your ways my ways, declares the Lord. &quot;As the heavens are higher than the earth, so are my ways higher than your ways and my thoughts than your thoughts. As the rain and the snow come down from heaven, and do not return to it without watering the earth and making it bud and flourish, so that it yields seed for the sower and bread for the eater, so is my word that goes out from my mouth; It will not return  to me empty, but will accomplish what I desire and achieve the purpose for which I sent it. You will go out in joy and be led forth in peace; the mountains and hills will burst into song before you, and all the trees of the field will clap their hands. Instead of the thorn bush will grow the pine tree, and instead of briers the myrtle will grow. This will be for the LORD'S renown, for an everlasting sign, which will not be destroyed.&quot; <strong>Isaiah 55:8-13</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8f09a8016ccf4b748e8c91395a031273" url=""><![CDATA[YOUR STATUS RESTORED!!<br/><br/>I have posted watchmen on your walls, O Jerusalem; they will never be silent day or night. You who call on the Lord, give yourselves no rest, and give Him no rest till He establishes Jerusalem and makes her the praise of the earth. The  Lord has sworn by His right hand and by His mighty arm: &quot; Never again will  I give your grain as food for your enemies, and never again will foreigners drink the new wine for which your have toiled; but those who harvest it will eat it and praise the LORD, and those who gather the grapes will drink it in courts of my sanctuary.&quot;<strong> Isaiah 62:6-9</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9a5b3a33ccd156b5b1297b5226a02199" url=""><![CDATA[THIS FAR, HE IS EBENEZAR<br/><br/>When you have eaten and are satisfied, Praise the Lord your God for the good land He has given you. Be careful that you do not forget the LORD your God, failing to observe His commands, His laws and His decrees....... Otherwise when you eat and are satisfied, when you build fine houses and settle down, and when your herds and flocks grow large and your silver and gold increase and all you have is multiplied, then your heart will become proud and you will forget the LORD your God..........You may say to yourself, &quot; My power and the strength of my hands have produced this wealth for me.&quot; BUT remember the LORD your God, for it is He who gives you the ability to produce wealth..........If you ever forget the Lord your God and follow other gods and worship and bow down to them, I testify against you today that you will surely be destroyed. <strong>Deuteronomy 8:10-19</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="70189f0c543d6e0f574db0a0db3c9903" url=""><![CDATA[THE TIME TO SERVE GOD IS NOW!!<br/><br/>Remember  your creator in the days of your youth, before the days of trouble come and the years approach when you will say, &quot;I find no pleasure in them&quot; - before the sun and the light and the moon and the stars grow dark, and the clouds return after the rain; when the keepers of the house tremble, and the strong men stoop, when the grinders cease because they are few, and those looking through the windows grow dim; when the doors to the street are closed and the sound of grinding fades; when men rise up at the sound of birds, but all their songs grow faint; when men are afraid of heights and of dangers in the streets; when the almond tree blossoms and the grasshopper drags himself along and desire no longer is stirred. Then man goes to his eternal home and mourners go about the streets.  Remember him-before the silver cord is severed, or the golden bowl is broken; before the pitcher is shattered at the spring, or the wheels broken at the well, and the dust returns to the ground it came from, and  the spirit returns to God who gave it. <strong>Ecclesiastes 12:1-7</strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71dee0928ee9c282ebcc2d5930d0688e" url=""><![CDATA[ARE U HIS FRIEND OR ENEMY?<br/><br/>The LORD is a jealous and avenging God; the LORD takes vengeance and is filled with wrath. The LORD takes vengeance on his foes and maintains his wrath against his enemies. The LORD will not leave the guilty unpunished. His way is in the whirlwind and the storm, and clouds are the dust of his feet. He rebukes the sea and dries it up; he makes all the rivers run dry. Bashan and Carmel wither and the blossoms of Lebanon fade. The mountains quake before him and the hills melt away. The earth trembles at his presence, the world and all who live in it. Who can withstand his indignation? Who  can endure his his fierce anger? His wrath is poured out  like fire; the rocks are shattered before him. The LORD is good, a refuge in times of trouble. He cares for those who trust in him, but with an overwhelming flood he will make an end of Niveveh; he will pursue his foes into darkness. <strong>Nahum 1: 2 - 8</strong><strong></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89a33e14d98f1bc3929f129ffcaa21c8" url=""><![CDATA[THE POWER OF WISDOM.<br/><br/>Wisdom, like an inheritance, is a good thing and benefits those who see the sun. Wisdom is a shelter as money is a shelter, but the advantage of knowledge is this: that wisdom preserves the life of its possessor. Consider what God has done: who can straighten what He has made crooked? When times are good, be happy; but when times are bad, consider God has made the one as well as the other. Therefore, a man cannot discover anything about his future.  Ecclesiastes 6:11-14.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>