<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="19">
		<document id="e96de40d08af3aa8fdb8c13d799c885d" url=""><![CDATA[Find out more<br/><br/>Hard numbers are hard to come by, but it is highly probably that the number of kids currently taking Karate lessons in the United States would be in the hundreds of thousands, if not more. You just type a term like 'Karate lessons for kids' on your search engine, and the huge number of centers offering the lessons that the search yields aver to the fact that there is great demand for the lessons. After all, if all those centers offering the lessons are managing to remain in business, and seemingly thrive, then clearly, there must be demand for the service they are offering.<br /><br />The critical thinker will, however, be more interested in understanding the factors driving that growing popularity of kids karate lessons. Those are, in effect, the attractions to the said lessons.<br /><br />As it turns out, one of the factors behind the growing popularity of karate lessons for kids is that in them, parents see a fun way to get their kids off the couches. Many of us are already familiar with the predicament facing us: where kids are getting into sedentary lifestyles too early in their lives, the end result being the kids' obesity pandemic currently facing most of the developed world. And this is happening at a point when the age of whipping kids into physical activity is long gone. Today, if you want your kids to lead an active lifestyle, you have to find ways of getting them to do so out of their own volition. And kids will normally only do something willingly if they perceive it as 'fun.' Now karate, correctly taught, comes across as such - and the kids are bound to love it, thus willingly getting them off the couches.<br /><br />Another factor behind the growing popularity of kids karate lessons is that in those lessons, parents see the opportunity to have their kids learn the much needed self defense skills in today's world. That is after taking cognizance of the fact that in spite of the world being a much developed place today, there are still people who are yet to evolve out of the savagery which is physical confrontation tendencies. War is still a basic fact of life. Sometimes, the ability to physically defend oneself actually becomes a life and death matter. And as we all know, the best time for physical skill acquisition is during the childhood, hence the desire by many parents to have their kids on karate lessons as early as reasonably possible.<br /><br />Yet another reason behind the growing popularity of karate lessons for kids is that it has been demonstrated that practice of the martial arts correlates favorably with high levels of self discipline. Previously, it was thought that it was because people were self disciplined that they would be inclined towards taking up the martial arts. But increasingly, it is being realized that the inverse is also true, where people who practice martial arts consistently eventually develop high levels of self discipline. And naturally, every parent who is cognizant of the relationship between high levels of self discipline and life happiness (as well as success) would want their kid to have such high levels of self discipline. Upon learning that one of the ways they can help their kids develop high degrees of self discipline is by enrolling them for kids karate lessons, that is exactly what they proceed to do.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LmxpdmVqb3VybmFsLmNvbS82ODQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Houston kickboxing</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdXBlcm5vdmEuY29tL0lvbG5pYU5wZWFtYXRpb24vYmxvZy82OTUxMjI_" target="_blank">Kids Martial Arts Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50ZXN0ZWQuY29tL3Byb2ZpbGUvdHlsZXJib3lsZTM2L2Jsb2dzLzQyMjIwNS8_" target="_blank">This site</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="12e141be4c08ce7e2f4464e5235cf76d" url=""><![CDATA[Click here<br/><br/>Fight or flight is an interesting choice. For most people, however, it is not a choice, but something they do blindly, no choice at all.<br /><br />Wake up! <br />If a dog snaps at you, there is intuitive movement. The movement is always away. Teeth win, hand lose, no contest, get the heck outa Dodge.<br /><br />If a human being snaps at you...hmm. Most people jump back, enter into flight mode. The problem is that it is a blind reaction. And, unfortunately, the few people who leap at the snapper...it is a blind reaction for them, too. Just a slightly different blindness.<br /><br />So what if your back was to a cliff, and a human snapped at you. Would you jump off the cliff? I mean, when do you start making choices? In this scenario your choice comes about because the fall off a cliff would hurt more than a snapping human. Surprisingly, most people would jump off a cliff.<br /><br />When you study martial arts you change that. At first, you get a little hair trigger. Somebody growls at you, and you growl back before you even think about what you are doing. And if they snap at you, they end up with a fist in their eye.<br /><br />But what if it is granny that tapped you on the back late at night? In that scenario you just knocked granny's false teeth out, armlocked her to the ground and stepped on her spindly, little neck. Grandpa ain't gonna be too happy about that.<br /><br />So you have to get past flight AND fight as blind responses. You must train until you move from choice, and not from reaction.<br /><br />When you do this, when you gain choice in your actions, no matter what the threat or how severe, you have increased your awareness. Or, to put it another way, you have woken up.<br /><br />Man, you see, is asleep...dreaming that he is awake. It's true.<br /><br />That guy filling out the voting form? He's as blind as the guy pulling the silver arm in a casino. Throw away money or throw away future...or throw away a whole country...it is a form of unconsciousness.<br /><br />You, reading this. You are only dreaming that you are reading this. You're actually asleep, and you will finish this bit of eye exercise and continue to be asleep.<br /><br />So, want to wake up? Do the martial arts. Learn Karate or Tai Chi or something. Become aware of all your potentials and choices. Stop dreaming that you're awake and...AWAKE!<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXJlY3RvcmlzZS5jb20vbGlzdGluZy80NjQyNDgtS2lkcy1LYXJhdGUtY2xhc3Nlcy1Ib3VzdG9uLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Kids Karate Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdXBlcm5vdmEuY29tL0lvbG5pYU5wZWFtYXRpb24vYmxvZy82OTUxMjI_" target="_blank">Find out more</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kZWluZWtvbGxlZ2VuLmRlL2Jsb2cucGhwP3VzZXI9dHlsZXJib3lsZTM2JmFtcDtibG9nZW50cnlfaWQ9NTU3NjkzMg__" target="_blank">Kids Martial Arts Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="397b0b033bba7f5da3f3055162374f83" url=""><![CDATA[Find out more<br/><br/>Kids karate lessons have been a great option for youngsters to take for many years and for a variety of reasons. The great news is that this category has finally begun to expand to include things like kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu as well as other forms of MMA. Surprisingly many parents are still unaware of just how beneficial kids mixed martial arts classes can be. <br /><br />Here are just a few of the reasons kids MMA classes are helping change and improve lives: <br /><br />Self-defense: Kids mixed martial arts classes help your child learn useful defense moves that could help protect them from a potential bully or other type of assault. Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu for example is probably one of the greatest ways a student can learn to recover from an attack that leaves them in the most vulnerable position - on the ground. <br /><br />Improve Fitness: Kids Karate Lessons can help your child or teen get into excellent physical shape. So many youngsters these days struggle with being out of shape, overweight or even obese. MMA can help whip your child in to shape no matter what their current physical abilities are. Most students start without ever having taken a karate class and are often times not physically fit yet. This training will change all of that. <br /><br />Increase self-confidence: Your child will also be able to become more confident and less shy from taking classes like this. Getting in shape, feeling certain one could defend him or herself and even getting and achieving goals like earning different belt levels are all just a few of the reasons kids MMA classes help them feel more confident and less shy. <br /><br />Enhance focus: Almost any age of child or teen who struggles with behavioral problems stemming from a lack of focus or respect for others can turn this pattern around with kids karate classes. Karate and mixed martial arts command both focus during training and respect for the teacher and other students. Your child or teen will begin to develop skills in both of these areas without even trying. The best part is this often happens almost immediately. <br /><br />Safe environment: Kids MMA Classes also gives children and teens a safe and productive place to go after school and on weekends. Too many kids these days get involved in the wrong kind of extra-curricular activities that can lead to involvement with drugs, violence and even gangs. Or you may be tired of your child wasting time attached to their laptop, gaming system or some type of handheld mobile device. Keep your kids off the streets and unplugged from technological gadgets by giving them a better option. <br /><br />Guess what? This is only a few of the ways kids MMA classes are helping changing lives. We also guarantee once your child is participating in kids karate classes your entire family's life may just change too. <br /><br />Visit us at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Focjj.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://ocjj.com/</a> for complete details!! <br /><br />At OC Jiu-Jitsu and MMA you will develop mixed martial arts specific strength and conditioning and also a detailed, technical ground game in our Brazilian Jiu Jitsu Orange County classes and the blueprint for a complete striking game in our OC Muay Thai fundamentals classes. OC Jiu-Jitsu &amp; MMA combines the most effective martial arts PROVEN in the Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC). <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYWlseXN0cmVuZ3RoLm9yZy9wZW9wbGUvMjA4NzcyOS9qb3VybmFs" target="_blank">Houston MMA</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50ZXN0ZWQuY29tL3Byb2ZpbGUvZXN0ZWJhbnJhc2NoMzcvYmxvZ3MvNDIyMjI0Lw__" target="_blank">Houston kickboxing</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy9pdGVtL2hvdXN0b24ta2lja2JveGluZw__" target="_blank">Click here</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b5ee319533a72843fcb6f6c6f0bcb664" url=""><![CDATA[Kids Karate classes Houston<br/><br/>Nearly every day more studies and research are pointing to the multiple and various benefits of traditional training programs especially those that are taught through martial arts classes to children across the globe. Yes, contrary to most beliefs, teaching your child any type of skill form like Taekwondo, Judo or Karate is not going to make them aggressive or violent. On the contrary, if taught in the authentic way, these classes can really enhance your children's personality and aid in healthy development of their mind, body and spirit in a completely holistic manner.<br /><br />The Real Essence of Martial Arts <br /><br />While enrolling your kids into martial arts classes can help them to learn effective techniques for defending themselves from getting bullied in class or outside, the key role of this training is much more than just teaching children about self-defense. Traditional schools like the ones that teach Taekwondo, Karate or Tai Chi are based on the tenets of absorbing the spirit of peace, compassion, justice, self-control and discipline amongst the students. Students who are initiated into Taekwondo martial arts classes take a pledge to never misuse their power and to apply compassion and peaceful living in all aspects of their lives. Understanding these facts about the basic value system of martial arts helps us further understanding the holistic influence of these practices in our lives.<br /><br />Exclusive Martial Arts Classes for Children <br /><br />With more and more parents becoming aware of the various benefits of enrolling their children in these classes, there has been a significant upsurge in the types of training programs that are now available for children. From traditional taekwondo, karate and judo lessons to training programs that have been customized for children with special needs, parents can now find the type of martial art form that will be perfectly suited for their children.<br /><br />Certain schools are also offering a contemporary form of teaching plan through which kids learn about various types of martial art techniques that are fused into one basic training program to make the classes all the more interesting and engaging. It is a great idea to begin young children through these integrated classes, before graduating into a particular discipline like Taekwondo or Judo or any other form as they grow older.<br /><br />The Holistic Benefits of Martial Arts Classes <br /><br />Most parents who enroll their children into these classes can notice positive changes in their personalities right away. As children spend more and more time training and learning these techniques they become more and more centered and self-assured. Most of the techniques taught through this arts rely on the repetitive training on particular movement unless and until the student is perfect in a particular move. This form of training helps children to tap into the innate ability to focus and produce results which in turn makes them more and more content and confident. Renowned classes like taekwondo also build effective social skills as the teachings help children in maintaining and nurturing respectful relationships with their peers as well as their fellow students.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BkeHBlYWNlLm9yZy9ibG9nL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LzIwMTIvc2VwLzA4L2ZpbmQtb3V0LW1vcmU_" target="_blank">Kids martial arts classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LmxpdmVqb3VybmFsLmNvbS83ODMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Houston kickboxing</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb290YmFsbG91dHNpZGVycy5jb20vZGlzY3Vzc2lvbi9ob3VzdG9uLWtpY2tib3hpbmc_" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4bd7c5c53529f32681bb4eacf018ab27" url=""><![CDATA[This site<br/><br/>If you are currently interested in getting your kids involved in martial arts, you will need to know where to go to get them started. It will be extremely important to make certain that you find the right place, because you will want to help them get as much out of this experience as possible. There are plenty of different places you will be able to go when it comes to martial arts for kids. Whether your kids are just starting out in the world of martial arts or they have some experience already, you will be able to enter them into the right class to help them build skills and abilities they never knew they could have. <br /><br />One of the first things you will want to do when looking for martial arts classes to enrol your kids in is go online, because it is there where you will be able to find all the information you need to get your children started. Keep in mind that it will be extremely important to make sure you choose the right place to take them, because there are definitely going to be some places that are better than others. <br /><br />Typically there are specific places just for martial arts lessons which are aimed at children and young adults. You will need to make sure that you look at as many of your options as possible though, because you will need to make the right decision in order to help them get the most out of the classes they attend. Whether they are interested in jujitsu or karate, you will need to spend a decent amount of time online researching various places in your area that can give your kids what they want. <br /><br />Throughout the process of looking for a place that offers martial arts for kids, you should make sure that you consider how much you should and are willing to spend. Although typically martial arts lessons do not cost a lot of money, there are still going to be some places that are more expensive than others. Sometimes more expensive classes suggest a more experienced teacher and therefore a better learning experience all around. Sometimes however more expensive just means more expensive, so you will want to avoid getting ripped off. <br /><br />Those parents that are currently interested in finding places that provide martial arts lessons for kids will need to go online and also visit a few places in person, just so they can get some idea of what each place is like. Since there are going to be so many options for you to look over, you will need to spend an adequate amount of time looking at what you have to choose from for the sake of your children. If you want your kids to learn martial arts in the best way possible while having lots of fun, you will need to find the right place for them to go so you will know they will get the full experience. <br /><br />Searching for a place that offers martial arts for kids in your area? Follow the links to locate numerous places that can provide martial arts for kids in a disciplined classroom format. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZW9mdXNpb24ub3JnL25vZGUvMjc3NTE3" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy8yMjYyMDU3" target="_blank">Houston MMA</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kZWluZWtvbGxlZ2VuLmRlL2Jsb2cucGhwP3VzZXI9dHlsZXJib3lsZTM2JmFtcDtibG9nZW50cnlfaWQ9NTU3NzA0OA__" target="_blank">Kids Martial Arts Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f7f9563ece9b8cc1d1d9845f041be114" url=""><![CDATA[Kids Karate classes Houston<br/><br/>Whoopie advised Sherri not to hover over her son to the point that he can not breathe. (Her son was born pre-maturely and is very little.) Whoopie told her that her son is incredibly cute, but if she wants him to have the life that she wants for him, he's going to have to learn what he can and can not do. She has to let him learn what he needs to learn, because he may be on a class trip and she may not be there.<br /><br />Sherri said that you have to be there sometimes to be the person to stop them from getting hurt. She told of a time when her son was trying to get back on the monkey bar, and evidently she was standing there. Someone came up and told her that she had to move. She said that she emphatically told the person, &quot;NO YOU MOVE. MY SON IS TRYING TO GET ON THE MONKEY BAR.&quot; Was Sherri being a bully, or was she just being a Mommy?<br /><br />Whoopie asked Jackie Chan if he hovered over his children. He said &quot;NO&quot;. He liked to see his son fall down and get hurt. He would not let their mother pamper them when they got hurt. He said that when a mother is not around when the child gets hurt, the child screams bloody murder.<br /><br />Jaden was asked if he wanted his mom around while he was doing the movie. His answer was&quot;Yes&quot;. He said he did get hurt on the set and no one cared. His mom was the only one that would give him sympathy. He said that she helps. He even gives up some of his recreation time to be with his mom. He likes being with his mom.<br /><br />Joy asked Jackie if he was a bully as a child. He said &quot;Yes&quot;. He said after he learned martial arts, he learned that it was not used to bully, but to help. Joy told Jackie that one of the things that bullies want is to be loved. She asked Jackie was that his problem and he said &quot;No &quot;.<br /><br />Jaden said that it was hard for his mom to watch him train for the movie, but his father pushed him to the limit. In the Movie, there was a bully who continuously beat up the karate kid (Jaden). The karate kid had to train and learn how to fight to protect himself.<br /><br />Every kid who is being bullied has to figure out how to protect himself/herself. Once you know how to protect yourself from bullies, your self-esteem will dramatically increase. That is what happened at the end of The Karate Kid. To find out more about self-esteem, look for my book, &quot;Formula For Success - Success Can Be Your Too&quot;, at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.margiewrobinson.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.margiewrobinson.com</a>.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mb290YmFsbG91dHNpZGVycy5jb20vZGlzY3Vzc2lvbi9ob3VzdG9uLWtpY2tib3hpbmctMA__" target="_blank">Kids Martial Arts Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVwaXhpZWNvbGxlY3RpdmUuY29tL2ZvcnVtdG9waWMvZmluZF9vdXRfbW9yZQ__" target="_blank">Kids Karate Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50ZXN0ZWQuY29tL3Byb2ZpbGUvZXN0ZWJhbnJhc2NoMzcvYmxvZ3MvNDIyNDU2Lw__" target="_blank">Kids Martial Arts Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f022ad02ae067e6d59b283dcff857323" url=""><![CDATA[Houston martial arts<br/><br/>The martial art form of Jujitsu is no longer just for adults. Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu is fast becoming popular with parents and children alike with many martial arts schools specializing in offering Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu training. <br /><br />Like adult instruction, Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu uses grappling techniques similar to judo. This technique enables development of stronger, more confident kids. The main attraction of Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu to many has long been how smaller people can defend themselves from larger enemies through the use of these training techniques. Because kids are more likely to associate martial arts with Karate, they might not be familiar with what Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu training has to offer so it is wise for parents to introduce them to this popular style. <br /><br />Check out these tips to help your child discover the benefits of training in Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu: <br /><br />Tell your child about the history of Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu and how it is used to promote health and strength to young people. The founder of judo, Kano Jigoro, taught martial arts to kids with an objective to promote spiritual strength and physical fitness. The majority of the training centers offering Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu operate with the same values and philosophy. <br /><br />Differentiate Judo, Karate and Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu. Inform your child that even though these martial arts have grappling and throwing techniques, Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu focuses on ground fighting techniques and the battle for dominance. <br /><br />A child who is being bullied by other kids at school or community can benefit from Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu since it provides techniques that will enable a smaller person to overcome a larger enemy. Also, with the knowledge of Jiu-Jitsu, your child will be more confident and physically fit so bullying from other kids might never be an issue. <br /><br />Have your child observe a Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu class in a local martial arts center so that they can be encouraged in enrolling themselves. Many schools offer sample classes for children to try out before committing to enrollment. <br /><br />Remember that most all kids love physical contact and wrestling. Think of all the time you have spent playing on the floor with your child. Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu allows your child to enjoy this type of physical activity while learning an effective self-defense. <br /><br />If your child already participates in Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu classes, make sure that you show your support for their training and accomplishes as they continue in their lessons. <br /><br />Are you or your children interested in taking up Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu? If you live in the Triangle NC area, check out Forged Fitness Facilities' 30 day free trial program on any of the kid's martial arts programs. To register for the 30 day free program and to know more about the benefits of Kids Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu in Raleigh, Morrisville or Cary, NC, visit our site online or call 919-877-7448. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYWlseXN0cmVuZ3RoLm9yZy9wZW9wbGUvMjA4NzcyOS9qb3VybmFs" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdXBlcm5vdmEuY29tL0lvbG5pYU5wZWFtYXRpb24vYmxvZy82OTUzOTQ_" target="_blank">Find out more</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy8yMjYyMTUx" target="_blank">This site</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c982f442347d90155cc3b636161dc9b0" url=""><![CDATA[Find out more<br/><br/>The IOW is one of the places that you should plan to visit with your whole family. If you have finalized your Isle of Wight holidays, you must book the luxurious and elegant Isle of Wight cottages in advance. Choose those that are just within the vicinity of the tourist attractions in the area. If you can book the holiday cottages near the hot spots, there will never be any problem with transportation during your Isle of Wight holidays, allowing you to go to as many places as possible. The holiday cottages are clean and can comfortably accommodate small or large groups. The holiday cottages are self-catering so you can cook as much as you want to. <br /><br />The West Wight Sports Centre <br /><br />If you are staying at the holiday cottages, the West Wight Sports Centre is a must during your Isle of Wight holidays. This sports centre is best visited in the morning, giving you enough time for other activities or other interesting places in the afternoon. You will find a 25 metre swimming pool with 6 lanes inside the sports centre where you can do several laps to keep fit. There is also a learner pool where your kids can try and learn how to swim. It would really be a great accomplishment if your kids can learn how to swim during this Isle of Wight holidays. Otherwise you can also take part in raft racing, snorkelling or canoeing where you can also take your kids with you. If you feel your kid is interested in the martial arts, you can let him join the karate lessons in the centre even if it is just for a short while. The West Wight Sports Centre is great for the whole family so make this a part of your day during your Isle of Wight holidays before you retire to your holiday cottages to rest for the night. <br /><br />The Isle of Wight Donkey Sanctuary <br /><br />Make this sanctuary a part of your Isle of Wight holidays especially when you are on this vacation together with your kids. Just within close proximity to your holiday cottages, the IOW Donkey Sanctuary is located between Shanklin and Ventnor. The place began operations in 1987 and is one of the most popular attractions for both locals and visitors especially those staying at the holiday cottages. Here you will find friendly donkeys and rare animals that are almost extinct which are being taken care of by the centre. This is an educational place for both adults and kids alike. <br /><br />The IOW Donkey Sanctuary opens its doors at 10:30 a.m. until 4 p.m. starting Easter until October 31 but just to make sure, call up the sanctuary from your holiday cottages to make sure that it is open when you go. Entrance ticket prices vary but donations are very much welcome to raise funds for the maintenance of the animals in the sanctuary. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BkeHBlYWNlLm9yZy9ibG9nL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LzIwMTIvc2VwLzA4L2hvdXN0b24ta2lja2JveGluZy0w" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LmxpdmVqb3VybmFsLmNvbS8xMzkxLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Houston MMA</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kYWlseXN0cmVuZ3RoLm9yZy9wZW9wbGUvMjA4NzcyOS9qb3VybmFs" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a913b4ba18c1fb11a11d891d2ee02e44" url=""><![CDATA[Kids Karate classes Houston<br/><br/>Self confidence is considered to be the most important part of life as it can leads to the success and happiness. It is very much crucial that the children should be given the opportunity at young age in order to develop this confidence.  Martial Arts Sydney is considered to be a great place to build the self confidence among the children. This article provides the simple ways to boost the confidence of a child. <br /><br />It has always been noticed that children will always imitate their parents as their role models. A good parent will surely be the excellent role model for your child. By boosting up the confidence you can provide a perfect body posture and can make your child a successful person. The sense of the Martial Arts Sutherland Shire will always enjoy a good time with children in the class because according to them spending the time with children can be the ultimate fun. <br /><br />If you are getting down and playing with the children, then you can explore more creativity of the children. This will definitely help in increasing the confidence of the child and he will become more focused towards his goals. The martial art schools in Australia are doing this task in a good manner because they know the names of each and every child which help in reinforcing their values. <br /><br />It is said that the principles which are developed carried in the martial arts will definitely affect the other areas of the life of a children. Martial Arts Inner West helps in discovering the good things in a child and praises them which help in building the self confidence. A good trainer will definitely help the child in losing his -labels' because according to them there are nothing like the asthmatic kid or the fat kid; all are the karate kids in their eyes. <br /><br />These martial art schools will help in teaching the good values to the children as well as also help them to take the critical decisions of their life which ultimately help them to deal with the pressure. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5CYW1CYW1NYXJ0aWFsQXJ0cy5jb20_" target="_blank">Kids martial arts classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5CYW1CYW1NYXJ0aWFsYXJ0cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iYW1iYW1tYXJ0aWFsYXJ0cy5jb20vbWFydGlhbC1hcnRzLWtpZHMtaG91c3Rvbg__" target="_blank">Kids Karate Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cd6388292c3a5f0b785b7d55cc968b78" url=""><![CDATA[This site<br/><br/>Most people know that karate and other martial arts classes require a lot of discipline. It's not easy learning the techniques, and your typical sensei is quite strict. But how does that translate into doing better at school?<br /><br />You might be surprised, especially at how little time it takes to show a difference in your child's behavior in school. My daughter took her first martial arts classes in kindergarten (Tang Soo Do, to be specific), and her teacher commented in the first month that my daughter's behavior in class had improved. That's well before any belts were even possible to reach, aside from the introductory white belt that all students received at the end of the first class.<br /><br />It's not just how kids behave in class that is improved, although that's a nice plus. There are more academic benefits to students who take karate and other martial arts classes.<br /><br />Discipline<br /><br />This goes beyond just behaving in class. There's always a goal to aim for in karate, whether it's reaching the next belt level or figuring out that new move. It's a lot of work, and that's good for kids to learn in one place, so they can apply it in school.<br /><br />Some senseis take things a bit farther and will also discipline kids in karate class for misbehavior at school. Most have very high expectations for how their students behave in their lives as a whole, not just how they behave at the dojo or studio.<br /><br />Focus<br /><br />Martial arts training takes a lot of focus. Students really have to pay attention to understand exactly how each move is performed, even when the sensei shows it slowly.<br /><br />That focus translates into how academic work is done. Kids learn to keep focus on their studies, which allows them to do it more quickly and accurately.<br /><br />Build Memorization Skills<br /><br />As your child advances in the martial arts, many forms have them memorize a kata, or a series of moves performed in a precise sequence. Even the early ones can be fairly complex, and take a lot of practice to memorize.<br /><br />While academic work should not all be memorization, a significant part of it will relate to having memorized the basics. This is an important skill for any student to master.<br /><br />Confidence<br /><br />Learning a martial art is a great way to build a child's confidence. It's an amazing feeling to master a new skill, especially one that is so challenging. This is a great confidence builder.<br /><br />It may not seem as though confidence is a skill much needed in school, but it truly can be important. Confidence means your child is more likely to speak his or her mind in discussions, or ask questions of the teacher. It can mean they cope better if they're bothered by a bully. It may help them to be less afraid to learn new things.<br /><br />Hard Work Is Rewarded<br /><br />Hard work in karate classes are rewarded when your child takes the test and earns either a new stripe on their belt or the next level belt. They won't get to the next level just for being in class; that stripe or belt must be earned. Karate helps them to see that they should respect their teachers, classmates, parents and others around them.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5CYW1CYW1NYXJ0aWFsQXJ0cy5jb20_" target="_blank">Houston kickboxing</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iYW1iYW1tYXJ0aWFsYXJ0cy5jb20va2lja2JveGluZ2hvdXN0b24_" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5CYW1CYW1NYXJ0aWFsYXJ0cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2081b16adf7611d08514f74fbda0ac5e" url=""><![CDATA[Kids martial arts classes Houston<br/><br/>Kids karate lessons have become extremely popular in recent days. Hard numbers are hard to come by, but it is highly probably that the number of kids currently taking Karate lessons in the United States would be in the hundreds of thousands, if not more. You just type a term like 'Karate lessons for kids' on your search engine, and the huge number of centers offering the lessons that the search yields aver to the fact that there is great demand for the lessons. After all, if all those centers offering the lessons are managing to remain in business, and seemingly thrive, then clearly, there must be demand for the service they are offering.<br /><br />The critical thinker will, however, be more interested in understanding the factors driving that growing popularity of kids karate lessons. Those are, in effect, the attractions to the said lessons.<br /><br />As it turns out, one of the factors behind the growing popularity of karate lessons for kids is that in them, parents see a fun way to get their kids off the couches. Many of us are already familiar with the predicament facing us: where kids are getting into sedentary lifestyles too early in their lives, the end result being the kids' obesity pandemic currently facing most of the developed world. And this is happening at a point when the age of whipping kids into physical activity is long gone. Today, if you want your kids to lead an active lifestyle, you have to find ways of getting them to do so out of their own volition. And kids will normally only do something willingly if they perceive it as 'fun.' Now karate, correctly taught, comes across as such - and the kids are bound to love it, thus willingly getting them off the couches.<br /><br />Another factor behind the growing popularity of kids karate lessons is that in those lessons, parents see the opportunity to have their kids learn the much needed self defense skills in today's world. That is after taking cognizance of the fact that in spite of the world being a much developed place today, there are still people who are yet to evolve out of the savagery which is physical confrontation tendencies. War is still a basic fact of life. Sometimes, the ability to physically defend oneself actually becomes a life and death matter. And as we all know, the best time for physical skill acquisition is during the childhood, hence the desire by many parents to have their kids on karate lessons as early as reasonably possible.<br /><br />Yet another reason behind the growing popularity of karate lessons for kids is that it has been demonstrated that practice of the martial arts correlates favorably with high levels of self discipline. Previously, it was thought that it was because people were self disciplined that they would be inclined towards taking up the martial arts. But increasingly, it is being realized that the inverse is also true, where people who practice martial arts consistently eventually develop high levels of self discipline. Upon learning that one of the ways they can help their kids develop high degrees of self discipline is by enrolling them for kids karate lessons, that is exactly what they proceed to do.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3R5bGVyYm95bGUzNi54YW5nYS5jb20vNzY3ODA3MTEwL2tpZHMta2FyYXRlLWhvdXN0b24v" target="_blank">Kids Martial Arts Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aWxhZ28yMS5jb20vZXZlbnQvSG91c3RvbitraWNrYm94aW5nLzEzNzA3NjYvcHJvZmlsZQ__" target="_blank">Kids Karate Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGl2ZW5vdGRlYWQuY29tL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3L0hvdXN0b24ta2lja2JveGluZy1wcm9maWxlLTI3OTE3NjIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Houston MMA</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="335f7ffb732fb7f5a00fcb2d2191bc50" url=""><![CDATA[Find out more<br/><br/>Unfortunately, the disadvantage to being raised in a small town is that if you are unlucky enough to be targeted by bullies, it can be more difficult to find places to hide.<br /><br />Everything was great in grade school. My friends and I were all from the same side of our 10,000 person town and had spent years getting to know each other. I was an average sized kid for my age, but was a little more soft spoken and polite than a lot of the kids in my class. My teachers always loved me because I never got in trouble or disrespected them or other students. For me, the problems began in Junior High.<br /><br />In my town, there were four grade schools and one junior high school. In seventh grade, all of the prior 6th graders were moved into the junior high school and mixed with kids from the other elementary schools. There was a small grade school that was on the outskirts of town that was part of this transition and included a little different breed of student than I had been used to. For the first couple of weeks of junior high, I clung to the friends I had known since kindergarten, but was also mixed into classes with many students I didn't know. Even though I was not a very coordinated child, I joined the football team so that I could at least feel like I was part of something. My problems really started when in algebra class.<br /><br />I've always gotten good grades in math. Despite this, somehow I ended up in a math class with all of the juvenile delinquents in my school. I remember sitting in class feeling horrible about how disrespectful of the kids were being to the teacher. He tried all sorts of discipline techniques with no success and because I was the one student in the class who paid attention to him and treated him with respect, he used to give me favoritism to some of the other kids. This brought some negative attention in my direction. The kids in my class started by teasing and calling me names, but that quickly escalated into throwing things at me and pushing in the halls. My teacher did everything he could to protect me from the bullying, but it only got worse. I knew that if I went to the principal, it would only make things worse, and I didn't have the heart to tell my parents. At this point, I determined that if I wanted the bullying to stop, I would have to learn to fight.<br /><br />Another unfortunate thing about living in my small town is that there was not a karate school that I could join. Up until now, I had only seen karate in the movies and had an unrealistic idea of what it entailed. Nowadays, I could probably just do some hunting online and find some great websites that would teach me martial arts through online videos, but the best I could do in my town was head on down to the library. Fortunately, the library did have a small section of martial arts books that I was able to check out. All of the books I brought home were very old and illustrated with black and white photography, but it was a start. I only wish I could have joined a dojo earlier in my childhood.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pYW1zcG9ydC5vcmcvc2VhcmNoLz90YWc9RmluZCtvdXQrbW9yZQ__" target="_blank">Houston kickboxing</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbmNvbXBhbnkuY29tL2Jsb2cucGhwP3VzZXI9dHlsZXJib3lsZTM2JmFtcDtibG9nZW50cnlfaWQ9MTg2NDk2NA__" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LnBvc3Rlcm91cy5jb20vdGhpcy1zaXRlLTUyNzg2" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="720b081aafb9e9cfca72a24375aaee04" url=""><![CDATA[Kids Karate classes Houston<br/><br/>Nearly every day more studies and research are pointing to the multiple and various benefits of traditional training programs especially those that are taught through martial arts classes to children across the globe. Yes, contrary to most beliefs, teaching your child any type of skill form like Taekwondo, Judo or Karate is not going to make them aggressive or violent. On the contrary, if taught in the authentic way, these classes can really enhance your children's personality and aid in healthy development of their mind, body and spirit in a completely holistic manner.<br /><br />The Real Essence of Martial Arts <br /><br />While enrolling your kids into martial arts classes can help them to learn effective techniques for defending themselves from getting bullied in class or outside, the key role of this training is much more than just teaching children about self-defense. Traditional schools like the ones that teach Taekwondo, Karate or Tai Chi are based on the tenets of absorbing the spirit of peace, compassion, justice, self-control and discipline amongst the students. Students who are initiated into Taekwondo martial arts classes take a pledge to never misuse their power and to apply compassion and peaceful living in all aspects of their lives. Understanding these facts about the basic value system of martial arts helps us further understanding the holistic influence of these practices in our lives.<br /><br />Exclusive Martial Arts Classes for Children <br /><br />With more and more parents becoming aware of the various benefits of enrolling their children in these classes, there has been a significant upsurge in the types of training programs that are now available for children. From traditional taekwondo, karate and judo lessons to training programs that have been customized for children with special needs, parents can now find the type of martial art form that will be perfectly suited for their children.<br /><br />Certain schools are also offering a contemporary form of teaching plan through which kids learn about various types of martial art techniques that are fused into one basic training program to make the classes all the more interesting and engaging. It is a great idea to begin young children through these integrated classes, before graduating into a particular discipline like Taekwondo or Judo or any other form as they grow older.<br /><br />The Holistic Benefits of Martial Arts Classes <br /><br />Most parents who enroll their children into these classes can notice positive changes in their personalities right away. As children spend more and more time training and learning these techniques they become more and more centered and self-assured. Most of the techniques taught through this arts rely on the repetitive training on particular movement unless and until the student is perfect in a particular move. This form of training helps children to tap into the innate ability to focus and produce results which in turn makes them more and more content and confident. Renowned classes like taekwondo also build effective social skills as the teachings help children in maintaining and nurturing respectful relationships with their peers as well as their fellow students.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aWxhZ28yMS5jb20vZXZlbnQvS2lkcytLYXJhdGUrY2xhc3NlcytIb3VzdG9uLzEzNzA3OTcvcHJvZmlsZQ__" target="_blank">Kids Karate Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGl2ZW5vdGRlYWQuY29tIw__" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NvbW11bml0eS5iYWJ5Y2VudGVyLmNvbS9qb3VybmFsL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LzU4ODQ1Njcva2lkc19tYXJ0aWFsX2FydHNfY2xhc3Nlc19ob3VzdG9u" target="_blank">Click here</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7ed28070e487e332b70ca536ee58cddc" url=""><![CDATA[Click here<br/><br/>If you are currently interested in getting your kids involved in martial arts, you will need to know where to go to get them started. It will be extremely important to make certain that you find the right place, because you will want to help them get as much out of this experience as possible. There are plenty of different places you will be able to go when it comes to martial arts for kids. Whether your kids are just starting out in the world of martial arts or they have some experience already, you will be able to enter them into the right class to help them build skills and abilities they never knew they could have. <br /><br />One of the first things you will want to do when looking for martial arts classes to enrol your kids in is go online, because it is there where you will be able to find all the information you need to get your children started. Keep in mind that it will be extremely important to make sure you choose the right place to take them, because there are definitely going to be some places that are better than others. <br /><br />Typically there are specific places just for martial arts lessons which are aimed at children and young adults. You will need to make sure that you look at as many of your options as possible though, because you will need to make the right decision in order to help them get the most out of the classes they attend. Whether they are interested in jujitsu or karate, you will need to spend a decent amount of time online researching various places in your area that can give your kids what they want. <br /><br />Throughout the process of looking for a place that offers martial arts for kids, you should make sure that you consider how much you should and are willing to spend. Although typically martial arts lessons do not cost a lot of money, there are still going to be some places that are more expensive than others. Sometimes more expensive classes suggest a more experienced teacher and therefore a better learning experience all around. Sometimes however more expensive just means more expensive, so you will want to avoid getting ripped off. <br /><br />Those parents that are currently interested in finding places that provide martial arts lessons for kids will need to go online and also visit a few places in person, just so they can get some idea of what each place is like. Since there are going to be so many options for you to look over, you will need to spend an adequate amount of time looking at what you have to choose from for the sake of your children. If you want your kids to learn martial arts in the best way possible while having lots of fun, you will need to find the right place for them to go so you will know they will get the full experience. <br /><br />Searching for a place that offers martial arts for kids in your area? Follow the links to locate numerous places that can provide martial arts for kids in a disciplined classroom format. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LmppZ3N5LmNvbS9lbnRyaWVzL2dlbmVyYWwvS2lkcy1tYXJ0aWFsLWFydHMtY2xhc3Nlcy1Ib3VzdG9uLTI_" target="_blank">Find out more</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3R5bGVyYm95bGUzNi5wb3N0ZXJvdXMuY29tL2hvdXN0b24tbW1hLTI2MDkw" target="_blank">Kids martial arts classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGl2ZW5vdGRlYWQuY29tL3R5bGVyYm95bGUzNi9LaWRzLW1hcnRpYWwtYXJ0cy1jbGFzc2VzLUhvdXN0b24tcHJvZmlsZS0yNzkxODQyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Houston kickboxing</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a4977ede943d2d687fd9f2aa2adf916" url=""><![CDATA[Kids Karate classes Houston<br/><br/>Bullies at school can affect your childs performance in class, they will always be teased, mocked and say hurtful things about them. Most of the time kids are afraid to inform the teachers of what is going on. Don't let this happen to your kid and arm them with knowledge in martial arts.<br /><br />Do you want to build your child's confidence and protect them from bullies at school. You know you can't always be around to watch them and keep them safe from the bad guys, it is best for them to be able to defend themselves. Why not enroll them in kids martial arts classes wherein they will be taught how to defend themselves in case they are caught in a tough situation.<br /><br />Kids learn fast, their minds are like a sponge that easily absorb knowledge, their bodies are flexible and teaching them while they are still young will benefit them as they grow. Today, there are fun and effective ways to build their confidence and they will be encouraged to participate in energetic and enjoyable specially designed self-defense program for kids.<br /><br />Your kids will learn how to focus and practice self- control because of the instructors who will guide and introduce them to fun karate drills and games that will develop their abilities to concentrate and focus. The highly skilled karate class instructors will be teaching the kids self defense skills and stress out that it must be used only to defend themselves and not to start or pick a fight with other kids. As the lessons go by, more strategies and techniques will be introduced to them which they can carry throughout their lives. Parents can now rest assured that no matter what happens to them, their child is prepared and strong enough to face life's tough challenges.<br /><br />Of all the activities, why martial arts? This kind of activity doesn't require a team so your little one's can practice and learn on his own but must be assisted by a trained instructor. Martial arts for kids is developed to allow them to value the importance of discipline and good manners. By enrolling your little one's in kids martial arts classes, rhode island area has the best self defense schools, parents can expect their kids to learn new ways on how to spend quality time than spending the entire day facing the computer and playing games. While these games can enhance their mental abilities, their bodies will lack movements because they are just sitting down. Unlike in martial arts, the body can move freely and they will perspire which is good for the body. It is undeniable that there is a great number of kids who are obese because they prefer to play computer games. Kids nowadays must engage in martial arts to avoid obesity that can affect their health and lead to unpleasant consequences.<br /><br />The kids martial arts classes is the place where your kids will have the opportunity to mingle with other children who have the same interest. This is a great and exciting activity that will never bore them and will prevent them from doing bad vices like drugs, drinking and smoking for this activity requires strict discipline.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbmNvbXBhbnkuY29tL2Jsb2cucGhwP3VzZXI9dHlsZXJib3lsZTM2JmFtcDtibG9nZW50cnlfaWQ9MTg2NDk5MA__" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aWxhZ28yMS5jb20vZXZlbnQvVGhpcytzaXRlLzEzNzA4MjIvcHJvZmlsZQ__" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LnhhbmdhLmNvbS83Njc4MDcyNTQvY2xpY2staGVyZS8_" target="_blank">Find out more</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="61af3f8131e0fdf81142443b784b7213" url=""><![CDATA[Houston kickboxing<br/><br/>Japanese martial arts Brazilian Jiu Jitsu is very dangerous to play without wearing its protective uniform i.e. Bjj Gi. This uniform is necessary to wear not only by those who are going to do it for the first time but also by those who are experienced fighters. Even in competitions it has become a rule to wear Bjj Gi and also they have some rules and regulations regarding the color, material, size of this uniform. <br /><br />So it is also necessary to purchase gi keeping in mind the terms and conditions of competition authority. The main reason to use this uniform is that some players wear hard dresses while fighting so it becomes difficult for their opponent to attach them and even they get injured by their uniform also. So they allow only such uniform that is not very much difficult to attack for opponents. <br /><br />Those who start their training in BJJ for the very first time, they feel very nervous but if you have your Brazilian Jiu Jitsu Gi then you will not feel nervous because you can protect yourself from your opponent. For beginners some very affordable gi is also available in market, as beginners generally prefer to take a cheap one. While training, you will teach some techniques to attack that are possible only with the help of this gi's. While training you should feel that you are fighting really, because there may be any situation when you may have to face your opponent so several situations are being taught in training period. <br /><br />While purchasing BJJ gi, you should not get confused with typical karate uniform. Brazilian Jiu Jitsu Gi is especially designed keeping in mind the safety of the one who wears it. It is designed very durable, tough and strong. They stitch it double or triple time to ensure its strength and always use thick material to prepare it so it can ensure long life. <br /><br />Other then BJJ gi, several other accessories are also available in market such as Bjj Kimonos, bjj belts and many more. All this are only because of the purpose of providing safety and protection to players and protecting them from opponents in fighting ground and from injuries. Because everyone knows that injuries are an inevitable part of martial art. <br /><br />If you want to start training or about to taking part in competition then to ensure your victory here is the name of the shop that will help you in your victory. K2fightgear.com is the name of an online shop where you will be able to select best quality of competition approved Brazilian Jiu Jitsu Gi, Bjj Kimonos and very thing for all your purpose. Here you can purchase it for women or kids also. <br /><br />Html about author:- Even after getting proper training in Brazilian Jiu Jitsu, you will have to purchase Jiu Jitsu Gi, Bjj Kimonos, bjj belts, Bjj Kimonos, it stands for Brazilian Jiu Jitsu Gi to participate in competition and win it. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5taWdlbnRlLmNvbS95b3VyX3BhZ2UvYmxvZy92aWV3X3Bvc3RpbmcuaHRtbD9waWQ9MzQwMzgxOCZhbXA7cHJvZmlsZV9pZD03NjI3MjcwJmFtcDtwcm9maWxlX25hbWU9dHlsZXJib3lsZTM2JmFtcDt1c2VyX2lkPTc2MjcyNzAmYW1wO3VzZXJuYW1lPXR5bGVyYm95bGUzNg__" target="_blank">Houston kickboxing</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbmNvbXBhbnkuY29tL2Jsb2cucGhwP3VzZXI9dHlsZXJib3lsZTM2JmFtcDtibG9nZW50cnlfaWQ9MTg2NDk5MA__" target="_blank">Houston kickboxing</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGl2ZW5vdGRlYWQuY29tIw__" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a2588eb2de38f12a05cd589b6407066" url=""><![CDATA[Find out more<br/><br/>Being in sports is a good defence against bullies for three reasons: athletes exude confidence, they are stronger than their average peer and sports provide a positive network of support.<br /><br />Yet all of that can be the reverse. Some athletes have poor self -image and feel that their only worth is based on the sport performance, this is usually an adult problem. By that I mean that the adults around the athlete CREATE the problem. The environment around some athletes may not be as positive as we would like, in fact it could be nurturing negative behaviour, and again being stronger or more physically imposing could be a negative. It can attract aggressive behaviour from bullies or it can lead the child athlete to exhibit bully behaviour without feeling that they are doing anything wrong. But let's focus on the positive role of sports. Let's assume that you are the parent of a positive child/athlete and you are supportive and understanding: Because if I can then we will see our child/athletes being positive and non-violent too. Kids understand that sports are games and games sometimes have losers. They do not define themselves as a loss or a win. They are self-confident and aware of their actions and inactions. They know that they are role models and they take that position seriously. These athletes are not targeted by bullies because the bully has no effect on them. They cannot get them to give in to their behaviour. Kids who bully may stop once they realize that other popular kids don't respect what they're doing.- Being in sports, aside from building confidence, also builds physical strength and skills. This is another layer of confidence that an athlete has over a bully. They know that they can protect themselves or others and thus remain un-threatened.ed.<br /><br />Lastly being in sports creates a network of support, a web of positive relationships that keep bullies outside of the circle of acceptance. There are also strong adults available who will not tolerate negative behaviour and so kids can feel safer. Many programs or leagues have strict rules in place and violators are removed from play. But the strength of the rules are only as strong as the enforcement. A few weeks ago when a NFL coach was given a year off for putting bounties on the heads of opposing players, the message that the offense wasn't too bad was sent to other coaches and players as the punishment for this offense was minimal. The coaches, parents and fans have to be willing to sacrifice victory for honour and integrity. Sadly, sometimes that's not the case.<br /><br />As role models athletes need to know a few things about how to stop bullies and how to protect others. Dr. Sue Limber, PhD, MLS, professor of psychology and associate director of the Institute on Family and Neighbourhood Life at Clemson University advises that kids should watch for these signs to see if a friend is being bullied:<br /><br />1. Do your friends suddenly seem worried about going to school or doing things with other kids in the peer group? 2. Do your friends seem more sad, moody, or depressed than usual? 3. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGl2ZW5vdGRlYWQuY29tL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3L0hvdXN0b24tTU1BLXByb2ZpbGUtMjc5MjA1OC5odG1s" target="_blank">Kids martial arts classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NvbW11bml0eS5iYWJ5Y2VudGVyLmNvbS9qb3VybmFsL3R5bGVyYm95bGUzNi81ODg1MDE3L2hvdXN0b25fbW1h" target="_blank">Houston MMA</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbmNvbXBhbnkuY29tL2Jsb2cucGhwP3VzZXI9dHlsZXJib3lsZTM2JmFtcDtibG9nZW50cnlfaWQ9MTg2NDE0NA__" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="90f5bec3feef4b1b8c4224b8a6f9bc81" url=""><![CDATA[Houston kickboxing<br/><br/>Every child, at one point in life, will beg his or her parents to be enrolled in karate classes. Few parents will act on this. Instead, many will sign their children up for baseball, soccer and other familiar team sports. However, those parents who enroll their children in karate lessons will be providing their kids with exceptional life skills designed to shape their character while keeping them fit.<br /><br />If you want your children to learn skills that will keep them physically, mentally and emotionally fit then karate classes are a great alternative to team sports. While team sports offer similar benefits, learning these skills can be limited to those kids on the playing field. Karate and martial arts ensure that every child participates, leaving no one &quot;riding the bench&quot; and feeling left out.<br /><br />Karate lessons improve children's ability to defend themselves in emergency situations. It teaches them combative moves that include punches, kicks, knee and elbow strikes, as well as open hand techniques. It may also include grappling and similar moves. These techniques are taught to show children the proper way to defend themselves and to help them become more &quot;stranger aware&quot;.<br /><br />karate classes also help children learn personal discipline and confidence. The sessions demand that each child respect and trust their instructor as well as each other. Most instructors will agree that karate is more of a character building activity rather than one that teaches children how to fight. Master Gichin Funakoshi said, &quot;The ultimate aim of Karate lies not in victory or defeat, but in the perfection of character of its participants&quot;. The best of instructors will stress that kids learn accomplishment, modesty, strength of mind and drive from their karate lessons.<br /><br />Children as young as five or six may be enrolled in karate classes where they will learn the basics of the sport. They will enjoy the challenge of learning and practicing new techniques while facing challenges that will teach them how to humbly accept achievement or defeat. Karate lessons will start them on an early path to attaining positive character traits. The unique formalities of karate are what truly teach children reverence and the rewards of good behavior. Karate classes are great for &quot;troublemakers&quot; because in order to excel, the child must understand and practice respect. They will not experience the joy of advancement and approval without the appropriate class behavior.<br /><br />The mental, physical and emotional benefits that martial arts and karate lessons can teach your children are immense. From learning techniques that keep their bodies moving, to learning how to carry themselves with poise, children of all ages will enjoy the fun of participating in karate classes.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS90eWxlcmJveWxlMzYvcG9zdHMvMjMyMzIxMi9UaGlzK3NpdGU_" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5taWdlbnRlLmNvbS95b3VyX3BhZ2UvYmxvZy92aWV3X3Bvc3RpbmcuaHRtbD9waWQ9MzQwMzc5NSZhbXA7cHJvZmlsZV9pZD03NjI3NTUzJmFtcDtwcm9maWxlX25hbWU9ZXN0ZWJhbnJhc2NoMzcmYW1wO3VzZXJfaWQ9NzYyNzU1MyZhbXA7dXNlcm5hbWU9ZXN0ZWJhbnJhc2NoMzc_" target="_blank">Kids Karate Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGl2ZW5vdGRlYWQuY29tL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3L0hvdXN0b24tTU1BLXByb2ZpbGUtMjc5MjA1OC5odG1s" target="_blank">Houston martial arts</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e5ecdd079194b6afbc74cd79ee237817" url=""><![CDATA[Houston kickboxing<br/><br/>Whoopie advised Sherri not to hover over her son to the point that he can not breathe. (Her son was born pre-maturely and is very little.) Whoopie told her that her son is incredibly cute, but if she wants him to have the life that she wants for him, he's going to have to learn what he can and can not do. She has to let him learn what he needs to learn, because he may be on a class trip and she may not be there.<br /><br />Sherri said that you have to be there sometimes to be the person to stop them from getting hurt. She told of a time when her son was trying to get back on the monkey bar, and evidently she was standing there. Someone came up and told her that she had to move. She said that she emphatically told the person, &quot;NO YOU MOVE. MY SON IS TRYING TO GET ON THE MONKEY BAR.&quot; Was Sherri being a bully, or was she just being a Mommy?<br /><br />Whoopie asked Jackie Chan if he hovered over his children. He said &quot;NO&quot;. He liked to see his son fall down and get hurt. He would not let their mother pamper them when they got hurt. He said that when a mother is not around when the child gets hurt, the child screams bloody murder.<br /><br />Jaden was asked if he wanted his mom around while he was doing the movie. His answer was&quot;Yes&quot;. He said he did get hurt on the set and no one cared. His mom was the only one that would give him sympathy. He said that she helps. He even gives up some of his recreation time to be with his mom. He likes being with his mom.<br /><br />Joy asked Jackie if he was a bully as a child. He said &quot;Yes&quot;. He said after he learned martial arts, he learned that it was not used to bully, but to help. Joy told Jackie that one of the things that bullies want is to be loved. She asked Jackie was that his problem and he said &quot;No &quot;.<br /><br />Jaden said that it was hard for his mom to watch him train for the movie, but his father pushed him to the limit. In the Movie, there was a bully who continuously beat up the karate kid (Jaden). The karate kid had to train and learn how to fight to protect himself.<br /><br />Every kid who is being bullied has to figure out how to protect himself/herself. Once you know how to protect yourself from bullies, your self-esteem will dramatically increase. That is what happened at the end of The Karate Kid. To find out more about self-esteem, look for my book, &quot;Formula For Success - Success Can Be Your Too&quot;, at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.margiewrobinson.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.margiewrobinson.com</a>.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5taWdlbnRlLmNvbS95b3VyX3BhZ2UvYmxvZy92aWV3X3Bvc3RpbmcuaHRtbD9waWQ9MzQwMzQ3MyZhbXA7cHJvZmlsZV9pZD03NjI3MjcwJmFtcDtwcm9maWxlX25hbWU9dHlsZXJib3lsZTM2JmFtcDt1c2VyX2lkPTc2MjcyNzAmYW1wO3VzZXJuYW1lPXR5bGVyYm95bGUzNg__" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS90eWxlcmJveWxlMzYvcG9zdHMvMjMyMzMyNS9LaWRzK0thcmF0ZStIb3VzdG9u" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NvbW11bml0eS5iYWJ5Y2VudGVyLmNvbS9qb3VybmFsL2VzdGViYW5yYXNjaDM3LzU4ODU0MzEva2lkc19rYXJhdGVfY2xhc3Nlc19ob3VzdG9u" target="_blank">Kids Karate classes Houston</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>