<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="21">
		<document id="5a442ee258ad09a5c0d8a24387224214" url=""><![CDATA[Used to subvert the authority of the emperor manager James:<br/><br/>Sports Network reports the Atlanta reporter bolone Jun recognition, and the third game of the Hawks, the last one, he arranged to rest under the presence of James, was 
<br /><br />the emperor's refusal. And the eagle of  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a>  the fourth, the same story happened, James again refused to rest, play the entire fourth quarter. 
<br /><br />Knights of the ritual is the beginning of James in the presence of the fourth quarter to rest, her energies to prepare the last minute of the decisive battle, but James is 
<br /><br />obviously to break such a &quot;custom&quot;: &quot;At that time, we only a few leading the competition is to the critical moment, I do not want to sit at such a time field. I have no problem 
<br /><br />with the physical, each playing more than 40 minutes for me is no big deal, I do not need rest. &quot; 
<br /><br />Under the leadership of James, Cavaliers to maintain and expand the lead to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9SYXltb25kLVdlaWwtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Raymond Weil Watches</a>  84 over the final 74 to overcome an eagle, and by 4 to 0 game sweep of the total rivals promotion. 
<br /><br />Before the Pistons swept the first round, while the Hawks and Heat seven struggle, Knight has been nine days of rest time now and again they swept, while the Magic and Celtics 
<br /><br />of the total score is 2 2, Knight will have a long rest time. Many people are discussing the advantages too much time to rest too long, in the end of the knight is a good thing 
<br /><br />or a bad thing. But James himself, the rest length of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9UYWctSGV1ZXItV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Tag Heuer Watches</a>  time, actually does not matter, &quot;We is not go home and sleep, even if no match, we will still be the same training, and 
<br /><br />maintain their own game. If you have to say that a good thing or a bad thing, Of course, I would say it is a good thing, we do not have to travel, do not go away, on the 
<br /><br />strength of the restoration of good. &quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f48495ce9e4b1acd916a7d3b51656882" url=""><![CDATA[Katy Perry saved by sister<br/><br/>The 'Hot N Cold' singer is always accompanied by <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9EaW9yLVdhdGNoZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Dior Watches</a> <em>Dior Watches</em>elder sibling Angela, 26, and says her sister's harsh stance has stopped her spiralling out of control.
<br />    She said: &quot;Angela is the one who kicks my a*s. The way she wakes me up is pretty horrible. She'll stand over my face with a glass of cold water and count to three. If I'm not up by three, she'll pour.
<br /><br />&quot;You need <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a>  'no' people around you, otherwise you'll end up in rehab. My sister doesn't care how many records I've sold or what I've done or what I have.&quot;
<br /><br />Katy also claims her sister is responsible for her success as Angela got her interested in singing at a young age.
<br /><br />She added: &quot;I fell into singing at the age of nine because I was copying everything my sister did. She started having <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  singing lessons and I was like, 'I want them too'. &quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d13e6c175ec4ff038578cb775b519aae" url=""><![CDATA[Peak experience<br/><br/>Terrified shrieks echoed through the cave's eerie darkness, mingling with the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a> screeches of the bats above us. People squirmed in panic but we were literally between two rocks and a hard place. Passing through A Thread of Sky in Fujian province's Wuyi Mountains means squeezing through a 163-m-long rift that is sometimes less than half a meter wide.
<br /><br />The tightest spots are pitch black at ground level but light shines several meters down through the crevice's opening high above, just enough to trace the silhouettes of bats flitting around. Someone said something about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a>  flying rats. My wife said something about vampires. Squashed between those gooey walls, excrement also came to mind.
<br /><br />Finally, we popped out of a slender crack into searing sunlight, which illuminated the limestone spires, looping rivers and fragrant tea gardens that make Wuyi Mountains a splendid travel destination.
<br /><br />Our subterranean experience seemed antithetical to the hours we had spent clamoring toward towering mountaintops. Wuyi's peaks average about 400 m, with its highest - the Three-Layer Peak - soaring 717 m skyward. They are part of a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  Cathayshan fold system, meaning that millions of years ago, the earth belched out tons of magma, which the sands of time ground into cones and pillars.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c6f0deefc0795f44b79d43ce037bc19" url=""><![CDATA[Mischa Barton's art attack<br/><br/>Mischa Barton loves throwing paint parties.
<br /><br />The former 'O.C.' actress enjoys inviting friends over <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  her New York home to create unusual art pieces by throwing 
<br /><br />colours around.
<br /><br />She said: &quot;We mess around and throw paint on canvases. It doesn't have to be serious. Art is about enjoying yourself, a moment in time. That is the most exciting stuff.&quot;
<br />     Mischa is predominantly based in Paris, France, and says the people she has met there have encouraged her to pursue her artistic ambitions.
<br /><br />She said: &quot;Paris is such an inspiring city. A group of friends there have <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a> brought out my creative side like 10 times 
<br /><br />more in terms of doing art, paintings, sculpture.&quot;
<br /><br />Mischa's next small screen project sees her play a model in 'A Beautiful Life', in a TV show produced by Ashton Kutcher.
<br /><br />The series is based on Ashton's early experiences as a male model and is set to air in the <strong>wholesale watch </strong><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9BLUxhbmdlLSZhbXA7LVNvaG5lLVdhdGNoZXMvR3JhbmQtTGFuZ2UtMS1XYXRjaGVzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Grand Lange 1 Watches</a>  US later this year.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4c5f0deb7fcc2ed31a8919258291c905" url=""><![CDATA[What is 30th Sep. days?<br/><br/>Translators are! Do not forget their own festival! 
<br /><br />&quot;9.30 International Translation Day&quot; just around the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9JV0MtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">IWC Watches</a>  corner, a series of activities on campus, &quot;the 
<br /><br />translation to make the world without barriers&quot; is the first time in more than 200 institutions of higher education in the country carried out in full swing. For too long, 
<br /><br />professional foreign language students for their future career orientation Thinking of a problem the most is: &quot;In addition to foreign clerks to do the ordinary, I can do?&quot; 
<br /><br />A number of activities, entitled &quot;Foreign Language professionals face new challenges and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a>  opportunities for change,&quot; 
<br /><br />the most popular eye-catching of the speech, a speech so that the first time college students understand that the real situation of the translation industry, translation 
<br /><br />industry professionals for the practical requirements of a foreign language, as well as foreign students how to become such as translators for the development of the core 
<br /><br />issues. Translation is a &quot;hybrid home&quot;, not only need to have the relevant vocabulary and grammar, but also the corresponding professional services and more familiar with the 
<br /><br />background knowledge; translation is highly practical skills, to go through a lot of practical applications can be handy. Therefore, translators should be the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9HdWNjaS1XYXRjaGVzLzExMC1HLUxpbmstV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">110 G-Link Watches</a>  most lovely, most respected group of people!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="34b96459b503b06151c31fbba8ce9070" url=""><![CDATA[replica watches<br/><br/>By May 23 U.S. 50 billion U.S. dollars Mr Adolf fraud fresh century, the United Kingdom has created a similar case. According to Hong Kong, &amp;amp;quot;Wen Wei Po&amp;amp;quot; quoted foreign reports, the day before the British police have arrested two men, together with <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a> another suspect at large, including one involving charges of 250 million pounds of &amp;amp;quot;Ponzi scheme.&amp;amp;quot; Three accused is alleged to have used as investment adviser to the illegal fund-raising, fictitious transactions high returns, the investors of their money by deception. It has been reported that <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9BLUxhbmdlLSZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDstU29obmUtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">A Lange &amp;amp;amp; Sohne Watches</a>  the victim throughout the world, at least 600 people have been deceived. 
<br /><br />Reported that in London the day before the police raided the two places in London and Surrey, the three locations, and with conspiracy to defraud and money laundering charges, were taken away by 40-year-old man and 43-year-old man Peacock Anderson, the police are Finally looking for a suspect. 
<br /><br />Police said three were the establishment of &amp;amp;quot;international business consultants,&amp;amp;quot; &amp;amp;quot;John Anderson, consultant&amp;amp;quot; and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9JV0MtV2F0Y2hlcy9TcGl0ZmlyZS1QaWxvdC1XYXRjaGVzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Spitfire Pilot Watches</a>  consultant Kenneth Peacock,&amp;amp;quot; three companies, claiming profits through short-term borrowing and a high of 6.5% per year lured investors return. The so-called short-term lending does not exist, the actual new customers with funds to pay for the return of the old investors, the so-called &amp;amp;quot;Ponzi scheme.&amp;amp;quot; 
<br /><br />United Kingdom Financial Services Authority (FSA) last year in November to freeze the assets of the company three and operation of three companies that had no operating license of a collective investment scheme, which means that investors have been deceived is <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9DYXJ0aWVyLVdhdGNoZXMvTGEtRG9uYS1XYXRjaGVzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">La Dona  Watches</a> not entitled to compensation from the Government.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2108eb521703b383b9a8c3246b63df23" url=""><![CDATA[Dylan "poem" on sale was actually Hank Snow song<br/><br/>NEW YORK – A &quot;poem&quot; purportedly written by a teenage Bob Dylan and up for auction at<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9BdWRlbWFycy1QaWd1ZXQtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Piguet Watches</a> Christie's is actually a song written by the late Canadian country singer Hank Snow, the auction house said on Wednesday.
<br />    Christie's announced on Tuesday the sale of the hand-written poem believed to have been written in 1957 when Dylan was 16 and away at Jewish camp.
<br />But Christie's failed to detect that the words, with a few minor variations, matched those of a song previously recorded by Snow, who died in 1999 at age 85.
<br />    Reuters discovered the lyrics matched the Snow song when alerted by a reader. Reuters then informed the auction house.
<br /><br />&quot;Additional information has come to our attention about the handwritten poem submitted by Bob Dylan to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  his camp newspaper, written when he was 16, entitled 'Little Buddy.' The words are in fact a revised version of lyrics of a Hank Snow song,&quot; Christie's said in a statement.
<br /><br />&quot;This still remains among the earliest known handwritten lyrics of Bob Dylan and Christie's is pleased to offer them in our Pop Culture auction on June 23.&quot;
<br /><br />The manuscript had been expected to fetch $10,000 to $15,000.
<br /><br />Christie's said Dylan, still using his <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9CcmVndWUtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Bregue Watches</a> given name Robert Zimmerman, signed the piece Bobby Zimmerman and submitted it to the Herzl Camp newspaper. The editor of the paper kept it for more than 50 years and recently donated it to Herzl Camp, a Jewish camp in Wisconsin, Christie's said
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c9f0f68df03e56c45b969e6de42ecd6e" url=""><![CDATA[Latest update: mainland flu tally hits 61<br/><br/>BEIJING -- Three more A(H1N1) flu cases were confirmed on the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a>  Chinese mainland Thursday, bringing the total number to 61.
<br />      A 35-year-old woman was tested A(H1N1) positive Thursday morning in Wuhan, capital of central China's Hubei Province, according to the provincial health administration.
<br />      The woman, the second confirmed A(H1N1) case in the province, arrived in Wuhan on May 30 on a flight from Dallas, the United States. The administration did not provide her flight details.
<br /><br />All five people who had close contact with her had been quarantined, said an administration official.
<br /><br />The second confirmed patient was a 24-year-old Chinese national who arrived in Beijing on May 31 from <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9QYXRlay1QaGlsaXBwZS1XYXRjaGVzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Patek Philippe Watches</a>  New York aboard Air China flight CA982, the Beijing Health Bureau said.
<br /><br />He was tested positive for the A(H1N1) late Wednesday night at the Beijing Center of Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).
<br /><br />Health authorities have confirmed 82 people had close contact with the man, 78 of whom were under medical observation.
<br /><br />Also on Thursday, north China's Shanxi Province reported its <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9WYWNoZXJvbi1Db25zdGFudGluLVdhdGNoZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Vacheron Constantin Watches</a> first 
<br /><br />confirmed A(H1N1) flu case, a 20-year-old man who returned from studies in Canada.
<br /><br />China has reported no deaths from A(H1N1) flu.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b9b564edcd2288ace36986a10516edbd" url=""><![CDATA[Najib following in dad's footsteps<br/><br/>Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Tun Razak will pay an official visit to China from <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a>  June 2 to 5 at the invitation of Chinese Premier Wen Jiabao, his first official trip to China as prime minister.
<br /><br />It would be understandable if he is overwhelmed with emotion. After all, he will be in the historic footsteps of his father and second prime minister Tun Abdul Razak Hussein who had the foresight to initiate links with this economic powerhouse,Malaysia Star reported.
<br />       In 1974, Tun Razak became the first Asean head to visit Beijing and establish diplomatic relations. Thirty five years later, his son returns as Malaysia’s sixth prime minister to renew and strengthen ties.
<br /><br />The parallels are <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9QYXRlay1QaGlsaXBwZS1XYXRjaGVzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Patek Philippe Watches</a>  significant. Five years ago, speaking on the importance of his father’s achievement, Najib said: “The significant improvement in Malaysia-China relations symbolise the prudence of putting aside differences and concentrating on the commonalities in the pursuit of peace and prosperity.”
<br /><br />Today, China has become an economic superpower and an important trading partner of Malaysia. Bilateral trade between the two nations totalled US$39.6billion last year. China is currently Malaysia’s fourth largest trading partner.
<br /><br />In the joint communique signed by Tun Razak and Chinese premier Zhou Enlai, on May 31, 1974, trade was not even mentioned. When Najib meets Chinese President Hu Jintao, however, that will be the foremost thing on the agenda besides strengthening cultural and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  people to people ties.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="70962d2fb01c2cabbe4f5dd45a58f15c" url=""><![CDATA[Yao happy to slam-dunk one for kids in need<br/><br/>Chinese NBA star Yao Ming knows how to thrill fans on the court. So this summer he is trying something different - enchanting children without even holding a basketball, just by using his voice.
<br />    Forced to withdraw from the NBA playoffs due to a  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  foot injury, China's basketball icon was invited by the Shanghai Special-care Foundation to voice the animated Chinese film The Magic Aster, which premieres on June 19.
<br /><br />In the movie, he gives his voice to the father of main actress Xiao Lan.
<br /><br />It was the first time Yao dubbed a Chinese film and his significantly shorter teammates this time include Taiwan supermodel-actress Lin Chi-ling and Hong Kong actor-singer Leon Lai.
<br /><br />&quot;A lot of animation produced in China is very good and I hope children can enjoy this one<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9UYWctSGV1ZXItV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Tag Heuer Watches</a>  and pass on traditional Chinese culture as well,&quot; Yao said yesterday in Beijing, where he is enjoying his layoff from the Houston Rockets' season after finishing his four-hour dubbing work for the movie.
<br /><br />The film tells a traditional Chinese fairy tale about justice fighting evil to recapture the magic aster, which protects people's happiness.
<br /><br />It is jointly produced by the Shanghai Film (Group) Corporation, Shanghai Animation Film Studio, Xiamen Shangcheng Science and Technology Co.Ltd for China's 60th birthday.
<br /><br />For sportsman Yao, joining such a production was a bigger challenge than playing in a tough NBA match.
<br /><br />&quot;It was very difficult at the very beginning, although I only had to sit there and talk,&quot; Yao recalled.
<br /><br />&quot;It's a totally different working style from basketball. I couldn't add much of my <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9BLUxhbmdlLSZhbXA7LVNvaG5lLVdhdGNoZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">A Lange &amp; Sohne Watches</a> 
<br />Actually, it is not his first involvement in movie production.
<br /><br />In 2004 he was the main character of the documentary The Year of the Yao. He also did voice-over work for the US animated television series The Simpsons with NBA player LeBron James and figure skating star Michelle Kwan.
<br /><br />This time, lending his voice to an animated Chinese movie is also a part of his charity work, since he will donate his earnings to the Shanghai Special-care Foundation, which he started with other people who worked for the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a> 2007 Shanghai Special Olympic Games.
<br /><br />Established in July 2008, the foundation helps mentally handicapped people and the poor. Part of the box office income from the movie will go to the foundation.
<br />     As one of the top sports stars in China, the 28-year-old Yao has always been involved in charity.
<br /><br />He created the Yao Ming Foundation to build schools in China after the May 2008 earthquake and supports charities like Chi Heng Foundation, China Youth Development Foundation and Project Hope.
<br /><br />In April, a special school was set up in Jiuquan city of northwestern China's Gansu province for children with learning disabilities.
<br /><br />&quot;There is no boundary for love and there is a large group of people in the world who need our care,&quot; said the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9SYXltb25kLVdlaWwtV2F0Y2hlcy9GcmVlbGFuY2VyLVdhdGNoZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Freelancer Watches</a> Shanghai native. &quot;I hope more people go to the cinema to enjoy the movie and support the charity.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="63bb6ac94ebc1e452e62810f8b961816" url=""><![CDATA[Philippine lawmaker wants the dead to stop voting<br/><br/>MANILA, Philippines -- A Philippine lawmaker frustrated by <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a> rampant electoral fraud has proposed legislation to get 
<br /><br />the names of the dead off voter rolls.
<br />Rep. Maria Victoria Sy-Alvarado said Monday she wants to make it mandatory for doctors and family members to report deaths to the civil registrar, which has to give the 
<br /><br />information to the Election Commission so it can update its voter lists.
<br /><br />The bill must go through a long legislative process before <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9KYWVnZXItTGVDb3VsdHJlLVdhdGNoZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Jaeger LeCoultre Watches</a>  becoming law. If 
<br /><br />enacted, government officials or employees would face up to 10 years imprisonment and be disqualified from public office.
<br /><br />In past elections, family members have reported finding the names of dead relatives on the lists. In some cases, someone has voted using their <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a> names.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7cdd1416ab24bd7165c700694a10746b" url=""><![CDATA[Israeli naval ship clashes with Gaza aid boat<br/><br/>JERUSALEM -- An Israeli naval ship clashed on Tuesday with a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a> small boat carrying international activists with aid 
<br /><br />destined for Gaza, an Israeli Foreign Ministry spokesman said
<br /><br />There were no reported casualties from the incident involving the small cabin cruiser &quot;Dignity&quot; that sailed from Cyprus late on Monday.
<br /><br />Israel has declared the coastal territory a closed military zone and said the Free Gaza Movement boat would not be permitted to dock.
<br /><br />Yigal Palmor, a spokesman for Israel's Foreign Ministry, said the boat failed to respond to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9BdWRlbWFycy1QaWd1ZXQtV2F0Y2guaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Audemars Piguet Watch</a>  Israeli naval radio contact, and that an Israeli vessel &quot;clashed with the ship.&quot;
<br /><br />Free Gaza Movement told Reuters their boat, carrying 3 1/2 tonnes of medical aid with 16 people aboard, was rammed and shot at while in international waters about 70-80 miles 
<br /><br />off Gaza by Israeli naval vessel.
<br /><br />Palmor denied there had been any shooting although the two ships made &quot;physical contact&quot;. He said no one had been hurt and that the Israeli ship escorted the aid boat back to 
<br /><br />Cypriot territorial waters.
<br /><br />Israel has declared areas around the Gaza Strip a &quot;closed military zone&quot; after it launched an <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  aerial offensive in the 
<br /><br />coastal territory on Hamas targets on Saturday, in which 345 Palestinians have been killed.
<br /><br />Free Gaza Movement said their boat was safe, but had sustained damage
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f4507ec8cee2dce587077ab8994f27c0" url=""><![CDATA[Meteorite hits boy, leaves a scar<br/><br/>A 14-year old German boy was hit in the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a> hand by a pea-sized meteorite that scared the bejeezus out of him and left a 
<br /><br />scar.
<br /><br />&quot;When it hit me it knocked me flying and then was still going fast enough to bury itself into the road,&quot; Gerrit Blank said in a newspaper account. Astronomers have analyzed the 
<br /><br />object and conclude it was indeed a natural object from space, The Telegraph reports.
<br />Most meteors vaporize in the atmosphere, creating &quot;shooting stars,&quot; and never reach the ground. The few that do are typically made mostly of metals. Stony space rocks, even if 
<br /><br />they are big as a car, will usually break apart or explode as they crash through the atmosphere.
<br /><br />There are a handful of reports of homes and cars being struck by meteorites, and many cases of space rocks streaking to the surface and being found later.
<br /><br />But human strikes are rare. There are no known instances of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9BLUxhbmdlLSZhbXA7LVNvaG5lLVdhdGNoZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">A Lange &amp; Sohne Watches</a>  humans being killed 
<br /><br />by space rocks.
<br /><br />According to a SPACE.com article on the topic a few years, back:
<br /><br />On November 30, 1954, Alabama housewife Ann Hodges was taking a nap on her couch when she was awakened by a 3-pound (1.4-kilogram) meteor that crashed through the roof of her 
<br /><br />house, bounced off a piece of furniture and struck her in the hip, causing a large bruise.
<br /><br />On October 9, 1992, a large fireball was seen streaking over the eastern United States, finally exploding into many pieces. In Peekskill, New York, one of the pieces struck a 
<br /><br />Chevrolet automobile owned by Michelle Knapp. Knapp was not in the car at the time.
<br /><br />On June 21, 1994, Jose Martin of Spain was driving with his <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a> wife near Madrid when a 3-pound (1.4-kilogram) meteor 
<br /><br />crashed through his windshield, bent the steering wheel and ended up in the back seat.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fd2903989d45ea1cacea8fff7f255c1e" url=""><![CDATA[Pentagon: DPRK missiles able to hit US soon<br/><br/>WASHINGTON - The Pentagon's second-highest ranking official claimed on Tuesday that the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a>  Democratic People's Republic 
<br /><br />of Korea (DPRK)'s missiles could reach the continental United States in the near future.
<br />Deputy Defense Secretary William Lynn told a briefing before the Senate Armed Services Committee that the DPRK's missiles could hit US homeland in three years at the quickest if 
<br /><br />the country continues to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9UYWctSGV1ZXItV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Tag Heuer Watches</a>  accelerate its weapon development.
<br /><br />Lynn added that he agreed with the assessment by Republican Senator John McCain that America should be prepared for a &quot;worst-case scenario&quot; with the DPRK.
<br /><br />Other Pentagon officials attending the briefing also said that the DPRK is working with other nations, including Iran and potentially Syria, to develop ballistic missiles.
<br /><br />However, US Defense Secretary Robert Gates told lawmakers last week that <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a>  missile interceptors are fully &quot;adequate&quot; 
<br /><br />to deter DPRK missiles for &quot;a number of years.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="927f1177d972b582885f25c1648abcf4" url=""><![CDATA[Becks notches up another start<br/><br/>EMBLEY, England: David Beckham was closer to achieving his dream of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a>  playing in another World Cup by starting and 
<br /><br />finishing his first competitive match for England since 2007 in Wednesday's 6-0 rout of Andorra in a qualifier.
<br /><br />A 112th England appearance at the age of 34 will raise Beckham's hopes of making the finals in South Africa next year, assuming his team qualifies, and of potentially breaking 
<br /><br />the national all-time record of 125 caps held by retired goalkeeper Peter Shilton.
<br /><br />Beckham has 17 goals in his 13-year England career, but he is <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9BdWRlbWFycy1QaWd1ZXQtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Piguet Watches</a>  yet to score at England's 
<br /><br />national stadium - the old or the rebuilt Wembley. The crowd shouted &quot;shoot, shoot&quot; in the dying moments on Wednesday, hoping to be there for his first Wembley goal.
<br /><br />&quot;It's obviously missing, but I don't care,&quot; Beckham said. &quot;At the end of the day, I'm happy with being in this team. I'm happy with performing in this team and playing with 
<br /><br />these players because it's a great team and a great squad to be around at the moment. Whether I score or not at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a>  
<br /><br />Wembley, we'll see. As long as we carry on winning, I don't care.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="379c008dfc8c384f0aa5af9bbf5f9c97" url=""><![CDATA[Apples and Alzheimer’s<br/><br/>A recent study from the Center for Cellular Neurobiology and Neurodegeneration Research at the University of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a>  
<br /><br />Massachusetts found that drinking apple juice could reduce your risk of Alzheimer’s disease.
<br /><br />Researchers gave mice the human equivalent of two cups of apple juice a day for one month. They found that the mice who drank apple juice produced less beta-amyloid, a small 
<br /><br />protein that harms normal brain cells and form <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9HdWNjaS1XYXRjaGVzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Gucci Watches</a>  the plaques found in the brains of people with 
<br /><br />Alzheimer’s disease.
<br /><br />Lead study author Thomas B. Shea, PhD. said his findings “suggest that regular consumption of apple juice can not only help to keep one’s mind functioning at its best, but may 
<br /><br />also be able to delay key aspects of Alzheimer’s disease and augment therapeutic approaches.”
<br /><br />The researchers did not identify the specific component in <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  apple juice responsible for the healing effect.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="96aad9bd0a4ef9a6dc24bbd129288c63" url=""><![CDATA[Tallest tower to open on Saturday<br/><br/>The uncompleted Shanghai World Financial Center (C) is seen with <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a> other landmarks at Shanghai's Lujiazui area in a file photo. Shanghai World Financial Center, the world's third-tallest skyscraper, is due to open on August 30, 2008. [File Photo: China.cn]
<br /><br />Shanghai World Financial Center, the world's third-tallest skyscraper due to open on Saturday, will have the world's fastest elevators, said its builder.
<br /><br />Elevators will travel at 10 meters per second in the 492-meter landmark tower at Lujiazui, said Shanghai Construction Group. Visitors will be lifted to the tower's observatory on the 94th floor in several minutes.
<br /><br />Three observatory levels will be open, from the 94th floor at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9WYWNoZXJvbi1Db25zdGFudGluLVdhdGNoZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Vacheron Constantin Watches</a>  423 meters above the ground to the 97th and 100th floors.
<br /><br />The highest observatory, named Sky Pavilion, is 472 meters above sea level and provides a bird's-eye view of the city's complete skyline.
<br /><br />On the 85th floor will be the world's highest swimming pool, part of the hotel that will occupy floors 78 to 93.
<br /><br />And the world's highest Chinese restaurant will open on the 93rd story of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a> building.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="334225c9294c9ebd83f22efe2a938d61" url=""><![CDATA[Diners' best picks<br/><br/>Shanghai
<br /><br />Yi Caf at Pudong Shangri-la: The walk-through design gives it a public market feel, with <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a>  cuisines from China, Japan, India, Southeast Asia, Middle East as well as Europe and North America. (Second Floor of Shangri-la Hotel, No 33, Fucheng Lu, Pudong New District; 021-58775372, 28286888)
<br /><br />Karaku: This is a famous Japanese restaurant whose specialty is <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9JV0MtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">IWC Watches</a>  Tempura. (Building 1, New World Nan Li, No. 338, Zizhong Lu, Luwan district; 021-63855777)
<br /><br />Guangzhou
<br /><br />Lei Garden: You can find typical Cantonese snacks and dishes. (4 Floor, Yi'an Plaza, No 33, Jiansheliu Lu, Yuexiu district; 020-83633268)
<br /><br />Carousel: Located on the top floor of the Garden Hotel, the ambience and views are great for large gatherings as well as intimate dates. Featuring food from China and abroad. (30 Floor, Garden Hotel, No 368, Huanzhi <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watch</a>  Donglu, Yuexiu district; 020-83338989-3986)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="54653716d5ce6ac705a8a8e44336b4be" url=""><![CDATA[Storm-hit Taiwan oyster farms to get relief<br/><br/>TAIPEI: Oyster farmers who sustained heavy losses during Typhoon Linfa are eligible for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a>  natural 
<br /><br />disaster relief funds, the Fishery Agency confirmed yesterday. 
<br /><br />Initial reports showed 5,400 floating oyster beds and 30 hectares of oyster racks were damaged by the tropical storm, creating a financial loss in excess of NT$278 million. 
<br /><br />Fisheries Agency deputy director, Chen Tian-shou, pointed out however that <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9SYXltb25kLVdlaWwtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Raymond Weil Watches</a>  although the 
<br /><br />agency had found through its own site visit that the total loss of the county's oyster farming industry exceeded the required minimum of NT$180 million, many oyster farmers are 
<br /><br />not eligible for relief funds, because they are not licenced as required by the Agricultural Natural Disaster Relief Regulations. 
<br /><br />In light of the fact that Chiayi county sustained such heavy losses, the agency says it will provide unlicensed farmers with financial assistance equal to one tenth of the fund 
<br /><br />amount so that they can start up their <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a> businesses again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a191ec14108020a4e34d666a5b2710de" url=""><![CDATA[No buyer for Pablo Picasso painting at NYC auction<br/><br/>NEW YORK — A Pablo Picasso painting of his young daughter and an <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a>  Alberto Giacometti sculpture of a 
<br /><br />cat, each estimated to sell for $16 million to $24 million, failed to find buyers at auction Tuesday as the art world struggles with the global financial crisis.
<br /><br />The Sotheby's auction house said bids for the two artworks at its impressionist and modern art sale fell below their reserve prices.
<br /><br />Picasso's &quot;The Daughter of the Artist at 2 1/2 with a Boat&quot; was painted in 1938 and remained in his possession until his death. A private collector has owned it since the 1980s.
<br /><br />Giacometti's &quot;The Cat&quot; last was seen at auction in 1975. The 1951 bronze sculpture, depicting a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9SYXltb25kLVdlaWwtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Raymond Weil Watches</a>  feline figure on a pedestal, is one of eight editions. It was consigned by a European collector.
<br /><br />The uncertain economy has played a part in art auction houses' decision this spring to offer fewer lots, lower pre-sale estimates and works by well-known artists and private 
<br /><br />estates that haven't been seen at auction in decades. In the fall, Sotheby's and rival Christie's took beatings when many works didn't sell or sold below their estimates.
<br /><br />Sotheby's said that of the 36 impressionist and modern works of art on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a>  auction Tuesday, 29 were sold, for a total of 
<br /><br />$61.3 million, well off their $118.8 million estimate. Last spring, Sotheby's offered 52 lots, which sold for $235.4 million.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="329ff67a8288de62f1128f40f3ae4fb1" url=""><![CDATA[Star hurdler shows old skills in open session<br/><br/>SHANGHAI: An intensive warmup followed by solid strides between hurdles and<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">replica watches</a> characteristically cool 
<br /><br />facial expressions.
<br /><br />Like he has a thousand times before, reigning men's 110m hurdles world champion and former world record holder Liu Xiang flew over the hurdles swiftly and squarely during an 
<br /><br />open training class at Xinzhuang Training Base of Shanghai.
<br />                  Except for the fact that he was not wearing spikes, it recalled to mind a healthy Liu who stormed to inspiring victories at the 2004 Athens Olympics and 2007 
<br /><br />Osaka World Championships. But with his Achilles tendon injury on his right foot still yet to fully heal, Liu is under doctors' orders to train in sneakers.
<br /><br />After being forced to withdraw from the heats at the Beijing Olympics, the 26-year-old is eager to return to the track, but according to the results from his latest physical 
<br /><br />check, is still not ready. Putting on a determined face, together with his team he is <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbS9UaXNzb3QtV2F0Y2hlcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Tissot Watches</a>  trying to 
<br /><br />convince himself and the world that he can rise to the top again.
<br /><br />&quot;Our working team and Liu himself have never given up,&quot; coach Sun declared at the media briefing after training. &quot;Liu's training today was satisfactory, although it was only 80 
<br /><br />to 90 percent of his previous training quantity.&quot;
<br /><br />The Shanghainese did everything to please more than 100 media that swarmed to the training center in eastern Shanghai. Toward the end of the session, he even ripped off his 
<br /><br />shirt and ran topless to show how much effort he has been putting in.
<br /><br />Last week, Liu advanced the date of his physical check to avoid media focus, prompting speculation he <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaGVzLXNwYWNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">wholesale watches</a>  would announce 
<br /><br />an early retirement yesterday.
<br /><br />But an optimistic Liu pays little heed to rumors.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>