<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="10">
		<document id="9ad7ed84f437b47c8781bd2fffa344a7" url=""><![CDATA[Just read<br/><br/>&quot;Never walk away far real friends, when you see some faults...be patient and realize that nobody is perfect...I am not perfect...but, I can always be a real friend.&quot; <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="11c4aa18902b374e2751e3ec31aa267a" url=""><![CDATA[Cute message<br/><br/>&quot;You learn to like someone when you find out what makes them laugh  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />, but you can never truly love someone until you find out what makes them cry <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry2.gif" alt=":)" />.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="389266b3be20927f97fee676d7060720" url=""><![CDATA[Let us pray<br/><br/>Merciful God, who in your great love and goodness hears the prayers of all your people and is ever-present with those who walk in the shadow of death: we hold in our prayers all who suffer loss and devastation in the wake of the tsunami disaster.
<br /><br />Comfort those who mourn. Give hope to those whose hope has been taken away. Strengthen the will of people everywhere to generously give help and aid. Guide governments and agencies leading relief programmes.
<br /><br />For the sake of your Son, Jesus Christ, who suffered and died for the life of the world. Amen
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1dd3c51670fe251a51cc933f5b93d197" url=""><![CDATA[CSI: Crime Scene Investigation - Las Vegas<br/><br/>How I love to watch Crime Scene Investigation!  Actions, comedy, heavy
<br />dramas and suspense story.  Mr. Grissom is a handsome Chief in the
<br />scene.  Oh how ironic Mr. Nick and Warrick!  And the gorgeous ladies
<br />Ms. Catherine and Ms.Sarah!
<br /><br />This show is one of my favorites.  I really enjoyed watching it until
<br />the last season.  The idea of the show follows 5 main characters who
<br />study in a crime lab in Las Vegas.  In the past, what audiences have
<br />found to be interesting are the police dramas but this show is
<br />original in the way that it has put the spotlight on people who work
<br />for forensics.  Terrific and fantastic!  The special effects and
<br />graphics on this picture are very unique.  In addition to that, I
<br />would like to recommend this show to everyone except for those with
<br />weak stomachs because the program gets a little explicit cases with
<br />the corpse.
<br /><br />Happy Watching!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fc88b6fb7ae31d12f46a04c0c2b5ac2b" url=""><![CDATA[LIFE IS SHORT - DO NOT TAKE LIFE FOR GRANTED-LIVE A BALANCE<br/><br/>Along time ago, there was an Emperor who told his horseman that if he could ride on his horse and cover as much land area as he likes, then the Emperor would give him the area of land he has covered.
<br /><br />Sure enough, the horseman quickly jumped onto his horse and rode as fast as possible to cover as much land area as he could. He kept on riding and riding, whipping the horse to go as fast as possible. When he was hungry or tired, he did not stop because he wanted to cover as much area as possible.
<br /><br />Came to a point when he had covered a substantial area and he was exhausted and was dying. Then he asked himself,”Why did I push myself so hard to cover so much land area? Now I am dying and I only need a very small area to bury myself.&quot;
<br /><br />The above story is similar with the journey of our Life. We push very hard every day to make more money, to gain power and recognition. We neglect our health, time with our family and to appreciate the surrounding beauty and the hobbies we love.
<br /><br />One day when we look back, we will realize that we don't really need that much, but then we cannot turn back for what we have missed. Life is not about making money, acquiring power or recognition. Life is definitely not about work! Work is only necessary to keep us living so as to enjoy the beauty and pleasures of life. Life is a balance of Work and Play, Family and Personal time.
<br /><br />You have to decide how you want to balance your Life. Define your priorities; realize what you are able to compromise.
<br /><br />Happiness is the meaning and the purpose of Life, the whole aim of human existence.
<br /><br />So, take it easy, do what you want to do and appreciate nature. Life is fragile. Life is short.
<br />Do not take Life for granted. Live a balanced lifestyle and enjoy Life!
<br /><br />Watch your thoughts; they become words.
<br />Watch your words; they become actions.
<br />Watch your actions; they become habits.
<br />Watch your habits; they become character.
<br />Watch your character; it becomes your destiny.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1196995529ef377fb3c1d0de4e1ce88c" url=""><![CDATA[('-')<br/><br/>Don't be too confident when someone tells you that they love you, the real question is &amp;quot;until when&amp;quot;? because just like seasons People change and so do Feelings..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="57002de38c229f619d03a93ff43d5231" url=""><![CDATA[Have u smiled today?<br/><br/>One smile can make someone's day, relieve someone's pain, show someone you care, or make someone know everything will be alright. ???
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e73b62c79be695cbbbde6902a35c856b" url=""><![CDATA[WHY GOD ALLOWS PAIN<br/><br/>BEST EXPLANATION EVER!
<br /><br />This is one of the best explanations of why God allows pain and suffering
<br />that I have seen: 
<br /><br />A man went to a barbershop to have his hair cut and his beard trimmed.
<br />As the barber began to work, they began to have a good conversation.
<br />They talked about so many things and various subjects.
<br />When they eventually touched on the subject of God, the
<br /><br />barber said:    &quot;I don't believe that God exists.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Why do you say that?&quot; asked the customer. &quot;Well, you just have to go
<br /> out in the street to realize that God doesn't exist.
<br /><br />Tell me, if God exists, would there be so many sick people?
<br />Would there be abandoned children?
<br /><br />If God existed, there would be neither suffering nor pain.
<br />I can't imagine a loving God who would allow all of these
<br />things.&quot;
<br /><br />The customer thought for a moment, but didn't respond
<br />because he didn't want to start an argument.
<br /><br />The barber finished his job and the customer left the shop.
<br />Just after he left the barbershop, he saw a man in the
<br />street with long, stringy, dirty hair and an untrimmed
<br />beard. He looked dirty and unkempt.
<br /><br />The customer turned back and entered the barber shop again
<br />and he said to the barber: &quot;You know what? Barbers do not
<br />exist.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;How can you say that?&quot; asked the surprised barber.
<br /><br />&quot;I am here, and I am a barber. And I just worked on you!&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;No!&quot; the customer exclaimed. &quot;Barbers don't exist because
<br />if they did, there would be no people with dirty long hair
<br />and untrimmed beards, like that man outside.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Ah, but barbers DO exist! That's what happens when people
<br />do not come to me.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Exactly!&quot; affirmed the customer. &quot;That's the point! God, too, DOES
<br />exist! That's what happens when people do not go to Him and don't look
<br />to Him for help. That's why there's so much pain and suffering in the
<br />world.&quot;
<br /><br />BE BLESSED &amp; BE A BLESSING TO OTHERS !!!!!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d10d707b590c2562baba7b0002a75268" url=""><![CDATA[Jokes<br/><br/>Son-&quot;Whats the difference between confident and confidential?&quot;
<br />Dad-&quot;You are my son of that I am confident. Your friend Timmy is also my son. That's confidential&quot; LOL <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="93c7b10689fa9714f9ec8397fed4d2d9" url=""><![CDATA[:)<br/><br/>Trials may hurt us. Sometimes we just feel like running away from all our problems. You know where's the best hiding place? Just inside God's loving arms..
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>