<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="13">
		<document id="935bde1cc566ea77c3f7db19f91e58b6" url=""><![CDATA[Futures Trading - The Futures Trade Recommendations in Need<br/><br/>Trading is not an easy job, especially being a trader in <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BpdGd1cnUuY29t" target="_blank">futures trading</a> market. Obviously, base on the current economy status, we can see how hard trading is. I know all of you clearly understand that. I am not here to threaten you. We just together look at the fact to see what should we do to get success in life. Though trading is just small part we should to in our life, it keeps an very important role in giving someone a happy family.  For this reason, I would like to one more time remind you the thing we may know clearly that it is really necessary to learn investing tips when we start running on our business. The questions are how and from where traders can get and share experiences? Join trading platform or forum! Actually, it is necessary to build up a multiple market, especially markets for commodity and futures traders, so that investors interested can easily find out trading tips, market recaps and forecasts, or any related topics they want. Understanding that, <strong>Pitguru</strong> has opened <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waXRndXJ1LmNvbS9wcmVtaXVtLXRyYWRlLXNlcnZpY2UuYXNweA__" target="_blank">Commodities Futures Trading Platform</a>  as Pit's special bonus for all traders and every subscriber who has concern on <em>finance,S&amp;P daytrading, futures options, futures oil, metals, grain, energy</em>, or any aspect related to the trading fields. This has been the common house for commodities traders to exchange investing tips. Pitguru will link you directly to the top floor traders by giving you insight and advice on opening futures calls, opening grain calls, and S&amp;P daytrading recommendations. Life is hard, but we can overcome all difficulties if we know how to share and listen.  Get the inside track before the market opens with live opening calls direct from the Pit, develop together! Join and get Trade Recommendations and Free Trading Tool to jump!<strong></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="833aecda2d4e7b3184651450b4afc102" url=""><![CDATA[Search Commodidy Futures Trading Sources for A Brigh Future<br/><br/>If there is anyone who can tell exactly answer for the question &quot;What kind of business that is easy to trade, not hard to get success, and does not cost too much to earn profits&quot;, it would have less tear, homeless or crime. To say that, that means being successful in trading floor is as hard as like building a big construction. When looking at a beautiful bridge, we just naturally say &quot;Wow! Such a wonderful building!&quot; Actually, there are not many people thinking of how hard for engineers and workers to build up this great construction. No one sees wounds, blood or hard days these builders had to work under heavy rain or intense heat... By this way, people look at a successful businessman. Success, nice house, great car, full money.... we may forget that those traders had to spend such difficult stages, even failures. No trader can stand high in trading floor without facing with challenges. That's why if we want to shorten the way to success, we need to learn from experienced experts. To me, this is the first lesson I should bear in my when I start joining in commodity futures trading market. Everyone surely fears of falling, and me too. I try to learn as much as I can to decrease unexpected situations on the way I go. I am not lazy to spend time joining in trading forums and finding commodity trading or <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mdXR1cmVzcHJlc3MuY29t" target="_blank">futures publishing</a> resources where I can get <em> commodity products, futures magazines, books, newsletters, and alerts</em>, can share, listen,  and learn trade recommendations on futures options from profitable traders. I do want to build a stable bridge for my future, a nice house for my loved ones. What do you guys want? Being a worker to make a building for the ones you love?
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c3b33ecbcdeb8f65eddf21e52f3fbd77" url=""><![CDATA[Futures Trading Updated Information by Pitguru Futures Blogs<br/><br/>Futures trading is not an easy kind of business to trade, we all know that, right?. So updating and sharing the information related to this market keep a very important role for the traders to get success in the future. As a member in <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BpdGd1cnUuY29t" target="_blank">Futures Trading</a> floor, <strong>Pitguru</strong> updated itself with the purpose of offering more necessary and useful news and tools for traders who have the same interest. More <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Jsb2cucGl0Z3VydS5jb20v" target="_blank">futures blogs</a>  about Energies, Grains, Softs, Finacials...are available right there to give you the latest facts and news around the markets. Besides, thanks to premium trade service, Pit will bring you forecasts and live trade recommendations direct from the floor. Especially, weekly Pit reviews on Energies, Softs, Metals, Grains, Financials, etc. can give you an outline view to prepare for our wisely decision to jump and pick the success. Always updates, always tries to help catch your goal in futures trading are Pitguru's target. Share and develop together, will you!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ab65841ae03b70e1c3e28fa398701ab6" url=""><![CDATA[Get to Know Selling Options and Option Pricing Models<br/><br/>You clicked at me, keep going, you may get to understand more about the <strong>premium collection program</strong>. Known as the the premium collection program, <strong>Time Means Money</strong> helps collect option premiums by using options pricing models and theory. This is what LaSalle Futures Group brings to traders so that ones who have interest can learn all the dynamics on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aW1lbWVhbnNtb25leS5jb20_" target="_blank">Options Pricing</a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RpbWVtZWFuc21vbmV5LmNvbS9vcHRpb24tcHJpY2luZy1tb2RlbHMuaHRt" target="_blank">Option Models</a> for their success in the  future. This program is used for all speculators who are at a point in their lives where they can assume some calculated risk. It is not a get rich quick program. The one will identify trades that have a statistically high probability for success. If you agree, we will enter and exit these trades for you. Participants must understand that even with probability on their side, there is a calculated risk of loss on each and every trade. Actually most options expire worthless and the logic of harnessing time makes sense to you. Understand that and would you like to learn more about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aW1lbWVhbnNtb25leS5jb20_" target="_blank">selling options</a> or how option selling can give you, just feel free to contact with Time Means Money.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9610384fc5e51704ee2ce4e8370f565d" url=""><![CDATA[The Options Trading Strategies on How to Trade Options<br/><br/>Since I know it is useful to you, the traders in options trading floor, I would like to stop by to write some words to inform you what we have more for futures options trading: <strong>Optionstradingexamples</strong>. As one of the members in the platform, I know “<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vcHRpb25zdHJhZGluZ2V4YW1wbGVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">How to trade options</a> ?” will be among the questions you may want to know the answer. Or  you hear traders talking about puts or calls, the bid and offer, you may have ever wondered what they meant?....if futures options trading is the market you care and want to join. All, we can easily get supports from Optionstradingexamples. The course to learn how to trade options will help explain those things and more. With the hope of sharing burdens with you, Optionstradingexample brings the course with valuable <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vcHRpb25zdHJhZGluZ2V4YW1wbGVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">options trading strategies</a> and information guiding you the right way to success. It’s my big pleasure to tell you the source. Happiness sometimes comes from such the very simple thing. I share with you and get big smiles on my face.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="653d41870874a686d33f47ca641c2f09" url=""><![CDATA[Commodity Futures Trading: Learn What Are Commodities!<br/><br/>Can you help us answer the questions: What are commodities? Or how to do commodity futures online trading? If you are traders in the floor, these will be not hard questions, right? That futures trading is actually commodity trading, and commodities are grains, metals, energies, softs, financials, etc. is just the very basic knowledge. However, investing commodity is not easy kind of business to trade. We need to learn a lot to get good result in all things we do. In the platform, it already has plenty of sources supporting us in commodity futures trading. But, it's said that learn, learn more, learn forever! There is no limitation for learning. So, I would like to share with you guys one more resource worthy to consider: <strong>Commodities Future Trading</strong>. Knowledge from grain futures to the popular energy and gold commodities, from futures trading to options trading will be widely issued to all type of traders in the floor. Discover the world of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NvbW1vZGl0aWVzZnV0dXJldHJhZGluZy5jb20_" target="_blank">commodity futures</a> for the bright future! I want to share. Happiness for you and me!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c1c62ec62ac64bcf2d476dbc18e9ee50" url=""><![CDATA[Futures Trading Blogs: Hot News on Financials, Grains, Softs<br/><br/>Do you need to get news about Financials, Energies, Grains, Metals, and Softs markets, etc? Understanding that keeping up with the trading markets plays an important role in traders' success, <strong>Pitguru</strong> widely shares <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waXRndXJ1LmNvbQ__" target="_blank">futures trading</a>  blogs with update information searched by experts. Prediction or Jeff skilling (Are you kidding me) (in Financials), Euro/USD breaks $1.50 and Weekend at the Borgata ( in Metals), The thing about markets is… (in Softs), WTI spreads pull Crude Price below $70 ( in Energies), Month end and new month (in Grains), Dubai gives a scare to the markets (in Energies and Metals), and many more. Put an eye in the markets you trade to have right decisions on time! That's the tip for success. Did you get the news? Register for Pitguru futures blogs for a successful biz! You will be linked directly to top of the trading floor. Interest in commodities futures? If yes, what are you still waiting for? Time means money, there we go!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e792735f3ba5328f1d579849f29b95c5" url=""><![CDATA[About The London International Futures and Options Exchange<br/><br/>In commodity trading world, traders can be classified into two classes: <em>hedgers</em> and <em>speculators</em>.  You know
<br />+ A hedger watches the underlying commodity and looks to manage the risk of the changing prices.
<br />+ A speculator tries to predict where a market’s price moves may be going, either up or down, and he will try to position himself to profit from the anticipated movement.
<br />You may surprise that commodities tend to be more successful when inflation increases, while bonds and stocks are less successful. So, why? The reasons may be what interested traders need to learn. This matter, <strong>LIFFE</strong> can help. Being a London Futures trader or a futures trader in everywhere all over the world, you will able to get <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpZmZlZnV0dXJlcy5jb20_" target="_blank">commodity exchange</a> , coffee price information from LIFFE also. Ah, LIFFE stands for <strong>the London International Futures and Options Exchange</strong>, and is based in London, England.  As its name, related information issued will effectively help investors in the same floor. A short introduction to you, learn more! You can get much more from <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpZmZlZnV0dXJlcy5jb20_" target="_blank">London Futures</a> .
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3ab8f127849050290b1fc33e21d5ae58" url=""><![CDATA[Futures Blogs: Lottery<br/><br/><span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"><strong>Lottery</strong></span>
<br />Futures blog talks in financial about LOTTERY
<br />&quot;The Yen could break out over the next few days and is currently trading at 1.13. The stock market wants to make a bullish move but is still worried about jobs and factory orders. My idea to take lottery winnings and create more slot machines at airports could really help the American people. Where else can we get significant amounts of money without taxing the consumer. Tax the rich! Well, in all honesty that’s stupid because they are the only people buying stuff. It is scary how much revenue is created after the government taxes lottery winnings. I think this should be investigated further. We can pay healthcare bills for the entire U.S if we make a big lottery donation.&quot;
<br /><br />To see what happen on grains, softs and other <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waXRndXJ1LmNvbQ__" target="_blank">futures markets</a> , bing the blogs!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="313a4c540ffc7bc7e11bdf94122ad0c4" url=""><![CDATA[View of Futures Crude Market<br/><br/>Futures crude market, these are many other markets, you may wonder why I would like to choose it to  talk about? You might not guess that futures crude oil is among the most popular and widely watched futures markets. You know, people keep talking about crude oil prices every day from Television shows to newspapers or magazines. Futures for crude oil trade on more than one exchange and are available nearly 24 hours a day. Thoes channels are watched widely by speculators, hedgers and the general public, since petroleum products can affect nearly every facet of life. From this care, we can see the importance of oil trading in our lives. However, be careful! We cannot negate the fact that crude oil trading involves a substantial risk of loss and is not suitable for everyone. There is no market easy to earn, and this is surely a hard one. Our job is trying to learn to understand more about the market to wisely solve problems we face.
<br />“Do not trade without a good understanding of the markets!”
<br />Learn more about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Z1dHVyZXNjcnVkZS5jb20_" target="_blank">futures crude oil</a>!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="70466bef01f14e6ad4e16c005157a7af" url=""><![CDATA[Energies Review in The Week of June 21st, 2010<br/><br/>Among the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BpdGd1cnUuY29tL0FydGljbGUuYXNweD9jbWQ9YXJjaGl2ZSZhbXA7ZGF5PTIxJmFtcDttb250aD02JmFtcDt5ZWFyPTIwMTA_" target="_blank">futures market</a> reviews, I'll keep update about energies reviews by Pitguru experts to help you guys keep up with the market. Start from today, the energies review for the week of June 21st will show you some necessary information for your business:
<br /><br />&quot;China announced that it would let the Yuan rise against the dollar. This will allow other countries such as the U.S. to sell products to China at more competitive prices. China has been accused of keeping the price of the Yuan down so that it can sell its products at lower prices. Presently this is good news for the U.S. but one should look at the silver lining. Are the Chinese doing this because they see bubbles forming in different places? Is the fact that they are making banks hold larger reserves show that their housing bubble is forming? Or how about that they are making new home buyers put down 30% instead of 20%.
<br /><br />Today, Existing Home Sales are expected to be around 6.10M. Wednesday, New Home Sales are expected to come in at 430k while the forecast shows a possible 450k number. Also, the rates are expected to rise 0.25% which may indirectly raise lending and mortgage rates to small businesses and new home owners. The 24th, Initial Jobless Claims are expected to be 460k which would be lower than the 472k at the last announcement. On the 25th a GDP estimate will be announced and is forecasted to be 3.0%.
<br /><br />The DOW and S&amp;P are up in premarket trading on China’s announcement. The DOW is up 90 points to 10484 and the S&amp;P is up 13.50 to 1123. The U.S. Dollar slipped on China’s news and is down to 85.679 but is in a relatively strong position. The Euro is still trying to fight and has not moved as drastically as expected to 1.15 as most economists forecast. This does not mean it will not sell off. Currently the Euro is trading at 1.2378.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b8d9823cc29219cdb80602d8dfb6acad" url=""><![CDATA[The Financials Review - Week of July 12th, 2010<br/><br/>Talk about finance, no one doesn't have any attitude. People care about it since it is important to all of us, especially to traders and investors. As it needs, from now on, I'll help keep track with the financial market with weekly reviews. Now, just check out <strong>The Financials Pitguru Review</strong> for the week of July, 12th, 2010!
<br /><br />The next few weeks are pivotal for Wall St as earnings are set to make an impact on what direction the market goes. Tonight Alcoa (AA) will announce its earnings and is the stock that typically shows how earnings will go. There is a slow cautious feeling on the floor as traders wait for statistics. A question to ask is does the market trend upward the week before earnings season? The past few earnings seasons it seems as though a cushion was laid down like a shock absorber. The DOW jumped 5% last week and has shown resilience at the 10,000 level for a few months. However the DOW is still down 9% from the highs of last April.
<br /><br />A report was announced showing that 25.5% or 43.4 million people have a credit rating below 599. This might be the most frustrating time for mortgage brokers that have the business but no way of getting the loans to go through. This could be another sign of a weakening housing market. A credit score of 680 is helpful in many situations and may be the cut off point for many Americans. (2)
<br /><br />It is wise to be cautious in earnings season especially for day traders. One needs to act short term but think long term. Questions to think about over the next few weeks for the long term: Is U.S. debt going to creep up and bite Americans like Greece or Spain? Could the housing market crumble again? How about the short term? Could earnings season point the market into a runaway bull? Could the U.S. bring confidence back to consumers? Look for correlations to try and predict future events. Obviously past results are not indicative of future results but it is nice to have a measurement when doing an analysis for the future.
<br /><br />Besides the reviews, for extra help, update information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NvbW1vZGl0aWVzZnV0dXJldHJhZGluZy5jb20vZnV0dXJlcy1wcmljZXMv" target="_blank">futures prices</a>  and currency will support much in your business. Check out: free <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29ubGluZWN1cnJlbmN5Y29udmVydGVycy5jb20_" target="_blank">currency rate calculator</a>!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d06479109e22d919e81b063c416c873a" url=""><![CDATA[Commodities Futures Investing Methods<br/><br/>Once you care about financials, metals, engergies, softs or grains markets, you will find it to interesting reading the <strong>Commodities Futures Investing Methods</strong>. We learn and get knowledge to be successful such the competitive markets.
<br /><br />First of all, just get to know more about <strong>Speculation vs. Hedging</strong>! To traders in floor, the terms are not strange any more, but I know that we are here start from different levels. You may be a newbie. Just have a short view of what are they. You know, there are two kinds of traders and the ones investing in commodity trading are partially the <em>hedgers</em>. He is the one who has a position in a cash market. A person who has an actual interest in the trading prices of a particular commodity.
<br />Many hedgers are farmers growing the actual products, but some of them are also end users of a <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NvbW1vZGl0aWVzZnV0dXJldHJhZGluZy5jb20v" target="_blank">futures commodity</a>, people with an equal interest in trading prices of goods they will buy at a later date. Talking about these markets, corn futures and wheat futures are good examples of markets where people watch trading prices intently. Let's get to know more how traders are working. A person who needs to buy wheat might use the commodity trading prices to place a trade in the futures market to hedge against an increase in the price of wheat. If the trading prices of wheat go up, the futures markets position would possibly gain in value while partially offsetting the increase in raw material costs on the cash market. How about corn? To hedge against a falling price of corn, a farmer might use corn futures market trades. If he sells corn futures now and the price goes down, his crop would be sold for less. However, he would make money in the commodities future trading prices. It would be also true for a wheat farmer wishing to use the commodity markets trading prices to hedge against falling wheat prices. Trading options on futures contracts carries the same possibility. Nevertheless, the expiration dates are a little different than futures contracts.  Some speculators will use futures markets rather than <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vcHRpb25zdHJhZGluZ2V4YW1wbGVzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">option future trading</a>. So, who are speculators? The larger group of participants in commodities future trading is <em>speculators</em>. This group has existed for almost as long as the market themselves. They are willing to assume the risk of trading prices exposure in the markets to attempt to profit from a temporary or long term change in the trading prices of futures contracts. They have a look at fundamental or technical reasons for the commodity trading prices to change and hope to profit from the change. In exchange for this opportunity, speculators create more buyers and sellers in the futures markets and increase the level of liquidity. This group assumes a huge amount of risk for the chance to profit in commodity trading. Do you know why so? The reason is they neither produce nor purchase the actual commodity, they have to offset their futures positions before the expiration date of the contract.
<br /><br />The chance to profit from the daily <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpZmZlZnV0dXJlcy5jb20vZnV0dXJlcy1wcmljZXMv" target="_blank">future trading prices</a> changes for goods is attractive to some traders.  Assess the overall risk and determine if it is right for your portfolio once you want to earn from these markets. Learn all you can about commodities markets and make an educated decision before you trade! Earning from these markets involves a substantial risk of loss and is not suitable for all investors. So, and advice for you is that &quot;Do not trade without a good understanding of the markets!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>