<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="8743b3ac2e702f6eb66903c2cd11ac1e" url=""><![CDATA[New Technology for Grid-Level Electrical Energy Storage Deve<br/><br/>In the aftermath of the recent United Nations Rio+20 Conference on Sustainable Development, the focus of many industrialized nations is beginning to shift toward planning for a sustainable future. One of the foremost challenges for sustainability is efficient use of renewable energy resources, a goal that hinges on the ability to store this energy when it is produced and disburse it when it is needed.
<br /><br />A team of researchers from Drexel University's College of Engineering have taken up this challenge and has developed a new method for quickly and efficiently storing large amounts of electrical energy.
<br /><br />The Challenge of Renewable Energy
<br /><br />Electrical energy storage is the obstacle preventing more widespread use of renewable energy sources such as wind and solar power. Due to the unpredictable nature of wind and solar energy, the ability to store this energy when it is produced is essential for turning these resources into reliable sources of energy. The current U.S. energy grid system is used predominantly for distributing energy and allows little flexibility for storage of excess or a rapid dispersal on short notice.
<br /><br />The Drexel's team of researchers is putting forward a plan to integrate into the grid an electrochemical storage system that combines principles behind the flow batteries and supercapacitors that power our daily technology.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">laptop battery</a>, acer laptop battery, apple laptop battery, dell laptop battery, lenovo laptop battery, toshiba laptop battery, sony laptop battery, hp laptop battery 
<br /><br />Existing Technology
<br /><br />Batteries store a large amount of energy, but are relatively slow in discharging it and they have a limited lifespan, or cycle-life, than their counterparts -- electrochemical capacitors, which are commonly called &quot;supercapacitors&quot; or &quot;ultracapacitors.&quot; Conventional supercapacitors provide a high power output with minimal degradation in performance for as many as 1,000,000 charge-discharge cycles. The capacitor can rapidly store and discharge energy, but only in small amounts compared to the battery.
<br /><br />The obstacle in the way of using either a battery or a supercapacitor to store energy in the grid is that energy storage ability is inextricably tied to the size of the battery or the supercapacitor being used. Supercapacitors, similar to lithium-ion batteries, are manufactured in fairly small cells ranging in size from a coin to a soda can. Large amounts of expensive material, such as metal current collectors, polymer separators and packaging, would be required to construct a battery or supercapacitor of the size necessary to function effectively in the energy grid. &quot;Packing together thousands of conventional small devices to build a system for large-scale stationary energy storage is too expensive,&quot; said Dr. Yury Gogotsi, director of the A.J. Drexel Nanotechnology Institute and the lead researcher on the project. &quot;A liquid storage system, the capacity of which is limited only by the tank size, can be cost-effective and scalable.&quot;
<br /><br />A Grid Energy Storage Solution
<br /><br />The team's research yielded a novel solution that combines the strengths of batteries and supercapacitors while also negating the scalability problem. The &quot;electrochemical flow capacitor&quot; (EFC) consists of an electrochemical cell connected to two external electrolyte reservoirs -- a design similar to existing redox flow batteries which are used in electrical vehicles. This technology is unique because it uses small carbon particles suspended in the electrolyte liquid to create a slurry of particles that can carry an electric charge.
<br /><br />Uncharged slurry is pumped from its tanks through a flow cell, where energy stored in the cell is then transferred to the carbon particles. The charged slurry can then be stored in reservoirs until the energy is needed, at which time the entire process is reversed in order to discharge the EFC.
<br /><br />The main advantage of the EFC is that its design allows it to be constructed on a scale large enough to store large amounts of energy, while also allowing for rapid disbursal of the energy when the demand dictates it.
<br /><br />laptop battery, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9hY2VyLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">acer laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9hcHBsZS1sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">apple laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9kZWxsLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">dell laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9pYm0tbGVub3ZvLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">lenovo laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS90b3NoaWJhLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">toshiba laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9zb255LWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">sony laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9ocC1sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">hp laptop battery</a>
<br /><br />&quot;By using a slurry of carbon particles as the active material of supercapacitors, we are able to adopt the system architecture from redox flow batteries and address issues of cost and scalability,&quot; Gogotsi said
<br /><br />In flow battery systems, as well as the EFC, the energy storage capacity is determined by the size of the reservoirs, which store the charged material. If a larger capacity is desired, the tanks can simply be scaled up in size. Similarly, the power output of the system is controlled by the size of the electrochemical cell, with larger cells producing more power.
<br /><br />&quot;Flow battery architecture is very attractive for grid-scale applications because it allows for scalable energy storage by decoupling the power and energy density,&quot; said Dr. E.C. Kumbur, director of Drexel's Electrochemical Energy Systems Laboratory. &quot;Slow response rate is a common problem for most energy storage systems. Incorporating the rapid charging and discharging ability of supercapacitors into this architecture is a major step toward effectively storing energy from fluctuating renewable sources and being able to quickly deliver the energy, as it is needed.&quot;
<br /><br />This design also gives the EFC a relatively long usage life compared to currently used flow batteries. According to the researchers, the EFC can potentially be operated in stationary applications for hundreds of thousands of charge-discharge cycles.
<br /><br />&quot;This technology can potentially address cost and lifespan issues that we face with the current electrochemical energy storage technologies,&quot; Kumbur said.
<br /><br />&quot;We believe that this new technology has important applications in [the renewable energy] field,&quot; said Dr. Volker Presser, who was an assistant research professor in the Department of Materials Science and Engineering at the time the initial work was done. &quot;Moreover, these technologies can also be used to enhance the efficiency of existing power sources, and improve the stability of the grid.&quot;
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9hY2VyLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">acer laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9hcHBsZS1sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">apple laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9kZWxsLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">dell laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9pYm0tbGVub3ZvLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">lenovo laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS90b3NoaWJhLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">toshiba laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9zb255LWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">sony laptop battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9ocC1sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">hp laptop battery</a> 
<br /><br />This concept for energy storage was recently published in a special issue of Advanced Energy Materials focused on next-generation batteries. The team's ongoing work is focused on developing new slurry compositions based on different carbon nanomaterials and electrolytes, as well as optimizing their flow capacitor design. The group is also designing a small demonstration prototype to illustrate the fundamental operation of the system. &quot;We have observed very promising performance so far, being close to that of conventional packaged supercapacitor cells,&quot; Gogotsi said. &quot;However, we will need to increase the energy density per unit of slurry volume by an order of magnitude, and achieve it using very inexpensive carbon and salt solutions to make the technology practical.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="61f3d11a9247dc46d82992b2e408cd41" url=""><![CDATA[Fast and Ultra-fast Chargers A Battery<br/><br/>Nowhere fast is actually fast-charging within greater need compared to using the electrical vehicle. Re-charging a good EV within min's replicates the actual ease of filling 50 liters (13 gallons) associated with fuel right into a container that's effective at providing 600kWh of one's. This kind of big storage space of one's within an electrochemical program is actually hard in order to comprehend along with a battery keeping this particular capability might consider 6 lots. Nevertheless, electrical power from the battery provides much more effective as well as solution propulsion compared to inner combustion motor.
<br /><br />Getting a good EV may usually consider lengthier compared to filling up the container along with fluid energy, and also the battery may usually provide much less power for each pounds compared to fossil energy. This particular percentage along with present battery technologies is actually approximately 1: 100 in support of fossil energy. Study much more regarding Internet Calorific Worth. Busting the actual guideline as well as making ultra-fast getting might trigger unnecessary tension towards the battery as well as stress the ability grid through dimming the town. Whenever referring to ultra-fast getting we should keep in mind that the actual battery is definitely an electrochemical gadget that's slow as well as manages to lose overall performance along with make use of as well as getting older. Getting the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZnbi1zejY4MC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Sony VGN-SZ680 Battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLWc3M2p3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">asus g73jw battery</a>  can't be when compared with filling up the container along with energy which has 12, 000Wh associated with calorific worth for each liter. In addition, whilst the energy container retains it's volumetric measurements, the battery starts in order to diminish through the period this simply leaves the actual manufacturing plant.
<br /><br />Ultra-fast Chargers
<br /><br />Ultra-fast chargers happen to be close to for several years. The majority of NiCd as well as niche kinds of Li-ion batteries, could be billed in a high price as much as seventy % state-of-charge (SoC). For a price associated with 10C (observe What's the actual C-rate? or even 10 occasions the actual ranked present, the 1A battery might in theory end up being billed within 6 min's, however you will find limitations. To use a good ultra-fast cost, the next problems should be noticed: The actual <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZnbi1zejY4MC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Sony VGN-SZ680 Battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLWc3M2p3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">asus g73jw battery</a> should be made to take a good ultra-fast cost. Present giving presents restriction along with numerous load up styles.
<br /><br />Ultra-fast getting just is applicable throughout the very first cost stage. The actual cost present should be decreased once the seventy % state-of-charge tolerance is actually arrived at.
<br /><br />Just about all tissue within the load up should be well balanced as well as within good shape. Old batteries along with higher inner opposition may warm up; they're no more ideal for ultra-fast getting.
<br /><br />Ultra-fast getting may just be achieved below reasonable temps. Reduced heat decreases the actual chemical substance response, as well as power which can't be soaked up leads to gassing as well as warmth accumulation.
<br /><br />The actual charger should consist of heat settlements along with other security procedures to prevent the actual cost when the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLWY4Mi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">asus f82 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLW42MWpxLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Asus N61Jq battery</a> battery will get unduly anxious. Failing in order to pay attention to in order to these types of problems might lead to quick disintegration from the battery as well as fireplace.
<br /><br />A good ultra-fast charger could be when compared with the high-speed teach that's competent to journey 300km each hour (188 mph) on the monitor constructed for this. The actual monitors, and never the actual equipment, control the most pace. Including capacity to the charger is actually not at all hard; the actual cleverness is based on evaluating the health of the actual battery as well as using the best quantity of optimum cost. An adequately created ultra-fast charger may reduce the present whenever particular problems happen. Essentially, just more recent batteries could be ultra-fast billed.
<br /><br />Don't ultra-fast cost batteries if at all possible as well as cost in a much more reasonable price associated with 1C or even much less. (The producer from the 18650 Li-ion suggests 0. 7C. Manufacturers associated with electrical vehicles choose in the event that EV proprietors cost from a good eight-hour or even 16-hour cost, each which tend to be beneath 1C. The actual 30-minute cost having a three-phase 440V electric outlet costs the actual battery from over 1C which technique ought to just supply in the event that absolutely no additional choice is available (1C may be the present score of the battery. The 1C cost or even release of the <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLWY4Mi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">asus f82 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLW42MWpxLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Asus N61Jq battery</a>  ranked from 1Ah is actually 1A.
<br /><br />Determine 1 even comes close the actual period existence of the lithium-ion battery whenever billed as well as released from 1C, 2C as well as 3C. The 1C cost as well as release period leads to the capability decrease through 650mAh in order to 550mAh following 500 series, highlighting a good 84 % reduce. The 2C speeds up capability diminish in order to 310mAh, symbolizing the forty seven % decrease, with 3C the actual isn't able following just 360 series along with twenty six % leftover capability.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a56994ab21e4d57e003bb9ab7b82b98e" url=""><![CDATA[Hot Asus F82 Battery Replacement<br/><br/>Premium Power Products compatible laptop battery for Asus K40 K4 F82.Asus F82 Laptop battery is designed to be 100% compatible and is designed to meet or exceed original specifications. Asus F82 Laptop Batteries replacement are warranted for a full year to ensure your complete satisfaction.
<br /><br />Asus F82 Battery Replacement Detail Info:
<br /><br />Tech Specs : Lithium-Ion,6Cell 4400mAh
<br /><br />Color : Black
<br /><br />Weight : 420.0g
<br /><br />Dimension : 120.91 x 81.41 x 19.41 mm
<br /><br />Condition : 30 Days Money Back 12 Month Warranty.
<br /><br />Quality : Asus F82 battery use high quality Sony LG Sanyo Samsung new Cells, certified by CE and RoHS.
<br /><br />Feature : Long Asus F82 battery life and maximum power, quick-charging !
<br /><br />Asus F82 Battery Fits Model:
<br /><br />Compatible Part Numbers : ASUS L0690L6,L0A2016,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLWEzMi1mODItYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">ASUS A32-F82 battery</a> etc.
<br /><br />Compatible Models :Asus f52, Asus f82, Asus f83s,ASUS K40 battery,K40AB,K40C,K40IJ,K40IJ-A1,K40IN,K40IN-A1,K40IN-B1,ASUS K50 batteryetc.
<br /><br />Why Buy Asus F82 Battery Replacement Here.
<br /><br />Brand new, never refurbished, 100% compatible, no memory effect.
<br />Over 500 full charge/discharge times.
<br />Fast shipping. 12 months warranty. We stand behind our Asus F82 Battery replacement 100%.
<br /><br />Nore Info:
<br /><br />&lt;&lt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLWY4Mi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Asus F82 battery</a>
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLWEzMi1mODItYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">Asus A32-F82 batterwy</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="797a341a4791b3816a18309991b3ed9e" url=""><![CDATA[Dell’s Development Computer, Project Sputnik, Coming this<br/><br/>Dell has announced a fall release for Project Sputnik, a notebook targeted specifically at developers. This official developer laptop will be based on the Dell XPS 13 and include Ubuntu 10.04 LTS pre-loaded, which will help provide an ideal computing environment for developers. 
<br /><br />Project Sputnik is optimized to provide a complete client-to-cloud solution, using a full set of Linux hardware drivers as well as Cloud and Profile tools. Developers will be able to use these features to immediately create micro-instances and easily push these directly to production servers. There will be a library of profiles, including Ruby and Android, which will expedite the lengthy set-up process usually involved when creating new development environments and tool chains.
<br /><br />Project Sputnik was launched to a select group of beta testers in May and positive feedback from the development community has ushered in the official launch. “By listening to developers, Dell can provide them with solutions and products to help make them more productive and allow for greater innovation,” said Barton George, project Sputnik’s lead and director of Dell’s web vertical marketing. “We have continued to be amazed by the amount and quality of interest and input we have received.”
<br /><br />This is not the first time that Dell has released a laptop running a Linux build rather than the popular Windows operating system. The Dell Inspiron Mini 9, released in 2008, ran a customized version of Ubuntu’s Netbook Remix. With Project Sputnik, however, Dell is demonstrating a commitment to open source software, releasing a notebook targeted at developers with an unmodified Linux build. This new laptop will help alleviate much of the work involved with setting up and maintaining a robust development environment.
<br /><br />Read More:
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xMzEwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1310 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE0NDAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">inspiron 1440 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE3NTAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">inspiron 1750 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE1ci1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">inspiron 15r battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE1NjQtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">inspiron 1564 battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dded550e2699f80a486b541814f50c8b" url=""><![CDATA[Laptop theft leads to "sextortion"<br/><br/>Back on April 7 of this year, a woman in Dover, New Hampshire called the police. Someone had broken into her house and stolen her MacBook Pro—normal enough in the grand scheme of criminal behavior—but also some of her underwear. Disconcerting. Making it even worse was the victim's knowledge that her now-stolen laptop contained not just e-mails and Web browsing history, but several years' worth of private, sexual pictures of her and several partners. But perhaps the underwear-and-laptop thief wouldn't find them.
<br /><br />Months passed. The computer was not recovered, but the situation hadn't gotten any worse—until the e-mails arrived. They began on July 10, coming from a Gmail address. &quot;What if I told you I have 'pics' of you?&quot; one asked. &quot;Like a lot. Would you send me more?&quot; A second e-mail added that the victim was &quot;crazy hot&quot;—unlikely to be much of a compliment coming from a random Internet creepo asking for more nude pictures.
<br /><br />They began corresponding, the woman trying to figure out how the guy had gotten her photos, which were stored only on her computer. (He sent her several of the unpublished photos as proof of his claim.) The guy on the other end of the Gmail account never admitted to burgling her home; he claimed that some random person with a craigslist account had just happened to send him the pictures.
<br /><br />Stringing him along
<br /><br />The local Dover police got involved, with a detective helping the victim to play the scenario out for time, convincing the perp to get explicit about his blackmailing intentions. After asking what sort of pictures he wanted—and getting a list in response, the victim e-mailed on July 11 to ask: &quot;And if I do that you'll tell me who e-mailed you?&quot; The stalker said he would.
<br /><br />He quickly grew impatient with this game, though; he demanded photos. (&quot;Sneak in to a ladies' room somewhere really quick and snap some hot sexy photos for me.&quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /> Or better—some videos. (&quot;Get loud for me.&quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy0xNy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps 17 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy0xNS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps 15 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby14cHMtMTMtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">studio xps 13 battery</a> 
<br /><br />To keep the conversation going, the victim acted like she might comply. On July 12, following Dover police advice, she sent a picture of her face and one of her stomach as teasers.
<br /><br />By July 16, the Secret Service, working out of its Manchester, New Hampshire office, had gotten involved and were guiding the victim's actions. She asked her stalker for an explicit description of what he would do if she didn't send the material he wanted.
<br /><br />&quot;You know I thought more about it and I'm a little concerned about who else you may be sending these photos to,&quot; she wrote. &quot;I still don't even understand how you have them to begin with and if they get out it'll ruin my reputation. I'm trying to start a new life and this would absolutely fuck everything up I'm trying to accomplish.&quot;
<br /><br />The message struck a nerve. The stalker replied: &quot;Alright be like that then, see what i do with these . . . think im a sick bastard? then im going to act like one. familiar with doxing? look it up, have fun!... definition of DOXING leaking Personal information about people on the Internet, often including real name, known aliases, email addresses, general location, pictures...&quot; He then mentioned the name of the woman's young child and provided their home address; he threatened to send the woman's sexual photos to her employer, former husband, and current boyfriend.
<br /><br />On the advice of the Secret Service, the woman retreated, apologizing for being &quot;a little nasty earlier&quot; and saying that she needed to protect her family.
<br /><br />&quot;Yeah i agree,&quot; replied her stalker, &quot;so i bet now youre more willing to comply to my request? see we do have a thing going. If you're still willing to do your portfolio. Im still here to help.&quot;
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby14cHMtMTM0MC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">studio xps 1340 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby14cHMtMTYtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">studio xps 16 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby14cHMtMTY0MC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">studio xps 1640 battery</a>, 
<br /><br />Uh, I know him!
<br /><br />In the background, of course, the Secret Service was identifying the sextortionist with the most obvious tool in their toolbox: the IP address lookup. On July 16, Google came back with the IP addresses that accessed the stalker's Gmail account. One resolved to the US Navy, another one to Comcast.
<br /><br />So on to the Navy—where NCIS apparently got involved in the hunt—and to Comcast, which on July 16 also provided a lookup. The Comcast IP address was assigned to a woman with the last name of Villegas, living in the nearby town of Kittery, Maine—about 12 miles from Dover.
<br /><br />This wasn't a random hit; the victim actually knew the woman. Indeed, it was one of her friends—and the friend's husband worked for the US Navy.
<br /><br />With the information in hand, the Secret Service moved quickly. On July 17, an agent filed an affidavit with a judge and obtained an arrest warrant for the husband, John Bryan Villegas. Villegas was arrested the next day and hauled before a federal magistrate, where he swore that he lacked the money to defend himself and was appointed a federal defender. Bail conditions include limited travel and no use of computers or Internet-connected smartphones.
<br /><br />If found guilty of being the sextortionist, Villegas could face up to seven total years in prison for making threats and for computer intrusion, and up to $500,000 in restitution.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4dcfa91c262a1a57a7d98bfd21fd752c" url=""><![CDATA[The Best Dell Laptops Reviews<br/><br/>Unless you're the type who can drop around $2,000 on a laptop without batting an eye, purchasing one is definitely no small decision. After all, our lives today are tightly intertwined with technology to the point that ostensibly ordinary devices like laptops have a huge impact on everything from your workflow to how you keep in touch with loved ones. Chances are that some of this swirled about in your head before you finally narrowed your brand of choice down to Dell. Maybe it was because of an especially poignant marketing campaign. Or maybe your coworker has been raving about the one she just got. Either way, by making the conscious decision to go with Dell, you're halfway there. Now, all you've got to do is decide which Dell to go with.
<br /><br />Existential hand-wringing aside, there are a wide range of features to consider. Let's start with purpose. Are you looking for a general desktop replacement laptop Or are you in search of something capable of heavy-duty 3D gaming If you fall in the first category, then you'd be better off with a Dell that sports a high-resolution display and an ergonomic keyboard/touchpad combination. Portability would also be a huge plus. In that case, check out the Editors' Choice-winning Dell XPS 15z ($1,534 direct, 4 stars), which features a terrific screen, roomy keyboard, and is less than an inch thick.
<br /><br />What about gaming Portability probably isn't a top priority for those in this camp. No, gaming is all about sheer, unbridled power, so you'll need a system with a powerful CPU/GPU combination as well as a large display. For this, you're looking at the Alienware M17x R4, which has the lastest Intel Core CPU and Nvidia graphics.
<br /><br />Maybe you just want a Dell laptop, plain and simple. Fair enough. Regardless of what you actually intend to use your laptop for, certain features transcend category altogether. For starters, you should consider a system with USB 3.0 connectivity. Not only is it speedy and backwards-compatible with older USB 2.0 devices, it's also fast-becoming more widely used. And what about a Blu-ray drive Do you plan on using your laptop for multimedia purposes If so, you'd be well-off with a system that also sports HDMI-out because, after all, wouldn't you rather watch The Dark Knight on a larger display instead of having to hunch over your laptop And because it's not really a laptop if it can't be moved around at all, battery life is always a tantamount consideration that cuts across all categories.
<br /><br />Sound like a lot Lucky for you, we've done most of the heavy lifting in this roundup by choosing the five best Dell laptops. Check out the reviews and find out exactly which Dell is right for you.
<br /><br />See More:
<br /><br />-- <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNDM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1435 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNDM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1436 battery</a> 
<br /><br />-- <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1535 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1537 battery</a> 
<br /><br />-- <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTU1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1555 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1536 battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d78ed1f64e9269c869f6767b43ad74f8" url=""><![CDATA[How To Choose Best Sony VGP-BPS13/Q Battery<br/><br/>If you know the stresses and annoyances of laptop batteries, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww.</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1xLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./q</a> failing, you are most likely looking for a solution to this issue. Standard laptop batteries can run out very quickly, and a lot of people are oblivious when it comes to doing your best to maintain a laptop batteries lifespan. The Laptop Battery that your laptop comes with, is usually going to be pretty standard and average, it will last you a while if you take care of it, but the only way you can keep using it, is if you constantly plug your laptop in via a Laptop AC Adapter.
<br /><br />Buying a decent laptop battery will do you wonders, a high quality laptop battery will transform your laptop. The reason your current laptop battery is so awful is because it is a bog standard laptop battery, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1zLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./s</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1iLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./b</a> and usually most laptops come with an average laptop battery, which isn’t good at all. If you want your laptop to last over an hour and still be fine when it isn’t plugged in, you need a high standard Laptop Battery. Of course when you are at home, or where a plug socket is available, it is recommended that you do plug in, as it will prolong any laptop batteries life, but with a decent laptop battery, you don’t have the concern of your laptop giving way when working without it being plugged in.
<br /><br />Thirdshopping.com is an online store where you find all kinds of brand laptop battery,Free Shipping Wholesale Marketplaces,More than 6000 Products Wholesale and Dropship,You Can Buy Camcorder Battery,Digital Camera Battery,This is your best opportunity to directly access the CA electronics online store.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="909110aae328fb866a3739606a301404" url=""><![CDATA[Difference between NiCad, NiMH and Lithium Ion batteries<br/><br/>Nicad vs. NiMh
<br /><br />The main difference between the two is that NiMH battery (the newer technology of the two) offers higher energy density than NiCads. In other words, the capacity of a NiMH is approximately twice the capacity of its NiCad counterpart. What this means for you is increased run-time from the battery with no additional bulk or weight. NiMH also offers another major advantage: NiCad batteries tend to suffer from what is called the &quot;memory effect&quot;. NiMH batteries are less prone to develop this problem and thus require less maintenance and conditioning. NiMH batteries are also environmentally friendlier than NiCad batteries since they do not contain heavy metals (which present serious landfill problems). Note: Not all devices can accept both NiCad or NiMH batteries. 
<br /><br />Lithium Ion
<br /><br />Lithium-Ion (Li-Ion) has become the new standard for portable power in consumer devices. Li-Ion batterys produce the same energy as NiMH battery but weighs approximately 20%-35% less. This can make a noticeable difference in devices such as cellular phones, camcorders or notebook computers where the battery makes up a significant portion of the total weight. Another reason Li-Ion batteries have become so popular is that they do not suffer from the &quot;memory effect&quot; at all. They are also environmentally friendly because they don't contain toxic materials such as Cadmium or Mercury.
<br /><br />More News:
<br /><br />&gt;&gt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNDM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1435 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNDM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1436 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&gt;&gt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1535 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1537 battery</a>
<br /><br />&gt;&gt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTU1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1555 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1536 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&gt;&gt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy0xNy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps 17 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy0xNS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps 15 battery</a>
<br /><br />&gt;&gt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9kZWxsLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">dell laptop battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb34e4cfa74814d367d6c7c3d4a9e3fa" url=""><![CDATA[Battery not Holding a Charge<br/><br/>via <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />ell.com
<br /><br />If your computer battery is not lasting as long as it used to, try the following troubleshooting steps.
<br /><br />Boot into BIOS and see if the battery still runs down quickly.
<br /><br />This will eliminate the possibility that Windows programs are causing the battery to run down too quickly.
<br /><br />Factors that may cause a xps 17 battery,xps 15 battery to run down quickly
<br /><br />Reset the BIOS.
<br />How to reset the Inspiron system defaults
<br />How to reset the Latitude system defaults
<br /><br />Flash the BIOS.
<br />Flash the system BIOS
<br /><br />Run the Recalibration Utility (For Specified Systems Only)
<br /><br />Some Dell Systems have programs for recalibrating batteries to accept a charge. This will run the studio xps 13 battery,studio xps 1340 battery all the way down and then recharge it completely. This will take several hours to run, so it is best to run it overnight. You should use the program for the specified systems only and using a program not designed for your system could void the warranty on the computer.
<br /><br />Latitude LM, or Inspiron 3000 or Inspiron 3200 systems use:
<br />BATRECAL.EXE 
<br /><br />Inspiron 5000, Inspiron 7000, or Inspiron 7500 use:
<br />I75BRCA0.EXE 
<br /><br />The Latitude LS, L400, and X200 and the Inspiron 2100 have battery recalibration options in the BIOS. This is on the Power page of the BIOS Setup. More Help Enabling the Battery Recalibration in the BIOS Setup 
<br /><br />Try another battery, if possible.
<br /><br />If the other battery has the same life, there may be a problem with something besides the studio xps 16 battery,studio xps 1640 battery .
<br /><br />More News:
<br /><br />You maybe like:
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fthirdshoppingcom.overblog.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://thirdshoppingcom.overblog.com</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fthirdshoppingcom.blogspot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://thirdshoppingcom.blogspot.com</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsellabetterday.blog.co.uk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://sellabetterday.blog.co.uk</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsellabetterday.xanga.com%2Fweblog%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://sellabetterday.xanga.com/weblog/</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fthirdshopping.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://thirdshopping.net</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e439835c27d95880c4cc17afb0b1db56" url=""><![CDATA[A big battery power your home<br/><br/>Evidently, you will find much more brand new houses designed with solar energy within Sacramento compared to elsewhere in the usa. The actual area can also be the website for any fairly thrilling check task within the world of one's storage space.
<br /><br />Within the following 1 . 5 years, the actual Sacramento City and county Power Area (SMUD) may assistance the $5. 9 zillion demo which will assess what size lithium-ion batteries may help slow up the fill upon electrical grid throughout intervals associated with maximum need.
<br /><br />Underneath the check plan, 15 houses within the Anatolia subdivision from the SolarSmart Houses neighborhood within Rancho Cordova, Calif., may set up the actual batteries within their garages; an additional 28 may reveal 3 positioned in community typical ares.
<br /><br />The actual houses is going to be changed to batteries throughout the morning several hours, once the area is usually the greatest as well as electrical power need over the area typically increases. The actual batteries is going to be billed immediately, whenever energy expenses tend to be reduce.
<br /><br />&quot;The purpose of this program would be to discover whether batteries may relieve fill need and supply much more electrical power whenever green power resources for example photo voltaic as well as blowing wind energy are not adequate, inch stated John Lau, helper common supervisor with regard to Power &amp; Grid Procedures, SMUD. &quot;The task will even assist all of us much better know how battery storage space as well as photo voltaic nylon uppers along with time-of-use prices, exactly where clients spend much more with regard to electrical power throughout maximum several hours as well as much less throughout low-demand occasions. 
<br /><br />Obviously the actual houses within the task had been made to become more effective compared to typical, having a impact that's around forty % scaled-down. However the demo will give you useful information about how exactly irregular power resources for example photo voltaic solar or even wind generators may take advantage of power storage space.
<br /><br />Based on SMUD, the actual batteries getting used within the person check houses tend to be regarding how big the small fridge and may energy a house with regard to in between 2 as well as 3 several hours, with respect to the product fill. The actual community-shared batteries tend to be larger, and also have around 3 times the capability from the in-home models.
<br /><br />Home owners may have sections which assist all of them observe how a lot power they're producing, as well as utilizing.
<br /><br />Brand new evaluation through Pike Investigation implies that the power storage space business is actually re-charging because much more green power installs range from the technologies like a element.
<br /><br />Power storage space tasks flower 8 % in order to 649 within the very first 1 / 2 of 2012, in contrast to last year. The amount of tasks that really grew to become functional throughout the very first 6 months of the 12 months had been 514.
<br /><br />Related Articles:
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNDM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1435 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNDM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1436 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1535 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1537 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTU1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1555 battery</a> 
<br /><br />&lt;&lt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXN0dWRpby0xNTM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">dell studio 1536 battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="489fe13ba895212a4455f62e352d76e4" url=""><![CDATA[How to Troubleshoot a Laptop Burning Smell<br/><br/>1.Troubleshoot the laptop by shutting down the computer and removing the AC adapter and the battery. Some laptop batteries cannot be removed unless the casing plate is unscrewed from the base. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwtaW5zcGlyb24tMTMuaHRt" target="_blank">Dell inspiron 13 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwtaW5zcGlyb24tMTUuaHRt" target="_blank">Dell inspiron 15 battery</a> 
<br /><br />2.Attach the AC adapter to the computer and turn the computer back on. If there is no smoking smell and laptop does not get hot, then the battery is faulty and must be replaced. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwtaW5zcGlyb24tMTQuaHRt" target="_blank">Dell inspiron 14 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwtaW5zcGlyb24tMTcuaHRt" target="_blank">Dell inspiron 17 battery</a> 
<br /><br />3.Continue to troubleshoot the laptop by moving it to a hard surface such a lap desk or a table. On some laptops, the vents will not function properly when the laptop is on a cloth surface. The overheating caused by the soft surface blocking the vents may cause a burning smell.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwtaW5zcGlyb24tMTQ3MC5odG0_" target="_blank">Inspiron 1470 Battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwtaW5zcGlyb24tZTE1MDUuaHRt" target="_blank">Inspiron E1505 Battery</a> Manufacturers of computers recommend keeping the laptop on a hard surface for proper airflow to cool the laptop.
<br /><br />4.Clean the laptop by lifting up the keyboard from the case. Check your laptop's user manual for guidelines on cleaning. Use a small hand vacuum to clean any dust.
<br /><br />5.Check that fan is running by listening for the sound of a fan while the computer is on. Even quiet laptops emit a low whirring noise. If the smell continues and there is no whirring noise from the fan, shut the laptop down immediately and have the fan replaced. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwtaW5zcGlyb24tMTUwMS5odG0_" target="_blank">Inspiron 1501 Battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwtaW5zcGlyb24tMTUyMC5odG0_" target="_blank">Inspiron 1520 Battery</a> 
<br /><br />A burning smell coming from a laptop indicates a failure in the laptop's cooling system. A laptop must be cooled in order to keep the electricity running through the laptop's hardware from melting the system. Signs of a cooling system failure include the laptop fan never shutting off, the fan running loudly, the computer restarting at random intervals, or the computer not starting at all. If a smoke smell comes from the laptop when it's running, irreparable damage may have been done to the internal components. Or, a faulty battery may be the cause of the smoking smell.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2FjZXIuaHRt" target="_blank">acer battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2FwcGxlLmh0bQ__" target="_blank">apple battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2FzdXMuaHRt" target="_blank">asus battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2RlbGwuaHRt" target="_blank">dell battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2hwLmh0bQ__" target="_blank">hp battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L2libS5odG0_" target="_blank">ibm battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdHRlcnktc3RvcmUuY29tLmF1L2xhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5L3NvbnkuaHRt" target="_blank">sony battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2f58e73c7929811ee856841df774566c" url=""><![CDATA[HP Envy Laptop PC Review<br/><br/>For anyone that is looking to get a thin and lightweight 15-inch laptop, it is going to be hard to find a better overall choice that the HP Envy Sleekbook 6 with its $600 price tag. The downside is that the lower price point also comes with a slower performing AMD platform. it will work for basic tasks but even the first generation Intel ultrabooks will often do better. The hard drive is definitely its weakest performance area especially comapred to ultrabooks with their SSD or cached hard drives. Still, the AMD platform did offer a surprisingly long battery life which may be very useful for those that have to be away from power for extended periods. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYXBwbGUtYTEwNzktYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">apple a1079 battery</a> 
<br /><br />HP's Envy Sleekbook 6 is essentially a design that tries to mimic the new larger 15-inch ultrabooks but using the AMD platform that helps it bring is a much lower $600 price tag which is hundreds less than the least expensive ultrabooks. Since HP and AMD don't have to mimic the AMD specs, things are a bit different in terms of performance but the overall size and weight are clearly in the ultrabook range. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYXBwbGUtYTEwNDUtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">apple a1045 battery</a> The system measures just under .8 inches thick making it very thin and at 4.5 pounds it is nearly a pound lighter than the average 15-inch laptop.
<br /><br />Powering the system is the new AMD A6-4455M dual core processor. This is a lower wattage part that has much more in common with the ultra low voltage Intel processors used for the ultrabooks. It is matched up with 4GB of DDR3 memory which is typical of most budget and ultrabook designs. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYXBwbGUtYTExNzUtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">apple a1175 battery</a> In terms of performance, it does a much better job than past AMD ultra-low offerings but is still slower than even the second generation Intel processors found in the first generation of ultrabooks. For the average user that is just browsing the web, doing email, watching videos and doing productivity software it will work just fine. Those looking to do more demanding tasks will definitely want to look at either a more powerful standard laptop or a newer generation ultrabook.
<br /><br />Since the HP Sleekbook is about being thin and light, it forgoes the optical drive similar to many ultrabooks. This is not as much of an issue in the past. For storage, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYXBwbGUtYTExODktYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">apple a1189 battery</a> buyers get a 500GB hard drive which is fairly typical and provides a decent amount of space for applications, data and media files. The drive spins at a 5400rpm rate which makes the system feel much slower than ultrabooks that either use solid state drives or some form of SSD cache in addition to a hard drive. This is particularly true when booting up or waking the system from sleep. If you need additional storage space, there are two USB 3.0 ports on the system for use with high speed external hard drives.
<br /><br />One of the big advantages that the Envy lineup of systems had was above average displays. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYXBwbGUtbWFjYm9vay0xMy1zZXJpZXMtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">macbook 13-inch battery</a> In the case of the HP Envy Sleekbook 6, think much more average. The 15.6-inch display panel comes with the very modest 1366x768 resolution typical of most low cost laptops. While the picture was fairly bright and colorful, the viewing angles on the screen left much to be desired. Small shifts off center on the vertical or horizontal cased significant color shifting and contrast loss. Graphics wise, the AMD Fusion platform has generally been quite good in comparison to Intel's HD Graphics found in most ultrabooks and budget laptops. In terms of 3D performance, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYXBwbGUtcG93ZXJib29rLWc0LTE1aW5jaC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">powerbook g4 15-inch battery</a> it actually falls slightly short of Intel's latest which means that this isn't something you can use for PC gaming beyond casual gaming at lowest resolutions and detail levels. The main benefit is that it does offer better acceleration for non-3D applications thanks to the support of OpenCL compared to Intel which excels just in video transcoding with compatible applications.
<br /><br />The keyboard design for the HP Sleekbook 6 uses the isolated layout typical of many systems now. It does not feature a numeric keypad that is typical of many 15-inch laptops which means that there is a fair amount of space on either side of the sunken keyboard. Overall, it offers a good feel and level of accuracy but it isn't quite as nice as some other Envy models. The trackpad is a good overall size but uses the integrated buttons. The button press is fairly stiff and has the issue of incorrectly registering right and left clicks. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYWNlci1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">acer battery</a>
<br /><br />With the lack of an optical drive, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYXBwbGUtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">apple battery</a> HP was able to put a slightly larger 60WHr capacity rating within the Sleekbook 6. This along with the lower wattage AMD Fusion processor should yield better overall running times. In my digital video playback test, the system was able to run for just over five and a half hours before going into standby mode. This is actually very good for the system and fares much better than many new ultrabooks equipped with hard drives that last generally under four hours. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvYXN1cy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">asus battery</a> HP's claim of nine hours of running time is a bit far fetched unless the laptop is idle for the majority of the time.
<br /><br />At $600, the HP Envy Sleekbook 6 is certainly a solid option for those looking for portability. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvZGVsbC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">dell battery</a> The closest similar systems would be the new low cost ultrabook options that generally offer smaller screens. The Lenovo IdeaPad U310 is a good example. It can be found for between $600 and $800 but it has higher performance and in a smaller package. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvaHAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">hp battery</a> The big difference is that it has roughly two thirds the running time of the HP. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNjb3VudC1sYXB0b3BzLWJhdHRlcnkuY28udWsvc29ueS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">sony battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="427513758c6d2cf0aecfb52e26264e9f" url=""><![CDATA[MacBook Pro Laptop From the Future<br/><br/> When Apple created major buzz around a new product in the past few years, it was almost always an iPhone or iPad. That’s why it’s so refreshing to see the world ooh and aah about an Apple computer again, the MacBook Pro With Retina Display. It certainly looks great on paper — a cutting-edge laptop loaded with the latest tech and a jaw-droppingly sharp screen. But does it really deliver the goods? The answer isn’t just yes. It’s “oh, baby.” Within minutes of taking our review sample out of the box here at the Mashable offices, a crowd of staffers gathered around to see what visions the glorious 2,880 x 1,800 retina display would show them. It didn’t disappoint. After setting up the laptop and putting it side by side with a six-month-old MacBook Pro with the same-size screen, the difference was apparent to anyone with eyes. Also apparent: How crazy thin this machine is — just 0.71 of an inch thick, or 0.03 inch thicker than the 13-inch MacBook Air. However, it’s a mite heftier at 4.46 pound to the Air’s roughly 3 pounds. If you’re used to the Air or some of the sleeker Ultrabooks like the Dell XPS 13, the retina Pro’s is still a size class above. However, it’s still significantly less bulky than the regular Pro, and still fits in the same bags.
<br /><br />Feasting Your Retina
<br /><br />Back to that screen. Perhaps surprisingly, the first thing you notice is the deeper colors, not necessarily the sharpness — although that becomes clear when viewing photos with lots of detail. Browsing through the Flickr feed of the NASA Goddard Space Center, the crowd could see those extra pixels working to show, say, the wispy clouds in satellite shots of earth.
<br /><br />Virtually all images were displayed with more vibrant colors and better contrast than on the older Pro.
<br /><br />It’s not just photos that benefit from the extra pixels, but text and iconography as well. Everything from the system fonts to app icons to the galactic background image looks sharper, with better contrast.
<br /><br />After I connected the retina Pro to an external (non-retina) Acer monitor, it became something of a game to drag windows from one screen to the other, watching the images and text magically transform as they crossed from edge to edge, becoming crisper and more affecting.
<br /><br />When you venture outside Apple apps, however, the experience isn’t so improved. Sometimes it’s actually worse than what you had before. Text in third-party web browsers like Chrome and Firefox appears jagged and pixelated because those apps aren’t rendering for retina resolutions.
<br /><br />Although those app developers will issue updates that will address those issues (Google is already doing so with Chrome), it emphasizes how new this screen tech is. Eventually, ultra-high-resolution displays will become more common. But for now the retina MacBook is an outlier, and early adopters will pay the price in non-optimized apps, at least for a while.
<br /><br />There’s one way around that issue, of course: Just stick with Apple apps, which appear to be all retina-ready. iPhoto (see the screenshot below) and Aperture in particular take tremendous advantage of the screen, and if you can bear to browse the web with Safari (and judging by the browser stats for Mashable readers, you can’t), your eyes will be satisfied.
<br /><br />It actually got me surfing with Apple’s browser for more than 5 minutes for the first time in years.
<br /><br />t’s worth noting that by default, the retina display scales the screen so everything is the same size as it would be on a regular MacBook Pro. If you really enjoy squinting, though, you can use the streamlined display settings to make more use of your pixels. Everything will appear smaller, but you’ll get more on the screen, and the processor can handle it. 
<br /><br />The Power of Pro
<br /><br />That processor, by the way, is an Intel third-generation (Ivy Bridge) quad-core Core i7, with a clock speed of either 2.3 or 2.6GHz (Turbo Boostable to 3.3 or 3.6GHz). It’s augmented by a discrete graphics processor, an Nvidia GeForce GT 650M with 1GB of dedicated memory (the laptop itself comes with 8GB, though you can configure it with 16GB at purchase).
<br /><br />That’s some serious power, but the retina Pro really needs it to drive all those pixels, particularly for graphics-intensive exercises, like video editing.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hcHBsZS1hMTA1Ny1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Apple A1057 battery</a> | <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hcHBsZS1hMTE3NS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Apple A1175 battery</a> | <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hcHBsZS1tODQzMy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">apple m8433</a> | <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hcHBsZS1hMTA3OS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Apple A1079 battery</a> | <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hcHBsZS1hMTA3OC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Apple A1078 battery</a> | <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hcHBsZS1hMTE4NS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Apple A1185 battery</a> | <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hcHBsZS1tODQxNi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Apple M8416</a> | <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hcHBsZS1hMTI0NS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Apple A1245 Battery</a> 
<br /><br />In addition to the meaty processing power, the new Pro has another performance advantage: a solid-state flash drive for storage. Since the drive doesn’t have moving parts like a hard disk has, the laptop can “lift” data off the drive faster, adding to the speed of the machine.
<br /><br />Just what can you do with that kind of power? We aimed to find out by re-creating a demo that Apple reps showed us: playing four simultaneous full HD video streams in Final Cut Pro X and making live cuts between them.
<br /><br />We made sure all the streams were all uncompressed 1080i files at 60 frames per second, cued them up, then watched for any stuttering or other problems. Check out the results in this video:
<br /><br />In our test, all the clips played just fine in the inspector window, never tripping up as we made rapid-fire cuts between them — an impressive feat. Apple says this is one of the abilities the solid-state drive bestows, and that the retina Pro is the only machine that can play four full-HD clips simultaneously.
<br /><br />The flash drive also speeds things up when copying files, but even better in that regard is the upgrade to USB 3.0. The retina MacBook Pro isn’t alone in getting better USB — all of Apple’s new laptops have it (native support for USB 3.0 comes hand-in-hand with Intel’s Ivy Bridge processors).
<br /><br />Still, it’s a welcome change, as is relocating one of the ports to the right side of the chassis, à la the MacBook Air.
<br /><br />Connectors &amp; More
<br /><br />USB 3.0 and flash storage are a great combo, though its benefits will be best realized with USB 3.0 devices. When I tried offloading a big 3.84GB file from the most common thing users will likely use — a USB thumb drive — it took an 7 minutes, 3 seconds. That was better than the old MacBook Pro, which took almost 10 minutes, but not as awesome as you’d think.
<br /><br />Although the improved USB ports are on all MacBooks now, the retina Pro boasts a connector that isn’t: a full-size HDMI port. This is the first time an Apple laptop has included HDMI, and Apple says it’s because its customers demanded it.
<br /><br />It’s pretty obvious why — to watch video services like Netflix on a big-screen TV. Apple may have been reluctant to include HDMI until now to avoid subverting its own Apple TV box. Could the appearance of HDMI on the retina MacBook signal that Apple isn’t as concerned about that anymore, possibly because it has bigger plans for the living room?
<br /><br />We’ll leave that question unanswered for now, and instead say that the HDMI connection is welcome and worked well upon connection to one of the Sony TVs here at the Mashable offices.
<br /><br />Generally, you’ll probably want to mirror displays when connecting to a TV (see the pic below), though that will letterbox the screen on the pro to a 16:9 ratio while you’re connected.
<br /><br />The MacBook Transformed
<br /><br />Which leads to an important factor: You’ll definitely need some accessories to enjoy the fruits of a full-featured laptop. Besides those adapters, you’ll likely need an external optical drive for the few times you’ll want to read an old CD-ROM or burn a DVD. Be prepared: Your final price tag will likely be more than you thought.
<br /><br />Also, the MagSafe power adapter is a different design from the regular MacBook Pro. Since the retina Pro is so thin, it had to be flattened a little, plus it discards the L-shaped connector on the recent Pros with more conventional plug design that came before it and is still used by the Air. That means older power adapters are incompatible with the new Pro — an important detail if you have an external Apple display that also powers your machine via MagSafe (Apple does sell an adapter, however).
<br /><br />Other changes MacBook Pro veterans will notice: The power button has a new home, right where the Eject button for the DVD drive used to be (no need for that anymore). There are also some curious omissions: First, the rarely-used Audio input is gone — there’s just a solitary headphone jack now. Also absent are the handy battery-status button, its accompanying LEDs, the sleep indicator and the infrared sensor. You sacrifice a lot to have a thin body, apparently. Thankfully the keyboard is still backlit.
<br /><br />You can see some of those absences in the photo below, which shows the MacBook Air, Retina Pro and Pro, all stacked together (more comparisons in the gallery).
<br /><br />The speakers in the retina Pro have clearly been given some vitamins, although users probably won’t notice until they cue up Spotify or iTunes. Listening to Ahead by a Century by the Tragically Hip on both machines, it was easier to pick out the individual voices among the band members on the retina MacBook, and the soundstage felt wider overall, with deeper bass.
<br /><br />Helpfully, the fan is whisper-quiet.
<br /><br />The Return to Apple’s Core
<br /><br />Taking a step back, it’s beautiful to see so much cutting-edge technology put into a laptop: The latest processors, discrete graphics, high-speed connectivity, up to 16GB of RAM, a flash drive that can be as massive as 768GB — and of course that ultra-high-res screen.
<br /><br />Such a package comes with a price: It starts at $2,199, and that’s just with 8GB of RAM and 256GB of storage. It should really be called the MacBook Pro With Retina Screen And An Eye-Popping Price Tag.
<br /><br />You get what you pay for, though, and in this case it’s a ticket to the future. More than even Intel has done with Ultrabooks, Apple has, with the retina MacBook Pro, drawn a dividing line between old laptops and the ones we’ll be using in the coming years.
<br /><br />With retina, it’s effectively obsoleted all of its other laptop designs and given its customers — and competitors — something to aspire to.
<br /><br />Putting the stunning retina display aside, you’ll probably be able to find a Windows machine that can beat it on an individual feature, be it speed, connectivity, convenience or storage. But as a package, nothing offers what this machine does.
<br /><br />That kind of focus on the breadth of experience is Apple’s bread and butter, and it’s good it see it applied full force to the category it helped invent: the personal computer.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9hY2VyLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">acer battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9hcHBsZS1sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">apple battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9kZWxsLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">dell battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9hc3VzLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">asus battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9ocC1sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">hp battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9pYm0tbGVub3ZvLWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">ibm battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9zb255LWxhcHRvcC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">sony battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">laptop battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="138db2a4d33f63a76f2aa525495e249b" url=""><![CDATA[U.S. Battery Maker in Financing Deal With a Chinese Firm<br/><br/>A123 Systems, a government-backed maker of batteries for electric vehicles, said Thursday it had reached a final agreement with a Chinese company that will provide emergency capital and eventually acquire a controlling stake. 
<br /><br />The deal with the Chinese company, the Wanxiang Group, one of China’s biggest auto suppliers, is considered crucial to the survival of A123, a centerpiece of the Obama administration’s efforts to support battery manufacturing in the United States.
<br /><br />A123, which is based in Waltham, Mass., said that Wanxiang will provide $25 million immediately. Over time, Wanxiang is expected to invest a total of $465 million and take an 80 percent ownership interest in A123.
<br /><br />David Vieau, the chief executive of A123, said Wanxiang had a record of investing in companies in the United States without changing management or diverting resources to its various Chinese operations.
<br /><br />“We have been hearing about a lot of anxiety regarding Chinese ownership,” Mr. Vieau said in an interview this week. “The fact is their track record in the U.S. has been excellent.”
<br /><br />Some Republican lawmakers have expressed concern about Wanxiang taking control of A123, which received $249 million in grants from the Energy Department in 2009, primarily to build a battery plant in Livonia, a Detroit suburb.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy1tMTUzMC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps m1530 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy1tMTMzMC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps m1330 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy1tMTczMC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps m1730 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xNzEwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1710 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xNTEwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1510 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xMzEwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1310 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xMzIwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1320 battery</a>, 
<br /><br />A123 has tapped about $130 million of its grant. Its Michigan factory is producing batteries for a variety of vehicles, including the Fisker Karma plug-in hybrid luxury car and a coming electric version of General Motors’ Chevrolet Spark subcompact.
<br /><br />But the company stumbled this year when it had to replace defective batteries in the Fisker model. Last week, A123 reported a loss of $82.9 million in the second quarter, up from a loss of $55 million a year earlier.
<br /><br />A123 had been seeking new investors since spring, and was approached by a subsidiary of Wanxiang based in Chicago. The Chinese company owns a variety of manufacturing businesses in the United States that employ a total of 3,000 workers.
<br /><br />But the pending Chinese investment is raising questions in Washington. Two Republican senators, John Thune of South Dakota and Charles E. Grassley of Iowa, sent a letter last week to Steven Chu, the energy secretary, about concerns that American tax dollars would benefit A123’s new Chinese investor.
<br /><br />After the deal was revealed last week, the Energy Department said that its grants to A123 were restricted to supporting United States manufacturing jobs.
<br /><br />Mr. Vieau said the Chinese investment would help preserve about 900 jobs at the Livonia plant and provide new international business opportunities for A123.
<br /><br />A123 has struggled mostly because of the slow pace of growth for electric vehicles in the United States. The company is also considerably smaller than Asian competitors that dominate the global battery industry.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g4 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g6 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g7 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS9ocC1sYXB0b3AtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">hp laptop battery</a> 
<br /><br />According to the agreement, A123 will receive its first $25 million investment from Wanxiang this week. Another $50 million will be received upon approval of the deal by the United States Committee on Foreign Investment and the Chinese government.
<br /><br />Wanxiang would provide the bulk by buying debt and warrants that ultimately could be converted into an 80 percent ownership stake.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d2d719c3dd12d295e468678ee88ea8ed" url=""><![CDATA[Laptop Battery not charging Recalibration<br/><br/>If your MacBook (any model) is not charging to 100%, it may need to be recalibrated. Apple explains how to do this, but basically it comes down to three steps:
<br /><br />Fully charge your MacBook (and leave it charged for about 2 hours)
<br /><br />Fully drain your MacBook (by using it on battery until it turns off)
<br /><br />Fully recharge your MacBook again.
<br /><br />That should help the battery indicator recalibrate so that it shows the correct information. If it doesn't, you might need to reset the System Management Controller (SMC), but in most case I've found that a simple recalibration will work.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww.</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1xLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./q</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1zLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./s</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1iLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./b</a> 
<br /><br />When I recalibrate, I prefer to make sure that my MacBook will not be interrupted at all either during the drain or the recharge period, so I will leave it on overnight while running Caffeine set to &quot;Indefinitely&quot; and let it really, fully discharge. Then, the next day, I will plug it in and let it charge through the workday, again running Caffeine to keep it awake. (Note: Caffeine will also keep your screensaver from running. You might prefer to go to System Preferences Energy Saver and set &quot;Computer Sleep&quot; to &quot;Never&quot;. I use an external monitor at my office with the MacBook closed, and simply turn off the power to the external monitor if I'm not going to be using it for awhile.)
<br /><br />Determining the health of your MacBook's battery
<br /><br />If recalibrating doesn't seem to help, you might need to check your battery's overall health. The easiest way to do that is to run the &quot;System Information.app&quot; found in /Applications/Utilities/. Note: &quot;System Information.app&quot; is the name of the app in Lion and Mountain Lion. Previous versions of Mac OS X called it &quot;System Profiler.app.&quot;
<br /><br />You can also launch &quot;System Information&quot; (or &quot;System Profiler&quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /> by going to the Apple Menu, look for &quot;About This Mac&quot; and then hold down the Option/Alt key and it will change (see image below).
<br /><br />Or, for maximum geek points, paste this into Terminal.app, which will run the &quot;system_profiler&quot; tool at the command line, but limit it to just the information relevant to the battery status.
<br /><br />Whichever method you use, look for the Cycle Count and the Condition as shown in the image at the top of this article.
<br /><br />Like religion, politics, and text editors, battery calibration is a topic which lends itself to vigorous debate and arguments across the Internet. Some of it is based on outdated information, some of it is just incorrect, and some of it may simply not be applicable to your situation. I would encourage you to read Apple's official information and guidance on the subject as your starting point to understand how to best care for and maintain your laptop's battery.
<br /><br />Lithium-ion polymer batteries, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy1tMTUzMC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps m1530 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy1tMTMzMC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps m1330 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXhwcy1tMTczMC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">xps m1730 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xNzEwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1710 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xNTEwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1510 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xMzEwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1310 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLXZvc3Ryby0xMzIwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vostro 1320 battery</a>, 
<br /><br />Calibrating your computer's battery for best performance
<br /><br />Determining Battery Cycle Count
<br /><br />Resetting the System Management Controller (SMC)
<br /><br />Finally, a reminder that if you don't like Apple's &quot;menu extra&quot; for monitoring your battery status, you might want to try SlimBatteryMonitor, a free alternative which I recently reviewed.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cf70ad6107cb5a90227a5c23b9cb6d9b" url=""><![CDATA[What is Baby Monitors<br/><br/>A baby monitor transmits sound, and sometimes video images, from one room to another, so you can keep tabs on your little one from any part of the house. Monitors have two parts – a transmitter and a receiver – and are particularly useful with infants who sleep in a room apart from their parents and wake up at night for feeding, changing, or comforting. Monitors are great for naps, too – you can be occupied in another part of your home and hear when your child wakes up and wants you.
<br /><br />For best results, place audio monitors within 10 feet of your baby's crib so they'll pick up every sigh, gurgle, and wail. You can carry the receiver around the house or leave it plugged in by your bed.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zZWN1cml0eS1hbmQtc3VydmVpbGxhbmNlL2JhYnktbW9uaXRvci5odG1s" target="_blank">Baby monitors</a> generally help mothers oversee the baby without being stuck inside the baby’s room all day. Through this, mothers are able to do what must be done around the house thereby accomplishing a lot. From the time baby monitors have been first released, countless of innovations have been made. 
<br /><br />A variety of products not only permits auditory signals to be heard but even allow the mother from the receiver’s end to visualize their baby and play music to soothe the baby even from a distance. To this date, they are no longer just an electric device to keep an eye when the baby cries but offers a number of advantages in ascertaining the baby’s well-being. 
<br /><br />Some top of the trade devices have sensors placed under the baby’s mattress that detects even the most subtle of movements including the baby’s breathing. When no movement is detected for a span of 20 seconds or if breathing is below the medically accepted rate, an alarm is triggered thereby notifying mommy. 
<br /><br />This proves to be truly useful in perceiving life threatening conditions. Whatever type moms choose to have, it will contribute enormously in making mom’s life easier. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zZWN1cml0eS1hbmQtc3VydmVpbGxhbmNlL2JhYnktbW9uaXRvci5odG1s" target="_blank">Baby monitors</a> are definitely mom’s best friend.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="882182a32b95d31b8bda56471fe986d5" url=""><![CDATA[Batteries Someday Be Possible in Your Shoelaces<br/><br/>LG Chem might not be as well-known as its parent, but that doesn’t mean the branch isn’t important. A new development by the South Korean electronics company could have major potential down the road.
<br /><br />What is it A whole new form factor, a battery that is a wire. The cable-like wire battery is just really small and yet is designed with flexibility in mind. You can bend it, twist it, no problem. Right now they are a few millimeters in diameter, but the idea is to continue to shrink the size of the battery as time passes.
<br /><br />During testing researchers powered an iPod Nano for 10 hours using a 25 centimeter long strand do accomplish it. LG is hoping to mass produce the technology by 2017, which gives them several years to work on shrinking the size of the wire-battery.
<br /><br />The future potential is actually pretty huge. A small wire battery could ‘wrap’ around the inside of a smartphone or tablet case and could even pair itself with a flexible screen and casing. Even more futuristic ideas include smart clothes that have wired battery strands within them that are so tiny you won’t notice them. The point They could power smart functions on the clothes or even work as a wireless charging back-up system for other electronic devices.
<br /><br />While some of these more advanced uses might be decades off, we only have about 5 years to wait before LG attempts to mass produce these things. The future looks bright when it comes to technological progress, that much is apparent.
<br /><br />Read More:
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">laptop battery</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE0NDAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">Inspiron 1440 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE3NTAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">Inspiron 1750 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWs0NTBuLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Dell K450N Battery</a> 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9hc3VzLWc3M2p3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">ASUS G73JW Battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWxhdGl0dWRlLWU1NDIwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Latitude E5420 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWxhdGl0dWRlLWU2NDIwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Latitude E6420 battery</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE1NjQtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">Inspiron 1564 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWprdmM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Dell JKVC5 Battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8dd7eaa125f2ed7123ccd6a182c2ebc5" url=""><![CDATA["Kids along with Cameras" gets to away in order<br/><br/>ArtWorks! lately obtained 10 brand new digital camera models donated through the Photo taking Historic Culture associated with Brand new Britain.
<br /><br />The actual digital cameras are now being utilized meant for the children along with Digital cameras aspect from the &quot;Postcards Through Brand new Bedford: the Photostory Task, inch based on the information discharge through ArtWorks!
<br /><br />&quot;On account associated with ArtWorks! I wish to say thanks to the actual Photo taking Historic Culture associated with Brand new Britain for his or her nice gift to aid the actual task as well as purchase the actual creative as well as academic development associated with Brand new Bedford's youngsters, inch stated N Smook, training as well as outreach overseer from ArtWorks!, within the information discharge.
<br /><br />inch... The children along with Digital cameras occasion as well as display is really a huge chance of youngsters to determine their own town along with clean eye. 
<br /><br />Through 6 in order to 7: thirty g. michael. Thurs, September. 13, ArtWorks! and also the &quot;Postcards Through Brand new Bedford: the Photostory Project&quot; coordinators may organize the photo taking pursuit associated with down-town Brand new Bedford. Youthful photography enthusiasts through age range 8 in order to eighteen tend to be asked to consider component as well as publish their own pictures towards the Children along with Digital cameras exhibit planned with regard to Oct within ArtWorks! gallery.
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9jYW5vbi1lb3MtNjBkLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">canon 60d battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9jYW5vbi1uYi00bC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">NB-4l Battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9jYW5vbi1uYi01bC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Canon NB-5L</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9jYW5vbi1scC1lNS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">LP-E5</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9jYW5vbi1scC1lNi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">LP-E6</a> 
<br /><br />A restricted quantity of the actual digital camera models is going to be readily available for children to make use of.
<br /><br />Based on the information discharge, Honest Sophistication, an area digital photographer who had been asked through the task creator in order to be a part of the actual Postcards Through Brand new Bedford task, chose to request their 8-year-old double kids when they had been curiosity about taking part in Children Along with Digital cameras.
<br /><br />Sophistication stated which in order to their shock, these were &quot;very fascinated as well as had been getting excited about venturing out in order to Brand new Bedford to determine what we should like a loved ones might catch. inch Then they put down on the pictures experience with regard to the very first time like a loved ones.
<br /><br />Stated Sophistication, &quot;Without becoming involved with this particular task, I'd possess skipped on this particular wonderful dad as well as boy connecting encounter along with my personal children as well as might have unfamiliar just how much they'd possess loved a good trip such as this. inch
<br /><br />&quot;Postcards Through Brand new Bedford&quot; may be the brainchild associated with Beatriz Oliveira that has joined along with other digital photographer Steve Hodgson as well as ArtWorks! to create this particular task idea alive. Oliveira is really a nearby marketing/events preparing expert as well as Hodgson is really a upon the market CPA as well as previous companion from Hodgson Pratt, Pratt &amp; Saunders.
<br /><br />Related News:
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LW5wLWZoNTAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">NP-FH50</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LW5wLWZnMS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">NP-FG1</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LW5wLWJnMS1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">NP-BG1</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LW5wLWZoNzAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">NP-FH70</a>,<a href="/" target="_blank">sony camcorder battery</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9vbHltcHVzLWxpLTQyYi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Olympus LI-42B</a> 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9uaWtvbi1kMzEwMC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nikon d3100 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9uaWtvbi1kNTEwMC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">nikon d5100 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9uaWtvbi1kOTAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">nikon d90 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9uaWtvbi1kNzBzLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nikon d70s battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9uaWtvbi1kODAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">nikon D80 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kaWdpdGFsLWNhbWVyYS1iYXR0ZXJ5L25pa29uLWRpZ2l0YWwtY2FtZXJhLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">nikon battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b05db5ecee03f3b8b88d00a0ddd60358" url=""><![CDATA[iPhone 5 review: hands on with the new features<br/><br/>Will you want to buy one? Like any of the top-end smartphones with which it's competing, such as the Samsung Galaxy SIII and Nokia's forthcoming Lumia 920, buying the top-end version will be a big commitment.
<br /><br />Two groups of people will be delighted to snap this up: anyone with an iPhone from before September 2010 (so the iPhone 3G, 3GS, or 4); and anyone who wants to get 4G superfast mobile broadband speeds and is with Orange (aka T-Mobile, aka Everything Everywhere). The first group will be delighted to get a new phone; the second, to get really rapid downloads in citiesThe screen isn't bigger than the Samsung Galaxy SIII, and only a side-by-side comparison with the (as yet unreleased) Nokia Lumia will tell how their camera software matches up.
<br /><br />But the iPhone is going to be available later this month — whereas Nokia hasn't given a date yet.
<br /><br />Android users considering a switch will probably enjoy features such as iMessage (the equivalent of BBM, but already bigger because Apple has a larger user base than BlackBerry).
<br /><br />And the software that runs iMessage works on every iPhone since 2009. There's nothing as good as the Siri voice control on any other system. And the simplicity of use is something people clearly like. But if you leave Android or BlackBerry, you'll have to abandon your apps — although the equivalents are almost certain to be available on the Apple App Store. The only difference? You might have to pay for the App Store ones. Android users also like the shortcuts built into the system, which they won't find on the the iPhone.
<br /><br />BlackBerry users meanwhile will miss the keyboard — but they'll like the giant screen. And they'll like and all the apps.The maps software will have to be closely compared against Google's; but the addition of detail on traffic from TomTom means that even though Apple is cutting more its ties to the search giant, the maps look great: during the demonstration Apple showed off an aerial view of Big Ben. Early UK users of the software already say it's great.
<br /><br />The new &quot;lightning&quot; connector, which makes about a billion existing ones obsolete in a flash, isn't going to ruin your life – you'll be able to get adaptors.
<br /><br />If you don't have a smartphone, the cost will look daunting. (Though the prices of the older iPhones has come down substantially.) Samsung's Galaxy S3 is becoming cheaper, and Nokia may be able to compete — once we know the prices. But the key difference there is that neither company designs the software that runs the phone. Samsung uses Google's Android; Nokia, Microsoft's Windows Phone. That limits both in subtle ways.Apple offers a walled garden, it's true – and it's hard to break out once you're inside. Android has the advantage that it offers many different brands, while Windows Phone is borne up almost entirely by Nokia. But with any of these you'll only buy once every couple of years. If the time and the price is right, the iPhone 5 is definitely the most integrated phone out there.
<br /><br />Read More:
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNDM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 436 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNjM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 635 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1lbnZ5LTE1LTExMDAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">HP Envy 15-1100 Battery</a> 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1lbnZ5LTE3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">HP Envy 17 Battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNDM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 435 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNjMwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 630 battery</a> 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNDMxLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">HP Compaq 431 Battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNjMxLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 631 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNjM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 636 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNDMwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 430 battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cf81879842f8d2d502a428b440a392ec" url=""><![CDATA[What To Do For A longer laptop battery life<br/><br/>People hope have long <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">laptop battery</a> life,what to do next for it.Now,There are some suggetion for your hope.
<br /><br />1. Unplug battery after each use.
<br /><br />2.Use the hard drive more than the CD/DVD drive. As power consuming as hard drives are, CD and DVD drives use more power than hard drive. Even having one in the drive can be power consuming. They spin, taking power, even when they are not actively being used. Wherever possible, try to run on virtual drives.
<br /><br />3.Clean battery contacts more often. Clean your battery's metal contacts every couple of months with a cloth moistened with rubbing alcohol. This keeps the transfer of power from your battery more efficient.
<br /><br />4.SHUT OFF the WiFi, if you don't need it. Usually, there is a switch, but sometimes you have to do it in the WIFI config.
<br /><br />5.Battery care. Do not leave a charged <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1lbnZ5LTE3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">HP Envy 17 Battery</a> dormant for long periods of time. Once charged, you should at least use the battery at least once every two to three weeks.
<br /><br />6.Hibernate is better than standby on a laptop. Although placing a laptop in standby mode saves some power and you can instantly resume where you left off, it doesn't save anywhere as much power as the hibernate function does.Hibernating a laptop will actually save more power as it will completely shut down itself .
<br /><br />7.Defragging your hard drive regularly. The faster your hard drive does its work the less demand you are going to put on the hard drive and your battery. Make your hard drive as efficient as possible by defragging it regularly. In Windows XP, you do this by going to &quot;My Computer&quot; and right click on the &quot;C:&quot; drive. Then, select &quot;Properties&quot; In Properties, click Tools. In tools click Defrag Now.
<br /><br />8.Dim the laptop screen. Most laptops come with the ability to dim your laptop screen. Some even come with ways to modify CPU and cooling performance. Cut them down to the lowest level you can tolerate to squeeze out some extra battery life.
<br /><br />9.No background programs. I-tunes, Desktop Search or screensavers, etc. All these add load to the CPU and cut down battery life. Shut down everything that isn't crucial when you're on battery.
<br /><br />10.Cut down on external devices. USB devices &amp; WiFi drain down your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1lbnZ5LTE3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">HP Envy 17 Battery</a> . Remove or shut them down when not in use.
<br /><br />11.Charging devices. If you charge other devices (like your iPod) with your laptop you will quickly wiping out the charge on your laptop battery.
<br /><br />12.Add more RAM memory. This will allow you to process more with the memory your laptop has, rather than relying on virtual memory. Virtual memory results in hard drive use, and is much less power efficient.
<br /><br />13.Laptop temperature down. Your laptop operates more efficiently when it's cooler. Clean out your air vents with a cloth or keyboard cleaner, or laptop cooling fan.
<br /><br />14.Optimize your power options in Windows. Go to Power Options in your windows control panel and set it up so that power usage is optimized (Select the 'max battery' for maximum effect).
<br /><br />15.Multitasking is a bad idea. Do one thing at a time when you're on battery. Rather than working on a spreadsheet, letting your email client run in the background and listening to your latest set of MP3.
<br /><br />16.Reducing laptop demands. Passive activities like email and word processing consume much less power than gaming or playing a DVD.
<br /><br />17.Buy an Energy Star or other efficient laptop. Laptops are getting more and more efficient in nature to the point where some manufacturers are talking about all day long batteries. Picking up a newer more efficient laptop to replace an aging one is usually a quick fix.
<br /><br />18.Memory Effect. If you're using a very old laptop, you'll want to prevent the memory effect will keep the battery healthy by fully charging and then fully discharging it at least once every two to three weeks. Exceptions to the rule are Li-Ion batteries (which most laptops have) which do not suffer from the memory effect.
<br /><br />19.Autosave function is not good. Microsoft Word and Excel's autosave functions are great, but because they keep saving at regular intervals, they work your hard drive harder than it may have to. If you plan to do this, you may want to turn it back on as the battery runs low. While it saves battery life in the beginning, you will want to make sure your work is saved when your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNjMwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 630 battery</a> dies.
<br /><br />20. Less graphics use. You can do this by changing the screen resolution and shutting off fancy graphic drivers. Video cards use as more power today as hard disks.
<br /><br />These are my recommendations, be sure to follow these operations.You will get what you want.
<br /><br />Good luck,everyone.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="764c85a5bd23c0295dfdaefcc6b6ecc8" url=""><![CDATA[Tablets Trump Laptops in High School Classrooms<br/><br/>During its quarterly earnings call on July 24, Apple announced that it sold 500,000 MacBook laptops to schools during the previous quarter—an all-time high for the tech company. It also announced that it had sold 1 million iPads to high schools and colleges, doubling its iPad sales to schools during the same quarter a year ago.
<br /><br />&quot;Education tends to be a conservative institution, but we're not seeing that at all on the iPad,&quot; Apple CEO Tim Cook said on a call with investors. &quot;The adoption of the iPad in education is something I've never seen in any technology.&quot;
<br /><br />The day before Apple's earnings call, News Corporation, the world's second largest media group, unveiled its new K-12 education division, Amplify. Headed by former New York City Public Schools chancellor Joel Klein, the new division is a partnership between News Corporation and AT&amp;T to provide tablet-based learning products. The two companies are launching a pilot program during the 2012-2013 school year, offering 4G tablet devices, Wi-Fi and 4G connectivity, and device management and technical services to select schools across the nation.
<br /><br />&quot;It is our aim to amplify the power of digital innovation to transform teaching and learning and to help schools deliver fundamentally better experiences and results,&quot; Klein said in a press release.
<br /><br />This growth in tablet use has motivated many schools to find ways to integrate the devices inside the classroom—with the goal of offering students the greatest technological advantages in preparation for college, says Michael Singleton, the social studies department head at Florida's Orlando Science Schools, a charter school.
<br /><br />[ <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g4 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g6 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g7 battery</a> ]
<br /><br />&quot;I would say an iPad will one day be the same as a book bag or a ruler or a pencil,&quot; Singleton notes. &quot;I think that the iPad will be an essential component to schools, [and] it's certainly something we can't ignore as a school—we need to embrace it.&quot;
<br /><br />Beginning this fall, all Orlando Science Schools students will be issued an iPad for use at home and at school, Singleton says. But there is a stipulation: Students must keep a still-to-be-determined GPA in order to continue using the iPad; those who fall below the target will forfeit use of the tablet. Teachers will also play a fundamental role in the implementation of tablet devices in the classroom, he notes, as they will be required to include them in their lesson plans.
<br /><br />While some educators may champion this requirement, other high school teachers still favor laptops in the classroom. Amy Schmidbauer, a special education teacher at Boca Ciega High School in Florida's Pinellas County Schools, says she still finds more advantages to using a laptop than a tablet device.
<br /><br />&quot;As far as having to type a paper or make a graph, we have to use laptops because it's so much harder to type [with tablet devices],&quot; Schmidbauer says. &quot;With iPads, too, kids get off task quicker. If I give them an independent assignment on an iPad and I turn my back for one second, they're playing [a game].&quot;
<br /><br />Many of the issues teachers have faced using iPads in the classroom can be solved through proper training, notes Joel Backon, director of academic technology at Choate Rosemary Hall, a coeducational boarding and day school in Connecticut. Backon will be overseeing iPad training for teachers at The Choate School, and he says most teachers have found iPads to be less intimidating to use than laptops after spending time with the tablet device.
<br /><br />&quot;Primarily, they're not dealing with an operating system you'd find on a laptop—it's pretty much invisible on an iPad, and all they're dealing with are the apps,&quot; Backon says. &quot;Some teachers had a little trouble adjusting to the touch screen, but over time I think they got used to that. Overall, the benefits of having a touch screen far outweigh whatever little hassles we may run into with it.&quot;
<br /><br />[ <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww.</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1xLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./q</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1zLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./s</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9zb255LXZncC1icHMxMy1iLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">vgp-bpwww./b</a> ]
<br /><br />Ultimately, the biggest adjustment for teachers will not be in understanding the functions of tablet devices but in incorporating them into their teaching styles, Backon notes.
<br /><br />&quot;Most teachers are accustomed to a teacher-centric classroom where the teacher is the center of the classroom and the giver of knowledge,&quot; he says. &quot;Now, the iPad allows us to put the responsibility of learning into the hands of the students.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="787764f53b541f36f7eb3ec074b51230" url=""><![CDATA[How to ensure that the lithium battery longevity<br/><br/>If the user wishes to extend the using time of battery, in addition, the quality of the charger must be to ensure proper charging techniques, are also essential, because of the poor quality of the charger or charging the wrong methods will affect the using time and cycle life of the battery. The following is charging techniques:
<br /><br />1. Battery factory, manufacturers have carried the activation and precharge batteries have more than electricity, the friend said battery charge in accordance with the time period of adjustment, standby is still a serious shortage, assuming the battery is indeed genuine battery, in which case adjustment period should be extended further 3-5 complete charge and discharge.
<br /><br />2. If you buy a new mobile phone battery is lithium-ion, 3 to 5 times charge commonly referred to as a period of adjustment, shall be filled with more than 14 hours to fully activate the lithium-ion activity. Lithium-ion batteries, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE1MjUtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">inspiron 1525 battery</a> have no memory effect, but there is a strong inert, should be given full activation can guarantee that used to achieve the best performance.
<br /><br />?3. Some automated intelligent rapid charger when the lights change, only 90% full. The charger will automatically change with the slow charging the battery is full. Best battery is full, otherwise it will shorten the usage time.
<br /><br />4. Before charging, lithium batteries do not need special discharge, discharge improper battery will be damaged. Charging as much as possible to slow charging, reduce the fast charge mode; time should not exceed 24 hours. Battery after three to five times a full charge and discharge cycles of its internal chemicals will be &quot;activated&quot; to achieve the best results.
<br /><br />5. Please use the original or the reputation of a good brand of charger, lithium batteries use lithium <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE1NDUtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">inspiron 1545 battery</a> charger, and follow the instructions, otherwise it will damage the battery, and even dangerous.
<br /><br />6. Many users are often in charge when the phone is open, In fact, this will be very easy to damage the phone life, because in the process of charging the cell phone circuit boards will be fever, may produce an instant return foreign phone current damage to the phone's internal parts.
<br /><br />7. The life of the battery charge repeated charge and discharge times, it should avoid the battery is more than power, this will shorten the life of the battery. Phone off for more than 7 days, the first mobile phone battery is fully discharged, adequate electricity and then use.
<br /><br />8. Phone battery self-discharge when not in use nickel-metal hydride battery daily discharge about 1% of the remaining capacity lithium <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE1NDUtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">inspiron 1545 battery</a> daily discharge of 0.2% to 0.3%. To charge the battery, try to use a dedicated outlet, do not share the outlet charger with TV and other home appliances.
<br /><br />9. Although the phone within the coverage area of ??the network, but charging the phone off, the phone has been unable to accept and make calls. At this point, can not use the phone through transfer functions, the phone transferred to the fixed phone on the side, in order to prevent loss of calls, also applies when the phone is not in the network coverage area or weak signal can not be connected.
<br /><br />10. Do not expose the battery to heat or cold day like a dog, you should not put the phone in the car, to withstand the scorching sun exposure; or get air-conditioned rooms, a place on the cold air blowing straight. When charging, the battery a little heat is normal, but can not get it to weather the high temperature &quot;suffering&quot;. In order to avoid this situation from occurring, it is best at room temperature for charging, and not in the phone cover anything.
<br /><br />11. Nickel-cadmium (N iCd) must ensure that the battery is charging the battery is completely discharged, recharge must ensure that the battery is fully charged.
<br /><br />12. If the mobile phone battery is placed too long and did not use, it is best to phone the maintenance department to apply to the battery for a living processing, can use a constant voltage direct current to adjust the voltage is 5 to 6V, current 500 ~ 600mA reverse connected battery . Note that the liberalization of touch up repeated three times, after such treatment, and then the original charger &quot;adjustment&quot; charge.
<br /><br />13. Not charging the longer the better, stop charging full <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWd3MjQwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Dell GW240 Battery</a> protection circuit shall be made, otherwise the battery will affect performance due to heat or overheating.
<br /><br />14. The lithium-ion battery must use a dedicated charger, otherwise may reach saturation, impact on its performance. After charging, should avoid placing more than 12 hours on the charger, the battery and the phone do not have to be long-term separation.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eb073f504a8f70df580ffd7121a4c3db" url=""><![CDATA[Envy m4 and Sleekbook Pavilion 14 and 15 Review<br/><br/>HP has announced a trio of new Windows 8 laptops, including a beefed up HP Envy M4 and two Sleekbook notebooks.
<br /><br />The M4 is the cream of this particular crop, with its brushed-aluminium looks and 14-inch HD display housing a third-gen Intel Core processor and optional Wi-Di for purshing HD images and videos to an external display wirelessly.
<br /><br />HP's Beats love continues apace with the Envy m4 offering a subwoofer and two speakers to make the most of Dre's audio enhancements.
<br /><br />And, as usual, there's a bunch of additional features with terrible names like HP's ProtectSmart that helps prevent data loss if you drop your laptop, as well as a cooling system and some extra security know-how.
<br /><br />If that sounds like something you need in your life, the HP Envy M4 is set for release on October 26 (three guesses what OS it'll be running), with a US price of $899.99 (around ?555 but UK pricing is TBC).
<br /><br />Marillion pavilion
<br /><br />The lower-priced, lower-specced options are the HP Pavilion Sleekbook 14 and 15, which HP is touting as 'ultrathin' in style. Available in &quot;sparkling black&quot; and &quot;ruby red&quot;, the 14- and 15-inch laptops come with optional bumps like up to 1TB of storage.
<br /><br />Both models offer Nvidia graphics, but the 14-inch edition is rocking an AMD processor, while the 15-incher comes with Intel innards with hyper-threading technology to aid multi-tasking.
<br /><br />The HP Pavilion Sleekbook 14 and 15 PCs will start at $499.99 (around ?310) and $559.99 (about ?350), respectively and should hit the US on October 26.
<br /><br />We've spoken to HP which confirms that the new laptops will be making their way to the UK, although pricing and availability are yet to be confirmed. Stay tuned.
<br /><br />Update: UK pricing for the two Sleekbooks has now been confirmed; the HP Pavilion Sleekbook 14 and 15 PCs start at ?429 and will be available from October.
<br /><br />Related News:
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNC1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g4 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNi1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g6 battery</a>,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1wYXZpbGlvbi1nNy1iYXR0ZXJ5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">hp g7 battery</a> 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNDM2LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 436 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNjM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 635 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1lbnZ5LTE1LTExMDAtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">HP Envy 15-1100 Battery</a> 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1lbnZ5LTE3LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">HP Envy 17 Battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNDM1LWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 435 battery</a>, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9ocC1jb21wYXEtNjMwLWJhdHRlcnkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">hp compaq 630 battery</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cffbfd889c8787b6d379d2767abaf817" url=""><![CDATA[Lenovo Launches Covertible Laptop computers<br/><br/>Chinese language COMPUTER huge Lenovo revealed Wednesday inside a Ny occasion a number of laptops which are convertible in to pills, wishing which it's versatility as well as fashionable strategy can make the impressive impact within the technology marketplace.
<br /><br />Within an job interview along with Cnet.com writer Shara Tibken, Lenovo president of North American Davic Schmoock talked about the flexibility of their new laptops and his optimistic view on the future of Lenovo as the second biggest PC maker and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25ld2JhdHRlcnkuY29tLmF1" target="_blank">laptop battery</a> in the world.
<br /><br />“What individuals would like is actually versatility. Individuals require, at the conclusion from the day time, a completely working COMPUTER because their own main gadget. However they additionally would like the flexibleness to utilize a pill, ” stated Schmoock, that launched 4 laptop computers convertible in order to pills like the IdeaTab Lynx and also the IdeaPad Yoga exercise 13. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE1NDUtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">inspiron 1545 battery</a> 
<br /><br />At the same time, Endpoint Systems Affiliates primary analyzer Roger Kay stated which Lenovo is actually utilizing these types of convertible laptop computers in order to contend with additional technology businesses.
<br /><br />“They’re attempting to include the actual range associated with type elements that may be successful, ” he or she stated. “Lenovo doesn’t truly understand what may earn, as well as nor will other people, ” stated kay.
<br /><br />Overseer associated with Lenovo’s worldwide item team Chris Hortensius stated the actual Home windows RT Gadget, the actual ThinkPad Yoga exercise 11, is going to be launched within Dec as the Yoga exercise 13 and also the ThinkPad Distort is going to be obtainable in United states marketplace upon Oct twenty six.
<br /><br />“We possess a item preparedness period, which specific [Windows RT] item, all of us experienced, wasn't very prepared, ” stated Hortensius.
<br /><br />In spite of Lenovo’s confidence regarding their own most recent make of laptop computers, a number of technology analyzer thinks convertible products is really a ‘compromise’ to finish person.
<br /><br />“Anything may have to converge, however the issue is which items tend to be regarding trade-offs, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGlyZHNob3BwaW5nLmNvbS9kZWxsLWluc3Bpcm9uLTE1MjUtYmF0dGVyeS5odG1s" target="_blank">inspiron 1525 battery</a> and also you start to help to make trade-offs to the stage exactly where that which you have remaining doesn’t make sure you anybody, ” Prepare stated previously this season regarding the thought of MacBook-iPad crossbreed gadget. “You may converge the toaster along with a fridge, however those activities are most likely not really heading end up being satisfying towards the person. ”.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>