<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="14">
		<document id="484e4a1f2dce2fb577654a9b0e41d351" url=""><![CDATA[Spain As A Tourist Destination<br/><br/>Spain is a country in Europe lying in the southern part. From Tarifa, one can get to see Africa from a 556 view. Spain is a great country whose history date from way back. It has great lessons to tell and a visit here will be not only exciting but also very educative at the same time. This makes Spain a great country to tour for people who love exploration and adventure. The country has a lot of scenic places and also heritage sites that will interest many tourists.
<br /><br />A lot of people from all over the world love to have vacations in Spain. The people who visit this land are mostly from Britain, America as well as other parts of Europe. Being a member of the EU, Spain’s economy is well developed and a lot of resources have been dedicated to creating facilities for the thousands of tourists that come to visit the land. Most of the tourist comes to visit Spain over summer and it is always a great experience.
<br /><br />This great land attracts tourists owing to the fact that it has some very amazing landscapes. The landscapes are so amazing that they will take your breath away. 
<br /><br />Spain is also home to some of the best beaches in the world owing to the fact that it has island territories and is bordered by to great oceans. The beaches are beautiful and the atmosphere is multi cultural making one feel immediately at home in the surrounding.
<br /><br />There are many places to visit and even more things to see when you visit Spain. There are also a lot of things to engage in during a visit. You will get to see things you have only read in books or visit places you have only read in history books making the experience all the more intriguing. 
<br /><br />To the north, there are great mountains surrounded by green patches. This helps you enjoy the scenery in a surrounding that is not only healthy but also very beautiful. For anyone who loves nature and enjoys hiking, the Pyreens are the place to be.
<br /><br />The northern part of Spain has seven provinces. In this area, four languages are spoken. All the four are very distinctive. The official language is Castilian. This is then followed by Basque then Galician, Catalan and finally Valencia languages. On the south of Spain is where the capital city is located, Madrid. There is exotic architecture found here that you will most definitely enjoy. There you also get to see ancient foot prints that were left by the Romans. 
<br /><br />The oldest university in Spain is situated in Salamanca. The place is worth visiting as Valencia and Murcia are on the east. In short, Spain is a great place to visit.
<br /><br />Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fvakantiehuizenspanje.villamar.nl"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://vakantiehuizenspanje.villamar.nl</a></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9jYWxvbmdl" target="_blank">click here</a> to plan your holiday
<br /><br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3VyYXJ0aWNsZS5jby51ay9zcGFpbnMtbW9zdC1mYW1vdXMtcGxhY2Vz" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yourarticle.co.uk%2Fspains-most-famous-places"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.yourarticle.co.uk/spains-most-famous-places</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N0aWNreXRhZ3MuaW4vdXNlci9oaXN0b3J5L3Njb3R0bmFzaDcv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstickytags.in%2Fuser%2Fhistory%2Fscottnash7%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stickytags.in/user/history/scottnash7/</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="af8602540222f521ad37115fc8f03829" url=""><![CDATA[Spains Most Famous Places<br/><br/>Spain is one of the most popular countries in the world. It is a commercial centre as well as a tourist hub. It has beaches, mountains, sceneries and heritage sites that make it attract many visitors each year. Spain shares the penisula of Iberia with Portugal. It is affiliated to the Balearic Islands. Its access to the coast line makes beach tourism possible. This attracts many people especially those seeking summer holidays.
<br /><br />Spain is bordered by the Mediterranean Sea as well as the Atlantic thus increasing its access to beaches. Canary Islands are also in its territory. So if you are looking for an exotic place to go on tour and an educative one at the same time, Spain is the ideal location for you. There are a lot of activities you can engage in as well as places for hiking and sightseeing. It is also a perfect place for religious people and those interested in history in general.
<br /><br />Spain’s main attraction is her beaches. That should not make one overlook the fact that it is diverse in culture and geography. There are lush meadows, snowy mountains, hills and green valleys. Those are located in the northern parts of Spain. The south is however almost a desert region.
<br /><br />The northern side hosts the charming creeks while the western and southern sides have beaches that are white sanded. Canary Island has black sand beaches. This is very exotic. This makes the canary island even more interesting. The sand is black owing to the fact that canary island is volcanic.
<br /><br />Over the years, Spain has become an important part of tourism. It’s actually the 3rd of the most popular destination in the whole of Europe. 
<br /><br />The capital of Spain is Madrid. Its location is perfect for communication with all other Spanish provinces. It holds the countries government. The historical royal palace is also located here and is one of the must visit places of Spain. The cities design is also awesome and it is always a pleasure walking on the streets of Madrid. The streets seem to converge at the city center.
<br /><br />Barcelona is a great city too and is tourist destination that is really celebrated. The architecture in this place is just magnificent, the works of Gaudi, one of the greatest architects that ever lived. You can enjoy water sports in this region as well as access the beaches.
<br /><br />Other places include Córdoba with its monuments, Costa del Sol, Torremolinos and Marbella. The tours you can have here include shopping, Gibraltar for sightseeing as well as the country side.
<br /><br />Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVucG9sbGVuY2EudmlsbGFtYXIubmwvZmluZEFsbFZpbGxhcy5waHA/ZmlsdGVyPVBvbGxlbmNhJmFtcDtsYW5nPW5s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fvakantiehuizenpollenca.villamar.nl%2FfindAllVillas.php%3Ffilter%3DPollenca%26amp%3Blang%3Dnl"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://vakantiehuizenpollenca.villamar.nl/findAllVillas.php?filter=Pollenca&amp;lang=nl</a></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9ibGFuZXM_" target="_blank">Visit this</a> to plan your holiday
<br /><br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3VyYXJ0aWNsZS5jby51ay9zcGFpbi10b3VyaXN0LWRlc3RpbmF0aW9u" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.yourarticle.co.uk%2Fspain-tourist-destination"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.yourarticle.co.uk/spain-tourist-destination</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29wZW50YWdzLmluL3VzZXIvaGlzdG9yeS9zY290dG5hc2g3Lw__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fopentags.in%2Fuser%2Fhistory%2Fscottnash7%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://opentags.in/user/history/scottnash7/</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f0b0b302cd2e728123f3ace9c50d6305" url=""><![CDATA[Spain’s Geography Islands Climate And Their Roles In Tour<br/><br/>Spain is ranked as 52nd country in the world in terms of size. It covers an area of 505,992 square km. Mt Teide is Spain’s highest peak and the volcano that’s ranked third in the category of largest mountains in the world from its base. Its latitudes are 26° and 44°N. The longitudes are 19° and 5°E.
<br /><br />Spain is a highly mountainous region and also has some major rivers. The mainland especially has very many mountains and mountain chains that are ideal for skiing most especially during the winter period. The mainland has high plateaus and mountain chains. The Pyrenees are the major ranges but there are others such as Sistema Penibetico, Sierra Morena, Montes de Toledo, Sistema Central, Sistema Iberico and Cordillera Cantabrica.
<br /><br />Some of the peaks here are so high that they have received international recognition. Spain’s highest point is Teide which is an active volcano of 3,718 meters and is located in the Canary Islands. The most popular plateau is Meseta Central found at the heart of Spain.
<br /><br />Spain’s major rivers include the Guadalquivir, the Guadiana, the Duero, the Ebro and the Tagus. Spain’s largest plains are the Guadalquivir in Andalusia. These are found at the coastal region of Spain.
<br /><br />Spain has a lot of territorial islands some of which are not inhabited.  The Mediterranean Sea hosts the Balearic Islands. The great Atlantic Ocean homes Spain’s most popular islands, the Canary Islands.  The uninhabited islands are mostly in the Mediterranean Sea in the popular Strait of Gibraltar called Plazas de Soberania. Some of the islands here include Pheasant Island, Isla Perejil, Isle of Alboran Alhcemas and Chafarine islands. All these islands are a major tourist attraction contributing greatly to Spain’s economy. 
<br /><br />Climate is yet another very important aspect of Spain. There are three climates in Spain. They are Mediterranean, Semi arid and oceanic climates. These are dependent on the specific locations within Spain and are categorized as such. 
<br /><br />The Mediterranean climate is evidenced by warm dry summers. This type of climate dominates the peninsula. Examples of the areas that experience this type of climate in Spain include Leon, Madrid and Burgos. These places attract a lot of visitors during summer.
<br /><br />Semiarid climate is experienced in the Spain’s southeastern quarter. It is prevalent in Ebro and Murcia valleys. Dry seasons go beyond summer. 
<br /><br />The oceanic climate is prevalent in the north. The climate is greatly influenced by the ocean and the diverse climates within the same region are what a number of people come to witness.
<br /><br />Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVucGxheWFkYXJvLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL2ZpbmRBbGxWaWxsYXMucGhwP2ZpbHRlcj1QbGF5YStkJTI3QXJvJmFtcDtsYW5nPW5s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fvakantiehuizenplayadaro.villamar.nl%2FfindAllVillas.php%3Ffilter%3DPlaya%2Bd%2527Aro%26amp%3Blang%3Dnl"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://vakantiehuizenplayadaro.villamar.nl/findAllVillas.php?filter=Playa+d%27Aro&amp;lang=nl</a></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9tZW5vcmNh" target="_blank">Visit Site</a> to plan your holiday
<br /><br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hcnRpY2xldXMuY29tL2FydGljbGVzLzEwNzIwOS8xL1NwYWlucy1HZW9ncmFwaHktLUlzbGFuZHMtQ2xpbWF0ZS1BbmQtVGhlaXItUm9sZXMtSW4tVG91cmlzbS9QYWdlMS5odG1s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.articleus.com%2Farticles%2F107209%2F1%2FSpains-Geography--Islands-Climate-And-Their-Roles-In-Tourism%2FPage1.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.articleus.com/articles/107209/1/Spains-Geography--Islands-Climate-And-Their-Roles-In-Tourism/Page1.html</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovLzUyLmNvLm56L3VzZXIucGhwP2xvZ2luPXNjb3R0bmFzaDcmYW1wO3ZpZXc9cHVibGlzaGVkWy91cmw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2F52.co.nz%2Fuser.php%3Flogin%3Dscottnash7%26amp%3Bview%3Dpublished"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://52.co.nz/user.php?login=scottnash7&amp;view=published</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="987202be316145a962ecd87a1b84d965" url=""><![CDATA[A Memorable Tour of Spain<br/><br/>Spain is a wonderful country for any kind of tourism. The fact that it has all the features fit for a great tourism destination makes it among the most visited and the most popular countries in the world. A tour of the country is definitely bound to be interesting, memorable and enjoyable in every aspect. 
<br /><br />The country has numerous regions which have cities and towns within then. The most amazing part of the country is that no matter which region, city or town you choose to base your tour, you are bound to get the very best of memories from your stay no matter how much time you have to spend. The areas have great features and attractions making the great spots for a vacation or a Spanish tour. The attractions in the country are well wrapped into the islands, beaches, monuments, cathedrals, churches, museum, parks, lagoons, mountains and even amusement parks among many other features. 
<br /><br />When planning for a memorable tour of Spain, the choice of the best spot is of great importance. It is important to remember that the kind of experience you get and also the activities you will be exposed to will depend on the area you have chosen to base your tour. While some of these areas are great for beach kind of holidays, some are ideal for green holidays especially for nature lovers. You of course want to end up in the best place for your kind of experience thus making it important to make a wise informed decision. 
<br /><br />It is also important to remember that the facilities differ from one place to another. You will be exposed to traditional simple accommodation facilities to the most modern and luxurious ones depending on the Spanish area you are in. It is important to check on the facilities that you will be exposed during the tour of Spain to ensure that you are getting the best in relation to what you value or what you like most. Fortunately, most of the areas have various options that you can choose from. 
<br /><br />It is also advisable that you choose a travel time that will expose you to some of the best events of the regions. The timing is also important since some areas could be open for certain periods of time in the year and you therefore want to get to the area when you have the perfect chance to enjoy everything that it has to offer you. 
<br /><br />Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuYnVnZXIudmlsbGFtYXIubmwvZmluZEFsbFZpbGxhcy5waHA/ZmlsdGVyPUJ1Z2VyJmFtcDtsYW5nPW5s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fvakantiehuizenbuger.villamar.nl%2FfindAllVillas.php%3Ffilter%3DBuger%26amp%3Blang%3Dnl"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://vakantiehuizenbuger.villamar.nl/findAllVillas.php?filter=Buger&amp;lang=nl</a></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9tYWxsb3JjYS8_" target="_blank">Click Website</a> to plan your holiday
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dvYXJ0aWNsZXMuY29tL2FydGljbGUvQVJDSElURUNUVVJBTC1DT05UUklCVVRJT05TLVRPLVNQQUlOLVMtVE9VUklTTS82OTY5MjEzLw__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgoarticles.com%2Farticle%2FARCHITECTURAL-CONTRIBUTIONS-TO-SPAIN-S-TOURISM%2F6969213%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://goarticles.com/article/ARCHITECTURAL-CONTRIBUTIONS-TO-SPAIN-S-TOURISM/6969213/</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2N3dXN0cmluZ3MuY29tL3VzZXIucGhwP2xvZ2luPXNjb3R0bmFzaDcmYW1wO3ZpZXc9aGlzdG9yeQ__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcwustrings.com%2Fuser.php%3Flogin%3Dscottnash7%26amp%3Bview%3Dhistory"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://cwustrings.com/user.php?login=scottnash7&amp;view=history</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c11ef5067b36966dce9fc18fccf814cc" url=""><![CDATA[ARCHITECTURAL CONTRIBUTIONS TO SPAIN’S TOURISM<br/><br/>Spain is a country that is very popular as a tourist destination. It attracts millions of tourists every year. There are a lot of places worth seeing and visiting in Spain for the discerning visitors. All tourists have something to look forward to while in Spain and can actually be guaranteed of a fabulous time in the region. There are many contributors to tourism in Spain that has led to the growth in the region’s popularity as a destination.
<br /><br />Spain architectural works are some of the most popular and unique styles in the world. The major contributors were the early settlers as well as religion. Spain’s architecture also has a major role in the history of the country and actually a lot can be learnt from the existence of some of the works that still stand to date. Spain’s architecture is very different from others in the world. Jews, Christians, Muslims, the Moorish people and the Romans played a major role in the development of architecture in the region.
<br /><br />Some of the most popular designs are Tarragona and Segovia canals, Cordoba and Alcantara bridges as well as the Merida Theater. Architecture has greatly improved the value of Spain over the years. The Spanish architectural wonders include the mosque in Cordoba that has been standing since the 10th century and the structures known as Hispano Moresque. The mosques were the great works of the moors. Spain greatly benefits from these structures today as they attract a lot of tourists yearly.
<br /><br />Jews and Christians also made their contribution in the architectural designs found in Spain today. The art lovers are sure to have a great time exploring all the great works of architecture that revolve around tourism. The Jew and Christian designs have been merged to make some quite spectacular unique designs. The works include the Santa Maria church, The Alhambra, the Alcazar, as well as the Christian Cathedral. All these churches have great designs. There are also places in Spain that are consider as most holy and still receive their major share of tourists.
<br /><br />Spain also has designs that can be termed as legendary. They include: the mingle between gothic styles and Moorish designs, Mudejar, and Mozarabic. There is ornamentation on the architectural works that attract the eyes of most visitors leaving them awed.
<br /><br />Gaudi works are also very popular in Spain and they can be seen in most places in Spain. All these places play a major role in the tourism sector attracting a great number of tourists every year.
<br /><br />Get more information on<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVucm9qYWxlcy52aWxsYW1hci5ubC9maW5kQWxsVmlsbGFzLnBocD9maWx0ZXI9Um9qYWxlcyZhbXA7YW1wO2FtcDtsYW5nPW5s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fvakantiehuizenrojales.villamar.nl%2FfindAllVillas.php%3Ffilter%3DRojales%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Blang%3Dnl"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://vakantiehuizenrojales.villamar.nl/findAllVillas.php?filter=Rojales&amp;amp;amp;lang=nl</a></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9pYml6YS8_" target="_blank">Read More</a> to plan your holiday
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hcnRpY2xlc2Jhc2UuY29tL2Rlc3RpbmF0aW9ucy1hcnRpY2xlcy9hLW1lbW9yYWJsZS10b3VyLW9mLXNwYWluLTYxOTYzODcuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.articlesbase.com%2Fdestinations-articles%2Fa-memorable-tour-of-spain-6196387.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.articlesbase.com/destinations-articles/a-memorable-tour-of-spain-6196387.html</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3B1YmxpYy5zaXRlam90LmNvbS9zY290dG5hc2g3Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fpublic.sitejot.com%2Fscottnash7.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://public.sitejot.com/scottnash7.html</a></a>.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a110851a2ea6f71274eedf8bb8728544" url=""><![CDATA[FESTIVALS IN SPAIN<br/><br/>There are lot festivities that are celebrated in Spain. Some are quite traditional and have been celebrated since time immemorial. These festivals are very unique and can only be seen in the land. All neighborhoods, cities, towns and regions have saints that are attributed feasts that are accorded a lot of importance. The festivals are celebrated in a religious manner every year. Some of the traditions are only celebrated in Spain. 
<br /><br />Bull fighting is a festival widely celebrated in Spain. The frequency of this occasion that used to be of great importance to the Spanish people has greatly declined over the years. This follows the intensive works of animal activists who name the festival as oppressive to the animals. It is a major part of Spain’s history as well as the traditions that are common with the Spaniards. The sport is quite dangerous as a lot of harm can be done to either the animal or even the rider. This activity has been reduced to a few occasions in the present and anyone who wishes to witness the fights must try making an early ticket booking so as not to miss the opportunity. 
<br /><br />Christmas festivities are common in all regions of the world. In Spain however, there are additional rituals that are involved with the festivities. There is a bonfire that is associated with Christmas in Spain. It initiates the Christmas celebrations. The celebration was initially to celebrate the shortest winter day. Spaniards jump over each other during this period symbolizing the overcoming of illness. They do not eat the Christmas dinner before midnight and the people stay awake for the rest of the night singing Christmas carols for the rest of the night so as not to waste the “goodnight” with sleep. 
<br /><br />There are celebrations dedicated to saints that are specific to different regions. There are feasts dedicated to patron saints as well as many other traditions that are quite different from any others in the world. 
<br /><br />Palm Sunday is also accorded a lot of attention and the celebrations in Spain are quite major. Palm Sunday sees the people go to church while the little ones are made to carry some palm leaves that are in turn blessed by the priests. Ash Wednesday is also important in the Spanish calendar. Ashes are applied as a sign of patience and to remind everyone that we are from the ashes and to ashes shall we return. Fasting marks the lent season. All this festivities are very attractive to pilgrims and generally to a number of tourists.
<br /><br />If you are looking for a luxurious villa for holidays <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9jYWxvbmdlLw__" target="_blank">Visit Here</a> and Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sLw__" target="_blank">huis te huur spanje</a>.
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dlbmVjYXN0LmNvbS9BZHZpY2UvZmVzdGl2YWwtaW4tc3BhaW4tNzAwNjMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgenecast.com%2FAdvice%2Farchitectural-contributions-to-spain-s-tourism-69519.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://genecast.com/Advice/architectural-contributions-to-spain-s-tourism-69519.html</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JsaW5rbGlzdC5jb20vdXNlcnMvc2NvdHRuYXNo" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblinklist.com%2Fusers%2Fscottnash"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://blinklist.com/users/scottnash</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9a271856ed58bf6596376d9cf5828d8c" url=""><![CDATA[Island Destination in Spain<br/><br/>Bearing in mind that the first type of tourism that was developed in Spain was beach tourism, the most popular places of Spain are actually the coastal regions as well as the island destinations. Summer holidays are an all time favourite amongst the other European countries who experience some very cold seasons.
<br /><br />Spain’s location is very prime. It actually enjoys two major water bodies, i.e. the Atlantic and the Mediterranean. These water bodies play a major role in facilitating the sun and sand destinations. Apart from the coastlines, Spain has some island territories in both oceans. The Mediterranean has the Balearic Islands while the Atlantic homes the Canary Islands. These are all wonderful places to go on holiday.
<br /><br />Fondly referred to as &quot;Mediterranean paradise&quot;, the Balearics live up to the title. The Balearic Islands has two parts. One is to the southwest while the other is northern. The north region is known as Gimnesias which is made up of Cabrera, Mallorca and Menorca. The south is called Pitiusas comprising of Ibiza and Formentera. The most popular island in this chain is Ibiza. The island is fondly called the ‘white island’. It has been a great destination from the 1960’s. 
<br /><br />It is a one of the regions that have a nudist approach as well as has the hippie culture. It is a celebrated destination especially among the young people because of the nightlife culture. The region receives a great deal of visitors each year. The most popular features here even more than the beaches are the discotheques. These are known to operate even in the very odd hours of the day. 
<br /><br />The Mediterranean culture is quite evident in the region. The wall paintings known as the Ses Fontelles are a major evidence.  Transportation in Ibiza is not hard as there is an airport serving the region as well as many shuttle cars that operate in the region. 
<br /><br />The Canary Islands as said earlier are located in the Atlantic sea. They were formed through volcanic activity as evidenced by the rich black sands at the beaches. The climate is sub tropical. There are other smaller islands affiliated to the canary island. The good climate makes the Canary Islands a perfect place to spend a holiday all year round. 
<br /><br />Canary Island has a total of seven islands that are further divided in two.  The two parts are Santa Cruz de Tenerife and Las Palmas provinces. These island destinations are the perfect choice for anyone who loves life and also having a good time.
<br /><br />If you are looking for a luxurious villa for holidays <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9jYWxvbmdlLw__" target="_blank">Visit Weblink</a> and Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sLw__" target="_blank">vakantiewoningen spanje</a>.
<br />Also read my articles at :<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2d1cnUtYXJ0aWNsZXMuY29tL2FydGljbGUucGhwP2lkPTM1MDY5" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fguru-articles.com%2Farticle.php%3Fid%3D35069"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://guru-articles.com/article.php?id=35069</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaWlnei5jb20vdXNlci9oaXN0b3J5L3Njb3R0bmFzaDcv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.diigz.com%2Fuser%2Fhistory%2Fscottnash7%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.diigz.com/user/history/scottnash7/</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f301ad7ae4a153c2bcd390e16780fe86" url=""><![CDATA[Major Attraction in Spain<br/><br/>Amongst the highly diverse regions in the world, Spain tops the list. Spain is amongst some of the best choices of a destination that one would ever make in their life. It is a great place for all people from all age groups as well as all walks of life regardless of the physical abilities.
<br /><br />There are a lot of places in Spain that one may choose from when trying to make a choice on a destination to visit. This will highly depend on personal interests’ unique with every individual. 
<br /><br />The initial attraction to Spain was actually the sun and sand. This initiated tourism in Spain still plays a major role in the country today. There are a lot of tourists who frequent the region just to be able to have a summer holiday at the seas shores of this country. There are also many activities that these people may engage in while in the country for the summer holidays. Most of the activities near the water bodies include water sports that are quite prevalent in Spain. These include sailing, windsurfing, snorkelling and diving among many other activities.
<br /><br />There is also the historic part of Spain. This has gained a lot of popularity in the past years following the discovery of many places and their historical significance. This has rendered some major contributions to the development of the tourism industry which has been growing at a quite tremendous pace.
<br /><br />The historic things to see in Spain include monuments, ruins as well as great architectural works. World Heritage Sites as named by UNESCO also play their role in upgrading tourism in Spain in that they also are accorded a lot of attention by the tourists that come to Spain.
<br /><br />Art lovers will also have a great time at the Spanish museums where they can sample some of the greatest works done by famous artists of the yester years. The landscapes are also an inspiration to anyone who has artistic abilities. 
<br /><br />The landscapes, flora and fauna also contribute to Spain’s popularity to a great degree. The environmentally sound people find the diversity in Spain quite captivating. It is a perfect place for bird spotting and hunting activities are actually allowed in some places in Spain. This adds to the activities that one may engage in while in Spain and also elevates rural tourism. 
<br /><br />Culture and festivities in Spain also have their impact in Spain. Spain is quite religious and thus there are many festivals that are held every year to mark religious celebrations. These attract a lot of pilgrims as well as general tourists to the region.
<br /><br />If you are looking for a luxurious villa for holidays  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9ibGFuZXMv" target="_blank">Visit Website</a> and Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVucG9sbGVuY2EudmlsbGFtYXIubmwvZmluZEFsbFZpbGxhcy5waHA/ZmlsdGVyPVBvbGxlbmNhJmFtcDtsYW5nPW5s" target="_blank">vakantiehuizen pollenca</a>.
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ncnVrcy5jb20vYXJ0aWNsZS5waHA/aWQ9NzA2NDU_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gruks.com%2Farticle.php%3Fid%3D70645"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.gruks.com/article.php?id=70645</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxpbmtyLmNvbS9zY290dG5hc2g3" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fweblinkr.com%2Fscottnash7"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://weblinkr.com/scottnash7</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a2662299045862eefcfc1527d52bb7fb" url=""><![CDATA[Spain – The Perfect Tourist Destination<br/><br/>Spain is Europe’s third largest country and is comprised of Balearic Islands, Canary Islands and Iberian Peninsula. It is one of the most popular holiday destinations of the world thanks to the amazing features that it has under its fold. The population of the country is around 40 million and it has Madrid as its capital and also the major transportation network center. The country has every feature that is considered essential for a memorable holiday and you will therefore find tourists from all over the world visiting the country. 
<br /><br />It has bustling cities and historical towns all of which offer much for the visitors to see and enjoy during their stay here. On the countryside of the country, you will find breathtaking mountains and regions full of rolling hills and also olive groves. Perhaps the most interesting feature of the country is the beaches, the unique culture and the sunshine that calls people from all corners of the world. Most of the regions and areas in Spain experience more sunny days making the climate very pleasant for any kind of holiday. 
<br /><br />Barcelona is one of the most popular cities in the country and it is therefore a must visit. The world famed coats of Brava and del Sol are also worth the visit while in the country and so is the region of Basque country. Other interesting areas that you can visit while in the country include Bilbao with the famed Guggenheim Museum and the beautiful town of San Sebastian. There is also Castilla y Leon, Leon, Burgos, Segovia and Salamanca cities. There are lots of monumental cities in Spain and this only means that you will have a wide variety to choose from when looking for the perfect holiday destination. 
<br /><br />The Spanish traditions are not left behind and visitors coming into the country will not only witness some of the most spectacular events but even get the chance to take part in the most interesting. One of the best traditions that cannot be missed by those coming here is the famous Flamenco that is a dance and music event. It is an event that is unique to Spain and visitors get the chance to enjoy it till dawn. Spain also has numerous islands with tens of beautiful beaches from where all fun activities, sun and sand can be enjoyed. They make the best spots for fun filled holidays for couples and even families. 
<br /><br />If you are looking for a luxurious villa for holidays <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9jYWxvbmdlLw__" target="_blank">Click Link</a> and Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sLw__" target="_blank">vakantiehuisje spanje</a>.
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tongshu.net%2Fothers%2Fspain-a%2580-the-perfect-tourist-destination.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.tongshu.net/others/spain-a%80-the-perfect-tourist-destination.html</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ib29rbWFyazR5b3UuY29tL3VzZXIvNTkxOTk2LXNjb3R0bmFzaDc_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bookmark4you.com%2Fuser%2F591996-scottnash7"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.bookmark4you.com/user/591996-scottnash7</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="625896f92e0c6729f0a453fdd27202ed" url=""><![CDATA[Tower of Hercules Spain<br/><br/>Monuments form a great part of tourist attractions since they not only give the visitors the chance to learn about the history of the country but also to see the great architectural techniques. Some of the monuments in Spain are famed for their unique architectural work while some hold great historical significance. The Spanish heritage is also hidden within the monuments and they therefore remain to be a treasure. 
<br /><br />The tower of Hercules is a national monument in Spain. It is found in La Caruna Harbor on the northwest part of Spain. This is a great example of monuments reflecting the heritage of Spain. Constructed back in the 1st century AD, it had the name Farum Brigantium. The careful preservation of this tower is what has seen it being raised to a national monument and it therefore attracts tourists from all over the world. It however underwent updating during the 18th century and it is actually currently a Roman lighthouse that is fully functional. 
<br /><br />This beautiful tower stands at 180 feet and it has a captivating sculpture park for its surrounding. Within this park there is a cemetery that is quite old as well as rock carvings Monte dos Bicos which are from the interesting Iron Age. The Tower of Hercules not only serves as a great Roman architecture relic but also has great insights as far as maritime routes and ancient systems of navigation are concerned. 
<br /><br />The tower offer magnificent views and it can be quite romantic. It is possible for people to get to the top area from where the beautiful views of the harbor can be enjoyed. It is one of the best monuments in Spain and one which cannot be missed by those visiting the area. It is visible from far and you will be amazed by just how strong it is even though it is quite old. The renovations and upgrading have put it in a better and stronger condition and it is clear that it will serve it lighthouse purpose for a very long time. 
<br /><br />Spain is one of the best holiday destinations of the world. It has a little of everything among them the wonderful monuments with a different story to tell for each. It is a country offering a wonderful touring chance for every kind of traveler or holidaymaker from the different parts of the world and you can be sure to enjoy your time within the beautiful country. 
<br /><br />If you are looking for a luxurious villa for holidays <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sLw__" target="_blank">Learn More</a> and Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sLw__" target="_blank">vakantievilla</a>.
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="/" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.articleritz.com%2F272465%2F53%2FSpain-The-Perfect-Tourist-Destination.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.articleritz.com/272465/53/Spain-The-Perfect-Tourist-Destination.html</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2N3dXN0cmluZ3MuY29tL3VzZXIucGhwP2xvZ2luPXNjb3R0bmFzaDcmYW1wO3ZpZXc9aGlzdG9yeQ__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcwustrings.com%2Fuser.php%3Flogin%3Dscottnash7%26amp%3Bview%3Dhistory"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://cwustrings.com/user.php?login=scottnash7&amp;view=history</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13cf81d423c15441e218752b8aa13f26" url=""><![CDATA[The Seville Cathedral<br/><br/>Spain has numerous monuments that are well spread out in the many regions of the country. They are mainly cathedrals, churches, museums and other buildings which have great historical, religious or architectural value to the country. It is true to say that you will always find something interesting in every part of the country thus making your tour or holiday in these areas most enjoyable and also memorable. 
<br /><br />Among the many attractions that you will find in Seville is the Cathedral. It is a popular monument that attracts thousands of visitors coming into Spain. It is actually a must see monument of the city and is among the largest gothic cathedrals that you will find in the world. It makes it to the list of gothic cathedrals such as San Pietro that is in Rome and the St. Paul’s cathedral that is in London. 
<br /><br />Where the Seville Cathedral now stands, there once used to be a huge mosque but unfortunately it collapsed. It was after this collapse back in 1401 that the construction of the Seville Cathedral began. It continued for a whole century and you will find the rectangular wide shape of this cathedral interesting. It is because it was put up on the base plan of the mosque thus the unusual shape the Cathedral now has. 
<br /><br />The Seville cathedral definitely has some areas that cannot be missed by the visitors taking the time to behold its beauty. They include the 30 chapels that are within it, the Christopher Columbus tomb that is on the southern entrance to the cathedral and also the Patio de Los Naranjos, a beautiful garden that is on cathedra’s northern side. This cathedral also has the La Giralda tower which is the most outstanding feature on it. It was put up in 1184 and it’s indeed a very unique part of the beautiful huge cathedral. 
<br /><br />The tower stands at 70 meters and has a sebka design on the outer part while the inner part has 35 ramps and an interesting observation platform. It is a great area to enjoy the beautiful view of the city and you will find visitors here in their numbers. The Seville Cathedral is definitely one of the places that are a must visit in the city. You can enjoy a guided tour of the cathedral to ensure that you get to see everything that is unique and valuable within and without the cathedral. 
<br /><br />If you are looking for a luxurious villa for holidays <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9jYWxvbmdlLw__" target="_blank">Visit this</a> and Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sLw__" target="_blank">vakantiehuizen in spanje</a>.
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pZGVhbWFya2V0ZXJzLmNvbS8/YXJ0aWNsZWlkPTM2MDAzMjYmYW1wO0NGSUQ9MjQxOTc4MDc5JmFtcDtDRlRPS0VOPTE4MzQzNjMw" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ideamarketers.com%2F%3Farticleid%3D3600326%26amp%3BCFID%3D241978079%26amp%3BCFTOKEN%3D18343630"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.ideamarketers.com/?articleid=3600326&amp;CFID=241978079&amp;CFTOKEN=18343630</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kZWxpY2lvdXMuY29tL3Njb3R0bmFzaDc_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.delicious.com%2Fscottnash7"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.delicious.com/scottnash7</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb43a0e34114072e4c82106554a86719" url=""><![CDATA[The Alhambra Palace in Granada Spain<br/><br/>This world famous palace of Spain is among the most visited places throughout Spain and it is therefore one of the monuments in Spain that you cannot afford to miss out on. It got its name Alhambra which stands for red from the reddish brown bricks used to construct its outer walls. It is located in the most beautiful natural place in Granada with snow capped summits for its backdrop. It is near the Sierra Nevada Mountain and the Darra River making a great location for a Spanish tour or holiday. 
<br /><br />Things to see on the palace
<br /><br />Just like any other monument or building in Spain, there are parts which cannot be missed while visiting the Alhambra palace. It mainly is divided into four parts including Palacios Nazaries, Alcazaba, Generalife and Palacio de Carlos. The Alcazaba which is a castle happens to be the palace’s oldest part having been put up in 13th century. The watch tower Torre de la Vela is where the panoramic view of the city can be enjoyed while Generalife is a wonderful garden of a palace. 
<br /><br />Other features of the palace which are worth checking out on your tour include the museums de la Alhambra and the Fine Arts. They are both within Palacio de Carlos V. The Salon de Embajadores has impressive embroideries and extraordinary art making it another feature that is worth checking out. It is a bog saloon once used by the ambassadors and the kingdom. Also worth seeing are the Patio de los Leones, the Women Tower and the Old Hamman, Albacin and the Kingdom Chapel. 
<br /><br />It is important for all visitors to know that the tickets to this beautiful palace can be very limited. This is as a result of issues to do with the conservation and therefore only a certain number is allowed to visit every day. It is important that you book your ticket a day before leaving for the site to ensure that you manage to explore the palace well. It is a popular palace that receives huge numbers of visitors and therefore to avoid the long queues, it is advisable to get the tickets in advance. 
<br /><br />There could be restrictions to certain parts of the Alhambra and it is therefore important to check on the schedules given so that you visit the palace when you can enjoy most of the areas that are of interest within it. 
<br /><br />If you are looking for a luxurious villa for holidays <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9ibGFuZXMv" target="_blank">Visit Site</a> and Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sLw__" target="_blank">vakantiehuis in spanje</a>.
<br />Also read my articles at :<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dvYXJ0aWNsZXMuY29tL2FydGljbGUvTWFqb3ItQXR0cmFjdGlvbi1pbi1TcGFpbi82OTk0NzU5Lw__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgoarticles.com%2Farticle%2FMajor-Attraction-in-Spain%2F6994759%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://goarticles.com/article/Major-Attraction-in-Spain/6994759/</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdHVtYmxldXBvbi5jb20vc3R1bWJsZXIvc2NvdHRuYXNo" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.stumbleupon.com%2Fstumbler%2Fscottnash"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.stumbleupon.com/stumbler/scottnash</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9c73526f196f398f933da6d20be8379c" url=""><![CDATA[Popular Holidays in Spain<br/><br/>Holidays in Spain are some of the most enjoyable and memorable. This is a country with lots of things to offer to both local travelers and international visitors. It has a pleasant climate in most regions thus making it a place you can enjoy a holiday at any given time of the year. Some areas in Spain have more sunny days and are popular spots for holidaymakers especially those from colder regions of Europe and other parts of the world. 
<br /><br />Beach Holidays
<br /><br />They are some of the most popular holiday options in Spain. With so many islands dotted with stunning beaches, it is definitely a great place for that deserved beach holiday. The beach offers fun activities to all and it is one of the major features that tourists look for in a holiday destination. Some of the beaches are ideal for specific water sports such as windsurfing while others are most suitable for scuba diving. Others will offer basically every water sport you could be interested in. 
<br /><br />When choosing the best spot for your beach holiday therefore, it is important to consider all the activities that you will be exposed to. The beach holidays will in most cases have beach resorts and modern hotels as your accommodation options. Always make a point of checking what each option has to offer you in terms of amenities and comfort. You will find everything from luxurious to adventurous thus it is not as hard to make a decision. 
<br /><br />Green Holidays
<br /><br />They are also quite popular in Spain. With lots of natural grounds especially on the inlands, the holidays are breathtaking and memorable in every sense. They are spent in areas with majestic mountains, shimmering lakes, plantations and landscapes that are breathtaking. The best activities that you will enjoy on your Spanish green holiday include nature walks, hiking, cycling, mountain climbing and also picnicking in the most attractive natural grounds. 
<br /><br />The green holidays also come with numerous options for your accommodation with the most impressive being villas. The villas come in different sizes and will therefore easily accommodate even families on holiday. They are located in the most beautiful areas making it possible to enjoy those beautiful sunrises and romantic sunsets. Hotels and apartments also make wonderful accommodation options for your green holiday in Spain. Always choose an option that will help in meeting all the holiday needs and expectations that you have. 
<br /><br />Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9ibGFuZXMv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fvakantiehuizenspanje.villamar.nl%2Fspanje%2Fcosta-brava%2Fblanes%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://vakantiehuizenspanje.villamar.nl/spanje/costa-brava/blanes/</a></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuc3BhbmplLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL3NwYW5qZS9jb3N0YS1icmF2YS9ibGFuZXMv" target="_blank">Visit Website</a> to plan your holiday
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb29kaW5mb2hvbWUuY29tL0FydC85NDg3NzkvNTMvU3BhaW4tQXMtQS1Ub3VyaXN0LURlc3RpbmF0aW9uLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.goodinfohome.com%2FArt%2F948779%2F53%2FSpain-As-A-Tourist-Destination.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.goodinfohome.com/Art/948779/53/Spain-As-A-Tourist-Destination.html</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dvdGFnZ2VkLmNvbS91c2VyLy92aWV3L2hpc3RvcnkvbG9naW4vc2NvdHRuYXNoNw__" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgotagged.com%2Fuser%2F%2Fview%2Fhistory%2Flogin%2Fscottnash7"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://gotagged.com/user//view/history/login/scottnash7</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e27a29d819c5911fea123c4a6773770" url=""><![CDATA[Religion And Tourism in Spain<br/><br/>Spain’s religion comprises of Judaism, Islam, and Catholicism. It is a country that homes some of the places that are considered as the holiest. Santiago de Compstela which is in Galicia is said to be third in holiness after Jerusalem and Vatican City. 
<br /><br />The Way of Saint James terminus is also found in Spain. The fourth and fifth holiest places are Santo Toribio de Liebana and Caravaca de la Cruz respectively. The areas receive a lot of pilgrims every year especially around the Easter period during the last week of lent. The holy week processions are a major tourist attraction. The processions are most important in many Spanish towns.
<br /><br />Semana Santa or holy week traditions have made the Spanish religion recognized. Most tourists and pilgrims plan a trip for long periods of time so as to be in Spain in time for the processions. The activities within the procession differ from one town to the other while some are known to be stricter than others. The processions are most glamorous in Andalusia regions specifically Zamora, Castile, Seville and Malaga. The holy week is considered to be one of the religious holidays in Spain. Malaga and Seville hold the most interesting processions. More somber processions can be seen in Castile and Zamora. 
<br /><br />Though the events may differ in arrangement from one location to the other, there are some common features one of which is the use of the penitential robe referred to as nazareno. This is worn by some of the people within the procession. This rope is designed in a way that it is able to keep he wearers face concealed by including a conical tipped hood. A cloak is also included in some cases. Colors are procession specific. These robes are historic by themselves. They were used during medieval period especially for penitents. In this way, people could clearly display penance while discreetly concealing their identity from the rest. 
<br /><br />In most processions, the nazarenos bear candles as well as wooden crosses. Some may be barefoot while others may bear chains or shackles on the feet so as to show penance. 
<br /><br />The Cartagena processions are said to have more uniqueness as well as very strict orders. In some processions, there are usually bands or even mournful singers that can be heard throughout the procession. These processions in the areas of Spain mentioned are great tourist attractions some of whom comprise of pilgrims from all over the world who come to witness this amazing event that occurs every year thus religion contributes to the tourism sector in a great way.
<br /><br />Get more information on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuZ2lyb25hLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL2ZpbmRBbGxWaWxsYXMucGhwP2ZpbHRlcj1HaXJvbmEmYW1wO2FtcDtsYW5nPW5s" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fvakantiehuizengirona.villamar.nl%2FfindAllVillas.php%3Ffilter%3DGirona%26amp%3Bamp%3Blang%3Dnl"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://vakantiehuizengirona.villamar.nl/findAllVillas.php?filter=Girona&amp;amp;lang=nl</a></a> and <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zha2FudGllaHVpemVuZ2lyb25hLnZpbGxhbWFyLm5sL2ZpbmRBbGxWaWxsYXMucGhwP2ZpbHRlcj1HaXJvbmEmYW1wO2FtcDtsYW5nPW5s" target="_blank">Click This</a> to plan your holiday 
<br />Also read my articles at : <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3VsdGltYXRlYXJ0aWNsZWRpcmVjdG9yeS5jb20vdHJhdmVsLWxlaXN1cmUvc3BhaW5zLWdlb2dyYXBoeS1pc2xhbmRzLWNsaW1hdGUtYW5kLXRoZWlyLXJvbGVzLWluLXRvdXJpc20v" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fultimatearticledirectory.com%2Ftravel-leisure%2Fspains-geography-islands-climate-and-their-roles-in-tourism%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://ultimatearticledirectory.com/travel-leisure/spains-geography-islands-climate-and-their-roles-in-tourism/</a></a> and do check out my bookmarks at <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N0aWNreXRhZ3MuaW4vdXNlci9oaXN0b3J5L3Njb3R0bmFzaDcv" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstickytags.in%2Fuser%2Fhistory%2Fscottnash7%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stickytags.in/user/history/scottnash7/</a></a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>