<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="19">
		<document id="b6e3f92f66b0d0a8193f6c5f0f7cfaba" url=""><![CDATA[Tens Acupuncture Massager Device - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Tens Massager and Medicomat Tens Acupuncture Massager Device - Painless Lekomat. Cyanosis can also appear at any time later  in life and often accompanies conditions in which lung function is compromised (resulting in an inability to fully oxygenate  the blood) or conditions in which the heart's pumping function is compromised. The presence of abnormal forms of hemoglobin  or other abnormalities of the blood cells can also sometimes cause cyanosis. <br /><br />Since the leg contains a number of different structures and tissue types, a wide variety of conditions and injuries can  cause leg pain. For diagnostic and therapeutic purposes, it is important to differentiate the exact type and location of any  pain in the legs. <br /><br />An decrease in body fluid can come from medications, fluid loss, lack of fluid intake, or illnesses such as diabetes. A  decrease in body fat can be intentially caused by exercise and dieting, such as for obesity. Weight loss is normal after  pregnancy. <br /><br />Pain in the abdomen can come from conditions affecting a variety of organs. The abdomen is an anatomical area that is  bounded by the lower margin of the ribs above, the pelvic bone below, and the flanks on each side. Although abdominal pain  can arise from the tissues of the abdominal wall that surround the abdominal cavity, the term abdominal pain generally is  used to describe pain originating from organs within the abdominal cavity. <br /><br />Acupuncture points to allow inserting metal needles (electro-acupuncture Lekomat stimulation) regulates the energy flow in a  particular functional area. Inserting needles into these points are re-establishes energy flow where it is disturbed or  interrupted, and by establishing a balance in the entire human body. <br /><br />The most common cause of a toothache is a dental cavity. The second most common cause is gum disease. Toothache can be  caused by a problem that does not originate from a tooth or the jaw. <br /><br />The earliest use of ear acupuncture dates back to ancient China. Although much of the information on this subject was lost  due to the historical burning of the books, the ancient Chinese stimulated many points on the auricle to rebalance the flow  of energy and restore health. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and  disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a  href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href=''  target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="62dcf0d8d1fb4b767ec8055e30479c38" url=""><![CDATA[Magnetic Therapy Apparatus - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Lateral Knee Pain Treatment and Medicomat Magnetic Therapy Apparatus - Home Treatment Strategies. Pinkeye, also called  conjunctivitis, is the redness or irritation of the membranes (conjunctivae) on the inner part of the eyelids and the  membranes covering the whites of the eyes. These membranes react to a wide range of bacteria, viruses, allergy-provoking  agents, irritants and toxic agents. Viral and bacterial forms of conjunctivitis are common in childhood. The leading cause  of a red eye is virus infection. <br /><br />Monitor for home treatment of high blood pressure works on the principle of traditional Chinese medicine and bio-electricity  of the human body. Blood pressure will be controlled after 5-7 treatments. Therapy can be a supplement or alternative to  medication for a gradual reduction in medication. <br /><br />Joint stiffness is the sensation of difficulty moving a joint or the apparent loss of range of motion of a joint. Joint  stiffness often accompanies joint pain and/or swelling. Joint stiffness can be caused by injury or disease of the joint and  is a common finding in the arthritis conditions. <br /><br />If you need more information about the effectiveness of ear stapling the best thing to do is to seek professional advice  regarding ear stapling. Many people are for it, but some people think it is not a good idea because it has been known to  cause pain in some people, and soreness in a persons jaw as well. However, if you contact a professional and ask as many  questions as possible you will find the information you need regarding this procedure. <br /><br />Monitor for home treatment and cure disease revealed automatically. Using special headphones placed over the ear shells  LEKOMAT fully automatic review and choose the appropriate acupuncture points through which the treatment is done. It is  particularly effective in diseases of the nervous system, asthma, bronchitis, allergies, stress. Treating high blood  pressure, poor circulation, headaches, migraines, depression, diabetes, dizziness, rheumatism, spondylosis, sciatica,  gastric ulcers. In a few minutes automatically reduces pain in the stomach, back, neck and legs. <br /><br />Dyspepsia is a disorder in which there may be symptoms of upper abdominal pain, belching, nausea, abdominal bloating, early  satiety, and, possibly, abdominal distention. Symptoms of dyspepsia originate from the upper gastrointestinal tract,  primarily the stomach and first part of the small intestine. The symptoms most often are provoked by eating, which is a time  when many different gastrointestinal functions are called upon to work in concert. <br /><br />How Acupuncture Works. Chinese doctors work with qi, a life force energy that flows through the body. When there is an  injury, improper diet or sometimes certain weather conditions, it blocks the flow of qi. The basic principle of acupuncture  is to establish balance in the flow of energy, removing blockages, and relieving pain or anomalies that result from excess  (yang) or deficiency (yin). <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and  disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a  href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href=''  target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1bf623e8ee80e9cbec0575878c96917" url=""><![CDATA[Electronic Tens Device - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Gastroptosis Acupuncture Therapy and Medicomat Electronic Tens Device - Family Doctor Medicobot. The treatment of the  headache depends on the type and severity of the headache and on other factors such as the age of the patient. <br /><br />The general procedure for having Ear Staples is to wear the first set of staples for up to six months, and then have them  removed for a week. Then, when the week is up, usually the staples are reinserted. The exact period of time that these  staples are left in may not be the same every time, so you should consult your acupuncture specialist to find out more  information about it. In fact, another source on the Internet suggests leaving them in for about 3-4 months as long as there  is no sign of redness or swelling in your ear. <br /><br />Some diseases are also associated with changes in the nails, which can include brittleness. The term onychoschizia refers to  splitting of the fingernails as well as brittle or soft nails. Taking biotin (a vitamin) supplements can help in some cases  of brittle nails, and application of moisturizers after soaking in water can also be of benefit. <br /><br />Pre-menstrual Syndrome (PMS) is a disorder that occurs in women during the last part of the menstrual cycle. PMS is quite  common. Between 50% and 70% of women, or more than 1 in 2, suffer from PMS. One woman in 20 suffers so severely that their  lives are seriously affected. <br /><br />Electroacupuncture-depth electro-introduced through the needle. Elektropunktura to Voll actually is a method that is  performed using devices called EAV organometar, developed by a German dr.R.Voll. It is also used for therapy and  diagnostics. Laser acupuncture - based on the action of laser light that is monochromatic, polarized and coherent. It is a  sterile, non-invasive and painless method, which if properly applied no side harmful effects. <br /><br />Most of us are familiar with the picture of someone getting an acupuncture treatment. We can also list a few things that  acupuncture is used for, including reducing anxiety and reducing or eliminating pain. However, few people know that  acupuncture is a wonderful thing to add to a cosmetic routine. <br /><br />Vertigo is a feeling that you are dizzily turning around or that your surroundings are dizzily turning about you. Vertigo is  usually due to a problem with the inner ear but can also be caused by vision problems and other conditions. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and  disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a  href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href=''  target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="843da5f8926b5a1c4d8778d42b07c837" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Electronic Acupuncture Treatment Devic<br/><br/>Migraine And Treatment and Medicomat Electronic Acupuncture Treatment Device - Effective Health Care Lekomat. Air pressure is used Lekomat bio-electricity to treat a man of his own illness. Improved functioning of the cell body and improved micro-circulation strengthens the immune system and thus achieve the goal of curing high blood pressure. Using this device the patient will no longer be exposed to the harmful effects and damage caused by excessive intake of drugs. <br /><br />Excessive sweating is referred to as hyperhidrosis, and some people may have a tendency to excessive sweating, known as primary hyperhidrosis. Sweating can also be a symptom of several medical conditions, especially when the sweating is excessive or inappropriate. <br /><br />People who snore can have any body type, although as a rule, snoring increases when people gain weight. Sleeping position may also affect snoring. Since the tissues of the pharynx are normally soft and floppy, when we lie on our backs, gravity pulls the palate, tonsils, and tongue backward. <br /><br />Ear acupuncture points may be stimulated for a longer period of time by using ear seeds or ear tacks. Ear seeds are small seeds from the Vaccaria plant. These seeds are held in place on the ear with a small piece of adhesive tape. Ear seeds may be left in the ear for a few days or up to two weeks. Ear tacks are very small needles with an adhesive backing. Ear tacks are inserted into the ear and left in the ear for a few days or up to one week. <br /><br />Monitor for home treatment of acupuncture cured LEKOMAT headache, migraine, depression, high blood pressure, poor circulation, diabetes, dizziness, rheumatism, spondylosis, sciatica, stomach ulcers, obesity, insomnia, menstrual problems. In a few minutes automatically reduces pain in the stomach, back, neck and legs. A detailed list of the device for bolesti.Posebna Home Treatment LEKOMAT is that you relieve the daily use of many drugs and medications. Use LEKOMAT is a very simple and painless, and most importantly, without damaging a counter. The device runs on two 1.5V batteries, and can be used by multiple people. <br /><br />The loss of skin cells from the scalp is a normal part of the life cycle of skin cells. However, excessive flaking of the scalp, or dandruff, is a common cosmetic problem experienced by millions of people. Dandruff is not contagious and is normally not a serious problem. Some cases of excessive dandruff accompanied by intense itching and patches of flaky skin on the face or elsewhere are actually a form of eczema referred to as seborrheic eczema. <br /><br />An interesting offer companies ElmedNet - hospitals and clinics is certainly the most interesting computer diagnostic device Lekomat-al, who in just a few minutes viewing the whole body and the diagnosis for 50 common diseases and suggested therapy. This phone can also carry out therapy. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fbd7f2e75b288ec4cb31640551923942" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Multi-Function Automatic Treatment Dev<br/><br/>Cure For Anemia and Medicomat Multi-Function Automatic Treatment Device - Nature Heal Medicomat. The moisture from tears on the front of the eye, the cornea, is important to avoid damage of the cornea. The tears drain from the eye through the tear ducts (lacrimal ducts). If the tear ducts become blocked, tears can well up in the eye and fall excessively. <br /><br />A wide variety of controlled clinical trials, outcome summaries and anecdotal reports about the use of acupuncture in addiction treatment have been appearing since the 1970s in journals specializing in addictions, mental health, public health, criminal justice and acupuncture. These reports differed vastly in terms of methodology, populations studied, statistical sophistication and clinical relevance as well as in their findings about the value of acupuncture. <br /><br />All Oriental medicine modalities are intended to improve the flow of qi (pronounced chee). Qi regulates the body's spiritual, emotional, mental, and physical balance and is influenced by the opposing forces of yin (negative energy) and yang (positive energy). According to traditional Chinese medicine, when yin and yang are balanced, they work together with the natural flow of qi to help the body achieve and maintain health. <br /><br />LEKOMAT monitor for home treatment of headaches all the work alone, fully automatic, finds all the disturbances and automatically treat headaches and other ailments. It is particularly effective in diseases of the nervous system, bronchitis, asthma, allergies, stress. <br /><br />Use of bio-electricity is a man to treat his own illness. The device is intended for users who have high blood pressure complicated by the weakening of the heart muscle, damage to kidneys, arteriosclerosis or coronary disease, the device helps regulate complications and is effective in preventing stroke. It can also be used as an additional drug therapy. <br /><br />People who snore can have any body type, although as a rule, snoring increases when people gain weight. Sleeping position may also affect snoring. Since the tissues of the pharynx are normally soft and floppy, when we lie on our backs, gravity pulls the palate, tonsils, and tongue backward. <br /><br />Excessive sweating is referred to as hyperhidrosis, and some people may have a tendency to excessive sweating, known as primary hyperhidrosis. Sweating can also be a symptom of several medical conditions, especially when the sweating is excessive or inappropriate. Sweating may accompany hot flashes during the menopausal transition. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fdc1b68cdb6523cae92e527cc3b9a6ba" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Detox Spa Device<br/><br/>Acupuncture Certification For Chiropractors and Medicomat Detox Spa Device - Medicomat Pain. Acupuncture (Lekomat) successfully treated smoker (diabetic) foot. The reason for the occurrence of smoking legs mainly arteriosclerosis, with the same symptoms as diabetic foot, and the main reason, of course, nicotine, in the case of diabetes - increased blood sugar. Symptoms usually show the legs ie the outermost peripheral organs of the heart. Acupuncture is very successful in solving the problem of addiction to nicotine and thereby prevent further destruction of atherosclerosis in the peripheral parts of the body so. smoker's legs. As for the diabetic foot, acupuncture successfully regulate blood sugar and thus prevent further destructive effect of diabetes as a cause of diabetic foot. <br /><br />Diseases for which acupuncture is effective, but further proof is needed to include it into mainstream healthcare - Diseases, symptoms or conditions for which the therapeutic effect of acupuncture has been shown but for which further proof is needed: Abdominal Pain (in acute gastroenteritis or due to gastrointestinal spasm), Acne vulgaris, Alcohol dependence and detoxification, Bell's palsy, Bronchial asthma (View detailed Acupuncture FAQ information) (most effective in children and in patients without complicating diseases), Cancer Pain, Cardiac neurosis, Cholecystitis, chronic, with acute exacerbation, Cholelithiasis, Competition stress syndrome,  Raynaud syndrome, primary, Recurrent lower urinary-tract infection, Reflex sympathetic dystrophy, Retention of urine, traumatic, Schizophrenia, Sialism, drug-induced, Sjögren syndrome, Sore throat (including tonsillitis), Spine Pain, acute, Stiff neck (View detailed Acupuncture FAQ information), Temporomandibular joint dysfunction, Tietze syndrome, Tobacco dependence, Tourette syndrome, Ulcerative colitis, chronic, Urolithiasis, Vascular dementia, Whooping cough (pertussis). <br /><br />Weakness may be generalized or may affect one muscle or muscle group exclusively. Diseases of the neuromuscular system, injuries, metabolic diseases, and toxins can all cause of measurable muscle weakness. <br /><br />Acupuncture (Lekomat) successfully treat anxiety. Regarding: fears, anxiety, neuroses, stress and depression as a consequence of modern life, and this time, the body forces them ACUPUNCTURE these ailments only, and successfully treated. Because, basically Chinese medicine is the philosophy and experience of the following: The body can not be considered completely healthy without the proper health of the soul. Chinese needles (from Lekomata pulses) do just that. <br /><br />Vision loss can also be considered as loss of sight that cannot be corrected to a normal level with eyeglasses. The causes of loss of vision are extremely varied and range from conditions affecting the eyes to conditions affecting the visual processing centers in the brain. <br /><br />And Lekomat multi-functional treatment apparatus, in accordance with the theory that the human visceral organ bio-electricity discharge stroma and cells in the pathological conditions, which the inactivation of the sodium pump must be activated by external force in order to exert its function. The Lekomat benign bio-electricity airwaves assist cells restore the normal bio-electricity activity. <br /><br />Acupuncture for pain in the back. Almost half of patients undergoing acupuncture felt relief that lasted months. Unlike them, she felt relief, only a quarter of patients on standard drug therapy and other means of official medicine. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cf669e5950ce0284d1e27120fb97a2c1" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Pain Relief Equipment<br/><br/>Biosensor and Medicomat Pain Relief Equipment - Latest. Pain in the ear can occur because of conditions within the ear, the ear canal, or affecting the visible portion of the ear (the pinna). Acute middle ear infection, medically called acute otitis media, is inflammation of the middle ear and is the most frequent diagnosis in sick children. Earache can also be caused by pain and inflammation of the outer portion of the ear. <br /><br />Acupuncture is the most studied aspect of traditional Chinese medicine. Although numerous scientific theories attempt to explain how and why acupuncture works, there exists no definitive explanation. Nevertheless, the effectiveness of acupuncture is widely recognized. The World Health Organization currently lists acupuncture as an effective treatment for forty aliments including abdominal pain, depression, neck pain, and migraines. <br /><br />Dry skin can be associated with symptoms, including flaking, itching, dullness, redness, pain, and tightness of skin. <br /><br />Natural headache treatment using acupuncture. Tension-type headaches are often associated with chronic neck and upper back muscle tension. In fact, a research study of tension-type headache sufferers showed a strong correlation between headache intensity and the degree of upper trapezius muscle tension as measured by electromyography[11]. Since acupuncture treatments can induce potent muscle relaxation effects (both general and local), most patients experience relief during, or immediately after the acupuncture session as demonstrated in our study[11]. <br /><br />Acupuncture is used to treat a lot of ailments which also happen to be the root cause of tinnitus. Hence, the tinnitus acupuncture treatment is an effective way of treating tinnitus. <br /><br />Cyanosis can also appear at any time later in life and often accompanies conditions in which lung function is compromised or conditions in which the heart's pumping function is compromised. The presence of abnormal forms of hemoglobin or other abnormalities of the blood cells can also sometimes cause cyanosis. <br /><br />Scientific discover, the liver is the body's largest continuous bio-electricity discharge organ, kidney and spleen serves as a supplement to the bio-electricity discharge regulation and the concentration of excretion adjust organs; the heart is intermittent bio-electricity discharge organ, doubles as a power cycle organ; the lung are intermittent bio-electricity discharge organs, at the same time it taking air exchange. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71e3fdc4755d80f27944065016d81b72" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Electronic Acupuncture Device<br/><br/>Frozen Shoulder Treatment and Medicomat Electronic Acupuncture Device - A Guide To Using Lekomat To Relieve Pain. The emergence of acupuncture is associated with the story of a warrior wounded by an arrow. Stick is removed and the wound is healed. Then he noticed that his illness was cured on the second part of the body. Acupuncture is mentioned in ancient China but 2800.god.pr.ne Huang Di Nei Jing - The Yellow Emperor (2698th - 2596.g. pr.ne), the author has written the first part of medicine. It is written in dialogue form the Emperor and his physician, and consists of two parts. <br /><br />LEKOMAT apparatus Home Treatment for Bronchitis all alone, fully automatic, finds all the disturbances and automatically treat bronchitis and other diseases. It cures headaches, migraines, depression, high blood pressure, poor circulation, diabetes, dizziness, rheumatism, spondylosis, sciatica, stomach ulcers, obesity, insomnia, menstrual problems. <br /><br />Detection is based on electrodermal measuring principle. When an organ has pathological change, bioelectric resistance of corresponding auricular point decreases, Medicomat apparatus will alarm indicating abnormal orgon through microelectronic detector. It reminds us going to hospital earlier for further examination. <br /><br />Loss of vision can occur suddenly or develop gradually over time. Vision loss may be complete or partial, involving only one eye or even certain parts of the visual field. Vision loss is different from blindness that was present at birth, and this article is concerned with causes of vision loss in an individual who previously had normal vision. <br /><br />Acupuncture leads to cure asthma, which is so far incurable disease. Acupuncture and treating the cause here and it is more successful than modern medicine. Acupuncture stimulation pulses from aprata Lekomat substances stimulate the production of prostaglandins, which expands the bronchi. Unlike modern medicine, this is a natural remedy. Hence, no chemistry result. Healing is a large percentage. <br /><br />Leg sores can arise from trauma, infection, tumors, or chronic medical conditions. Any process of inflammation or tissue damage can manifest as a sore on the leg. Leg sores may affect primarily the skin or can extend into the subcutaneous tissues, muscles, bone, and deeper structures of the leg. Common causes of leg sores include insect bites and stings, cuts and abrasions, and skin infections. <br /><br />Western doctors are now starting to recognize the world of good acupuncture and traditional Chinese medicine can do for female health problems. Here, we are going to look at two common health issues that TCM has produced excellent results for – endometriosis and urinary tract infections. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="78c24dcf2320a7b1e118932601c100e5" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Laser Tens Acupuncture Therapy<br/><br/>Natural Cure For Headaches and Medicomat Laser Tens Acupuncture Therapy - Treating Pain Naturally Medicomat. There are many causes of chest pain. One is angina which results from inadequate oxygen supply to the heart muscle. Angina can be caused by coronary artery disease or spasm of the coronary arteries. Chest pain can also be due to a heart attack (coronary occlusion) and other important diseases. Do not try to ignore chest pain and work (or play) through it. Chest pain is a warning to seek medical attention. <br /><br />Because we expose our feet to potential injury in our daily lives by walking, we have all experienced pains in the feet at one time or another. There are many common causes of foot pains, such as blisters and corns. There are also less common causes of foot pain, such as sciatica and osteomyelitis. Treatments for foot pain depend on the particular cause. <br /><br />Constipation means different things to different people. For many people, it simply means infrequent stools. For others, however, constipation means hard stools, difficulty passing stools (straining), or a sense of incomplete emptying after a bowel movement. The cause of each of these types of constipation probably is different, and the approach to each should be tailored to the specific type of constipation. <br /><br />Elbow pain is most often the result of tendinitis, which can affect the inner or outer elbow. Treatment includes ice, rest, and medication for inflammation. Elbow pain has many other causes including arthritis and bursitis. <br /><br />How Can Acupuncture Treat Hypertension? While the ancient Chinese Medical doctors did not describe hypertension in the same manner we do today, Oriental Medicine theory accounted for the various physiological processes surrounding this condition. In this system of medicine, various physiological relationships exist between each of the internal organs. When these relationships become disharmonious, a variety of disease patterns manifest. By observation of the tongue, palpation of the pulse at the radial artery, and listening to an individuals signs and symptoms, an Acupuncturist is able to discern the appropriate pattern diagnosis.Then, the acupuncturist will decide upon a selection of acupuncture points to balance the body. <br /><br />Your first question might be if any children are actually acupuncture clients? Sure! Nearly all children find acupuncture treatments very easy, even enjoyable. Especially the younger ones, for acupuncture needles are not painful, and younger children don't have our a needle is painful association that adults do. Children also seem to be more aware of their bodies than adults, and can feel themselves feeling better quite quickly. Also, the improvement in energy and vitality is often so clear with children. <br /><br />Are there differences for acupuncture treatment with children? The general treatment is similar, determining the locations and times to insert needles in order to effect the treatment. (Needles are inserted to different depths depending on the treatment, anything from just under the skin up to a maximum of a few inches. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c8a96c66710b96bfd402370e00f5323e" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Disease Detecting And Curing Apparatus<br/><br/>Influenza Prevention and Medicomat Disease Detecting And Curing Apparatus - How to Cure Medicomat. When using Lekomata feel a tingling sensation and even hear the music softly. Very effectively relieves pain, and regularly helps in the treatment of many diseases. All this, of course, sounds a bit odd, but the fact that the Lekomat gold medalist in Brussels Eureka and Marconi Medal for innovation. <br /><br />Blisters can accompany some types of skin rashes and inflammatory conditions, including certain autoimmune diseases. Depending upon the cause of the blisters, blisters may occur singly or in groups. In contrast to abscesses and boils, which are collections of inflammatory fluid found deep in the tissues, blisters are found in the most superficial layer of skin. <br /><br />Seizures can be caused by head injuries, brain tumors, lead poisoning, maldevelopment of the brain, genetic and infectious illnesses, and fevers. In fully half of the patients with seizures, no cause can yet be found. <br /><br />A seizure is the uncontrolled electrical activity in the brain, which may produce a physical convulsion, minor physical signs, thought disturbances, or a combination of symptoms. <br /><br />Alternatively, a rash may be unrelated to an infectious organism, such as from an underlying medical illness. Medications, chronic medical conditions, and allergic reactions (hives) are among the multiple different causes of rash. <br /><br />Leg swelling generally occurs because of an abnormal accumulation of fluid in the tissues of the lower extremity. The medical term for leg swelling from excessive fluid in the tissues is edema. Persisting indentation of a swollen leg after pressure from a finger is known as pitting edema. <br /><br />The eye has a number of components. These components include but are not limited to the cornea, iris, pupil, lens, retina, macula, optic nerve, choroid and vitreous. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="98c17e5062a09631608af6d00c9bd2b4" url=""><![CDATA[Distributors Wanted - Tens Acupuncture Therapy Machine<br/><br/>Rhinitis Treatment and Medicomat Tens Acupuncture Therapy Machine - A Few Ways. There are variations of acupuncture that do not rely on the use of needles. The ideas behind these are identical with standard acupuncture technique. The knowledge of acupuncture points, the organization of the body, and the importance of proper energy flow for a healthy body are all exactly identical to standard acupuncture therapy. The main difference is that the needle is replaced by a different technique to manipulate the acupuncture point. <br /><br />Health Care - TCM has it, good health resulted from smooth energy flows within cannels and points. The daily usage of Medicomat stimulator helps to dredge the meridians and collaterals, active the body cells, improve the immune system and maintain a balanced environment in inner body. It makes you stronger and more energetic and keeps you in a good health condition as well. <br /><br />Acupuncture to a quicker recovery - Studies show that acupuncture is subjecting the postoperative recovery period is achieved, with fewer problems. Successful regardless of the type of surgery. <br /><br />Auriculotherapy is typically considered one form of acupuncture, but there are both differences and similarities between the two procedures. Acupuncture is a form of medical treatment involving the stimulation of acupuncture points located on energy channels extending over the surface of the body, which are known as meridians. Different perspectives of auriculotherapy focus not on the acupuncture meridians but on the use of the ear as a localized reflex system connected to the central nervous system. <br /><br />You do not need directions or knowledge of medical doctors. apparatus for Home Treatment LEKOMAT everything works itself automatically - the examinations and then carries out acupuncture treatment without needles, without pain. He is successful in diseases of the heart, lungs, stomach and kidneys. It is particularly effective in diseases of the nervous system, bronchitis, asthma, allergies, stress. <br /><br />A decrease in sex drive can develop both due to medical conditions as well as to psychological or emotional issues. Inhibited sexual desire is a type of sexual dysfunction that affects both men and women. A reduction in sexual desire has been associated with low levels of testosterone in men. Likewise, women in the menopausal transitions sometimes report a decrease in sex drive. <br /><br />Projecting parts holographic reflex theory has it, all biological and genetic information of human body are reduced on the projectingparts, such as ear, hand, foot and so on, in an orderly manner as small zones and acupuncture points. If there is any organ has pathological changes, the bio-resistance of corresponding acupuncture point in the projecting parts will be lower than before. Thus treatment and diagnosis can be achieved. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a73ac8376d60393fd79a789c28bb645d" url=""><![CDATA[Acupuncture Stimulator - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Breast Enlargement Equipment and Medicomat Acupuncture Stimulator - Medicomat Polyclinic. A bruise can sometimes be associated with a temporary raised area in the skin. When a bruise fades, it becomes green and brown as the body metabolizes the blood cells and bilirubin pigment in the skin. A bruise is best treated with local application of a cold pack immediately after injury. <br /><br />The treatment of the headache depends on the type and severity of the headache and on other factors such as the age of the patient. <br /><br />A type of neurological disorder, intracranial hypertension is a condition where the pressure of the cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) inside the skull exceeds the normal range. The patient, in this case feels incessant pain in the head. This disease was also called Pseudotumor Cerebri and Benign Intracranial Hypertension. <br /><br />It may seem strange that stimulating certain areas on the body or ear with acupuncture can help to restore health, however if it were not successful at restoring health it would not have survived the 5000 years that it has. Perhaps the final word should be left to the people who use acupuncture. According to a survey of 20,000 people by the consumer association WHICH magazine, acupuncture is the fourth most popular treatment among the different complementary therapies. Over 80% of those who received acupuncture reported that they had benefitted from the treatment. <br /><br />Is acupuncture recognized methods? WHO (World Health Organization) in 1979. was verified as a method of acupuncture treatment in 120 diseases and conditions. <br /><br />The duration of treatment for acute oboljena - high intensity pulses lasting 10-15 minutes, two or three times a day. For chronic conditions - medium intensity pulses lasting 20-30 minutes, the two three times a day. Chronic diseases are treated longer (2-3 months). Treatment should be repeated daily. Any cure for seven days. Usually two or three are sufficient treatments, with a break of several days between courses. This treatment is completely safe and will not harm the use of the device for longer periods than recommended (for example, if the user falls asleep). <br /><br />Find out if I am the right practitioner for you - USD125 initial session,  USD75  follow up sessions. OR, get unlimited sessions with Medicomat apparatus for USD175 including airmail shipping. Many users have referred their friends, relatives, neighbors and colleagues for our Medicomat apparatus. This is the best compliment any health provider can receive. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="61e5b83efc830a1a901fee6c797dc600" url=""><![CDATA[Medical Device Acupuncture - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Hypertension Causes Cure and Medicomat Medical Device Acupuncture - Why Choose Lekomat Treatments. In general, stress is related to both external and internal factors. External factors include the physical environment, including your job, your relationships with others, your home, and all the situations, challenges, difficulties, and expectations you're confronted with on a daily basis. <br /><br />Lekomat apparatus cures diabetes and other diseases, and pain. The device detects and treat disorders of fully automatic using the principles of Chinese acupuncture and Japanese computer techniques. Treating poor circulation, diabetes, high blood pressure, headache, rheumatism, spondylosis, sciatica. It is used 2-3 times a day for 20-30 minutes. <br /><br />Safety Information - This device should not be used over acute swollen or skin eruption areas. People who have a pacemaker, defibrillator or installed metal device in their bodies should limit their use of these massage devices. If you are pregnant, please consult your doctor before using this product. This device can not be used on wet skin. Keep away from water and heat sources. Children should be supervised if operating this device. <br /><br />Acupuncture as a complementary therapy will help to reduce cravings to eat more than your body needs. Many people no matter how hard are trying to lose weight using traditional methods as diets and exercises find it extremely difficult to get rid of excessive pounds and stabilize weight. So if you are one of them look for alternatives like acupuncture therapy. <br /><br />LEKOMAT monitor for home treatment for sciatica all alone, fully automatic, find all the diseased parts of the body and automatically selects the appropriate acupuncture points through which the treatment is done. It is used 2-3 times a day for 20-30 minutes. Usually 2-3 treatments are sufficient for 7 days, and treatment of chronic illness takes longer. Reduce your daily use of drugs and medications. <br /><br />And Lekomat multi-functional treatment apparatus, in accordance with the theory that the human visceral organ bio-electricity discharge stroma and cells in the pathological conditions, which the inactivation of the sodium pump must be activated by external force in order to exert its function. The Lekomat benign bio-electricity airwaves assist cells restore the normal bio-electricity activity. <br /><br />Many migraine sufferers also experience attacks in low air pressure environments such as rainy weather, airplane trips, or climbing to high mountains. This phenomenon can also be explained by the parasympathetic rebound theory described above. It is known that the body is shifted more towards the sympathetic dominant state when in high air pressure (i.e; sunny days) and shifted to the parasympathetic dominant state during low air pressure such as on rainy days and in high altitude. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="13000c3a182c2abb9af787ba33682642" url=""><![CDATA[Therapeutic Head Massager - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Lateral Knee Pain Treatment and Medicomat Therapeutic Head Massager - Family Doctor Medicomat. At the end of the study showed that women who received real acupuncture reduced the intensity of heat waves and swings, and the results were getting better with treatment length. The researchers found that the release of endorphins suppress heat waves and stabilizes body temperature, but still can not say how much effect lasts after the acupuncture. <br /><br />Methods of operation: First connect the two wires with the ear mold, and wear them. Open the power strength switch, gradually pushing up from 1-5 till the maximum strength you can bear is good, whatever disease is required to do the ear needle treatment, 2-3 times every day, each time for 25-30 minutes (even longer time for treatment is no side effects). <br /><br />Acupuncture is a method of treatment of traditional Chinese medicine that is performed inserting thin needles into specific points on the body to restore or improve physical and spiritual health of individuals, but in the industrialized Western countries some doctors use it to achieve much more specific objectives. <br /><br />Golfers elbow is quite similar to tennis elbow except the inflammation occurs on the inside of the elbow, around the bone called the medial epicondyle. It too can be treated with acupuncture. Golfers elbow is also referred to as medial epicondylitis. The inner part of the elbow becomes painful and tender as a result of damage or tearing of the tendons and muscles of this area. <br /><br />The reasons for the overgrowth of fungus are unclear but may be related to increased oil production, hormonal changes, stress, neurologic disorders such as Parkinson's disease, recovery from chronic conditions such as stroke or heart attack, suppression of the immune system, and infrequent shampooing. There is also some evidence that dandruff may run in families. Scalp flakiness may also be caused by psoriasis or other skin ailments or infections. <br /><br />Research results are consistent with the theory that with stimulation of pain messages from the brain can block. Of 1100 patients undergoing examination and divided into groups with different therapeutic approach, improvement was felt 47 patients who had undergone acupuncture treatment, 44 patients with false acupuncture and 27 patients with conventional therapy. <br /><br />Severe menstrual cramps, particularly if paired with excessive bleeding or passage of large blood clots, can occasionally be a sign of endometriosis or other disorders of the female reproductive tract. Menstrual cramps are also known as dysmenorrhea. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f4232b97ca11b403afa65d3c49a41042" url=""><![CDATA[Home Massage Equipment - Distributors Wanted<br/><br/>Cause Of Vitiligo and Medicomat Home Massage Equipment - Lekomat Center. We provide high quality affordable health care. Orthopedic Acupuncture uses fine filaments to help relieve your painful muscles and joints. Ligaments can be strained or sprained causing restrictions in your movements. <br /><br />It’s believed that energy stream through the meridian points, thus acupuncture puts in needles in diverse parts of the body for smooth flow of energy. Inserting needles this way unblocks the energy points, and offers comfort from particular type of disease. <br /><br />Ear points detection and bidirectional diagnosis through hands and ears points: all kinds of potential diseases can be rapidly determined in a few minutes; the state of an illness without symptoms for the present can be correctly diagnosed, so as to give the efficacy of treating a disease in advance. <br /><br />There have been many studies that show a connection between acupuncture treatment and healing on many different levels. Allergies, asthma, arthritis, depression, fertility and migraine headaches are just a few of the many different conditions that have been shown in clinical settings to be helped with acupuncture treatments. <br /><br />Projecting parts holographic reflex theory has it, all biological and genetic information of human body are reduced on the projectingparts, such as ear, hand, foot and so on, in an orderly manner as small zones and acupuncture points. If there is any organ has pathological changes, the bio-resistance of corresponding acupuncture point in the projecting parts will be lower than before. Thus treatment and diagnosis can be achieved. <br /><br />Japanese method of treatment is generally very inconspicuous, minimalist way, acupuncture, and MOXIBUSTIA, which uses low IgE, which either does not pierce deep into akuta?ku, or the skin just above the akuta?ke scratch, the needle will remain very short, and so on. <br /><br />Acupuncture Treatment for Bell’s Palsy. Acupuncture has been very successful in treating this condition, especially if you start treatments early. It can get your face back to normal. Different doctors use different treatments, but they will usually use acupuncture, massage, therapeutic exercises and a heat lamp to stimulate acupuncture points to free up the flow in the body alleviating pain and reduce swelling. Compared to other ailments, Bell’s palsy takes a number of treatments; it may take up to 10 visits to get you back to normal. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7e4928f3de6d1584fb0ce1eed7255015" url=""><![CDATA[Electronic Acupuncture Device<br/><br/>There A Cure For Hyperhidrosis and Medicomat Electronic Acupuncture Device - Lekomat Positive Effects. Small household appliances for the treatment of hypertension using human bio-electricity to treat their own illnesses. Using this device the patient will no longer be exposed to the harmful effects and damage caused by excessive intake of drugs. The device is intended for users whose blood pressure exceeds 160/95 mmHg. Daily treatment of 50-10 minutes can reduce pressure for 20-30/5-10 mmHg. Blood pressure will be controlled after 5-7 treatments. <br /><br />Seizures can be caused by head injuries, brain tumors, lead poisoning, maldevelopment of the brain, genetic and infectious illnesses, and fevers. In fully half of the patients with seizures, no cause can yet be found. <br /><br />LEKOMAT monitor for home treatment of anxiety all the work I was totally automatic, finds all the disturbances and automatically treat anxiety and other disorders. It cures headaches, migraines, depression, high blood pressure, poor circulation, vertigo, rheumatism, spondylosis, sciatica, stomach ulcers, obesity, insomnia. <br /><br />Pain in the vagina or the female external genital organs (the vulva, which includes the labia, clitoris, and entrance to the vagina) most commonly is a result of infection. Vaginal pain during sexual intercourse is referred to as dyspareunia. Infection of the vagina is referred to as vaginitis. <br /><br />According to the theory of traditional Chinese medicine, human ear is just like a reverse foetus. Each human organ has its corresponding acupuncture point on the ear. When certain organ has pathological changes, the bioelectric current of the corresponding acupuncture point on the ear will change. By detecting the bioelectric changes, it can determine whether a certain organ is normal or abnormal or pathological. It differs from other devices in that it can give an early diagnosis in a few minutes and then result in an early treatment. <br /><br />There are many types of alopecia (hair loss), each with a different cause. Alopecia may be localized to the front and top of the head as in common male pattern baldness. It may be patchy as in a condition called alopecia areata. Or it can involve the entire head as in alopecia capitis totalis. <br /><br />Sensitivity to light is the inability to tolerate light, medically known as photophobia. In someone who is light sensitive, any type of light source (sunlight, fluorescent light, incandescent light) can cause discomfort. Photophobia typically causes a need to squint or close the eyes, and headache, nausea, or other symptoms may be associated with photophobia. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ce779dce9c5eb11cc6f353045f1dadd4" url=""><![CDATA[Laser Tens Acupuncture Therapy<br/><br/>Acne Cure At Home and Medicomat Laser Tens Acupuncture Therapy - Very Easy And Painless. Infections in the lungs, sinuses, or airways can also cause bad breath due to the presence of nasal secretions that may drain into the mouth. Coughing up sputum from lung infections can also cause bad breath. Dry mouth can be a side effect of certain medications, increasing the tendency to develop bad breath. Certain chronic diseases that severely restrict liver or kidney function may also alter the odor of the breath. <br /><br />Diseases are classified based on eight basic principles: hot-cold, surface-deep, extra-lack of energy, belonging to yin or yang. In addition, we distinguish between the internal, neutral, and external factors that can cause disease. Internal factors can be identified with the emotions. It is well known how much stress, worry or grief can affect our health. Neutral factors are usually in excess consumption of food, alcohol and drug abuse. External factors are highly expressed, because they relate to the impact of wind, cold, moisture or heat on our body. <br /><br />In another study, conducted in Norway, women are tested after the acupuncture treatment, which lasted 12 weeks, reported that heat waves less strength and less likely to occur. The researchers note that the sample is too small to be able to make a firm conclusion, but if future studies show the same results, acupuncture can be very important way to combat the symptoms of menopause, especially in women who are opposed to the use of hormone therapy. <br /><br />Auricular therapy is a branch of acupuncture specifically related to the ear. It is based on Traditional Chinese Medicine and is used to treat a variety of conditions. Ear acupuncture is a holistic approach to medicine that attempts to treat the entire person with acupuncture points found on the ear. <br /><br />Acupuncture is one of Oriental Medicine’s most important treatment modalities. Oriental medicine  is over 3000 years old. It is a refined medical system to diagnose, treat illnesses, prevent disease and improve well-being by restoring balance and harmony within the body. <br /><br />When you normally think of acupuncture, you think of a person sitting with several needles inserted into their skin, into parts of the body like the ear, the arm, or the wrist. This is a good picture of a patient that is having an acupuncture treatment. These treatments last anywhere from a very short time up to thirty minutes or more, depending on the symptoms that are being treated. These needles are more frequently inserted just far enough into the skin to firmly keep them there, though an acupuncture practitioner may insert different needles somewhat further in depending on the treatment plan. Sometimes the needles are twirled in place, sometimes they are warmed before insertion, or have heat applied to them during insertion. Generally there is no discomfort when a needle is inserted, manipulated, or removed. Occasionally a slight twinge may be felt, but not more than that. <br /><br />The practitioners of this acupuncture treatment have to undergo a special acupuncture-training course. This method can also be carried out without the needles and is used according to the conditions. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="956ed56feabdf2176c96acd4f2eb1d2e" url=""><![CDATA[Disease Detecting And Curing Apparatus<br/><br/>Somnabulismus Therapy and Medicomat Disease Detecting And Curing Apparatus - A Successful Medicobot. People with a depressive disease cannot merely pull themselves together and get better. Without treatment, symptoms can last for weeks, months, or years. Appropriate treatment, however, can help most people with depression. <br /><br />The most common cause of a toothache is a dental cavity. The second most common cause is gum disease. Toothache can be caused by a problem that does not originate from a tooth or the jaw. <br /><br />LEKOMAT monitor for home treatment treating anxiety and other disorders detected and treated disorders fully automatically using the principles of Chinese acupuncture and Japanese computer techniques. Treating migraines, depression, poor circulation, diabetes, high blood pressure, headache, rheumatism, spondylosis. <br /><br />A seizure is the uncontrolled electrical activity in the brain, which may produce a physical convulsion, minor physical signs, thought disturbances, or a combination of symptoms. <br /><br />Blisters are small raised areas that are filled with fluid and located in the superficial layer of the skin. They look like bubbles on the surface of the skin. Although they are often caused by irritation or friction, blisters can also represent disease processes. <br /><br />LEKOMAT monitor for home Spondylosis Treatment works on the principle of electronic acupuncture without needles without pain, and improve the feel, but after a day or two. Treating spondylosis, rheumatism, sciatica, headaches, migraines, depression, high blood pressure, poor circulation, diabetes, dizziness, stomach ulcers, obesity, insomnia, menstrual problems. <br /><br />apparatus for Home Treatment LEKOMAT everything is fully automatic - the examinations and then carries out acupuncture treatment without needles, without pain. The list of diseases that monitor for home treatment is a long LEKOMAT treated and feel improvements after only a day or two. It is particularly effective in bronchitis, asthma, allergies, headaches, insomnia, stress, obesity. In a few minutes automatically reduces pain in the stomach, back, neck and legs. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f78e0ad2ebfdd24c4e779fb94f117e94" url=""><![CDATA[Tens Acupuncture Therapy Machine<br/><br/>Acupuncture Heart Problems and Medicomat Tens Acupuncture Therapy Machine - Medicobot Health. It would be even more time before we would accept the concept that acupuncture weight loss was another possibility for this strange eastern practice. <br /><br />A number of factors can cause this imbalance, but again we are seeing stress and lifestyle (especially diet) as major contributors. Your doctor will start by using acupuncture to release blockages, but you will have to compliment the acupuncture therapy with dietary and lifestyle changes to see them really go away. <br /><br />Daily treatment of 50-10 minutes can reduce pressure for 20-30/5-10 mmHg. Blood pressure will be controlled after 5-7 treatments. Two treatments of 10-20 minutes a day can stabilize blood pressure and hypertension in more pronounced. Therapy can be a supplement or alternative to medication for a gradual reduction in medication. <br /><br />Facial Rejuvenation - Beauty comes from within. On a physiological level, Medicomat device continually stimulates the holographic acupuncture points, helps cell reproduction and growth, increases microcirculations, adjusts endocrine system, decompounds melanocyte, balances skin color and makes you look more radiant. <br /><br />Depression is an illness that involves the body, mood, and thoughts and affects the way a person eats and sleeps, the way one feels about oneself, and the way one thinks about things. Depressive disorders are characterized by pervasive mood changes that affect all aspects of an individual's daily functioning. <br /><br />Numbness or tingling sensations in the tongue, medically known as paresthesia of the tongue, most commonly occur due to damage to the nervous system. The medical term for the absence of sensation is anesthesia. <br /><br />The device is intended for users whose blood pressure exceeds 160/95 mmHg. The treatment is safe and without harmful effects. Using this device the patient will no longer be exposed to the harmful effects and damage caused by excessive intake of drugs. <br /><br />Visit the site &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.lekomat.org</a>' target='_blank'&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flekomat.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://lekomat.org</a>[/url], it lets you expirience pain and disease relief in the comfort of your own home. Medicomat a fully automatic apparatus for home cure, alternative therapy, &lt;a href='<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicobot.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.medicobot.com</a>' target='_blank'&gt;pain treatment[/url] and &lt;a href='' target='_blank'&gt;healthcare at home[/url]. Affiliates and Distributors Wanted.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>