<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="11">
		<document id="c9bed958e6475e41668c74d9f28b7eb5" url=""><![CDATA[An angel<br/><br/>the face of an angel is all that is there
<br />one beautiful freckle eguals one terrifed tear
<br />not ready to leave but has to go 
<br />wants to go back but god says no
<br />leaving your life is a scary thought 
<br />but i guess it's something that can't be fought
<br />a mother,a father, a sister, and friends
<br />a meaningful life that suddenly ends
<br />an angel is ehat she was meant to be 
<br />now think of all she can see
<br />looking over her friends night and day
<br />saying i love you in her own special way
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2dc7a05268aac81b8c4d5e66f23a6815" url=""><![CDATA[Faith, hope, and Heart<br/><br/>I was once told only in dreams
<br />Do dreams come true.
<br />But I'm to tell, here and now,
<br />Your dreams are up to you.
<br />Like &quot;The Rose&quot;,
<br />we may pass through life
<br />&quot;Not Understood&quot;.
<br />And maybe we won't
<br />make all the friends we should.
<br />But always treasure what you have
<br />and in the mirror what you see,
<br />Then strive to get all you can
<br />and be all that you may be.
<br />On the rocky roads of life,
<br />you must be strong to fall apart.
<br />But, I tell you from my soul to keep
<br />Faith, Hope, and Heart.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e7acafd529ca76eeedfbed8ddcc2ddf9" url=""><![CDATA[goodbye<br/><br/>Her tears did freely flow
<br />As I told her I have to go
<br />She continued to cry
<br />As she spluttered out &quot;Why?&quot;
<br />Whilst I calmly explained
<br />I was asked, &quot; Is it me? Am I to be blamed?&quot;
<br /><br />Reassuring her that she is one I could never shun
<br />My reasons had nothing to do with anything that she had done
<br />My move, many times has it been delayed
<br />If things had of worked out different, I would be able to stay
<br />She gave me a hug, wet cheek resting upon mine
<br /><br />Granted we will be many miles apart
<br />We will still be as one in the heart
<br />At first the distance between us will be strange
<br />Remember, you are my daughter, that will never change
<br />In the background played a song on a cassette
<br />It is one neither of us will forget
<br /><br />I first heard it on the wonderful morn
<br />As I was told my daughter was born
<br />It is called &quot;A little ray of sunshine&quot;
<br />Forever will it be hers and mine
<br />I can still see the tears glistening in her eyes
<br />I can still hear her disdained cries
<br /><br />Although I know I am right with what I have to do
<br />My heart is still broken, torn in two
<br />My love for her is stronger than bricks and mortar
<br />She is my babe, my one and only daughter
<br />Her tears did freely flow
<br />As I told her I have to go.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5ca6dc568c5a3192a85cc2e0b15e2774" url=""><![CDATA[Baby I Love You<br/><br/>Sweet baby I 
<br />love you for real 
<br />I can't explain 
<br />just how I feel 
<br />You are to me 
<br />a special love 
<br />And the love I
<br />feel is from above 
<br />To never hurt you 
<br />is my true desire 
<br />Yet right now 
<br />my heart is on fire 
<br />It burns in away 
<br />I can't explain 
<br />Completely different 
<br />from other pains 
<br />It's sadness 
<br />yet joyful too 
<br />Devastated
<br />yet hopes crushed 
<br />Still strongly unbearable
<br />yet copes 
<br />Baby I love you 
<br /><br />Amanda always know that i will always love u and that i will be there for u until the end.. or so i thought
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c5c8318b811602f84b36f9d95ebe2b2d" url=""><![CDATA[Ready 4 love?<br/><br/>Take my hand and lead the way;
<br />tell me all you want to say.
<br />Whisper softly in my ear,
<br />all those things I want to hear.
<br />Kiss my lips and touch my skin;
<br />bring out passions deep within.
<br />Pull me close and hold me near;
<br />take away my pain and fear.
<br />In the darkness of the night,
<br />be my beacon, shine your light.
<br />In the brightness of the sun,
<br />show me that you are the one.
<br />Give me wings so I can fly;
<br />for I can soar when you're nearby.
<br />Enter my heart, break down the wall,
<br />it's time for me to watch it fall.
<br />I've been a prisoner, can't you see?
<br />Break my chains and set me free.
<br />Strip me of my armor tight;
<br />you'll find I won't put up a fight.
<br />Release my soul held deep within . . .
<br />I'm ready now, let love begin.
<br />for u amanda
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="136d5f5cca97245c68baa6a9a0b78a2e" url=""><![CDATA[Amanda, my true love...<br/><br/>I never thought that you would be my life
<br />my heart and my eyes.
<br />I never thought that loving you would be so beautiful
<br />so unbelievable and so true.
<br />I never thought that being with you would be so warm
<br />so honest and so great.
<br /><br />In each moment, you belong to me
<br />I join my dreams with reality
<br />inspired by the wonderful sound of your voice
<br />and the sparkling looks of your eyes.
<br /><br />You have changed my world
<br />and added new taste to my life.
<br /><br />Although the distance between us is miles away,
<br />believe me, you are closer to my heart than my blood veins.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24688d00a99ab69a69bf4ee83c02535c" url=""><![CDATA[unconditional<br/><br/>No hesitation,
<br />No Disbelief at all.
<br />My love and desire for you,
<br />Is nowhere near small.
<br />You keep my heart beating,
<br />You brighten my day.
<br />No one can make me smile like u do,
<br />There's no possible way.
<br />You complete me,
<br />Really, you do.
<br />There is absolutely no trouble,
<br />For me to say &quot;I Love You&quot;.
<br />I love you for you,
<br />The past means nothing.
<br />Me, you, and the future,
<br />That, for me, is everything.
<br />I give you my heart,
<br />Let me hold yours.
<br />I know its still fragile,
<br />But ill cherish it, love it,
<br />Always and forevermore.
<br />love u amanda
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d307ee19ae04aa75a4b78098fd8bc756" url=""><![CDATA[i love you baby<br/><br/>I love you so much. People say that at my age, I don't really know what love is. Well, then maybe there's another explanation for the way I feel about you. How every second I am away from you seems like an eternity. How every time I try to think of something else, I can only think of one thing, and that's you. How every time I see you, I smile more and more, and how I'm so happy I could cry. How every time I talk of you to others I feel like a giddy little kid with a secret to tell. How every time I speak, I want to tell someone how wonderful you are. How the times I'm most happy are when I am with you and I miss you the most right after I leave your side. Maybe there is another explanation for this uncontrollable feeling inside of me, but right now, I'll hold the thought that I love you inside my heart forever. 4 amanda
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1e23c1f027c61ee6998f3cd46a8126a1" url=""><![CDATA[Soldiers<br/><br/>I want to thank all of those soldiers that are defending our freedom and trying their best to keep the USA safe from terrorism and from x-president bush <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/ranting2.gif" alt=":)" />. you guys are over there working and defending us and the soldiers who are at home keeping the united states from falling apart thank you and the soldiers that have stuck up and defended me and my beautiful fiance amanda. i am hoping i can be over there soon to stop this war or have my own word in. god bless america. Third Class Private Jason B. Bennetts-Chemical Ops Specialist
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9a23d21a4cb4e488ddcd0beaba4bf28" url=""><![CDATA[read<br/><br/>/ A true boyfriend would.....
<br />• Grab her butt when you kiss her, it's a real turn on. 
<br /><br />• Stay on the phone with her even if shes not saying anything. 
<br /><br />• When she's mad hug her tight and don't let go then kiss her 
<br /><br />• When she says she's ok dont believe it talk with her 
<br /><br />• remember her..because 10 yrs later she'll remember you 
<br /><br />• Call her at 12:00am on her birthday to tell her you love her 
<br /><br />• Call her before you sleep and after you wake up 
<br /><br />• Treat her like she's all that matters to you. 
<br /><br />• Tease her and let her tease you back. 
<br /><br />• Stay up all night with her when she's sick. 
<br /><br />• Watch her favorite movie with her. 
<br /><br />* stick up for her even if you're friends don't like her 
<br /><br />• Give her the world. 
<br /><br />• Let her wear your clothes. 
<br /><br />• When she's bored and sad, hang out with her. 
<br /><br />* give her your jacket when she's cold 
<br /><br />• Let her know she's important. 
<br /><br />• Kiss her in the pouring rain. 
<br /><br />• When she runs up at you crying, the first thing you say is; 
<br />&quot;Who's ass am I kicking babe?&quot; 
<br /><br />If you do post this in the next four minutes the one you love will : 
<br />•Call you. 
<br />•Kiss you. 
<br />•Love you. 
<br />•Text you.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ff32155f8c0a6b96129bdb8fdb9466dc" url=""><![CDATA[untitled<br/><br/>So near yet so far,
<br />The love that was once there is now lost,
<br />never to be seen again,
<br />her smile,
<br />grace,
<br />laughter,
<br />beauty,
<br />all memories lost forever,
<br />the joy replaced by burning and dread,
<br />her touch a distant memory,
<br />broken,
<br />dead, 
<br />is there a point in living for tomorrow?
<br />no more waking to see her smiling face,
<br />no more looking forward to and dreaming of our wedding day,
<br />no more of ... anything...
<br />just those last words repeating in my head,
<br />pain,
<br />silence...
<br />darkness...
<br />tears...
<br />misery.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>