<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="13">
		<document id="7b6e0c0c432f4ada292b11c9aac93908" url=""><![CDATA[who am i ?!?<br/><br/>Who am i really i dont know
<br />I've started to cut maself  so does that mean Im EMO <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> i get called emo cuz i cut Maself. I cut ma wrist today again. Why the Fuk am i doin this <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" /> i cut maself yesterday coz I was confused and depressed. I h8 lyf at Times. i lyk this person and i dont kno why though i mean as if hes gonna lyk me bak  hes prob to gewd for meh  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> will anyone understand me. Im just a confused girl in a cruel world. 
<br /><br />WHO AM I ?!?
<br /><br />i will find out one day <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/book.gif" alt=":)" /> who i really am and find my true self
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="371f357c5803b0567b0c278654f1d838" url=""><![CDATA[EMOS<br/><br/>why do ppl dis emos 
<br />some recken they r fuked up and desreve to die but they have  more of a right to live then the ppl that dis emos.
<br />and y do they think there gay??? honsetly
<br /><br />if you support emos or are one
<br />let me kno wat u think of ppl that say shit lyk this coz i beleive it just aint right
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e7094ecefc8217053ae64b1085a58e63" url=""><![CDATA[BoYfRiEnD aApLiCaTiOn<br/><br/>1. Your Name:
<br />2. Age:
<br />3. Fave Color:
<br />4. Whats your sign?
<br />5.Phone Number/e mail (if i dont have it):
<br />6. Location:
<br />7. Height:
<br />8.Hair (color and style):
<br />9.Piercings/tattoos:
<br /><br />HERE COMES THE FUN ... ... ...
<br />1. Are we friends?
<br />2. Do you have a crush on me?
<br />3. Would you kiss me?
<br />4. ...with tongue?
<br />5. Would you enjoy it?
<br />6. Would you ever ask me out?
<br />7. Would you make a move on me in a movie theater?
<br />9. Would you take care of me when I'm sick?
<br />10. Do you want to tell me something that you couldn't before?
<br />11.Would you walk on the beach with me?
<br />12. If you heard a rumor about me, would you defend me?
<br />13. Do you/have you talked about me?
<br />14. Do you think I'm a good person?
<br />15. Would u take a nap with me?
<br />16.Do you think I'm cute?
<br />17. If you could change anything about me -would you?
<br />18.Would you dance with me?
<br />19.Would you come over for no reason just to hang out?
<br /><br />What Do You Think Of My?
<br />1.Personality:
<br />2.Eyes:
<br />3.Face:
<br />4.Hair:
<br /><br />W0ULD Y0U...
<br />give me your number?_______________
<br />kiss me?
<br />let me kiss you?
<br />watch a movie with me?
<br />take me out to dinner?
<br />drive me somewhere?
<br />hug me?
<br />buy me food?
<br />take me home to meet your family?
<br />would you let me sleep in your bed if i didn't have one?
<br />sing car karaoke w/ me?
<br />sit in the doctors office with me because I didn't want to go alone?
<br />re-post this for me to answer your questions?
<br />give me a piggyback ride?
<br />come pick me up at 3 am because my car ran out of gas in the middle of nowhere?
<br /><br />HAVE Y0U EVER...
<br />thought about me?
<br />thought there might be an &quot;US&quot;?
<br />thought about hookin up with me?
<br />found yourself wanting to kiss me?
<br />wished i were there?
<br /><br />If you don't repost this, your crush will never notice you again.
<br />ladies repost this as Boyfriend application
<br />boys repost this as Girlfriend application
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="21fae3a37ef7495758b03502b04b77d9" url=""><![CDATA[DADDY PLEASE NO<br/><br/>DADDY PLEASE NO 
<br />This is just wrong.. 
<br /><br />you are one sick person if you dont repost this i feel for you if 
<br />this doesnt touch you because this is just wrong. read this. its disgusting 
<br /><br />Walking in my nighty; rubbing my eyes 
<br />My fathers sitting on the sofa with his friend 
<br />He pats the seat in the middle; i sit 
<br />Shivering so cold; a quilt he lends 
<br /><br />&quot;Jessy you love me don't you&quot; a smile; his 
<br />Their breathe spirts weep 
<br />&quot;Daddy you know i do; what is it?&quot; 
<br />He smiles at his friend; his hand creeps 
<br /><br />His friend takes my hand; looks me in the eyes 
<br />Daddys creeping up my nightie; cold hands 
<br />I try to pull his hand away; 
<br />their grip is strong! 
<br />They look at one another; nod; something planned 
<br /><br />I feel my palms sweat; Daddys under my knickers 
<br />&quot;Daddy im going to bed! Night&quot; Pulling again 
<br />But there grip is to strong for weak me 
<br />I look at both; and ask, who are these men? 
<br /><br />His fingers going up me; pulling away 
<br />His friend leans forward; a kiss? Why? 
<br />His toungue moving mine; my eyes squint 
<br />Lean back and away; &quot;Why are you doing this?&quot; 
<br />No answer, i feel the pain inside me; him 
<br />Chucks the quilt on the floor; me to 
<br />I try and scamper away, but im not fast 
<br />&quot;O Daddy please, i love you&quot; 
<br /><br />His friend; pulling at my nightie 
<br />And my Dad pulling my pants down 
<br />His friend pinning my hands to the floor 
<br />As my Dad lies himself on the ground 
<br /><br />I squirm; as Daddy friend pulls me up 
<br />And places me ontop of Daddy; thrusts within 
<br />I cry; i bite; i scratch; i slap; i fail 
<br />&quot;O Daddy please you win you win!&quot; 
<br /><br />I can feel my skin rip; my virginity breaking free 
<br />I can feel the blood seep down my leg 
<br />&quot;Daddy your hurting me please&quot; 
<br />I plead to him and his friend; not even a beg 
<br /><br />Daddys laughing; why does he laugh? 
<br />His friend shoves himself in my mouth and moans 
<br />Tieing my hands together; moving in and out 
<br />&quot;Ride me Jessy&quot; He laughs and groans 
<br /><br />They smile at one another; laugh to 
<br />They roll me over and spread me wide well 
<br />My daddy sits on my face; himself in again 
<br />While his friend talks and pushes himself inside 
<br /><br />I can hardly breathe; i gag for air 
<br />I cough and splutter; cry and weep 
<br />I beg and plead; but its no use 
<br />Theyve already made me hurt and bleed 
<br /><br />I stare into his eyes; that look upon me 
<br />This is not my Dad; where is he? 
<br />If he was still here; would he care 
<br />Would he actually even; see? 
<br /><br />Finally they get of and lie me on the sofa 
<br />My cheeks blouchy from tears and pain 
<br />They play with them selfs; all over me 
<br />Rub it in; making me feel the shame 
<br /><br />&quot;Why Daddy? Please tell me why?&quot; 
<br />Dad looks at his friend; and waves him away 
<br />&quot;Jessy i love you&quot; he smiles and kisses my cheek 
<br />&quot;Is that all you have in your heart to say?&quot; 
<br /><br />He puts my nightie on me 
<br />he walks me to my bedroom door 
<br />Ever since that night; His friend 
<br />And himself every Friday come back for more 
<br /><br />&quot;Night sweet Girl; You are my life&quot; 
<br />Closing the door, tears still down my face 
<br />Still the smell of him and his friend 
<br />Fade into me like disgrace 
<br /><br />I watch the Moon go down; the sun come up 
<br />&quot;Jessy its school&quot; Knocking at my door 
<br />I cant help but cry; weep in pain 
<br />Because im so scared he wanted more 
<br /><br />But one night daddy took it too far 
<br />Daddy and his friend came back for one last shot 
<br />They were worried they would get caught 
<br />So he and his friend took me to a cemetary lot 
<br /><br />I was blindfolded and my hands were tied back 
<br />&quot;Daddy please!! Not tonight!&quot; 
<br />Daddy and his friend both had their last fun 
<br />After that i tried to put up a fight 
<br /><br />I begged daddy &quot;Please no more!&quot; 
<br />All he could say &quot;Shut up, you stupid Bitch!&quot; 
<br />Daddy unblindfolded me at last 
<br />He said I love you so much 
<br /><br />He went back into the car and pulled out a bat 
<br />&quot;Daddy I swear I wont say a thing!!!!&quot; 
<br />I was dead 
<br />After only one swing.......................... 
<br /><br />**... Please if you care for all the children and women who have been raped 
<br />repost this bulletin with the Headline &quot;daddy please no&quot; 
<br /><br />If you do not repost this you are promoting rape and violence and you are a horrible person!!!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eaf8996f1377c9ca6febc852bf236be0" url=""><![CDATA[EMO POEM<br/><br/>The cutting has began
<br />Hiding my wrists
<br />From what ive done 
<br />Am I becoming Emo
<br />Becoming depressed at times
<br />No one understands me
<br />I don’t know who I am anymore
<br />My vision I cannot see
<br />Will anyone understand
<br />Im blood through to the core
<br />I cut to deep
<br />I freak
<br />So scared if I have cut my vein or not
<br />But I haven’t
<br />I see the Light 
<br />It’s so Bright
<br />My vision has cleared
<br />The cutting has ended
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="36630f0789aefdfdacd3a764f09fcefe" url=""><![CDATA[Her Silent Death<br/><br/>As the Sun Sets
<br />The Moon will Rise
<br />The Night Gets Dark
<br />All the Lights Go Out
<br />In Her Street
<br />People go to bed 
<br />To Wake Up in the Morning
<br />But She Wont Be
<br /><br />Shes Sad
<br />Shes Upset
<br />Hates Her Life so Much
<br />She wants it to Stop
<br />Forever and be of no more
<br />Feeling this Horrible Pain
<br /><br />Staring out the Window
<br />Looking Upon the Dark Night
<br />Decides to go out There
<br /><br />She Carry's a Knife
<br />In Her Hand Of Fate
<br />FInding a Place So Silent
<br />So Peaceful
<br /><br />She Stands there
<br />With her Hand of Fate
<br />She Does It
<br />Gets Rid Of it
<br />The Hurtful Life Long Pain
<br />Falls to the Ground
<br />Lying There Motionless
<br />Heart Stabbed
<br />Eyes upon showing her Pain
<br />There she had
<br />Her Silent Death
<br /><br />I Wrote This Last Year
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8c708aa990530893bb136ec49ee8228a" url=""><![CDATA[WhEn A gIrL mISsEs YoU..........<br/><br/>Girl facts...x: 
<br /><br />When you catch a girl 
<br />glancing at you, 
<br />she wants you to look 
<br />back and smile...x 
<br /><br />When a girl bumps into your arm 
<br />while walking with you 
<br />she wants 
<br />you to hold her hand...x 
<br /><br />When she wants a hug 
<br />she will just stand there...x 
<br /><br />When u break a girls heart 
<br />she still feels it when 
<br />you run into each other 3 years later...x 
<br /><br />When a girl is quiet, 
<br />millions of things are running through her 
<br />mind...x 
<br /><br />When a girl is not arguing, 
<br />she is thinking deeply...x 
<br /><br />When a girl looks at you with eyes full of 
<br />questions, 
<br />she is wondering how long you will be 
<br />around...x 
<br /><br />When a girl answers, &quot;I'm fine,&quot; after a 
<br />few seconds, 
<br />she is not at all fine...x 
<br /><br />When a girl stares at you, 
<br />she is wondering why you are playing games...x 
<br /><br />When a girl lays her head on your chest, 
<br />she is wishing for you to be hers forever...x 
<br /><br />When a girl says she can't live 
<br />without you, 
<br />she has made up her mind that you are 
<br />her future...x 
<br /><br />When a girl says, &quot;I miss you,&quot; 
<br />no one in this world can miss you more 
<br />than that...x 
<br /><br />When a girl is mean to you after a break-up 
<br />she wants you back, but shes 
<br />scared she'll get hurt and knows 
<br />you're gone forever...x 
<br /><br />Guy Facts...x: 
<br /><br />When a guy calls you, 
<br />he wants to be with you...x 
<br /><br />When a guy is quiet, 
<br />He's listening to you...x 
<br /><br />When a guy is not arguing, 
<br />He realizes he's wrong...x 
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I'm fine.&quot; after a few 
<br />minutes 
<br />he means it...x 
<br /><br />When a guy stares at you, 
<br />he wishes you would care about him and 
<br />wonders if you do...x 
<br /><br />When your laying your head on a guy's 
<br />chest, 
<br />he has the world...x 
<br /><br />When a guy calls/texts/comments you everyday, 
<br />he is in love...x 
<br /><br />When a (good) guy tells you he loves you, 
<br />he means it...x 
<br /><br />When a guy says he can't live without you, 
<br />he's with you til your done...x 
<br /><br />When a guy says, &quot;I miss you,&quot; 
<br />he misses you more than you could have 
<br />ever missed him or anything else...x 
<br /><br />repost this in 10 minutes and your true 
<br />love will 
<br />call you 
<br /><br />someone was in your mind as you read this?? 
<br /><br />Post this as 
<br /><br />IF YOUR A GUY &quot; When a guy misses you...&quot; 
<br /><br />AND 
<br /><br />IF YOUR A GIRL POST IT AS &quot;When a girl misses you...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5a4155de6ef9c665fe1edf42e9b44245" url=""><![CDATA[Dieing Love - Poem<br/><br/>It started strong
<br />For so long
<br />As it opened up
<br />It got shut down
<br />After a while it was left 
<br />For love felt untouched
<br />tried again and again
<br />Love was feeling pain
<br />Feeling like its waisting time
<br />Time is running out for this
<br />Dieing Love
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3b2c8d5ba58a84d78d1c11df90464133" url=""><![CDATA[HI EVERYBODY<br/><br/>HI EVERYONE
<br /><br />I havent been on pan.netin ages because of my internet got stuffed up so i couldnt update anything <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />
<br />Life has been great besides a few family things thats on so sorry i will try to get some new ones ASAP promise.
<br />Cant wait till my birthday im so excited yay im gonna be 15 finally.
<br /><br />please reply to my blog i wanna see how my friends on pan.netare goin i  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> all mi friends pan.net
<br /><br />chat laterz bye xx.. having breake
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="512da8c78fb825575c2a199ce36e095f" url=""><![CDATA[Work Experience<br/><br/>hi mi bootiful guyz 'n' galz
<br /><br />Im at work experience atm yay wat fun its like a day spa so they do massages, waxing and all that kinda stuff. its only for 5days and this is day 1, four more days to go cant wait lol.
<br />i finished skool on friday went home at lunch time so that was pretti radicule.
<br />Anywayz the phone has only rang once so far, thank goodness for that.
<br /><br />chany ..xx..
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e3e9429cf340d784118945e4cbb86efd" url=""><![CDATA[Broken Heart Poem<br/><br/>This life is sin
<br />Its like suicide everyday
<br />Breaking apart into pieces
<br />of the most broken heart
<br />Wishing it would stop
<br />No longer to be beating and alive
<br /><br />Some days this heart loves 
<br />Some days this heart needs
<br />This heart will always grieve
<br />As dark as pain its self it still breaths
<br /><br />This heart use to be red for loving 
<br />This heart is now black 
<br />For all the hatred it has
<br />Stitch this broken heart back
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="de4567fbdb6ab7b8c4cc3e2aea7cfc50" url=""><![CDATA[suggest things<br/><br/>Hey people, if anyone is reading this
<br /><br />I havent done a blog in like forever so i though i mite update mi friends on here and whoever looks at mi profile.
<br /><br />So i officially have a boyfriend now um hes on pan.netaswell but dnt have many friends, i think his pan.netis Kaboomsta. been wit him for like 3weeks nd counting.
<br /><br />Christmas is coming up very soon YAY im hopefully gonna get mi hair dyed b4 chrissy im gonna go blueberry again coz i love that colour.
<br /><br />Im gonna be year 11 next year scary as lol cant wait not. and that will be mi final year of school because i dont wanna go to yr12 dont think i will be able to handle it.
<br /><br />I was thinking if you like reading mi poems, blogs, looking at mi pics mayb you could suggest things to mi like um shout outs to people, writing poems, doing blogs anything like that even doin pix nothing dirty though mayb videos only mayb so if you have any idea send mi a private message  or a comment on ur idea or this blog message
<br /><br />thanx for reading mi blog if you read this far i love ya for it 
<br />peace out chany xx
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e99d7c270c69a6ab2c5b88b0448cbb84" url=""><![CDATA[She was the Scene Queen of Mean<br/><br/>She has always been the Queen
<br />Duh of mean Scene
<br />She thinks she rules the school
<br />Everyday shes wearing stacks of make-up
<br />Walking around with her followers
<br />All the guys thinks shes hot
<br />But shes just a slut
<br /><br />She got expelled for pashing a cute guy
<br />The next day she got redeemed
<br /><br />As i said she was the Scene Queen of Mean
<br />We use to be friends 
<br />But shes only fake nice to me now
<br />I went to the toilets only to find on the bathroom mirror
<br />It was horrific blood from the Scene Queen 
<br />She was in much pain
<br />She looked at me the shame in her eyes
<br />I could see she hurt
<br />Crying her eyes out
<br />Make-up running
<br /><br />Seeing her like that her pink ink hair
<br />I couldnt help but stare
<br />The poor love
<br /><br />Scene Queen told me everything she was, was fake
<br />Just like make-up, hiding everything
<br />Scene Queen said shes really Emo
<br />The Sceen was just a front
<br />Like i said she <span style="text-decoration:underline">was</span> the Scene Queen of Mean
<br /><br />hope ya like mi new poem it didnt take too long to write
<br />please comment ur thoughts on it and if i should do a sequel to it
<br />thnx chany
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>