<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="10">
		<document id="2dd37692d3abd85f8161a467c6652194" url=""><![CDATA[:-<br/><br/>after a long long time writing here again, don't know what to tell about what happened to me since last time wrote here...
<br />I've got lots of problems... problems ?? (I don't know if that word is proper!)
<br />anyways, I've been through a lot, I still am... so it's a few days I'm thinking about visiting a doc, a psychologist. hope it helps.
<br />today I'm going to plan for my coming exams, and I swear I'll study ... I wanna stop screwing up.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="553c42f319f9a6ad62d3f171dd3c0ce7" url=""><![CDATA[depression<br/><br/>Yeah,,, again I'm depressed .......
<br />many bad things come, and I let them come,,,, and after a while, since I'm human being not a piece of metal , I break down,,,, I get depressed .... here u go ... enjoy your depression ....
<br />I knew all of them , every thing, has effect on me, but the fact that I look ! healthy and ok doesn't mean I shouldn't take care of myself ...
<br />you've had this experience like a million times before,,,,, why are u repeating it ???????
<br />I guess it's something so foundational. yes, it is.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="34b880c892c55a0bbc5039a948460fbc" url=""><![CDATA[ciao!<br/><br/>hi, this is the first time i'm using this website and amir naimi is the only friend and caller of me.
<br />let's see how it works !!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ec3ea38abe623d897b1024253994ee70" url=""><![CDATA[today and yesterday<br/><br/>hey,
<br />you know, yesterday I woke up fresh did my exercise, took shower and was full of energy for a new day, and I did my work very well and funny and strange things happened to me.
<br />today I woke up, was too difficult to get out of bed and my eyes were half closed for 2,3 hours !! no exercise, no washing, nothing, went to toilet 2 times in the morn' !! and 2 very bad things happened to me.
<br />I can't believe it, the secret movie was repeating for me exactly the same.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f2517b0541c98a10ea689114506c44b6" url=""><![CDATA[boyz!<br/><br/>Hi,
<br />I don't know what I should do that the boys just leave  me alone to live my life with liberty.
<br />really I'm looking for an answer, you guys are really stupid (I'm sorry) and i just don't want to spend a minute of my life with you. just wanna live my own life
<br />and as pcd says, i don't need a man to make me feel good , and I do all my things myself. I don't want you near meeeee
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cf59328b28aa9f28f27a6b7914a7f6f4" url=""><![CDATA[Donald Trump<br/><br/>he has written a book named ' Think Big and  Kick Ass ' I love this book, I have the Persian version which I bought in book fair in Iran, and I love it.
<br />it gives lots of energy to go. whenever I read a part of it , then I just want to fly away and do something big, cause I have thought big !!! that's the only book I carry around whenever I go and whenever I am in the bus or waiting for sth , i read a few pages ,but I'm finishing it.
<br />I really love him, he is my idol, I define success in him. he is successful and happy, and I want to be happy and successful.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4fcc0372bef560079f2e5186da7ad238" url=""><![CDATA[the world<br/><br/>I can't believe it, how the world in moving.
<br />today I heard a very very bad news, that made me even cry after 3 weeks, and I am shocked.
<br />I'm 100% sure that every things is going to go very well, and I believe that great things are on the way to happen to me. but now,
<br />I know I just need to relax my mind and don't think about the problem itself , just think about the solutions.
<br />there are thousands of solutions out there , I need to find them.
<br />I exactly know how this world works , I don't need to worry. every thing will be cool after a little while, if I keep my faith, if I just be positive and still be thankful.
<br /><br />I'm writing this after a few hours, I've heard some news ! but that problem is kind of solved now. and I'm happy about it. although this problem just reminded me of the other big problems , but that concern is now gone and I feel better now,really
<br />Thanks God and the existence and all the good , great people around me for the information, for their support and every thing.
<br />I really feel lighter than before <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="51fff030b97b72ccc8bdf830d25e660f" url=""><![CDATA[first exam<br/><br/>Ooooh, finally did it <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> yeah , today I gave my first exam in Rome ! I had to do it to show myself that it's not that scary and it's very normal to give an exam more than once, so I now feel better, in terms of faith and confidence in myself
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="178a1cfee5b5e42f981b32b9fe96ab64" url=""><![CDATA[changing the major<br/><br/>Hi, I came to Italy to study Artificial Intelligence and Robotics !!! and I guess I had made the worse choice ever !!! haa haa haaa, yeah. you know it's good chance to know that the path you've taken is a wrong path. and you have the fortune of changing it. this is amazing. 
<br />now i'm understanding why I couldn't go to Germany and all the doors got closed, cause it has not been a good choice for  me, you know , of course it's better than Italy but when you consider it entirely you'll see the computer science has not been a good choice, maybe yeah good for my bachelor but not for master.
<br />and I figured out something!
<br />you know, I've always had this vision of being a boss/ manager in the future, since I've been in high school.
<br />and it's been always my final goal and even though I've always thought of studying computer science or AI, but this never has been my destination to be a programmer. never. 
<br />when ever I wrote down my goals I wrote that I want to own a huge company and I want to be the CEO of the company, nothing less. I've never had an idea how, but this is my goal.
<br /><br />so in these days since i've come back to Italy again after that problem which I had in my country, I've been alone but very very happy. and I have thought and searched on net about these new majors I'm thinking of plus, the business !!! wow
<br /><br />big news is coming soon.
<br /><br />now I don't let negative people or people that overstep the border around me to bother me or bring negative feelings or thoughts to me, and I have been very serious about it.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3c6a34fb319bce6d08f32dc0435f41a3" url=""><![CDATA[after along long time<br/><br/>it was so funny, i was searching my name on google and found my blog !
<br />its so good to wrote here if nobody disturb me ...
<br />so its 8 days to my birthday and sales.. yeah they're together
<br />and its exams season
<br />i like those that study well, get good marks and then go have fun ... discipline ...... i could never have it , is it because i dont have any talent in it or sth else?!
<br />anyway , i also study but not much ... its like im just playing
<br />yeah im playing with my life and my future .. its so scary
<br />i really feel the lack of a close friend
<br />u know whenever i needed someone , he/she has arrived .. im sure about this time. i need a beautiful nice hard-worker english speaker friend .. waiting for u girl
<br />i gotta sleep now but cant
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>