<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="ea239a9df4e31698f7b6794a1fe95a68" url=""><![CDATA[The North American Version Of The Game Of Final Fantasy Xiii<br/><br/>Square Enix announced in a promotional video at the official North America website. that the PS3/Xbox 360 role-playing game &quot;Final Fantasy XIII&quot; would be launched on March 9, 2010 in Europe and America. Square Enix has preannounced on North American official website of &quot;Final Fantasy XIII&quot; that he would announce the breaking news on 13 November.The Most Charming <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie</a> in the Year Of 2010: 10 Sizzling Finds
<br /><br />It is confirmed that the big news is the release data in Europe and America, and simultaneously releases PS3 version and Xbox 360 versions in North America and Europe On March 9, 2010. Surprise! Newest <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19CYWlsZXlfQnV0dG9u" target="_blank">ugg bailey button</a> at Keen Price The official has announced that the Europe and American Edition will invite the well-known British singer Leona Lewis to sing the theme song &quot;My Hands&quot;. As to the Japanese Edition, the Japanese female singer Sugawara will sing the theme song.
<br /><br />&quot;Final Fantasy 13&quot; will launch the Japanese PS3 Edition on December 17 in Japan and Asia. The price will be 9240 yen, and the PS3/Xbox 360 English portion which will be put out at North America and Europe areas in March 9th 2010 is 59.99 dollars. On May 8, 2006 of United States time, SQUARE ENIX finally announced to everyone the highly anticipated the latest news of &quot;Final Fantasy&quot; series in the annual E3 show of Electronics Show, this is the &quot;Final Fantasy XIII,&quot; Series.
<br /><br />The full name of the series is &quot;FINAL FANTASY 13 FABULA NOVA CRYSTALLIS&quot; including &quot;Final Fantasy 13&quot; as an orthodox sequel of &quot;Final Fantasy&quot; series. There is also a rumor class work, &quot;FINAL FANTASY VERSUS XIII&quot;, namely, a cell phone game &quot;Final Fantasy AGITO 13&quot;. Unlike the official sequel FINAL FANTASY XIII in which a female stars, FINAL FANTASY Versus XIII, which will comes out on PS3, Its leading role is a male, red eyes under grayish blue hair.
<br /><br />Games stage is a nation which is keeping peace by the power of crystalloid. Its building style is very similar with that in nowadays. There is also modern Japanese style in another space but not the earth.
<br /><br />The male leader holds arms in black clothes, he is the noble member of the kingdom. The associative perception of this game squints towards action. By the powerful function of PS3, A brand new &quot;FINAL FANTASY&quot; series work will be presented in front of us.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="761c892134c19bd40175067ec3a6006a" url=""><![CDATA["Gossip Girl" Costume Worth Tens of Millions of<br/><br/>A popular television show can bring endless enthusiasm to audience, moreover, the attire of every protagonist in the TV show will set off another round of new fashion trend. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> Rank First in the List of Most Wanted Vouchers in 2009 The hot TV series Gossip Girl is a good example. Purchase Most Enchanting Series of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie &amp; Fitch</a> The clothes in the play’s wardrobe count for approximately 12 million pounds.What is Highest Choice for Professionals? <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> !
<br /><br />With no doubt is that &quot;Gossip Girl&quot; is the most popular TV play in recent year, it has described luxurious life in upper east side in US which is the ordinary people can not reach. This story makes many young people pursue this TV series with the curiosity to upper life and the admiration to the beautiful and upscale clothing.
<br /><br />Exquisite clothes in Gossip Girl lead the fashion wave. Fashion Empire, full of world famous Big, hits the super-luxurious fashion show of Gossip Girl. The Play shows New York rich girls who have clothes,bags,jewelry,shoes and other accessories designed by world's famous designer.
<br /><br />Every season, the leading roles Leighton Meester and Blake Lively’ clothes are stored in a wardrobe. The wardrobe is unbelievable because of it has occupied 1500 square and five floors high. Actor Chace Crawford said: &quot;They often get lost in the closet, just like a child into a candy shop, in fact I am afraid if my time of trial assenbly is placed after Blake, because this will certainly delay my shooting of next act.&quot;
<br /><br />For clothing stylist Eric Daman, it needs to take a long time to arrange suitable clothing for each scene. He said&quot; We have to prepare at least five to six sets of clothing for each role, then eighty for a season and you must figure out that 80 from500.&quot;
<br /><br />The celebrity in the fashion circle Victoria Beckham will challenge the small television screen at this time. She was invited to be a guest performer in the popular American Gossip Girl. The 35 year-old Victoria Beckham was invited by “Gossip Girl” player Blake Lively, Blake Lively is a fan of Victoria Beckham’dressing style.
<br /><br />As a matter of fact, both Blake and Leighton Meester are fascinated with and always dressed in Victoria's designs Blake, as well as stylist Eric Daman, attended the release ceremony of the latest season of Victoria Beckham's brand . And they also asked VB to act in the Gossip Girl and to choose some fo her fashionable pieces in it.
<br /><br />The spicy girl is not an actress. Because she need to blend in the young Gossip girls who live in the aristocratic private schools in Manhattan, her role is hard to be set. It is said that she will play the England actor Ed Westwick 's lost mother. However, she joked that she would rather play his ex-girlfriend.
<br /><br />There is no doubt that when starring in the play,Victoria will wear her own brand clothing.By the moment the audience will enjoy another fashion feast.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5d8004c23d707991f1ed90b0492f8284" url=""><![CDATA[The Finest Dressing In Valentine Day Create Sweeter<br/><br/>Valentine's Day is coming, have you already began to wonder to give him a perfect appearance surprisingly and heat up your romantic love to the boiling point. Ordinary day makes him dress up routine,then to the sweet harvest of love this holiday, might as well comes to change the body perfectly,let him see a different brand new you. Romantic princess: Each girl has the princess complex and always fantasizes about wearing a cute pompon silk skirt and being picked by the prince on a white horse to go dancing one day.Design <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> on Doll's Festival
<br /><br />Clothing mix: The dress of princess style exactly become the hot election of the designers this season, some wonderful design emerge in an endless stream. Last Week My Father Chose <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> for My Mother With a gorgeous feeling, the pretty printed satin fabric is the key point to create a romantic and sweet feeling, the princess sleeves and pompon edge also let you fill with pride temperament of princess. Accessory rule: the girl with long hair can choose a beautiful ribbon or a card to decorate, and it is also a good choice to have a diamond jewelry of gorgeous feeling.
<br /><br />2. Dancing spice: perhaps no matter how honest a man is, he will drool seeing a spice girl, so you, a girl dressed ordinariy all along, may as well put up a 180-degree makeover to test his nerves. Clothing match: mysterious and sexy black is the best choice, but it must be distinguished from the kind of dull black inside business wear. You can choose a tight T-shirt interspersed with sequins and the perfect cut close to the body is the trump that hightlight your magical stature and it is necessary that you expose the perfect skin.
<br /><br />If you work out hard to lose some weight for Valentine's Day, you can definitely impress him greatly. Principles of ornaments: the exaggeratedly shiny ornaments are necessary to create sexy feeling. The dazzling or shiny silver ornaments and other metal ornaments could make you full of a sense of cool and sexy.
<br /><br />Lovely wizard: If he likes your lovely and cute look, you can dress yourself as a little cute witch on Valentine's day. Lovely you walk beside him, the youth comes to you just like your love will not become old forever. The match in clothes: if you have a pair of perfect long legs, don't waste the born gift, it will make you look energetic with mini skirt matching with long boots.
<br /><br />Knitted fabric is the first choice of girls who love to be dress lovely in the winter, in orde to match with the special day, choosing the knitted sweater with shiny beads will make you be more radiant. Accessory Rules: Choose acessories with cartoon images. Bright colors are also a magic weapon for creating beautifulness. Never stop being pure and pretty.
<br /><br />Gentle lady: Valentine's Day, the least error-prone and makeup, is to send the Rourou image of the lady. Match of costumes: the dress of soft colored grids could show your lovely side. But on this sweet festival, black and white are too monotone. then the woman may choose quite a small taste of the light-colored jacket to match, butterfly knot, the small round neck is a beautiful building charming details can not be ignored.
<br /><br />Acessories rule: accessories are not too much. One or two fine and modern jewelry can improve your overall atmosphers of the trendy sense. If it is not the gift he had sent you, it is more perfect!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="43bad83881b59f76ce58b6fe4b7d173f" url=""><![CDATA[The North American Edition Of Final Fantasy Xiii Will Be On<br/><br/>The other day Square Enix announced it formally in the column of latest publicized films on North American official website that Play Station 3/Xbox 360 RPG Game Final Fantasy XIII will be published in European and American areas on March 9th, 2010. The Misunderstanding of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> You Should Know Square Enix had forecasted that an important news would be given in November 13rd in the official web site in North America of &quot;FF XIII&quot;
<br /><br />Now official confirmation of the breaking news is its sales date in European and American areas, PS3 / Xbox 360 will be released synchronously on 9th Mar. 4 Benefits About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> 2010 in European and American areas. It was also officially made public that the well-known British female singer Fiona Lewis would be invited to sing the theme song &quot;My Hands&quot; for the Europe and America version. As to the Japanese Edition, the Japanese female singer Sugawara will sing the theme song.How to Handle the Threats of your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> 
<br /><br />Final Fantasy 13 will be release the PS3 in Japanese on Japanese and Asian area on December 17th. The price will be 9240 yen, and the PS3/Xbox 360 English portion which will be put out at North America and Europe areas in March 9th 2010 is 59.99 dollars. On May 8, 2006 the United States time, at E3 show, the annual ectronics show, SQUARE ENIX El finally announced the latest news of &quot;Final Fantasy&quot; series that everyone had highly anticipated for, that was the &quot;Final Fantasy 13&quot; Series.
<br /><br />This series of works are known collectively as &quot;FINAL FANTASY XIII FABULA NOVA CRYSTALLIS&quot;, including &quot;Final Fantasy XIII&quot;, the series orthodox continuation work of &quot;Final Fantasy&quot;. There is another unofficial biography work &quot;FF Versus XIII&quot; which is a mobile game &quot;FF Agito XIII&quot; Unlike the official sequel FINAL FANTASY XIII in which a female stars, FINAL FANTASY Versus XIII, which will comes out on PS3, The hero in the game is a male role, with a pair of red eyes below grey blue hairs.
<br /><br />The plotline set amist in a country which try to maintain peace through crystal strengh.Its style is close to morden but much more like the modern Japanese architectural one,while it doesn't exist on the earth but in another space.
<br /><br />The main character is one member of the royalty of this kindom with black clothes and sharp weapon. The overall sense of the game is more inclined to Action, I belevie that through the power of PS3 function. the game that showing before us will be a brand new series of Final Fantasy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="31b68fd6e60c4372c0fd334cf0afc84d" url=""><![CDATA[Basics to Choose Dressing for Wedding<br/><br/>Maybe you have been dazed by all these gleaming wedding dresses! Then how to choose among them which most suitable to you? Is princess, the loose skirt, next to the skin or queen? Is the gently beautiful fibroin soft satin is the romantic flower bud silk lining? Where should you begin, pay attention to which questions?Miley Cyrus Love 
<br /><br />1. You May Lethe These When Maintain <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19CYWlsZXlfQnV0dG9u" target="_blank">ugg bailey button</a> Select wedding day! You must determine the wedding season, exact time, place and style before choosing wedding dress. Wedding dress style should coordinate with wedding party style. If your wedding is very fashionable, you can choose the wedding dress in front of trend; if it is a traditional one, there is no doubt to choose the classical and grand dress.Superior and Fashionable <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19CYWlsZXlfQnV0dG9u" target="_blank">ugg bailey button</a> on the Cheap Now!
<br /><br />2. Do enough homework, collect some of your favorite dress pictures ahead and make marks, marking your favorite style and plate type, particularly the details at places such as neck, waist and so on. When exchanging views with your dress designer or consultant, remember to bring your pictures so that your thoughts and opinions can be better conveyed to your listener.
<br /><br />3. Completes the budget, the formal clothes and other matches the expense which plays the part of spends, generally occupy suitably the wedding ceremony expense 6-15%. If budgets is quite ample, you may have custom-made one section most to suit oneself regard the formal clothes.
<br /><br />4. Choose the location. The shops specializing selling wedding dress and photo studios are everywhere to be found, where to find your dream dress? In general, wedding dress shops of large-scale and professional tend to have a complete set of dress style you are looking for, in addition, the designers are more experienced, and the quality of the products is reliable. In addition, you can follow the advice of your friends who got married not long ago, choose two or three of the places they suggest.
<br /><br />5. To ensure enough selection time: If you expect to customize wedding dress, you’d better start to select the wedding dress one year in advance (9 month at least), in order to ensure enough selection time. Because it will take about 4 months to design a wedding dress, and you'd better receive it 2 months before the wedding so that you can do minor changes.
<br /><br />6. You need to find yourself a consultant. You have to bring an experienced consultant with you while selecting the dress, it can be your mother, your friend but there is one thing that should not be ignored, she has to have a good understand of you, she knows what suits you best. You should pay attention to the following two points: first, make sure that she won’t impose her opinion on you; second, don’t go shopping in company with your mom and friends at the same time. Because all people can let you try on her to think that most attractive most suits your formal clothes, you will feel are at a loss how to proceed. One day gets down, is not only utterly exhausted, will possibly have achieved nothing.
<br /><br />7. Understand yourself. It is the most important you should choose dress style according to your own body type. You can try on one of the dress each from four basic style, including princess type, big skirt type, close type and queen type when you firstly visit the bridal salon.
<br /><br />8. Suitable size. If your dress isn’t custom-made, when you choose the dress, the size of the plump parts, like the chest, waist and hip should be suitable. Then looked again other spots are whether appropriate. Must pay attention, chooses the formal clothes take the slightly big spot as suitable. If has been big, changes the small spot to be very easy, but let a clothes fill-out not too be possible.
<br /><br />9. Opinion from experts. To choose the dress suit you most, you have to be good at listening to the opinions and ideas of the dress consultant and designers because they are more experienced than you, their designs have made thousands of brides the most dazzling stars on the wedding ceremony. If you are satisfy with the latest style, while they suggest you choose the pompon skirt with thin aiguillette or you surprise with their views, you have to think twice in that their choice might be the best for you.
<br /><br />10. Try the dress. You may choose the right dress for yourself, but ignore to try it, in fact, trying the dress carefully is really important. It can not only make sure that you are brilliant on the wedding, but also it can make you look graceful and decent. And you will feel comfortable and free.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a0a4cc4aa8d575e392034e650f6dd7df" url=""><![CDATA[Anonymous Woman Sued Michael<br/><br/>According to reports, a woman claimed that Michael Jackson was stalking her while he was alive, demanding $50 million in damages from his estate. 10 Whys and Wherefores That Will Bring about Harm to Your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> The woman called Helen Harris-Scott indicted Jackson last Friday and asked for the compensation. Fashion News: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie &amp; Fitch</a> are in the Leading Place for Fall The woman claimed that in 2006, Jackson had erected a tracing device in her car and tapped her phone. and even had &quot;organized criminals watching me inside my house in L.A. and reporting to him&quot;. She added Jackson had mentioned her in the lyrics he wrote. Originally, she planned to claim compensation of 100 million dollars from Jackson but now the compensation has been lowered to 50 million.
<br /><br />Michael Jackson passesd away in June,2009, and after his death the apartition and treatment of his wealth has arosed a big strom. He was the icon of world's popular culture, enjoyed the extreme notability and had great influence all over the world, thuswas known as the King of Pop. With the outstanding music talent, he had noticeable achievements in composition of lyrics and music, scene making, music arrangement, singing, dancing and instrument playing. He and Elvis Presley, the Beatles are called the greatest immortal symbols in history of pop music, while his achievements have already surpassed the latter two. He mentained his record in his sales of records in many countries and regions for a long time. He had received high-standard meet from leaders in the world. Reagan, Bush, Clinton, American president in a row invited him to the White House and rewarded him. He created the modern MV, among which the music video of his single &quot;Thriller&quot; as the world's first modern MV was known as &quot;the greatest music video&quot; in the history. It is commented by a authoritative institution: Without MJ, the development of popular music will push back 20 years, and the appearence of MV will be 50 years later.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f8e9d1725618a153b8f232dce9e19b43" url=""><![CDATA[Do You Know the Proper Way to Greet the Unfamiliar Dogs<br/><br/>In a modern metropolis, more and more people have companion animals. In the street, passers-by can not help being attracted by the lovely and lively little dogs, some people even can not help touching them. So what should we do to say hello to the lovely dogs under the premise that security is guaranteed.Hot Exhibition - <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> In Fashion
<br /><br />Say &quot;Hi&quot; to a strange dog When we see a lovely pet dog, You should first extend one fist under the dog's nose and make sure you show the back your fist. When he becomes familiar with you savour, he will show good to you by wagging his tail. Then you can be close to him.Recession Chic â€“ How to Be Most Cool-Looking on a Budget
<br /><br />Kids should be cautious when they have a touch with the unacquainted dogs because not all dogs like to play with kids. Children should be taught to approach an unfamiliar dog after the dog owners allowed. At the same time, don't let infants alone with dogs as much as possible.
<br /><br />To comply with Social Law of Dogs Many dog bites is because people do not understand the social law that dogs will issue a warning before biting in most cases.
<br /><br />It is they are showing the warning when the hair of the dog's back stand on the end with their four legs strongly treading the terra and the time they slightly wave their tale and bark with the uplifting head. In such dangerous situations, I suggest you better pretend nonchalance and pull slowly far away from the dog. Avoid the direct eye contact with the dog and don't run because of nervousness.
<br /><br />Dogs' instinct of hunting would keep it running after you if you do so.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3c70b199e7a042741412be4b4e717e72" url=""><![CDATA[Best Makeup- The Biggest Surprise in Saint Valentine's Day<br/><br/>Valentine's Day is coming, and do you bring your honey a surprise on the sweet day. Hot Exhibition - <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> In Mode It will be a good idea to integrate the elements of fashion together, creating the a perfect makeup, making yourself the best beautiful gift on Valentine's Day!How to NOT Wear <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie &amp; Fitch</a> : Wonderful Tips
<br /><br />Sweet pink surprise: in the romantic Valentine's Day, pink color which is the symbol of love becomes the unique choice of women. How to leave a different impression on your honey? As a matter of fact, tender, lovely, and mild pink can also make eyecatching &amp; passionate makeup. The dense normal pink eye shadow, sounds make the eyes phase contrast peach. With the foot of the fashion, it can make you eyes big and charming to paste the exaggerate, pink and super-long fake eyelashes which are fashion in this year. I believe that when you appear before him, he must get stunned at your beauty and could not take his eyes off you. Specific steps are as follows.
<br /><br />STEP 1 First, apply the light pink eye shadow evenly and slowly along the upper eyelid from the outer corner of the eye to the inward corner of the eye, covering the whole area of the eye socket. STEP2 Then emphatically color the eyelash roots with dark pink eye shadow, gradually shade towards the outer corner of the eye and stick the false eyelash close to the eyelash root. Thirdly, using the brush dips the transparent pink blush, brush it from the cheeks to the temple. STEP4 In order to highlight the beauty of your lovely plump lips, you can choose shiny pink lip with a gloss jelly texture and then with a lip brush dipped it to outline your lips uniformly.
<br /><br />Romantic icy blue trap helps you allure him, thus blue is a must in every fashion tide. Slightly sparkling embellished by golden eye shadow, you maximize the female softness and elegance; meanwhile combined with the coldness of ice blue, you will show the full sense of the future. The low-key blush and silhouette may show the endless charm of women. While the delicate and aqua pink lips can not hide the cute and pleasant intimacy. On sweet Valentine's Day, it is necessary to have a warm candlelight dinner. In the flickering candlelight, no more than a pair of cool, deep, mysterious yet gentle aqua blue eyes looks more deadly. Facing so perfect, the temptation of how he would refuse to love! Please click the steps.
<br /><br />STEP1 use light blue eye shadow powder grounding, smear the entire eye socket, so that follow-up dark blue eye shadow easier to color, which will make your eyes looking more natural. STEP2 then blue eye will shadow from eyelid dizzy in the eye socket, and to the brow middle wipe on shining golden shadow carry bright, finally affix eyelash. The third step is to blush brown or perhaps dark brown blush on the prominent cheekbone on both cheeks and put on profiles on each side to emphasize the illusion of depth. Fourthly, you can choose the pink to match the whole make up, and using the jelly-like lip gloss to take the place of lipstick to improve the shine effect.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="164f58dc86aa568b9af40cb3b75fa93a" url=""><![CDATA[Twelve Methods For Bring Beautiful Appearance<br/><br/>Everyone likes being pretty, especially having soft and white skin. What is the Future of Perfect <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> ? God Knows! Do you know how to make your skin looks prettier? Remember to apply pre-make cream and sun-block cream before go outside in summer and do cleansing immediately back home. To sleep, cut a small cucumbers into thin pieces, place them on the face to get down in a few minutes, the face will be white and tender for a month.What is the Future of Elegant <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> ? God Knows!
<br /><br />Drink two bottles of water one with salt after get up every day could clean the intestines and stomach. To use the cheapest pads before going to bed with make-up water being completely soaked, apply to the face for 20 minutes ,3 times per week, then your skin will have unexpected bright and refreshing. Wash your face with warm water first, then cool it down with cold water, your face will be extra clean and your pore will disappear.
<br /><br />Sure to drink plenty of water which does not stay up late, eat less oil-fried things, keep the skin clean. After washing your face, pour some cream on dressing pads and place them directly on your face every night. You can even some cream on your forehead and chin. This method can not only eliminate speckles but also whiten your skin. Drink less water at night and drink more during the day. Use moisturizing facial mask before sleep; eat more fruits. Don't smoke and stay up. All these can ensure bright and tender skin.
<br /><br />Use cold tea bag to cover eyes: first, use the cold tea bags to cover eyes for five minutes, next do an action similar to yoga, for this action first make leg crossed, and then raise hands high to get down forward and maintain this position about ten minutes. It is not easy to keep this gesture for 10 minutes; you need to practice for a period of time, but the effect is really good! Prepare a bottle of purified water (600cc). Wash your face with purified water for 3 to 4 times per week and often moisturize your face by dressing pads weltered by purified water, your face will definitely become tender and beautiful!
<br /><br />According to a medical report, besides uva and uvb which everyone is familar with, ultraviolet rays also contain a so-called uvc. Uvc and uvb easily give rise to skin sunburn in daily sunny days. But you'd better use umbrella in cloudy days for the uva long-wave radiation can still do harm to skin, so the umbrella can prevent early aging.
<br /><br />With hot spring bath, the hot spring bath not only can make your skin white and smooth, but also can reduce fatigue. For an allergic person, it can help better the allergy.
<br /><br />Keep it in mind that when you choose skin-care products, you had better not seek cheapness. Sometimes, cheapness means intimations or counterfeit goods. Do all of the above, everyone could have the enviable and beautiful skin.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a946dd3e20968369296ceb905a338496" url=""><![CDATA[Luxe and Fine - Lux Brand Gucci<br/><br/>Though the fashion brands dazzle people's eyes, the businessmen show appreciation for the GUCCI style which is not only fashion but also elegant. To Admire the New Classic <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie &amp; Fitch</a> of Paris Hilton The clothes if this brand is mainly based on the principle of simplicity. It is perfectly embodies in man’s clothing this season, which is new and unique in cut, showing the Venitien style in the 18th century. Plus jeans, space and the color of rock star, making it bold with a little unruly and charming.You Should Remember 9 Points of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> 
<br /><br />The founder Guccio Gucci found Gucci in Florence, Italy, in 1923. The Right time to Look Great With, The Best <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> to Enjoy Gucci group is the largest apparel group in Italy today. In addition to apparel, Gucci also deals with leather bags, leather shoes, watches, scarves, ties and perfumery, etc. Gucci brand has always been famous for high class, luxury and sexy, and becomes consuming darling of rich high society by the brand image of &quot;a symbol of status and wealth&quot; .
<br /><br />From the late 40's to the 60's, Gucci in succession releases a series of classical design such as leather bag with bamboo handle, soft shoes with metal pads and scarves with textile printing. The unique design and excellent material of the become the sign of elegance and extravagance, and is liked by Jacqueline Kennedy, SophiaLoren as well as Duchess of Windsor etc. ladies.
<br /><br />Gucci brand color has two group which are green, red and green as well as blue, red and blue, to distinguish the natural leather and dyeing leather products. At the same time, the company founder Guccio Gucci to name initials as jewelry shading, while high-quality cotton cloth known as GG, for the manufacture of handbags, jewelry and clothing.
<br /><br />After World War II, owing to lack of leather these raw materials so that take canvas as alternatives. The trademark logo of GG and eye-catching red and green as a symbol of Gucci appeared in all kinds of canvas briefcases, handbags, wallets and other Gucci products. The distinguished Gucci has developed into a brand rivaling Louis Vuitton in bag industry. Meanwhile it became a coping and imitating object for other manufacturers around the world.
<br /><br />In the next 10 or 20 years, with the range of products continues to expand, Gucci which took Florence as the base in the early years rise sharply and the product throughout Europe and America and Asia. It not only has popular shoes, bags and cases but also clothing, perfume, domestic commodities, headbands and other accessories. It can be said that to some extent it is owing to these species continue to expand and develop which improve the popularity of Gucci brand and make it no longer only limit to the original markets field and become the popular brand day by day.
<br /><br />Because of much false products appearing Gucci band has to cost much money and strength to fight against the fake to assure its good enterprise image. In fact, with years of production and operation, making Gucci own some signs of classic products such as flat shoes and the never changed gold jewelry. Gucci is alsolight soled shoes which need not to ne fastened, thus bring a huge business profit for Gucci. Gucci leather goods particularly are famous for tanning, delicate leather products as its most obvious features.
<br /><br />In 1989, Dawn Mello was appointed as Gucci's assistant manager and innovation guide, making Gucci's brand, the past symbol of luxury and glory, become a &quot;necessary&quot; chic. After 1994, TomFord enables Gucci to look brand-new.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b7ab255a1e59de36d7ef1427c37676f3" url=""><![CDATA[The Necessary Wearing Apparel in Autumn and Winter of 2009<br/><br/>When the autumn has already come, the footstep of winter would be closer. Do you want to have fashionable seasons? Let's just look at some necessary items of this year!Mary-Kate Olsen Keep an Eye on <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie &amp; Fitch</a> 
<br /><br />Essential style 1:Retro section shirts
<br /><br />Stand-up collar with lace and puff sleeve are so delicate and beautiful that make people feel enchanted. Top brands Crafts of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> The light color delivers the quality of elegance. If matched with full-length skirts and clean bob, this kind of shirts may create a classical beauty. Ancient-return shirt and long trousers could integrate the classic and modern style. Such dress would be necessary for office girls. Also they can assort the dress with long skirt to improve the disposition.
<br /><br />2. High beltline onepiece dress
<br /><br />Black can match every color and black one-piece dress is very cute. Simple bright silver with black cotton yarn always makes you look like a beautiful Barbie doll. The upgrade in waist highlights tall figure, dress material decides wearer's temperament, cotton dress shows sweet, while the blended fabric skirt plus cardigan can create a small lady style.
<br /><br />The third style: sweet pea coat.
<br /><br />Pink stripe overall with bronze short skirt would keep both cute and calm image. That would let you feel comfortable even in the early autumn. Candy-like colors with high sweet, the refined fresh and bright, but also with good childish suspects, with candy-color T-shirt to match the simple downloading is pleasing.
<br /><br />The fourth style: shattered flower patterns
<br /><br />The white one-piece dress full of pink strawberries shows the natural beauty of spring. The accessories is in harmony with the classical designs, combining chastity with fascination. Romantic tiny flowers are the symbols of sweetness .We should choose colors that are simple and elegant, while the patterns are vigorous on the whole in early spring.The complicated patterns will be heavy.
<br /><br />Do you feel heart touched when seeing such sweet and cute assortment? Just go to find the item you prefer! Hope you would become the most charming and shining guys in this autumn and winter.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dec0c6e56ef7ffaf329bfd0d43bf026e" url=""><![CDATA[Worthwhile Benevolence of Warren Buffett<br/><br/>The auction of having charity lunch with investment guru Warren Buffett set a world record of 2. Why Shop <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19CYWlsZXlfQnV0dG9u" target="_blank">ugg bailey button</a> for Actressewww. million U.S. dollars, which surprised the world's richest man. Buffett recently said that his lunch time will not be extended because of the high bid. However, people who gained the opportunity with high-priced does not think its wasteful. The person who spent 650,000 US dollars on the lunch says that to communicate with the famous investor, every cent costed is worthy. This price was more than 3 times of the close price of last year, which broke the record of charity auction on ebay. Buffet told the reporter of the Association Press, &quot;It takes me aback.&quot;The Merits and Misunderstanding of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> 
<br /><br />The lunch price increases every year, but the conversation time doesn’t grow. Why such opportunity can still attract more and more people? Guy Spier, CEO of American Aquamarine Capital Management Company, who bid to the opportunity, had lunch with Baffet as he wished. He explained personally after the lunch that such “pilgrim” is worth of it as he could listen to what this master has to say to him.
<br /><br />While having dialogue, Spier asked his doubt on every specific issue, and Buffett always inspired him by showing a simple and philosophical viewpoint. During their lunch, Buffett often mentioned his own life as well as his way of dealing things. For example, when he was a child, his father taught him to make judgment based on what he thought was right or wrong, instead of others’ opinion. &quot; It's very important to live your own life on your own standard,&quot; Spier quoted Buffett's saying. Just by asking yourself a simple question, you can figure out whether you’ve lived with this principle. And the question is that are you willing to be a finest sweetie to the world’s eyes, but the worst to your own, or you willing to be the finest sweetie to your own eyes, but worst to the world’ s? Buffett did very well when using this idea in invest: depend on himself completely, do investing in his own ability range, and cooperate with those who have the same concept of value.
<br /><br />Buffett didn't change his mind though he was criticized because he has been reluctant to invest in this area when the network economy developed rapidly in the late 90s of the last century. People who calmed down from the investment frenzy understand Buffett after the bubble economy broken. “Can you get a better example?” Spier said this in the weekly ?Time?, “Two days after we had lunch together, the price of the chance to have lunch with Buffett for the next year has come out in eBay, it is two million, one hundred thousand dollars. Fact proves that our sixty hundred and fifty thousand dollar is absolutely cheap. ”
<br /><br />On the day of releasing views of charitable lunch, Buffet visits the beverage brand D&amp;Q of his Berkshire Hathaway Co.Ltd., tasting the newest ice cream and chatting with the local 6 cadettes. Buffett told those middle school or college girls it is better to read more books before they enter the invest world. “It would be much better, if you can ponder and research the investment.” Buffett said. When asked how should they manage financing in university by these girls, Buffet said that they should avoid using credit card because students are likely to slip into a credit debt due to relatively high interest rate. “If I borrowed money at the age of 18 or 20, I would be possibly broke then.” Buffett said.
<br /><br />Inspired by the late wife Susan, Buffett who have the reputation of &quot;stock god&quot; auctioned the opportunity of having lunch with him since 2000, and donated it to the San Francisco Glide Foundation to relief poverty hunger and homelessness. The auction had been held in San Francisco, but moved to ebay in two thousand and three.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6add5fbe356abafe26c11af8c419726c" url=""><![CDATA[Some Practical Business Simulations for 3G<br/><br/>3G has spread all over the planet, ranging from Europe and North America to Asia Pacific. Outline the Reasons of the Popularity of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> The most different thing compared to 2G is that 3G is shouldering the responsibility to change people's habits of using phones.Suitable Ways that Deserve to Learn for Maintaining Your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> 
<br /><br />The age of 2G adopts vocal communication-based application model, While 3G will change to concentrate on data service. In other words, in addition to voice services,people need to find more applications based on wireless data transmission.
<br /><br />Global mobile operators and industry chain partners, giving full play to imagination and creativity, has developed a wide range of innovative and effective business models, Among them, there are three models proved to be practical at now.
<br /><br />The first one is to use the ad income to make an allowance to or cover the customers’ WAP fee. This kind of mode succeeds in mobile music, game distribution, mobile Internet browsing, mobile networking and many other wireless application services.
<br /><br />The second mode is to establish the fare structure of diversity to reduce the users' network access fee. One of the common forms that reflects the model is to make the cost of service by multiple users sharing. For example, lots of people share the same broadband internet connection in an internet bar.
<br /><br />Another embodiment is the service that only charges for small and varied amount of money in the name of usage without a set fee. For instance charge for the poundage according to each transfer transaction, or the media music fee according to the time.
<br /><br />And the last form is to sell some basic service to the customers with an affordable price and then cross-sell or up-sell some services. The third business mode is to provide mobile services for improving community health care, education or welfare in cooperation with the government or non-profit organizations. In this model, mobile networks operators can enjoy subsidies, preferential loan and/ or preferential tax policies. The U.S. mobile networks operator Sprint have developed mobile medical services by use of 3G.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7f529a7850a42eafaf0851645b7a5ae" url=""><![CDATA[Mystique for Icelanders' Longevity<br/><br/>The special geological formations makes Iceland underground heat billowing, there are more than 800 natural hot springs, the water temperature can reach 75 degrees Celsius. Hotsprings are used in domestic purposes. As long as you turn on the faucet, you can enjoy a hotspring spa. Icelanders like the open-air swimming, of course, swim in the Hot Springs Village. Most Icelanders born a few months, he was taken to the hot springs their parents learn how to swim.How to Buy Men the Perfect Gift for Youth Day
<br /><br />In this case, the open air swimming pools are the hottest social gathering places where you can come aross statesmen, entrepreneurs and artists. With no formal wear but swimsuits and without different positions and status, everyone is the same and equal so whether they talk about business or have a chat, it is quite easier for them to just feel free to communicate with each other about feelings. In Iceland, the hotsprings are also the best choices for young lovers. Being there, lovers can not only be honest with each other, but can also be more intimate because of the hot water.Hottest, Newest, Latest: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie &amp; Fitch</a> 
<br /><br />An Iceland friend of writer, Frank says, “Hot spring spa is an essential program for travelers in winter”. He also introduces that Icelandic spring spa differs from Finnish spa which is dangerous from high temperature sharply into ice water. Icelandic hot spring bath is mainly taken by a gradual increase of temperature into three gradual heating process, this is both the skin and cardiovascular protection.
<br /><br />Winter, in Iceland, if has been invited to a friend's house,t o the public hot spring spa is essentially a fixed item. It is regarded as the supreme guest treatment if you were invited to private hotspring pools. On one hand, there is existing fewer and fewer private pools, on the other hand, only seniority and intimate friends coming a long way could be invited to private pools to enjoy meals and bath. I have been so lucky to be ionce nvited to Grook's homely pool. We had growing fun while enjoying spa and our enthusiasms were fully stirred up.
<br /><br />It is just as my friends said, the hotspring spa is Icelanders' secret of longevity.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3b03fef3d1e0a16cd9f78ef82714645b" url=""><![CDATA[Worthwhile Benevolence of Warren Buffett<br/><br/>The auction of having charity lunch with investment guru Warren Buffett set a world record of 2.11 million U.S. dollars, which surprised the world's richest man. Buffett recently said that his lunch time will not be extended because of the high bid. However, people who gained the opportunity with high-priced does not think its wasteful. The person who spent 650,000 US dollars on the lunch says that to communicate with the famous investor, every cent costed is worthy. This price was more than 3 times of the close price of last year, which broke the record of charity auction on ebay. Buffet told the reporter of the Association Press, &quot;It takes me aback.&quot;09 Winter, the World of Sterling <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> !
<br /><br />The lunch price increases every year, but the conversation time doesn’t grow. Why such opportunity can still attract more and more people? Guy Spier, CEO of American Aquamarine Capital Management Company, who bid to the opportunity, had lunch with Baffet as he wished. He explained personally after the lunch that such “pilgrim” is worth of it as he could listen to what this master has to say to him.Get Ready Fast â€“ Quick and Easy Ways for <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> 
<br /><br />While having dialogue, Spier asked his doubt on every specific issue, and Buffett always inspired him by showing a simple and philosophical viewpoint. During their lunch, Buffett often mentioned his own life as well as his way of dealing things. For example, when he was a child, his father taught him to make judgment based on what he thought was right or wrong, instead of others’ opinion. &quot; It's very important to live your own life on your own standard,&quot; Spier quoted Buffett's saying. Just by asking yourself a simple question, you can figure out whether you’ve lived with this principle. And the question is that are you willing to be a finest sweetie to the world’s eyes, but the worst to your own, or you willing to be the finest sweetie to your own eyes, but worst to the world’ s? Buffett did very well when using this idea in invest: depend on himself completely, do investing in his own ability range, and cooperate with those who have the same concept of value.
<br /><br />Buffett didn't change his mind though he was criticized because he has been reluctant to invest in this area when the network economy developed rapidly in the late 90s of the last century. People who calmed down from the investment frenzy understand Buffett after the bubble economy broken. “Can you get a better example?” Spier said this in the weekly ?Time?, “Two days after we had lunch together, the price of the chance to have lunch with Buffett for the next year has come out in eBay, it is two million, one hundred thousand dollars. Fact proves that our sixty hundred and fifty thousand dollar is absolutely cheap. ”
<br /><br />On the day of releasing views of charitable lunch, Buffet visits the beverage brand D&amp;Q of his Berkshire Hathaway Co.Ltd., tasting the newest ice cream and chatting with the local 6 cadettes. Buffett told those middle school or college girls it is better to read more books before they enter the invest world. “It would be much better, if you can ponder and research the investment.” Buffett said. When asked how should they manage financing in university by these girls, Buffet said that they should avoid using credit card because students are likely to slip into a credit debt due to relatively high interest rate. “If I borrowed money at the age of 18 or 20, I would be possibly broke then.” Buffett said.
<br /><br />Inspired by the late wife Susan, Buffett who have the reputation of &quot;stock god&quot; auctioned the opportunity of having lunch with him since 2000, and donated it to the San Francisco Glide Foundation to relief poverty hunger and homelessness. The auction had been held in San Francisco, but moved to ebay in two thousand and three.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="48d1116717d13249e6eaf3b49d88d75a" url=""><![CDATA[The Development About The Expected St. Valentine's Day<br/><br/>Valentine's Day, on February 14 of each year, is one of the traditional festivals of westerners. Kristen Stewart Enjoy {p2}&gt; With regard to the so-called Valentine's Day today, its origin can be traced back to ancient Greece, the Greeks were very popular in the worship of Pan.For What Reasons People all Choose Them?! Most Amazing <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie &amp; Fitch</a> Are on Exhibition
<br /><br />Regarding the current Valentine's Day, it can be traced back to ancient Greece. Now Here is the Chance!! <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> is Most Glamorous for Love in 2009 Greeks' Worship of Pan at that time is very popular. Indeed, &quot;panic&quot; has the literal meaning of &quot;of Pan&quot;, and this kind of application can be vivid. Pan should blow upon his Pandean pipes while guarding herds, but he is distracted easily. He had many love-affairs with many fairies and goddesses. A sculpture describes that Pan was on intimate terms with Venus Aphrodite, with Eros hovering above in their wings, just as the Cupid described in the card now.
<br /><br />Many Romans worship a Deity of same like, Faunus who was described as a combination of man and goat either. Each year on February 15, the Lupercalia, Romans would hold parties or festivals to commemorate Faunus. During this Festival, some men wearing inch strand run around hill, waving goat whips in their hands.
<br /><br />Any woman who want to be conceived can stand beside the runway. The Romans believed that it can heal the woman's infertility without any medicine if she was whiped by a running man. It is said in Brewer's Phrase and Fable Dictionary, &quot;St. Valentine was a Roman priest. He was imprisoned because he assisted the persecuted Christians. He returned to Christianity later and was beaten to death on February 14 at last.&quot;
<br /><br />Ancient custom to celebrate Valentine's Day was related with Valentine, in fact, it is purely a coincidence. In fact, this festival may be related to Faun Festival or seasons for birds mating in ancient Roma. The Characteristic of Valentine's is to exchange gifts for lovers. People would like to express their affection by valentine cards till now. The card usually depict Cupid, the heart hit by an arrow and other things.
<br /><br />Cupid with Valentine's Day relationship as the above-mentioned dictionary says: Cupid (Latin cupido, meaning desire, love), Rome, Eros, equivalent to the Greek Eros Eros.
<br /><br />He is usually represented by a cute little boy with two wings, covered eyes, hand-held bow and arrow.&quot; World Book Encyclopedia provides further information on the origins of Valentine's Day, in fact, different opinions. The Encyclopedia states: It is said that during the period 200 AD, Roman emperor Claudius II prohibit young men getting married. He believed that unmarried men can become much better soldiers, a priest named Valentine violated the emperor's command, and priested over the wedding for young men secretly.
<br /><br />According to &quot;The Catholic Encyclopedia&quot;, in 496 AD, St. Gelasius?abolished Lupercalia Festival at the end of 5th century and pointed February 14 as Valentine's Day. This festival is in vogue called &quot;St. Valentine's Day&quot;, to be Valentine's Day. After the 14th century, people began to commemorate this day. This custom originated from the ancient faith and named after &quot;saint&quot; of Christian country regardless of the true origin of Valentine's Day. It is also esploited by the business community and becomes another excuse for making profits.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d0e5a5a458d15451d4a30e2bc0980f10" url=""><![CDATA[BURBERRY, Dignitary Personality and Enjoying Life<br/><br/>In 1891, Burberry opened a store in London Haymarket which is the first one in the capital of Britain. 4 Things You Must Know About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> And now it is still the company headquarters of Burberry. With traditional, refined design style and production, Burberry was granted &quot;Royal Warrant&quot; badge by Queen Elizabeth in 1955. Today, the classic Burberry plaid, unique function of cloth and elegant tailoring has become synonym of British style.How I Use Evernote to Organize Everything (25) 
<br /><br />Thomas Burberry, the founder of Burberry opened a tailor's shop in the Basingstoke of Hampshire of the United Kingdom in 1856 AD. He developed a kind of twill fabric – Gabardine which has been widely used by the British pilots and the military soon for its durable and practical characteristics in 1879.
<br /><br />In 1901, Burberry designed the pattern of first trench coat, and the First World War broke out, trench coat of Burberry is designated as the senior British army uniforms. In order to coordinate with military use, the design also revised to double-breasted, shoulder covers, backside has warm thick slices, and in waist attached D-type metal ring for putting ammunition, knife and so on. This practical dust coat is just the well known Trench Coat. Until today, if you want to look up “windbreaker” in British Oxford Dictionary, you will find that “Burberry” has become a synonym for windbreaker, with extraordinary meaning.
<br /><br />Another classic thing of Burberry is its check which is composed of beige, red, black and white lines. The check pattern which ued inside the coat before made its debut in 1924. And it was elegant Till today, Burberry's clothes and ornements can be called two classics the same as Trench Coat.
<br /><br />At the end of 1990s, there appeared many new brands in fashion world. Burberry has to break through under this circumstance. The CEO of current brand, Rose Marie Bravo, has joined in Burberry in 1997, and successively invited Roberto Menichetti and Christopher Bailey to hold the post of design director. In the rest time of embracing the philosophy of previous people, through unique designs and thinking, they re-interpret the new dynamic philosophy of Burberry's. Besides, famous photographer Mario Testino was dedicated himself in the fashion advertisement of Burberry. Meanwhile, thanks to the joining of super models Stella Tennant and Kate Moss, Burberry has obtained wide reputation.
<br /><br />Except traditional fashion, in order to suit the diversification society, Burberry extended its products to other areas. He put classical elements into it and publiced related products which made traditional English honourable individuality and life taste go on to extend into it and got a brand new life.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bb3795e63fc9de310dc56c2b75ea6465" url=""><![CDATA[The World-Known Car of German, BMW<br/><br/>Compared with some Big Brother, such as Alfa Romeo, Fiat, Ford, Mercedes Mercedes-Benz, Peugeot, Renault, Rolls-Royce, etc. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> Also Turn into the Luxurious that are Affordable by Common People it appears that BMW she is a very young factory. Do You Know These Attraction of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> ? Anne Hathaway Give You the Answer BMW cars remind people of the Jaguar, because they have many similar historical backgrounds and temperaments. However, the BMW depot that has nearly a century of vicissitudes appears more mature and more stable than those much younger Japanese depots, and its story is more moving and emotional.
<br /><br />BMW AG is specializing in luxury cars, motorcycles and high-performance engines, ranked the world's top 20 automotive companies. The company was founded in 1916; its founder is Karl Rapp and Max Fritz. At the very beginning, it was named BMW Aeroplane Co., but was renamed as BMW AG later in Aug. 1918. It is headquartered in Munich, Germany with 50000 employees. Annual production is 0.5 million vehicles and 30000 motorcycles. BMW starts its entrepreneurship from aero-engine business, so the blue on the signs stands for sky and white for the propeller. Blue and white sign is symmetrical shapes, but also is the emblem of Bavaria State where the company was in. Like Benz, BMW also aims to produce autos with high quality, high performance and high technology. The production is not high but it shares the same reputation in the automobile industry as Benz.
<br /><br />Concerning acceleration performance and high speed performance, BMW leads the world, so the first choice police cars in Germany are from BMW. The motorcycle of BMW in the international market is the most expensive, even more than luxury car, priced up to thirty thousand. As the BMW cars style in racing, therefore the BMW cars often steal the show in the world racing activities. BMW currently has subsidiaries and production plants in 13 countries, there are 10 subsidiaries at home.
<br /><br />Luxury BMW sedans which are now available on market include the new 3 series, the new 5 series, the new 7 series and the new 8 series. And, BMW 850 is the latest and most luxury sedan.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eba96d3c7b084b3be73788127d9045a8" url=""><![CDATA[The Incorrect Ways Of Doing Thing Is Harmful To Conscientiou<br/><br/>The parents destructive criticism him when a child did not do a thing well, such as the child has a profanity. The denial of the child will make him feel too painful because of doing one things wrong. He will find that the responsibility is the same as suffering.Tips to Upkeep 
<br /><br />As a man, if in his unconsciousness, the responsibility is equal to the pain, then he can not become a good husband. As a woman, if in her unconsciousness, the responsibility is equal to the pain, then how could she take care of her children! If we are too strict about children, it will only let them fear to take responsibility, and be afraid of failure and punishment. If we are too harsh on children and punish them when they made a mistake, which will lead to the children's irresponsibility because he think that he can't take responsibility.Spice Up <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> on Thanks Giving
<br /><br />Taking the place of kids and taking care of everything for them will lead to a sense of dependence of them. A basic principle is each life has to bear his responsibility as a man independently. No one can take responsibility for others; however, some parents think that they can. In fact, you can only help them at present, but not in the future, nor as an individual being.For What Reasons People all Choose Them?! Lovers all Want <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> 
<br /><br />You must trust the children in order to build their sense of responsibility, even you don't. It's more efficient to trust and persuade them patiently other than forbid children to do this or that thing.
<br /><br />Parents domineer, require and force children with their own standards, so once they are forced they take no responsibility.
<br /><br />Parents are always worried about their child and supervise him. But when the child said to you:“I can manage myself. Don’t worry”, you shouldn’t express your distrust even you really worry.
<br />What you should do is to make a further certainty of rules. You ask him: “How do you prepare to take care of yourself? What do you do everyday? What books do you read? From what time to what time…”
<br />So, from the beginning of talking about general responsibility to confirm that down later, it is actually equivalent to the two sides having reached an agreement, signed the contract.
<br />Praise them if they fulfill their promise; otherwise, help them find out the reasons for the failure. Then, they can keep their self-esteem and learn to keep promise also.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9e15d2e182c46d44742d98705315f0be" url=""><![CDATA[Worthwhile Beneficence From Buffett<br/><br/>The charity auction of having lunch with investor Warren Buffett has made a record of 2. Courteney Cox also Are Crazy about Attractive <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> 11 million dollars, which surprises this world’s richest man. Recently, Buffett said that the lunch time will not be extended because of the high bid. However, the person who got the opportunity with high price did not regard it as wasteful. Every penny is worth of it as long as you can talk with this master, said someone who spent $ 650,000 dollars to have lunch with Buffett last year. The amount is three times more than the bid price for having lunch with &quot;stock god&quot; last year and it set the highest charity bid of eBay. &quot;This (amount) surprised me,&quot; Buffett told The Associated Press on 1st.9 Signs Reminds You to Alter Your <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> 
<br /><br />Lunch price is rising year after year, but the time for dialogue is not long, why can this opportunity attract more and more people? Guy Spier, CEO of American Aquamarine Capital Management Company, who bid to the opportunity, had lunch with Baffet as he wished. After the lunch, he explained that to listen to the counsel of the investment master at such a close was really worthy.
<br /><br />During their talking, Spier asked questions on every specific thing to which Buffett answered with simple yet philosophical hint. During the lunch, Buffett often mentioned about his own ideals of living and working. For example, since his childhood, his father often told him that you should try to judge by yourself, and not by depending on others’ opinion. &quot;Living your own live by mind your own yardstick to, and this is very important,&quot; Spier quoted Buffett's words. You can figure out whether you act upon such principle or not by asking yourself a simple question: are you willing to be viewed as the best lover by the whole world and as the worst one by yourself, or vice versa? When these ideas are applied to the investment, Buffett has done exceptionally well: he completely trusts in himself, and invests in the &quot;scope of their ability&quot;, and cooperates with those who have the same values with you .
<br /><br />The development of network economy was rapid in the late 90s of last century, Buffett was often criticized because he has been reluctant to invest in this area, but he has not shaken. When the bubble burst, people who calmed down from the investment frenzy began to understand Buffett. “What better example can you follow?” Speer wrote in the “Times”, saying that “two days after our lunch, eBay gave the strike price for having lunch the next year, 2.1 million dollars. It proves that our 650 thousand dollars is definitely a bargain price.”
<br /><br />On the day making comment on charity lunch, Baffet also visited D&amp;Q, a brand catering in his Berkshire Hathaway Inc, tasting the latest ice-cream and at the same time chatting with six local girl scouts. Buffett told these girls who are still in secondary school or at university that it is best to read more before entering the investment area. “If you still have some thoughts and research on the investment, that would be better,” Buffett said. When the kids asked the world’s richest man what they should to manage money in college. Buffett responded that, if possible they should minimize the using of credit cards because the current interest rate is high and students are easily to fall into credit debt. &quot;I may have bankruptcy if I borrowed money at age eighteen or twenty,&quot; Buffett said.
<br /><br />Inspired by his dead wife Susan, Buffett began to auction the opportunity to have lunch with him since 2000 who has the reputation of &quot;stock god&quot;, and he donated all the money to the Glide Foundation in San Francisco to help people of poverty, hunger and homelessness. The auction once proceeded in San Francisco, transferred to the &quot;eBay&quot; in 2003.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8685dd9e917eb46e41ad033b3717fe62" url=""><![CDATA[The Good Points On Coaching Your Baby To Creep<br/><br/>Crawling is indispensable when the children grow up, which are of great advantage for the children's physical and mental development. The development of the baby crawling movements can be roughly divided into two steps. The first stage is about 7 months, mainly abdominal peristalsis, limbs moving irregularly. The second stage is at around 8 month-old when the limbs of the babies begin to crawl, that is, they crawl here and there with their hands and knees. And eventually they can crawl with their hands and feet while they can straighten their two buttocks and legs. Crawling is so decisive to the development of infants' body coordination that parents without exception should give their babies such trainings according to their different Months of Age.Proper Tips to Regain <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> 
<br /><br />Babies aged 4 to 6 months start crawling. When crawling, the head and neck are raised, chest and abdomen lifted correspondingly. If babies keep this practice for times every day, not only limb muscles can be tempered but also multiple benefits can be got, because the entire body is supported by upper and lower limbs. And then other benefits are following. Improve capacity for action Crawling could practice the strength of large muscle activity of baby body, especially the coordination and flexibility of the limbs activities, which is a comprehensive and strength fitness activity.Give an Outline of the Reasons of the Popularity of <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19CYWlsZXlfQnV0dG9u" target="_blank">ugg bailey button</a> 
<br /><br />Moreover, the crawl will help to develop visual perception, spatial sense, and balanced sense that will promote physical coordination. What is On Fire Now? Absolutely <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie &amp; Fitch</a> ! In addition, it will also improve the blood circulation and promote muscle and bone growth and development.
<br /><br />Second, it will also enhance physical fitness. Crawling is first coordinated movement for the whole body of baby that will train the strength of chest, back muscles, abdominal muscles and limbs muscle. In addition, crawling consumes much energy which is good for babies to eat more , to have a good sleep, and to grow faster in weight and height. Enhance parent-child communication.
<br /><br />Crawling can enhance the communication between mother and child. After baby learned how to crawl, the successful experience increases continuously under the parents’ guidance, as wee as the experience of exciting, failing and other experiences. These experience to enrich the baby's emotion, research shows that the baby crawl, often see parents excited state reptile significantly higher than not. What's more, it will promote the development of social emotional. After a child could crawl, he is more likely to touch things that his parents forbid him to, or do things that are not allowed by parents, which objectively provides more chances for emotional interactions between parents and children.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5ccd6b28ea78109de1d2356a6f489755" url=""><![CDATA[Latin Shape Your Body<br/><br/>Enjoying Latin storm just as tasteing waterfall sunshine and charming ardourBrown skin, wild dance, Ricky Martin's song, and hip twist of Ronaldo in the running, this is the visual experience Latin gives us.People's sight fade out of the elegance of court dance, gaze into rumba, cha-cha and heart rhythm like hurricane and showers from soft music and graceful dancing world, and perceive the rhythm of modern city in the cheerful life of latin dance.What's Florid now?: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank">ugg classic tall</a> !
<br /><br />Latin music's charm lies in its unique melody and its variety of dance steps. How to NOT Wear <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> : Good Tricks Right now, Latin dance becomes a new favorite of the fitness group.The enthusiastic music, expeditious rhythm, smooth action and dynamic dance full of unique personality make Latin dance become a passionate, elegant and comprehensive method for fitness.Latin dance can fully release emotions and reduce stress, meanwhile consume a great deal of fat, which is good for figure shaping, especially noticeable on the waist, abdomen, and buttocks.Women in Mumbai all Are Obsessed with to Wear <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> 
<br /><br />People shake off the traditional body building and mix themselves with the wildness and passion of Latin. Latin dance brings our city fresh.It heard of sb:latin dance is maybe magic dance which can bring about love.Latin dance is especially suitable for women. When the music sounded, the body swings up charmingly with the rhyme. That’s the sexy and real woman.
<br /><br />The lady pursuit of beauty can try slimming by latin dance, beacuse it not only can help to lose your weigh, but also can shape your body and increase your temperament.In zestful gymnasium , when passionate latin dance encounters gymnastics, monotone physical fitnessbecome passionate and hot.Imagine this, won't Latin style swinging and wiggling make these ladies more charming?Exercise is no longer boring when mixed with unrestrained Latin.
<br /><br />If you havent done such sports, hurry to swing together with us !
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="91d142b860a2107622063696f1af9d47" url=""><![CDATA["Amalfi Rewards of the Goddess" : Japan's Respe<br/><br/>Since Meiji Reform, Japan has devoted to the worship of Europe; it has been obsessed by the ancient roman civilization and Greek mythology. During the second World War, Japan has hoped that axis powers could win, so maybe it can carve up some European civilization with Hitler. The cartoon in modern age and the local works are all express their dream for European civilization. In the field of movie, obtain local material has be been driven into an impasse, and people also have lost some interesting in CG pictures. The best way is to focus on ancient Roman civilization.Recession Chic â€“ How to Be Most Cool-Looking on a Budget
<br /><br />The background of Amalfi Rewards Of The Goddess can be America, but the tragic of the hero will loss its power as there are not church old city. The box office of this film in Japan is good, in the top ten that almost occupied by local cartoon movie, it can still rank five. It is not only attributed to the power of super stars, but also to the warship for European civilization of Japanese. &quot;Vengeance of political victim” is a familiar theme in Japanese movies. Japan itself is a capitalist country with multi parties which are in power in turn. As soon as there is scandal about those who are in power, one who are out of power would instigate the mediums to attack and expose. And there must be some innocent victim. The film tells the story that “victim” plans to assassinate the foreign secretary and the opposites act to stop the assassination. The director meant to add tragic color to this revenge story by the legend of Amalfi. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> , Give You A A-list Life
<br /><br />In the scene that Saeko Yakami who acted by Amami Yuki sent ransom money to Almafi, there are many setting to express city architectures and religion. And then, Hirosho Kataok introduced the legend of Almafi to Saeko Yakami. This setting is intended as the theme of political victim is not the most part but is important, and this also why the film would screen in Italy. They considered the problems of one sector, but had ignored those of another. It din not mix together the plot and the scenes well. When Kosaku Kuroda who played by Yuji Oda and Saeko Yakami shuttled in each spot in Roman, we can remind of Angel and Demon –a film that also shoot in Roman. The latter has better mixed the plot and scenes. Two Japanese ran about madly in the streets of Roman, which made me fell mercy to them, maybe the director meant to express their hopelessness and loneliness. However, the old architectures served as a contrast.How to Resume like Katherine Heigl in <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX0NhcmR5" target="_blank">ugg classic cardy</a> 
<br /><br />The main plot of kidnapper has kept the high level as usual. The diplomat was calm and acted accurately at the moment of truth. The surveillance video has become the most important key. Although some plot is stupid, is not bad on the whole. Especially the earlier shot of Hirosho Kataok’s partners, they all looked at Kosaku Kuroda quirky, which lay the groundwork for the future plot. Since Saeko Yakami has compelled to join in the party of Hirosho Kataok, her manner has been different, she was indecisive while was firm and anxious before. It was dangerous to let Saeko Yakami lead to cut off the alarm system, and it was ludicrous that the guarder had listened to her. Luckily, it was not factal. Director has spent enough part to let Amami show her love for her daughter. Therefore, it was reasonable for what she did later.
<br /><br />Rewards of the Godness hoped to use Roman civilization as a big gift for the Fuji celebration. Both Vatican and the Holy Trinity were irreplaceable, and the key point was that Japanese could film aboard by its own. Only this can make Japanese feel proud. Japanese are more familiar with Roman than other “foreigners”. They have owned ancient Roman civilization. So, their attitude is different from other foreigners’. Other “foreigners” only see the familiar Japanese stars: Yuki Amami, Yuji Oda and Erika Toda.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3f51c83786498d0e7b7c113e1c56037d" url=""><![CDATA[China Mobile's Trend in Development and Its Fourth Brand<br/><br/>After entering the WTO, traditional and emerging industries of China develop fast, and the competition among communication industries turn white-hot. But I always ask myself and peer a word, how does China Mobile develop in the future? How can Chinese enterprises get rid of the short-lived result?Attention! <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYmVyY3JvbWJpZTRzYWxlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Abercrombie</a> May Cause Ruin to You
<br /><br />According to the national conditions, since the carry out of the birth control, child position becomes the highest one throughout history. They became today's &quot;emperor&quot; from previous &quot;dog&quot;, as long as what the kids want, no matter how hard their parents will meet them. We can often see when a family dine out,it's up to the children to choose where to eat.And very often they choose either McDonald's or KFC. No children would ever say he wants to use China Mobile,when the parents ask what they want,which is a problem deserved researching.Several Easy Tips for You to Spice Up Luxurious <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> 
<br /><br />Actually, it is not difficult to see that if enterprises want to keep sustainable development, they must have their brands, and what is more important, it aims at the huge customer group in future. How to Find Your Perfect <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1Nob3J0" target="_blank">ugg classic short</a> How to train up the children to be the loyal consumers of China Mobile in the future? The answer is the brand and experience. From this conclusion, we can image that the future trend of CMCC business hall will be the place for brand exhibition and experience.
<br /><br />The information industry of China has been in a stage of rapid development. The licenses of 3G is going to release. And the five-year infant industry protection of WTO is coming to the end. And in 3G times, the most important things are experience and sale, business hall should not only operate pure poll and consultancy, it should operate more product experience. If a person has nothing to do, he would go shopping as his first thought. Bu no one would like to look around in the business hall of China Mobile. Business lobies always wait for customers to come to charge or consult, or come to complain. No consumer comes to business hall in the idea of playing, or hunting for new business to stimulate demands and consumption.
<br /><br />The wise action of China Mobile is launch the fourth brand to position the children and young people, the core purpose is to train a potential big customer. When a brand blasts into the mind of a child,it will follow him all his life. Children's psychological is in the process of growth and maturity which would affect the child’s future character, values and outlook on life. And if China Mobile choose to strength its brand during this period, it is certain to bring large group of customers to itself in the future. When all these customers become pillars and trunk members, they would certainly create incalculable value and profits for China Mobile.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>