<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="16">
		<document id="f2c81af262a49c7e375e36e2b0a8acbb" url=""><![CDATA[Roura DErm Surgery : From flab to fab abs<br/><br/>From flab to fab abs
<br /><br />I want to have a great body. Who wouldn't?
<br />In my line of work, I meet a lot of people; and superficial or not, appearance is important. Besides, when you are out there interviewing bigwigs in sports, you would feel inferior standing next to their flexing muscles!
<br />            Having a great body is the easiest way to create a good first impression. People who have toned bodies appear healthier and more in control of themselves. They seem to be go-getters, success-oriented and results-driven. After all, how can they entrust you with their business or with themselves if you cannot take care of your own body? Besides if I know that I look good, I become confident and that's the first step in winning people over. 
<br />            So, like everybody else wishing to have that perfect body, I became a regular fixture in the gym. With my busy schedule, holding three jobs, it was a miracle that I was able to squeeze some work-outs in. I even did the popular “After six diet” and even played some sports like basketball and tennis. Needless to say, I lost weight but it was not fast enough for me. I still have the bulges and the flabs that I had before on my tummy and torso. They say workouts would remove them in time but I did not want to look like I was a body builder.  I want to have a toned body and not look like a muscleman.
<br />            When I heard that I can get a six pack in just six hours at the Roura DermSurgery center , I had mixed reactions: Excitement because it could be the solution to my problem, and apprehension, because it is an entirely new procedure and I still had doubts if it really works.
<br />So I researched on the procedure and consulted with Dr. Claudine S. Roura, head of Roura DermSurgery. I was relieved to find out that it was not so new after all. Yes, it is being introduced here in the Philippines for the first time but in other countries, it has been performed on countless patients for a good number of years with wonderful results. In fact, it is all the rage in Europe and US. And it is fast gaining popularity here.  According to Dr. Roura, she has received a lot of invitations to speak about the technology in the provinces. 
<br />            VASER high-definition liposculpture (VAHDL) improves the contours of the body by 'sculpting' the fats and the muscles in the area. While regular liposuction can just trim away the fats, VAHDL can sculpt the body in a way that can never be achieved by conventional liposuction. According to Dr. Roura, this is not however something that you do just to quit gym after. Like regular liposuction, you also have to maintain the shape with exercise, work out and a healthy diet. 
<br />            This is just an answered prayer for people like me who cannot seem to achieve the desired muscle definition that they want even if they work out more frequently than other people. High definition liposculpture can remove the deep and superficial fats that block the detail of the underlying muscles. Liposculpture is also perfect for models, celebrities, fitness buffs, executives and anybody who wants to get a sculpted body in just a quarter of a day. 
<br />Having exhausted all the possible questions about VAHDL, I decided to give it a try. The only thing I can clearly remember is that before the procedure, Dr. Roura drew lines all over my body.  
<br />            When I woke up after six hours, I already saw the results. It was of course still raw but I can already see the muscles! The first thing she told me is to wait a month before I return to my regular exercise routine. I can return to my other regular activities like going to work, just nothing too strenuous. My body still needs time to heal. Two weeks after the procedure, I can already see my new abs and in two months, I already saw the full effect despite the swelling.  I was so happy with it, I recommended the procedure to all my friends and even my family. According to Dr. Roura, it is actually in four months that you will really see the final results. I am still waiting until the four months is up but from the looks of it,  so far, my 6 packs will be a perfect 10. 
<br /><br />For more information about the Dr. Caludine Roura please visit <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.rouradermsurgery.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.rouradermsurgery.com</a> or call 4898526 / 09189264468
<br /><br />(Robbie Pangilinan is a sports columnist and writer for a newspaper. He is also a marketing consultant for TV5 and a Business Development officer for a AIRSPEED INTERNATIONAL COMPANY - Forwarding company)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8e4152c4dc13ef82fdd876ab93e568b" url=""><![CDATA[Cheri Mercado: Reporting in Style<br/><br/>Cheri Mercado: Reporting in Style
<br /><br />Try Stepping into her shoes. You can't be too serious right out of the
<br />bed. Whenever your morning ritual involves the car radio or breakfast
<br />in front of the television, the anchor on your morning show coffee
<br />talk have to be perky to prep you for the day ahead.
<br /><br />Cheri Mercado says she used to work for 10-15 hrs a day when she was
<br />in ABS-CBN. She used to host &quot;Magandang Umaga Bayan&quot; in the morning,
<br />went to gather news from 9am to 4pm as a field reporter, at one time
<br />she was anchoring the &quot;Global News&quot; late at night, and hosted &quot;Coffee
<br />Talk&quot; – a lifestyle show that featured achievers 40 years old and
<br />below in ANC all under the Kapamilya network.
<br /><br />But things started changing when she found out that &quot;there was a life
<br />growing inside her&quot; and that was when she decided to shift priorities.
<br /><br />&quot;The life growing inside of me was all that mattered then.  All of a
<br />sudden the rat race didn't make much sense and I couldn't take care of
<br />my health with the kind of demands and schedule I had. God works in
<br />amazing ways that doors opened just at the right moment.  TV5 offered
<br />a spot for me in their news, promising to be lenient with the demands
<br />while I was pregnant and giving me a four-month break after giving
<br />birth! It was totally a wish come true.&quot;  That gave Cheri a chance to
<br />breastfeed her baby fully for a year and slowly eased back into what
<br />she truly loved doing – delivering the news.
<br /><br />Now with TV5 reformatting, she anchors TEN – The Evening News with
<br />Martin Andanar, a former reporter from GMA7.    It's the only news
<br />format of its kind on Philippine television.  TEN presents stories in
<br />a countdown format, presenting their top story at the end of the show.
<br />It's also a lot friendlier – none of the abrasive and pumped-up
<br />energized style that's been the template for years. &quot;We have the
<br />highest respects for what the other stations are putting in their
<br />newscasts. We simply want to offer an alternative.  We just tapped
<br />into what people are interested to know and what the whole editorial
<br />team feel that we all should know.  And that is not limited to
<br />politics and entertainment news.  We also put in our plate technology
<br />news, socio political awareness stories, commentaries, events, foreign
<br />news, sports and the like.&quot;
<br /><br />Asked how she feels about the newly-relaunched TV5, Cheri says &quot;It's
<br />amazing! It's invigorating, like being pumped up with a fresh batch of
<br />adrenaline.  It's exciting.  Makes me want to get up every single day
<br />and do more.&quot;
<br /><br />Being a mother is still the priority for Cheri.    She's seriously
<br />considering home schooling – teaching her 4-yo daughter Christiana at
<br />home.  &quot;It's a big step.  A serious step, and I totally admire those
<br />who do it and those who have done it.  I am totally intimidated by the
<br />thought.  But my heart is screaming for me to do it, so I'm
<br />half-a-step close to arriving at that decision.&quot;
<br /><br />When not at work, Cheri loves spending time with her stockbroker
<br />husband Mike.  They confess to being mallrats.  &quot;We really should be
<br />more athletic! We're working on that too!&quot;
<br /><br />ON FASHION
<br /><br />I used to love playing &quot;dress up&quot;.  I come from a brood of four girls
<br />and my mom would always dress nicely, her bags and shoes always
<br />well-coordinated.  I love the fact that my work encourages this love
<br />for clothes and shoes (smiles).&quot;
<br /><br />When I was a reporter, jeans were my best friend.  I'd pimp up my tops
<br />for a more fun look worn with heels that could segue to a night of
<br />drinks with friends.. Now, my preference would be dresses and shoes.
<br />Shoes, shoes shoes! I love them and I'm frustrated by them.  I'm a 4
<br />½ and that's almost an impossibility to come by.  Out of frustration,
<br />I've been known to buy shoes just because they fit.
<br /><br />My preference for dresses are from Mia Urquico and Yvet and Choc
<br />Religioso.  They're brilliant and they know how to flatter a woman's
<br />body.
<br /><br />Books
<br /><br />I have always loved reading. My favorite book would still be You Can
<br />Heal Your Life by Louise Hay.  I just finished reading &quot;crunch time&quot;
<br />by Mariah Fredericks , it's funny.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="735fdb9e9860f41a9ca73c6be7a6cdc4" url=""><![CDATA[GLENN DOMAN SEMINAR<br/><br/>Diliman Educational Corporation (DEC) will be holding the second part of a continuing lecture series entitled How to Multiply Your Child’s Intelligence to be held on March 14 and 15 at the Philippine Trade Training Center (PTTC) in Pasay City. Mr. Douglas Doman, Vice President of The Institutes for the Achievement of Human Potential (IAHP), will be conducting the seminar. He is the son of world renowned Glenn Doman, founder of the IAHP based in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania U.S.A. The IAHP has been providing literature and programs for parents who are interested in neurological development of both brain-injured and normal children.    
<br /><br />Mr. Douglas Doman will be discussing the topics, namely: How to Multiply Your Baby’s Intelligence and What to do About Your Brain-Injured Child. For more details information about Diliman Preparatory School and its offerings, you may log on to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gtcsports.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">www.gtcsports.net</a>  or contact Mr. Mhicks Castro of Diliman Educational Corporation’s Business Development Group (BDG) at 951-0382 / 931-0731 loc. 804/809
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="64d629b5b6ee04635c9b3a08e774c1df" url=""><![CDATA[CHERI MERCADO NOW A CALAYAN ENDORSER<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/pangilinan99/photo/photoid=24141851" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_3838179_24141851.jpg" /></a>AS THE FINAL PHASE OF HIS FIRST ALBUM IS NEAR COMPLETION DR. MANNY CALAYAN AND DRA. PIE CALAYAN HAD INITIAL TALKS WITH TV5 ANCHOR/ HOST CHERI MERCADO- SANTOS REGARDING THE POSSIBILITIES OF BEING ADDITION IN THE BROOD OF CALAYAN SURGICAL ENDORSERS...NOW IT'S CONFIRMED CHERI SIGNED CONTRACT WITH CALAYAN SURGICENTER YESTERDAY.
<br />CONGRATS CHERI! WELCOME ABOARD
<br />Posted by DJ Robbie at 7:19 PM 0 comments
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4f6a47dbfd2370355f9d05b95914e05f" url=""><![CDATA[LEAVING A LEGACY TO YOUR CHILDREN - LIVING AS AN EXAMPLE<br/><br/>By Robbie pangilinan
<br /><br />Hairstylist of the Stars. Cutting Edge in the hairdressing craft. Trendsetter. Always makes a difference. Exceptional. These are just some of the best descriptions that could ever be said about Pin Antonio, Owner and Creative Director of Salon de Manila. A businesswoman and a mother.
<br /><br />Salon business actuality came to her when she was in 1st year College, taking up Fine Arts at the University of Santo Tomas. It was when her sister, Ruby Tubig commenced with what she describes “a small salon in our small apartment” in February 1983. This was the beginning of Salon de Manila as a single proprietorship beauty salon, which later became a family corporation in September 1993, then got its trademark patented in April 1997 from the Intellectual Property Office (IPO) , and is currently running with 6 branches around Metro Manila.
<br /><br />Pin Antonio simply started with watching the staff do their tasks after her classes and had the feeling that she can carry out what they execute. As she says, “I believe that I am a born artist, so learning the craft was not hard for me.” True as it is, she has been at the back of Salon de Manila, which has been known to provide perfectionism on its beauty related services. It can be pronounced that she paved her way through the hairdressing conquest.
<br /><br />However, aside from the inborn talent, she also went through a lot of trainings, and joined a lot of contests. This started when she was trained by her late sister and then joined a competition where she garnered 6 awards. Among the awards is the mostly craved for Most Stylish Hairstyle under an international category. Afterwards, she decided to study and be further updated with the skill. In 1998, she went with her sister to Vidal Sassoon Academy in Los Angeles, California. That was when my passion for the expertise has grown,” she says.
<br /><br />The year 1995 was truly a struggle for Pin Antonio. Her sister died and it really affected her. She was already planning on migrating to the United States, but was stopped by her husband, Sonny Mangundayao who is currently the President and Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of Salon de Manila, when she was offered to handle the creative aspect of the business as he takes care of the logistics, and the story goes on.
<br /><br />She never stopped learning. She keeps on attending various trainings specifically in London and the United States with Vidal Sassoon, and Toni and Guy. This is one way to get the latest hairstyles, then she also shares her knowledge to people interested with hairdressing by conducting trainings with them. In the year 2004, the Hair World competition in Singapore paved the way for  her talent and perseverance to give Salon de Manila the Best Salon in Asia title when she won against 16 Asian countries.
<br /><br />Looking at it, she seems to be a very busy person. On the other hand, she is also a loving mother to her four kids – Adlai, Andrai, Scion, and Isaiah. She says, “being in the business and being a mother is not easy, but I just know that doing what is right somehow protects myself on being a good example to my children. I am the same person at home and at work. I just have one face. I know that I am in the right path on leading them.” 
<br /><br />The celebrity hairdresser was very glad to say that two of her children are also inclined with the same interests, and that they are born artists as well. She sent Adlai to Malaysia and Singapore to undergo trainings on hair coloring. She said that Scion was very good in makeup so she is now handling the makeup department.
<br /><br />“When Scion and Adlai finally decided to work in our Salon, I got excited and overwhelmed, because that was our desire! I asked one of our staff to give them pointers on the principles of haircutting, and another on coloring. When I saw their interests ripen, I personally trained them. Not only with haircutting, but in every characteristic of being a great stylist. I gave them pointers, teach them secrets, and everything I know about the skill. I want to pass it on to them so someday they can also fly like eagles in the expertise!” She expresses with enthusiasm.
<br /><br />It is a great pleasure for most parents to see their children follow their steps on their career, or simply have the same interest. It is also best to know that somebody in the family can take care of the business when retirement season comes. It gives a peace of mind as to who the business heritage can be transferred to.
<br /><br />Business or plainly work must be studied and taken care of very well, and, children must also have enough discipline, training, love, and attention. Teaching kids the logistics of business is important, as well as having the right character at work. Salon de Manila is such a successful business. Nevertheless, after all the glory of being called the trendsetter in hairstyle, and after all the praises for the skill from different celebrities, the master of hairdressing stresses what she thinks is important to pass on to her children, “I show them my love, my forgiving and understanding heart, and I let them feel it. My heart, My passion for work, my heart in handling our people, which is with concern, love, and affection, handling the business with righteousness, ethics, love and fear of God. I’m sure, and I know that someday, when we pass these on to them, they will be successful as well. Living as an example is important on leaving a legacy. What you show them is the most important teaching you could ever leave with them.”
<br />#<img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_1377534_29022393.jpg" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c40098ef77516cc846ca8a6e04eef7af" url=""><![CDATA[Love Your Hair<br/><br/>You love your body. You do everything to be in top shape—eating balanced meals, exercising regularly, keeping a health regimen. Yet, with all the pollution in the environment and the stress of daily living, maintaining a healthy lifestyle seems complicated and tedious.
<br />The same goes true with your hair. Having healthy hair starts with loving it. Salon de Manila proprietor and renowned hair stylist Pin Antonio says, “First of all, love your hair. This may sound obvious but is often taken for granted by many. Maintain your hair with love and consistency.”
<br />Pin, who is known for her very modern and chic hairdos, reveals her personal hair care regimen, “I have my hair cut and trimmed appropriately, once a month. I invest in the best products for my hair like treatments and build-up remover which I pamper my hair with every week. Then, every three months I have my hair color done with salon quality products.”
<br />Pin even treats her hair like her own baby—nurturing it with love and care. She even says, “I really pay close attention to my hair and listen to its needs.”
<br />The famous hair trendsetter describes healthy hair as thick and dense, fine and silky, not too oily or rough. Healthy hair should also be lustrous, shiny and glossy, “This means that the hair is pliable or easy to work with because it is not limp or lank,” Pin shares.
<br />But healthy hair goes beyond the surface. As Pin says, getting your hair healthy is easy, keeping and maintaining it is the hard part. Not everyone may have been born with great locks, but everyone can maintain healthy hair, following a few basic steps and doing the steps consistently.
<br />Pin reveals the secret, “Make sure you wash your hair when needed. This is a different routine for everyone, some wash their hair every day, others do it every other day. Find the routine that suits you and keeps your hair looking good all the time and stick to it. You should shampoo and condition thoroughly using a medium circle of shampoo with a lesser amount of conditioner. Brush your hair often. This will not only keep it tangle-free but will stimulate new growth at the roots. Eat nutritious food. An over-all balanced diet of lean proteins, fruits and vegetables, whole grains, legumes, fatty fish like salmon and low-fat dairy will help keep hair healthy.”
<br />She also recommends taking the proper amount of vitamins and minerals daily such as vitamin B-complex, vitamin B6, vitamin C with bioflavonoids, vitamin E and beta-carotene. Flaxseed oil and daily dosage of magnesium, sulfur and zinc are also recommended.
<br />The human hair is very sensitive. Pin says that no matter how much you keep your hair clean, the rigorous routine of daily life exposes the hair to extreme conditions that may cause hair damage. The sun and humidity can damage the hair cuticles which results to dry, drab, split, brittle or frizzy hair and ends. Hair loss is often caused by pollution like dust, smoke emitted by vehicles that contain high levels of carbon, cigarette smoke, and other carbonic gases. Excessive bleaching and perming can also cause damage to hair. Even too much alcohol consumption and lack of sleep can contribute to damaging hair severely. In this day and time, stress virtually affects hair. It naturally weakens body systems and that includes the hair. Hair becomes dull, lifeless and slow-growing.
<br />Pin recommends the following in order to prevent or lessen hair damage:
<br />• Use a scarf or cap over the hair when traveling during the day to protect the hair from direct sunlight, dirt and smoke.
<br />• For people who travel a lot, wash hair as often as often as possible and ensure the use of a good conditioner.
<br />• Avoid leaving oil on your hair as the tendency to absorb dust is higher.
<br />• Give your hair the privilege of a massage regularly.
<br />• Choose hairstyles that are not very long and are easily manageable.
<br />• Never leave the house with wet hair because the hair cuticles are opened. Hair is fragile at this point.
<br />• If you are going to sunbathe, make sure to protect your hair by wearing a hat especially if your hair is colored. If you can, comb in a cream leave-on conditioner while you are out in the sun.
<br /><br />Ordinary kitchen products can also do wonders for your hair, says Pin. Sometimes, these natural products are even better than commercial ones. “For example,” Pin shares, “mix honey and eggs and leave on hair for 10 minutes, then rinse off. Then, mix whipped egg whites with the yolk added with water in a blender. Wash hair with hot water and apply the mixture. Massage on hair for 10 minutes then rinse off with cold water.”
<br />Milk and coconut oil are also superb for the hair, as is mayonnaise. It may sound (and smell) gross but liberally applying mayonnaise to your hair, covering and leaving it overnight, and washing it in the morning can treat damaged hair.
<br />A lot of commercial products are also good for the hair. Choosing between natural and commercial care all depends on the preference of the person. “Believing in a product and seeing the results of that product is what’s important,” Pin says.
<br />Salon de Manila, which Pin and sister Ruby Tubig started years ago, offers personalized hair care depending on the needs of each client. “In Salon de Manila, we usually recommend mild rebonding for frizzy and not-so-curly hair. Split ends may be treated with regular treatments of our salon quality product line as well. There are cleansing agents we recommend for people who have scalp problems like dandruff. These cleansing agents resolve the dandruff problem in a short time, purify the scalp and combat the bacterial attack that caused the flaking, resulting in a healthy, restored and clean scalp. For coarse hair, we recommend thermal relax and for limp and oily hair we use volumizing products.”
<br /><br />Your crowning glory needs tender loving care. Pin has this to say, “Healthy and wonderfully styled and cut hair gives you an image overhaul. A good hairstyle can change your look completely. It can chop off years from your face and make you look younger. Hair is part of the wardrobe. So, find a stylist you trust who’ll treat you and your hair with respect, and who will give you stunningly gorgeous hairstyles!” And when it comes to hair care and hairstyle, no matter what color, length or style your hair is, Pin Antonio and Salon de Manila can help make it shiny and healthy
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="243c2921f7b5411d4d35a7f523ef0de4" url=""><![CDATA[JINKEE PACQUIAO CHRISTMAS GIFT<br/><br/>JINKEE’S CHRISTMAS GIFT
<br />By Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />After all
<br />the year’s victories and scandals, Jinkee Pacquiao truly deserves a diamond
<br />ring and even more.
<br /><br />She never
<br />left her husband’s side, through good times and bad, so to speak. Her presence
<br />during every fight of the pound-for-pound king adds not only inspiration to
<br />Manny but sweetness to every victory won. Amidst the nasty and ugly rumors that
<br />hounded their marriage when Manny Pacquiao was linked to a sexy actress, Jinkee
<br />remained strong.
<br /><br />“Para
<br />din akong boksingero, 'pag kailangan, fight,” Jinkee said in an interview. “I
<br />need to be strong for my children,” the lovely Pacquiao queen said.
<br /><br />The rumors
<br />of the alleged affair were brought about by Manny Pacquiao and Krista Ranillo’s
<br />becoming close friends while they were shooting the upcoming film “Wapakman”
<br />where they ironically play adversaries. The issue became hotter when the two
<br />were reportedly seen in several places together, fueled by a veteran actress’
<br />Facebook advice to Jinkee that seemed to confirm the boxer’s and young actress’
<br />rumored romance.
<br /><br />Pacman’s better half is grateful to the
<br />people who stood beside her in this “storm” in their marriage. “Tapos na
<br />'yong bagyo. There is sunshine after the rain,” she reportedly said.
<br /><br />“…nagpapasalamat [ako] sa concern niya sa'kin kahit di naman kami magkakilala
<br />talaga. Thank you sa message mo, sa concern mo sa'kin,” was Jinkee’s message to
<br />actress Gina Alajar in an interview on a showbiz TV program. Jinkee likewise
<br />thanked Kris Aquino for serving as her confidante in this issue.
<br /><br />And although Jinkee herself says that
<br />the rumors between the People’s Champ and Krista Ranillo are not true, she
<br />admits that she was affected by it. But, she remains strong.
<br /><br />The confident beauty says, “Ipaglaban
<br />mo kung anong meron ka. Kailangan walang aagaw. Kailangan nag-iisa ka lang sa
<br />asawa mo.”
<br /><br />Indeed, she is the only one for
<br />Manny. Despite the many scandals linking Manny to several women in the past,
<br />their marriage remains intact, primarily because Jinkee knows how to handle
<br />negative reports for the sake of their family. She says, “Kailangan for my family, for my
<br />children… I will survive! Kailangan maging strong lang
<br />talaga. Test lang ito ng Panginoon sa akin.
<br />I know that the Lord wants us to be together.” She says her love for Manny is
<br />200%.
<br /><br />Even as she is undecided if she will watch the movie “Wapakman”,
<br />Jinkee’s support for her husband is solid. “Hindi naman ako showbiz na tao. Papag-isipan ko pa kung ano
<br />[manonood ako]. (I'm not a showbiz type person. I'm still thinking if I am
<br />going to watch),” the charming wife, who would rather spend time on the
<br />family’s many businesses, said.
<br /><br />Besides her boutique in General
<br />Santos City, the Pacquiaos recently opened a souvenir shop called Team
<br />Pacquiao at Robinson’s Place. She also owns several coffee shops. She is the mother of
<br />four little kids—Jimuel, Michael, Princess and Queen Elizabeth. And she is a
<br />sight to behold with her glowing white skin and sexy figure. No wonder she
<br />is the latest endorser of Belo Medical Group’s Smart Lipo and Belo Diet Injections.
<br />Jinkee can be a star if she chooses to, but she wants to remain a private
<br />person despite being married to the most famous boxer in the world today.
<br /><br />Manny was
<br />said to have been upset when Jinkee went to Belo for treatments because he sees
<br />his wife as already perfect. After Jinkee’s explanations, and seeing that the
<br />treatments turned Jinkee into a sexier and lovelier woman, Manny has even agreed
<br />to pose with her for the Belo billboards.
<br /><br />For all these, Jinkee deserves more than the diamond-studded ring which
<br />Manny reportedly gave to Jinkee as a “peace offering”. Jinkee says, “Nagulat lang ako
<br />na naisip niya magbigay at happy ako na may gift ako this
<br />Christmas.”
<br /><br />Jinkee Pacquiao is indeed like a diamond—beautiful, timeless, a rare
<br />find. And Manny Pacquiao is definitely lucky to have her. #
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c11e0437d24debee66137dccb3e84cde" url=""><![CDATA[WHO IS ROBBIE PANGILINAN?<br/><br/>Robbie Pangilinan has more than 11 years of experience in Marketing and Public Relations, specializing in Sports Events and Writing, Image Building, Photography, and Talent Scouting. He has extensive training and media experience, having organized numerous PR projects and sports events all around the Philippines.
<br /><br />He is the Executive Vice President for Marketing and PR Director of Gemini Talents Corporation, a company engaged in supplying talents for TV commercials, special events, sports management, training seminars, and educational programs in multi-media productions. Since its incorporation in 1987, GTCSports Entertainment, Inc. has partnered with the Philippines’ top advertising agencies like Basic Advertising, McCann Erickson, Production Village, AMA, and Publicis. Also a bonafide member of  the Talent Agents Organization of the Philippines or TAO.
<br /><br />GTCSPORTS Entertainment believes that people learn best when actively involved and perform best when training and educational programs are an integral part of their daily business. It practices the learning principle “Maximum Media = Maximum Retention” in its training and development activities.
<br /><br />Gemini Talents Corporation continues to expand its pool of management trainers, able talents and consultants who are experts in their respective fields.
<br /><br />His company is likewise a key player in the Sports Web Industry in the country today, having conducted hundreds of sports events. He is also the PR Consultant of Salon De Manila in the Philippines, thepublicist of Contours Body Sculpting Institute in Makati City, and the PR Manager of Senator Nikki Coseteng and the Province of Marinduque.
<br /><br />Robbie writes for the Manila Bulletin, Manila Standard, Manila Times, PoliceFiles and XFiles Sports.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2eb97e71036ce9b8e064992d255113ee" url=""><![CDATA[DPS launches the Stargazer on January 15, 2010<br/><br/>By Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />Diliman Preparatory School (DPS), known for its innovations in the world of learning, opens another door for its students—the door to the vast universe.
<br /><br />DPS launches the Stargazer on January 15, the day when a partial solar eclipse is expected to be seen in some parts of the country. The Stargazer is a powerful telescope priced between 45,000 to 60,000 pesos. DPS bought two telescopes to enable its students to see the wonders of the universe with their own eyes.
<br />The launch of the Stargazer deliberately coincides with the date of the longest solar eclipse since 1992, which, according to the Philippine Atmospheric Geophysical and Astronomical Services Administration (PAGASA), will be seen in Metro Manila between 3:49 and 5:51 p.m., with the maximum eclipse at 4:53 p.m.
<br />Housed in the DPS Campus along Commonwealth Avenue in Quezon City , the Stargazer is meant to be used by the public for free. Of course, priority users are DPS students who can also enjoy the annual Quadrantid meteor shower which will peak until Monday, January 18.
<br /><br />DPS is in partnership with the University of the Philippines ' Astronomical Society which will offer assistance to the students as they explore the Solar System through the Stargazer.
<br />Under the leadership of DPS President and former Senator Anna Dominique &quot;Nikki&quot; Coseteng, DPS is celebrating its 40th year with activities and projects that mark the school's rebirth in terms of academic programs, facilities and overall philosophy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7086e505b9ea238924d512c2fa6731a7" url=""><![CDATA[What Nikki Wants<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/pangilinan99/photo/photoid=29022197" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_5510095_29022197.jpg" /></a>
<br />By Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />Anna Dominique M.L. Coseteng, Nikki as known to many, can honestly say that she has “been there, done that.” She was a congresswoman representing the 3rd District of Quezon City. A senator for two full terms. A TV host for nine years. A radio commentator. One-time actress who co-starred with former president Joseph “Erap” Estrada in “Sa Kuko ng Agila”. An entrepreneur. A school administrator. A mother and a grandmother. In all of her 57 years of existence, she now knows what she has always wanted to be – a peoples’ servant.
<br /><br />Maybe it’s her many years in public service, or the example she saw in her mother, former Philippine ambassador to Mexico Alicia M.L. Coseteng. Maybe it’s her passion, her wanting to give everything and everyone her best, or her hunger for learning. Maybe it’s her desire to always change for the better. Maybe it’s her love for the arts &amp; what is beautiful. Maybe it’s all of these combined that make Nikki Coseteng a genuine servant, in might and in heart.
<br /><br />Nikki’s mother together with two close friends Felisa Generoso and Irma R. Apelo, along with close relatives, founded Diliman Preparatory School in 1968 and became its first president. Today, DPS is one of the most renowned schools in the country known for its standard of excellence as manifested by its graduates and faculty. The institution owes its recent success to its current president, Nikki, as well as its officers and faculty who dream of making DPS a center for educational innovations through improved and energized curricula and state of the art facilities.
<br /><br />Just like in serving the country, passion is still what drives her to be in tiptop shape for the school. “I didn’t dream of being a politician. The same way I never dreamt of running a school as its president. However, I was taught early in life to do things with passion, commitment and compassion. Anything one gets into with commitment and passion will surely generate the best results,” Nikki relates.
<br /><br />The still beautiful Nikki admits to being a perfectionist—to a fault. She even has “25-hour work days” just to get things done the way they need to be. “I just do what I have to do right, in the highest possible standards notwithstanding constraints and limitations. I am not bothered by what other people think if they don’t add anything positive to what needs to be done,” Nikki shares.
<br /><br />Nikki has been very busy managing DPS and introducing more and more innovations. DPS celebrated its 40th year with activities and projects that mark the school’s rebirth in terms of academic programs, facilities and overall philosophy. Nikki aims to create a state-of-the-art learning environment for DPS students through an educational program that is future-driven, innovative, holistic, transformative, interdisciplinary and value-laden. Many have raised an eyebrow and frowned upon DPS’ innovations like its sports facilities, classroom renovations, audio-visual library, Science, Math and computer laboratories, IT programs, online grading system, registration, enrolment and library, among others especially when it cost millions and millions of pesos. But Nikki stood firm and delivered all the changes, transforming DPS and making it a globally competitive school. “My first responsibility and commitment is to our students and their parents. I delivered what I believe they deserve. I am sure, the profits will come soon. It is most unfair to just think of making large profits without prioritizing the development of school facilities and enhancing the students learning experience,” Nikki says.
<br /><br />Nikki introduced to the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia the progressive education that DPS is known for. She explained the Edulynx English Proficiency Intervention Program (ePIP), Glenn Doman method of learning and teaching, and Robotics to 200 members of the Filipino community during her Middle East trip last January.
<br /><br />Believing in holistic education, Nikki even volunteered DPS to be the venue of the Wing Chun Association of the Philippines’ headquarters when its masters visited the country. Vice Consul of the US Embassy Niel Gibson, Education Manager of the British Council William Gancia, First Secretary of the Embassy of Greece, Consul and the Deputy Head of Mission Nikolaos Verghis, and Third Secretary and Consul of the Czech Republic Monika Kazdova were some of DPS special guests who were impressed by the school’s UN celebration last October.
<br /><br />Nikki is well-loved by the students not just because she is very organized and is the epitome of grace and Filipina modesty, but because she knows how to “ride” their interests. She secured a partnership with cosplay.ph in opening the first-ever Cosplay Museum that boasts of costume displays that range from spectacular robotic and creature costumes to elegant gowns and anime garb. DPS students can learn how to make costumes and express their creativity through various school programs. 
<br /><br />She also took innovation to the next level when she launched the DPS Astronomy Center during the January partial solar eclipse. DPS now has a mobile digital planetarium, the first of its kind in the country. Nikki likewise enjoined the 3,000 DPS students, teachers, staff, and parents to walk 6 kilometers from the DPS campus to the La Mesa Ecopark, where they planted trees as their way of “greening” the world.
<br /><br />Nikki knows that she could not have done all these alone. She believes that it’s a team effort. “If everyone involved is in tune and the chemistry is right, it’s a sure shot formula for success,” she says.
<br /><br />“Mind over matter is my mantra,” she says seriously, then jokes about it, “If you don’t mind, it won’t matter.” With Nikki’s infectious passion and heart of a servant, nothing else should matter but success. #
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3173e82f0a571ba6ae5f0f55211392e9" url=""><![CDATA[MVP joins SCOOP; TV5 missing<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/pangilinan99/photo/photoid=29022253" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_8030753_29022253.jpg" /></a>
<br />By Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />Sports advocate and business tycoon Manny V. Pangilinan joined the SCOOP sa Kamayan weekly session Friday even as his own TV5 network failed to cover the event.
<br /><br />TV5’s nonappearance during the forum sponsored by ACCCEL and QTECH Solutions has raised speculations, especially as the two giant networks, ABS-CBN and GMA, along with Sports Radio 918 and all newspapers, were all represented. 
<br /><br />SCOOP organizers invited TV5 News to attend the event but the network seems to have overlooked the invitation. Rumors have it that some TV5 people are not supportive of MVP’s management. Last year, the PLDT group acquired a 75 percent interest in ABC5 and there had been dramatic changes since last year changes that some ABC5 veterans found hard to accept. 
<br /><br />But despite TV5’s nonattendance, Pangilinan was able to clarify some issues regarding his resignation as chairman of the Ateneo de Manila University’s Board of Trustees which might lead to his discontinued financial support to the school’s sports program, specifically its basketball team.
<br /><br />Pangilinan, more popularly known as MVP, has tendered his irrevocable resignation from the board after accusations that the speech he gave during the university’s commencement exercises was found to be plagiarized. The chairman of PLDT and Smart admitted he was hurt by what happened and said he will meet with Ateneo’s team members and officials before deciding whether to continue helping or not. 
<br /><br />Pangilinan, also the president of the Samahang Basketbol ng Pilipinas (SBP) and chair of the Amateur Boxing Association of the Philippines (ABAP), said that he will instead focus his efforts on the national basketball team and the RP boxing team. The Smart-sponsored basketball team is aiming to bag at least fourth place in the Asian Games while the boxing team eyes for a gold medal. 
<br /><br />MVP, who came to the SCOOP session with ABAP president and PLDT senior vice president Ricky Vargas, dreams of the basketball team making it to the 2010 London Olympics as well as quenching the country’s thirst for a gold medal for 86 years.
<br /><br />MVP has high hopes that the RP basketball and boxing teams will garner wins in the Asian Games, then in next year’s FIBA-Asia championship to qualify for the 2012 Games.
<br /><br />Pangilinan emphasized that the SBP is not only training the national team but also aiming to take on an active role in the basketball scene in Southeast Asia. Known as Asia’s basketball capital, the Philippines ought to send a candidate to the coming Southeast Asian Basketball Association congress and elections in Bali, Indonesia, MVP declared, though he did not announce the position yet. #
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f327f8a52cc9638d3992fb663901a408" url=""><![CDATA[What Matters Most<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/pangilinan99/photo/photoid=29028325" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_10356581_29028325.jpg" /></a>
<br />By Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />For Nikki Coseteng, what matters most is not her being a senator for two full terms, nor her being a congresswoman of Quezon City. It’s also not her nine-year stint as a TV host and a radio commentator, not her one-time movie appearance, and not the distinction she holds as the first female team manager in the Philippine Basketball Association and being the league’s vice president in the ‘80s. It’s not even the renowned school where she is now president. What truly matters in her life is her family.  
<br />Nikki raised her two children alone. As a single mother, she admitted that she was extremely busy with her career and business, but always found time to be with Julian and Kimmy during their birthdays, holidays and other special occasions. Nikki describes herself as both a typical and an atypical mother, “Typical in the sense that I helped them with their homework and school projects, like mothers do. I was atypical, too, because I was at the same time involved in different advocacies and earning a living,” Nikki relates.  
<br />Nikki was a disciplinarian. She set the rules and made sure that everyone at home followed them. “I was tougher on them than my parents were on me,” she says. Nikki taught her children to be independent-minded and learn to stand on their own, to make right decisions towards attaining their dreams and to be honest in every way. Being a single parent, finances were a bit difficult so Nikki also inculcated in her kids the concept of wise spending and living within their means, “Or more likely, my means,” she clarifies. “I provided for their needs and sparingly gave in to their wants,” she adds. 
<br />Despite the difficulty of bringing up two kids alone, Nikki loved them like no other. They can tell her anything without fear that she would get angry or disappointed with them. That solid sense of security, Nikki says, was very important and critical in Julian and Kimmy’s development. 
<br />The three—Nikki, Julian and Kimmy—enjoyed traveling and visiting different countries together, learning about other cultures. They also took frequent vacations to Baguio City and liked going to art shows and exhibits, and museum or gallery hopping. Of course, they always had a great time eating out. Times spent with the children’s grandparents and great grandparents remain to be Nikki’s favorite moments. She could not forget the time they went all the way to Akron, Ohio to root for Julian who represented the Philippines in the 1983 Soapbox Derby championship where he won.
<br />Now that Julian is 37 and Kimmy is 33, they still would like to travel and visit different countries together with their mom, but the three are all very busy, especially because the two children now have their own families. Julian, a three-term councilor of the 3rd district of QC, is now running for another term. Kimmy worked in Singapore for several years, so the mother-daughter team was apart for long. Nikki instead spent her time with her grandchildren, often visiting Kimmy’s two children in Singapore and always taking Julian’s son Ryan out to the mall or zoo. When their schedules permit, the three grab lunch or have dinner together.
<br />Nikki is very proud of how her children turned out to be. Julian, who got his mother’s looks, political thinking and passion for public service, is immersed in barangay activities and concerns. Kimmy is a sought-after marketing and communications manager in the corporate world. Julian is the gregarious and outgoing type while Kimmy is a silent and disciplined person who stays away from the limelight. “Both my kids have grown up to be really trustworthy, committed, productive and passionate persons. They both have a kind heart, and are generous, sometimes to a fault. They are honest in expressing their feelings, responsible and accountable for their actions; they do not envy anyone and are not greedy. Both are very independent. I’m proud to say that they never gave me problems that could not be solved overnight,” Nikki beams.
<br />Some of Nikki’s likes and attitude also rubbed off on the two children. “They share my concerns regarding the state of our country. Like me, they have a soft spot for the downtrodden. I love to explore and discover new things and so do my kids. They got their love for nature, culture and adventure from me, as well as their dedication to work, love for family, deep spirituality, and progressive thinking,” Nikki shares. For her children, Nikki has these wishes: excellent health, happiness, fulfillment, success and prosperity, in that order.
<br />Nikki used to have the fear that she would die before her children reached 21 years old. Now, she is sure that because she raised Julian and Kimmy to be independent and self-sufficient, they can stand on their own. “I gained my freedom at 40. When they were in their 20s, my children were already on their own. I am extremely proud of that. They did not need me anymore!” Nikki proudly says. 
<br />For Nikki, seeing her children loved, appreciated and successful, and knowing that she did her part well, are what matters most. #
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c14c3a640f4110dd96514dfa988b2451" url=""><![CDATA[SDM MALE TALENTS<br/><br/>by Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />The salon of popular showbiz and political personalities, Salon de Manila (SDM), is one of the country’s most innovative salon brands. A leader in style trends. A fearless inventor. A passionate pioneer. 
<br /><br />On its 25th year in the salon industry, SDM has handpicked three young gentlemen who embody the spirit of its “Manila’s Cutting Edge” campaign. These “alpha” males, together with three other ladies, are SDM’s brand ambassadors for being cutting-edge themselves. 
<br /><br />SDM Creative Director and internationally-known stylist Pin Antonio believes that these three exemplify SDM’s unconventional excellence. “Their stories are threaded by the underlying theme of starting something good and coming out better, if not ahead, just like SDM,” the Stylist of the Stars shares.
<br /><br />Pinoy Big Brother’s Hermes Bautista is thrilled at taking chances. He owes his now budding showbiz career to just that—chance. Hermes finished his studies here then went on to the US to “the real world” in his hometown San Diego, California. But chance would bring back to the Philippines when he came across the PBB auditions, which he passed easily. The aspiring leading-man believes that chance is a matter of choice.
<br /><br />Isaiah Antonio, on the other hand, is always mistaken for a model. Truth is, he is a singer and musician. Isaiah touches the heart of his audience with his smooth, soulful vocals and a guitar virtuoso. Realizing his potential in his chosen field, Isaiah takes his talent to a higher level as he chose to major in Music Production in college. He considers his talent as a gift, which he willingly shares to anyone. His world of pop and rock is filled with rhythm and soul.
<br /><br />Completing the list is Tom Rodriguez, an illustrator at heart.  Tom is proud to have graduated from The University of Advancing Technology in Temple, Arizona with a degree in Digital Animation. Tom was on his way to enlist for the US Navy but as chance would have it, his curiosity would send him back home to the Philippines to live inside Big Brother’s house. Tom always believes that he has nothing to lose and everything to gain by trying.
<br /><br />These alpha males are the beginning of a fresh, new outlook. They are today’s brightest and tomorrow’s big news. The three young gentlemen reflect a new generation of SDM styles—style being the reflection of an attitude and not just the mere look of the times.  They are SDM’s alpha males—and they will change the way things are. 
<br /><br />“These individuals have taken unconventional routes in their respective fields but nonetheless, excel in them. Each of them is unique, fresh and always headed forward. They have passion for their craft—just like SDM,” Pin says. #<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/pangilinan99/photo/photoid=30515797" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_404156_30515797.jpg" /></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d654f620f1a43d34cf761815a5f0c48" url=""><![CDATA[The “It” Girls<br/><br/>by Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />Salon de Manila (SDM), the salon of popular showbiz and political personalities, is known for being one of the country’s most innovative salon brands – a leader in style trends, as a matter of fact. SDM has always changed the way things are—fearlessly inventing new styles and pioneering new trends in the salon industry. 
<br /><br />This year, SDM once again reinvents itself, and this time, it has chosen three young women who embody the spirit of its “Manila’s Cutting Edge” campaign. These “It” girls, together with three other males, are SDM’s brand ambassadors for being cutting-edge themselves. SDM Creative Director and internationally-known stylist Pin Antonio believes that people need faces to serve as endorsements of the salon. “Whether they be celebrities or long-time clients, we believe that the best endorsement comes from a satisfied customer,” Pin shares.
<br /><br />These three young girls are confident, passionate and motivated—truly cutting edge. But most importantly, like the styles that Salon De Manila creates, these girls are expected to be tomorrow’s big news. “All of them are young, talented, stylish, and though they are still on their way to establishing themselves in their respective fields of expertise, they have already achieved something,” Pin says.
<br /><br />Megan Young heads the three girls in radiating unique and unconventional style just like SDM. One of today’s fastest rising talents, Megan has been making her own name and carving her own niche on mainstream entertainment. At a young age, Megan has an impressive list of work experience. She has been a VJ, has acted in several telenovelas, has done a number of films, and has graced the spreads and covers of the country’s top beauty and fashion magazines. She is also a top choice as an endorser or image model of brands. Megan also hosts, sings, and dances—truly oozing with talent and appeal. 
<br /><br />The second lady, Bettina Carlos, is a print, ramp, and commercial model for fashion magazines, couture designers, and consumer brands. Bettina hosted the youth-oriented show Y Speak and is a columnist in a respected daily where she shares her precious insights opens young minds to become more socially aware. Bettina has just begun to scratch the surface of her enormous potential.
<br /><br />Cathy Remperas is the popular Boholana sent by Big Brother to Finland in an exchange of cast members, known as the Big Swap. Back home, Cathy is a local beauty titlist, an events host and a model on her way to become a nurse. Cathy is indeed beauty and brains.
<br /><br />These individuals have taken unconventional routes in their respective fields but nonetheless, excel in them. Each of them is unique, fresh and always headed forward.
<br /><br />“They will change the way things are,” Pin excitedly shares.
<br /><br />The three young women reflect a new generation of SDM styles—style being the reflection of an attitude and not just the mere look of the times.  The three are definitely SDM’s “It” girls. #
<br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/pangilinan99/photo/photoid=20378333" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_156048_20378333.jpg" /></a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/pangilinan99/photo/photoid=30515787" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_2464646_30515787.jpg" /></a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="64149ae69aae52bd19584c8281f0760a" url=""><![CDATA[Lady gaga "Tessa Valdes "<br/><br/>By  Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />Socialite-philanthropist Tessa Prieto-Valdes celebrated her 16th birthday (over and over again, she says) on September 8 at her best friend Tim Yap’s Republiq Café. 
<br /><br />The fuchsia, black and white invitation showed Tessa in an extravagant costume as a Sea Princess aka Mermaid, complete with a shiny tail and a sparkling tiara. The invite said, “Come celebrate with me… as I swim into another beautiful year of love, laughter, excitement and everything my heart desires.”
<br />Around 50 close friends joined Tessa for a dinner and come 10 pm, the all-night party at the Club started. Pole dancers and performers gave life to the already festive atmosphere with dance music by the Club’s DJ Funk Avy.
<br />Well-wishers included JM Rodriguez, Rajo Laurel,  Rachel Alejandro,  Dr. Hayden Kho, Dr. Vicki Belo, Claudine Trillo, Ruffa Gutierrez, Anton San Diego, and other prominent personalities from the fashion, design, publishing, and entertainment world. 
<br />Tessa is known to throw well-organized, fun and lavish parties attended by the country’s elite. The theme of the party is Sea World Adventure.
<br />One of Tessa’s favorite gifts was a large portrait from Contours Advanced Face and Body Sculpting Institute’s Dr. Claudine Roura. Tessa is the endorser of Contours’ Revalift procedure.
<br />Tessa, who celebrates her birthday on September 6, wished for more blessings and good health for herself and her family. 
<br /><br />#<img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_11352488_30794610.jpg" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5e9f9e0bece931c972f5d7832178f72e" url=""><![CDATA[If There’s a Will<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/pangilinan99/photo/photoid=33948032" target="_blank"><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/10031450_5863814_33948032.jpg" /></a>
<br /><br />By Robbie Pangilinan
<br /><br />There is much more to Will Devaughn than the perfectly chiselled body and the absolute to-die for face. The hunk commercial model turned actor is a loving son, a wonderful brother, and a patient lover.
<br /><br />What William Devaughn Stumpf treasures most in his life is his family. He reveals he has never met any of his grandparents, uncles, aunts, or cousins. The family he dearly loves is composed of his mother and brother.
<br /><br />“It’s just me, my mom and my brother. And that’s all I need,” Will says.
<br /><br />Will’s mom is of German descent and his is from an African-American family. Will, his mom and his older brother Kevin stayed in Germany until Will was 5 years old. The family then moved to the US and transferred from one state to another until before Will turned 20. His mom now lives in Radcliffe, Kentucky while Kevin lives in New York. Will’s stepfather, who somehow replaced his real father in Will’s life, is in Iraq where he works for the US government as head of security. 
<br /><br />Will’s search for the father he never knew brought him to the country. He thought his search will end when he joined Pinoy Big Brother Celebrity Edition 2 in 2007 where he emerged the 4th Big Placer.
<br /><br />A true Filipino by heart, Will came to the Philippines to follow a dream and his heart. The Filipinos welcomed him warmly as he tried his luck in modelling. Lady luck smiled at this handsome young man and soon, Will was in television commercials and print advertisements everywhere.
<br /><br />Will has done hosting stints, movies and television series.  He played the character of Patrick in Regal Entertainment’s trilogy film Desperadas. He has another movie in the works. In the small screen, Will was seen in a cameo role in Komiks Presents: Da Adventures of Pedro Penduko before he went inside the Big Brother House. He also played a supporting role in Love Spell: The Bet.
<br /><br />The Kapamilya Network gave Will his break when he played a main role as Monty in Precious Hearts Romances: The Bud Brothers which made afternoon TV viewers swoon over him. He also starred opposite Judy Ann Santos in the soap Habang May Buhay and again in Precious Hearts Romances: You’re Mine, Only Mine. He guested in Shall We Dance, Your Song Presents: Gimik 2010 and Magkaribal.
<br /><br />Mid-October last year, Will decided to take a great leap forward and signed a contract with the Kapuso Network. He was formally introduced at GMA’s Sunday noontime variety show Party Pilipinas and hosted the show Beauty Queen. He is Elvin in the Fantaserye Dwarfina.
<br /><br />Through it all, Will’s family has been behind him, supporting him all the way, even as it meant seeing him only once a year. What Will misses the most is snowball fighting with his brother in Germany.
<br /><br />Before Will entered showbusiness, he was a Medical Technician in Anaheim, California. Actually, Will wanted to get into the Air Force but did not make it because his vision was 1100, over exceeding the Air Force limit of 300. Yes, the piercing eyes that could melt anyone’s heart were once “legally blind” until three years ago when Will had LASIK surgery. He now has almost 20/20 vision. Will holds a bachelor’s degree in Surgical Technology from Bryman College in California. If Will is not in showbiz, he is most likely to be working as a medical technologist or a pharmaceutical salesman. Because he came from the medical discipline, Will knows that being healthy is very important. His priority when not working is working out at the gym.
<br /><br />“I always mix up routines at the gym so that I don’t get bored easily. I make it a point to find a new workout program every now and then,” Will shares. He also likes playing basketball.
<br /><br />This gentleman looks up to Gary Valenciano and Ogie Alcasid and keeps in touch with his close friends from ABSCBN like Rafael Rosell, Jon Avila, and John James Uy. “We walk the same path but have different shoes on,” he says of his contemporaries. 
<br /><br />The PBB Celebrity Edition 2’s “True Lover” admits he is not in any relationship at the moment, but that he would love to settle down in the future.
<br /><br />“Getting married and having kids has always been a dream of mine. It will happen, just not now,” he says.  
<br /><br />“When I do get married and become a father, I want to be a good role model to both my wife and children. I want to be the kind of dad who my kids can talk to about anything. A father and a friend. Fairly strict but still the ‘cool’ dad,” Will adds. 
<br /><br />Also a budding entrepreneur, Will is working on a business with a few friends that they hope to launch soon. 
<br /><br />When asked what his dreams are, Will says, “I am living the dream.” #
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>