<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="e0654ed8d6757b1f9d02b6b1fda4f67f" url=""><![CDATA[safe sex YALL!!!! make sure yeah?<br/><br/>Nike Condoms - Just do it
<br />Toyota Condoms - Oh what a feeling
<br />Ford Condoms - The ride of your life
<br />Microsoft Condoms - Where do you want to go today?
<br />Optus Condoms - Yes!
<br />KFC Condoms - Finger lickin' Good
<br />M&amp;M's Condoms - Melt in your mouth not in your hands
<br />Duracell Condoms - Keep going and going and going
<br />Pringles Condoms - Once you pop you can't stop
<br />Sydney Olympic Condoms - Share the spirit
<br />Hyundai Condoms - All day, everyday
<br />Tip top Condoms - Good onya mum
<br />Panasonic Condoms - Even more than you expected
<br />VB Condoms - As a matter of fact, I've got one now
<br />Swan lager Condoms - They said you'd never make it...
<br />Vegemite Condoms - Puts a rose in every cheek
<br />Harn Condoms - How can one man have so much talent
<br />Levi Condoms - Do you fit the legend
<br />Nescafe Condoms - It brings you together
<br />Quicken Condoms - Quicken easy
<br /><br />*The following brands probally wont sell as well*
<br /><br />Mitsubishi Condoms - Please consider
<br />AFL Condoms - I'd like to see that
<br />Goodyear Condoms - If it only saves you once a year...
<br />Samboy Condoms - The flavour really hits you
<br />TAC Condoms - Speed kills
<br />Nobby's Condom - Nibble Nobby's Nuts
<br />Bolle Condoms - Put them on your face
<br />Kahlua Condoms - Drink the rhythm
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a7a6c49cdb686d8be4bd9c99589e14a3" url=""><![CDATA[boyfriend application form<br/><br/>Girls Title it &quot;
<br /><br />1. Your Name:
<br /><br />2. Age:
<br /><br />3. Fave Color:
<br /><br />4. Whats your sign?
<br /><br />5.Phone Number:
<br /><br />6. Location:
<br /><br />7. Height:
<br /><br />8.Hair (color and style):
<br /><br />9.Piercings/tattoos:
<br /><br />HERE COMES THE FUN ... ... ...
<br /><br />1. Are we friends?
<br /><br />2. Do you have a crush on me?
<br /><br />3. Would you kiss me?
<br /><br />4. ...with tongue?
<br /><br />5. Would you enjoy it?
<br /><br />6. Would you ever ask me out?
<br /><br />7. Would you make a move on me in a movie theater?
<br /><br />9. Would you take care of me when I'm sick?
<br /><br />10. Do you want to tell me something that you couldn't before?
<br /><br />11.Would you walk on the beach with me?
<br /><br />12. If you heard a rumor about me, would you defend me?
<br /><br />13. Do you/have you talked about me?
<br /><br />14. Do you think I'm a good person?
<br /><br />15. Would u take a nap with me?
<br /><br />16.Do you think I'm cute?
<br /><br />17. If you could change anything about me -would you?
<br /><br />18.Would you dance with me?
<br /><br />19.Would you come over for no reason just to hang out?
<br /><br />What Do You Think Of My?
<br /><br />1.Personality:
<br /><br />2.Eyes:
<br /><br />3.Face:
<br /><br />4.Hair:
<br /><br />W0ULD Y0U...
<br />give me your number?_______________
<br />kiss me?
<br />let me kiss you?
<br />watch a movie with me?
<br />take me out to dinner?
<br />drive me somewhere?
<br />hug me?
<br />buy me food?
<br />take me home to meet your family?
<br />would you let me sleep in your bed if i didn't have one?
<br />sing car karaoke w/ me?
<br />sit in the doctors office with me because I didn't want to go alone?
<br />re-post this for me to answer your questions?
<br />give me a piggyback ride?
<br />come pick me up at 3 am because my car ran out of gas in the middle of nowhere?
<br /><br />D0 Y0U...
<br />think I'm cute?
<br />want to kiss me?
<br />want to cuddle with me?
<br /><br />AM i...
<br />____odd but fun?
<br />____cute?
<br />____funny?
<br />____ cool?
<br />____interesting to talk to?
<br /><br />HAVE Y0U EVER...
<br />thought about me?
<br />thought there might be an &quot;US&quot;?
<br />thought about hookin up with me?
<br />found yourself wanting to kiss me?
<br />wished i were there?
<br /><br />If you don't repost this, your crush will never notice you again.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c15493ac4abf0483d21fd9707a2c0a22" url=""><![CDATA[love hate<br/><br/>No matter how much i hate you i will always love you just that little bit more 
<br />When i see you upset all i want to do is run straight up to you, hug you and never let you go 
<br />But i know in my heart this could never happen
<br />You are my best friend even though we have our differences i still love you and i also think that you may even be my one true love my soul mate
<br />No matter how much i try to deney these feelings the love defeats all and i end up likeing you more and its tearing my heart up every day
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3ec2ef4e8542d9415c64457f38462ae9" url=""><![CDATA[my life<br/><br/>I sit here just wishing i could get out of here 
<br />I can't take it any more
<br />I need to get out, i need somewhere to go
<br />I get treated like i am nothing just a
<br />piece of grass or something which i am not
<br />I get punched in the back of the head,
<br />I get wacked on my arms, my body aches form it
<br />I fear i may end up with damage to me emotionally and psychology when im older
<br />All i want is for all my pain and worries to go away
<br />I get depressed  from them
<br />I want to run away and never look back
<br />Living here i fear for my life because i know if 
<br />I stay any longer i will end up doing something
<br />stupid
<br />I don't feel safe and i won't until i get out
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a7f667bbcba8fc0a3c9176af84b13fbb" url=""><![CDATA[wat does yur name say bot u<br/><br/>T: Nice smile
<br />I: Loves to laugh
<br />F: People wild and crazy adore you
<br />F: People wild and crazy adore you
<br />A: Easy to fall in love with
<br />N: Gorgeous
<br />Y: Makes people laugh
<br /><br />A: Easy to fall in love with
<br />B: Loves people
<br />C: Really easy to fall in love with
<br />D: good listener
<br />E: Freakin' beautiful eyes
<br />F: People wild and crazy adore you
<br />G: Never let people tell you what to do
<br />H: Funny
<br />I: Loves to laugh
<br />J: JOKESTA
<br />K: Really silly
<br />L: Great kisser
<br />M: Makes dating fun
<br />N: Gorgeous
<br />O: Good in bed
<br />P: Popular with all types of people
<br />Q: A hypocrite
<br />R: Good bf/gf
<br />S: Lives life for fun
<br />T: Nice smile
<br />U: Very broad minded
<br />V: Has one of the best personalities ever
<br />W: Gets blamed for everything
<br />X: Never let people tell you what to do
<br />Y: Makes people laugh
<br />Z:Never lets you down
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="171efd6d68aca9be28edf5a9be788f7e" url=""><![CDATA[im for sale<br/><br/>im for sale
<br />Here's the rules of PAN Adoption....
<br /><br />If your a guy you must pick a girl, if your a girl you must pick a guy.
<br /><br />Put in the subject &quot;I'm for sale&quot; and
<br /><br />see who wants to own you.
<br /><br />The first person to send you a message
<br /><br />saying &quot;I own you&quot; owns you.
<br /><br />It's that simple...
<br /><br />P.S.
<br /><br />Repost cause it is funny and surprising to see who gets you first!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="258e8ceda77ac078d282744f8dc6aec9" url=""><![CDATA[Missing Brisbane gurl??? 19 years old<br/><br/>19 year old Coie Wilson, went missing from The valley nightclub, the family, on friday night/saturday morning.
<br /><br />Authorities are appealing for public help to find a 19-year-old south-east Queensland woman missing since Saturday night.
<br /><br />Police say Coie Wilson became separated from friends at a nightclub in Brisbane's Fortitude Valley early on Saturday morning before leaving with an unknown person.
<br /><br />She spoke to her mother by phone about lunchtime on Saturday and made arrangements to be home at Ipswich, west of Brisbane by 8:00pm AEST.
<br /><br />Ms Wilson was last seen on Mt Nebo Road, on Brisbane's westside at about 10:20pm AEST on Saturday, telling a witness her van had broken down and she was trying to contact her family.
<br /><br />She has not been seen since.
<br /><br />Police found her abandoned van on Mount Nebo Road the following morning and say Ms Wilson's purse, money and identification were in the van.
<br /><br />Now its time to use your myspace for something real, no one cares bout what u had for breakfast yesterday, who your fav band is and what colour shirt you are wearing right now. Repost THIS message and maybe someone will come forward with some information on a missing girl from OUR neck of the woods. It could be you or your best friend or your sister. THIS HAPPENED IN THE VALLEY!! THIS IS OUR HOME AND SHE IS ONE OF US!!! COIE WILSON IF YOU ARE HIDING COME OUT!!! YOUR PARENTS ARE SICK WITH GRIEF!! And if you know where Coie is or have any info call 1800 333 000. and if your the guy she left the valley with then just tell someone where she is!! PLEASE!
<br /><br />REPOST THIS MESSAGE!! and lets hope it reaches the guy she left with or her or someone who knows ANYTHING about her disappearance
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d29c79acbbcc04c00be67e5bd67908fc" url=""><![CDATA[i cry<br/><br/>I cry myself to sleep every night,
<br />because your not here with me.
<br />I cry allthe time because once
<br />again you have lied to me.
<br />U promised me you wouldn't,
<br />hurt me but once again i belived it
<br />what a fool i am.
<br />I cry because when i close my,
<br />eyes your all that i see and all the,
<br />memories of you come rushing back.
<br />I sit here crying because you say you
<br />love me but your with her instead of me
<br />Im just gona forget about you because me remembering you just hurts.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ddfa4d133c80fde540b47bd87162f47e" url=""><![CDATA[so sad<br/><br/>Girl: slow down, i'm scared
<br /><br />Guy: No, this is fun.
<br /><br />Girl: No it's not. Please it's too scary!
<br /><br />Guy: Then tell me you love me.
<br /><br />Girl: Fine I love you. Slow down!
<br /><br />Guy: Now give me a BIG hug.
<br /><br />Girl : *hugs him*
<br /><br />Guy: Can you take my helmet off and put it on yourself? It's bugging me.
<br /><br />Girl: Alright, now slow down
<br /><br />Guy: I love you babe
<br /><br />(in the paper the next day):
<br />A motorcycle had crashed into a building because of brake failure. Two people were on it, but only 1 had survived.
<br /><br />The truth was that halfway down the road, the guy realized that his brakes broke, but he didn't want to let the girl know. Instead, he had her say she loved him and felt her hug one last time, then he had her wear his helmet so that she would live even though it meant that he would die.
<br /><br />If u love any one this much re-post this
<br />just to show them that you would give your life for them
<br />to have a love this strong is rare, so treasure everymoment, live laugh and love all you can
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f5a31003188ed3577198a4ce9fa61e45" url=""><![CDATA[What is Love<br/><br/>Love it may only be a four letter word but it makes such a big difference to a persons life.
<br />Love is when I hear from you and i want to jump for joy.
<br />Love is when im around you and I can't get that smile of my face.
<br />Love is when my heart beats it goes out of control. 
<br />Love is when I only ever think about you no matter what im doing.
<br />Love is where I find myself writing little things about how much I love you 
<br />Most of all love is what I feel for you.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a3e569ed9d4715db98432614122a6a06" url=""><![CDATA[don't want to be hurt anymore<br/><br/>I put up with shit from my family
<br />I dis my friends that dis you
<br />I tell my friends that they don't know you like i do
<br />now i'm thinking maby i don't know you like i thought i did.
<br />Because the man i know wouldn't hurt me or make me cry, but this is exactly what you have done
<br />You think that saying the words i love you makes everything ok but it don't.
<br />I love you but i have had enough pain in my life.
<br />So if your going to just cause me more pain i say this is the end.
<br />I don't want it to be the end but it's up to you
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fb5d3c2b5a0eabdb3534000751283243" url=""><![CDATA[marry me :)<br/><br/>WHOS UR SECRET LOVER??
<br />THIS IS HOW THIS WORKS. THIS IS THE FACEBOX MARRIAGE THE 1ST PERSON TO REPLY SAYING I DO IS YOUR FACEBOX HUSBAND/WIFE
<br /><br />EVEN IF YOUR IN A RELATIONSHIP POST THIS YOU'LL BE SURPRISED AT JUST WHO WANTS YOU
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b9b98cd2bffa93285ebed25870de0cab" url=""><![CDATA[my poem<br/><br/>I told you i loved you 
<br />You told me you loved me too 
<br />We could be so great 
<br />Just you and me
<br />I love you with all my heart
<br />Tell me how could it be
<br />You make me happy 
<br />But sometimes you make me cry
<br />You may not have a place in my life
<br />But you will always have a place in my heart
<br />I.L.Y and i always will
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="9df0921391332e8e018971196f3a9c5d" url=""><![CDATA[now im not with you<br/><br/>Every night i would go to sleep
<br />Thinking about how much i love you 
<br />Now i go to sleep
<br />Thinking how much i wish i had you again
<br />i wish things were different
<br />But there not
<br />Every time i feel i got something good
<br />It just blows right back in my face
<br />You give me hope that someone actually loved me 
<br />And then you just take it away 
<br />Thats just not right
<br />You say if i was to move closer thing could work
<br />But i don't see that happening soon
<br />And i no you wont wait 
<br />And i know i will be too late for you 
<br />I know you would want me to move on 
<br />But if only it was as easy as that
<br />I told you i was afraid of getting my heart broken 
<br />And you told me you wouldn't 
<br />But you did
<br />I do understand i truely do but if only ... 
<br />I will always think of if only ....
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6c9c81a7ee09524571a77b1dcfb7a402" url=""><![CDATA[NASTY SEX JOKE<br/><br/>Okay so a guy is
<br />near the
<br />end of his
<br />senior
<br />year in high school.
<br />Unfortunately,
<br />he still has to share a room with his
<br />younger
<br />brother who is only 9
<br />years
<br />old.
<br /><br />One night, he decides to bring his
<br />girlfriend home
<br />for a little fun.
<br />They
<br />have bunk beds and the guy notices that
<br />his little
<br />brother is already
<br />asleep
<br />on the lower bunk, so he and his
<br />girlfriend climb
<br />up
<br />to the top bunk.
<br />As you
<br />might expect things start to heat up.
<br /><br />The guy remembers that his little brother
<br />is
<br />sleeping below so he tells
<br />his
<br />girlfriend to whisper &quot;lettuce&quot; if she wants
<br />it
<br />harder and &quot;tomato&quot; if
<br />she
<br />wants a new position.
<br /><br />Lettuce!!!
<br /><br />Tomato!!!
<br /><br />Lettuce!!!
<br /><br />Tomato!!!
<br /><br />Lettuce!!!
<br /><br />Tomato!!!
<br /><br />She screams.
<br /><br />Lettuce!!!
<br /><br />Tomato!!!
<br /><br />Whoa!!!
<br /><br />PULL IT OUT!!!
<br /><br />PULL IT OUT NOW!!!
<br /><br />I can't get pregnant!
<br /><br />Then the little brother shouts up, &quot;Hey,
<br />would you
<br />guys stop making
<br />sandwiches up there! You're getting
<br />mayonnaise
<br />all over my
<br />face!*!*!*!*!
<br /><br />Post This
<br /><br />1 hour- You'll have bad sex
<br /><br />20 min - Your crush will kiss you
<br /><br />15min - Your crush will tongue you
<br /><br />5-10 min - Your crush will ask you out
<br /><br />under 2 min - You will stay with your
<br />crush forever
<br /><br />repost this as
<br />NASTY SEX JOKE
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2d4fa9a36cff877541e36e3ff40e24d0" url=""><![CDATA[scared<br/><br/>POST THiS iF YOU AREN'T SCARED TO SEE HOW PEOPLE THINK OF YOU
<br /><br />0 = ewwwwwwwwwwww!
<br />1 = Definetly not attractive.
<br />2 = Decent
<br />3 = Fine
<br />4 = Fine as hell!
<br />5 = I'd do you.
<br />6 = Pretty damn sexy!
<br />7 = Lovable, I LOVE YOU!!!
<br />8 = I wanna make you my …
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="211f08fab24da009e68fc36658856266" url=""><![CDATA[the sweetest boy ever<br/><br/>girl:
<br />I love you.
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Yeah I know everyone does!
<br /><br />-Girl:
<br />Really?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Yeah...everyone of my friends that are girls tell me that everyday.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Oh...but am I only your friend?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />No...you're my girlfriend...why?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />So when I say I love you I really do mean it.
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Yeah I know you do mean it...its just that you dont need to tell me that you love me anymore cuz I know you love me since the day we been together and i love you more each and everyday.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />......
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />So wanna go somewhere tonight for our 7th anniversary?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Yeah...where?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />I dont know...maybe movie then dinner?
<br /><br />-Girl:
<br />Ok.
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Ill pick you up after I get off and get ready ok?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Ok. What time do you get off?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />In 2 hours and then I gotta go home and yeah get ready which takes about 15-20 mintues...
<br /><br />-Girl:
<br />hey...I thought you didnt have work today...
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />One of my co-workers called in sick.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Oh okay! So ill see you around 7:30 then?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Yeah! and babe?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Yeah?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />I love you.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />I love you too!
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Ok my manager is like looking at me so yeah.... i gotta go.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Ok bye.
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Bye.
<br /><br />****************************
<br /><br />2 hours later...
<br /><br />The guy drives to his girlfriends house and walks up to the door and rings bell.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Hey! (gives a kiss to her boyfriend)
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Wassup...you ready?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Um...wait...let me get my bag and we can go ok?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Ok.
<br /><br />They both watched a movie and ate dinner...once they were done eating they head back to the car but before she got into the car...
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Wait! Can I blind fold you?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Why??!
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Its a suprise.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />What kind of suprise?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />A big one.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Okay but only if you promise me that you will hold my hand while we're driving.
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />I promise.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Ok blind fold me...
<br /><br />So they drove off...........and then they stoped.
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Ok we're here!
<br /><br />-Girl:
<br />Where?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Wait let me walk you to the place!
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />What place?
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Somewhere! (and gives a kiss to her on the lips)
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Baby!...
<br /><br />The boy walks her to the place.
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Ok...let me take the blind fold off.
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Where are we?
<br /><br />He takes it off her and she opens her eyes and sees the view of the city and at that same spot...that's where he first asked her to be his girlfriend....
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Omg...(tears come down)
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Why are you crying?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />This is where you first asked me out...
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />What are you doing the rest of your life? (he asked on his knees and after he says that...behind him...in the air it says &quot;Will you marry me?&quot; in fireworks)
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />(tears come down faster)
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />I wasnt at work when you called me...I was planning this whole thing!
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Get up!
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Yeah?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />(kisses him)
<br /><br />- Boy:
<br />Is that a yes or a no?
<br /><br />- Girl:
<br />Yes.
<br /><br />If you don't repost this you will have the loneliest life!
<br /><br />BUT!
<br /><br />If you do repost this, you will have a relationship that will last as long as you want it to!
<br /><br />You have 3 minutes to repost this.
<br /><br />if your a girl repost this as &quot;THE SWEETEST BOY EVER&quot;
<br /><br />And if your a boy post as &quot;WHAT I WOULD DO FOR MY GIRL
<br /><br />1) Would you flicker your eyelashes on my face so its like a butterfly landing?
<br /><br />2) Would you make up 'pet' names 4 each other and talk real cute?
<br /><br />3) Would you tell me that I'm sic in a cute voice when I'm obviously unwell?
<br /><br />4) Would you rub my back to make me feel better?
<br /><br />5) Would you get excited everytime I called?
<br /><br />6) Would you come out with me anytime of the day or night just coz I want 2 be with u?
<br /><br />7) Would you sit in a pub with me?? (sometimes I jus wana have a drink and leave)
<br /><br />8) Would you listen to my advice coz maybe I'm right?
<br /><br />9) Would you say that your all mine and keep your word?
<br /><br />10) Would you dress up everytime u see me coz u wanna impress me?
<br /><br />11) Would you watch a movie with me but not end up watching much of it?
<br /><br />12) Would you miss me if i was gone 4 a minute?
<br /><br />I actualy dont think he's asking much...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fae6e8b9f4c5ec888db68fc69fd05d66" url=""><![CDATA[virgin worst nightmare<br/><br/>virgin girl asks her boyfriend to come over Friday night
<br /><br />and have dinner with her parents. Since this is such a
<br /><br />big event, the girl announces to her boyfriend that
<br /><br />after dinner, she would like to go out and make love
<br /><br />for the first time.
<br /><br />* * * * * * * * *
<br /><br />Well, the boy is ecstatic, but he has never had sex
<br /><br />before, so he takes a trip to the pharmacist to get
<br /><br />some condoms. He tells the pharmacist it's his first time and
<br /><br />the pharmacist helps the boy for about an hour.
<br /><br />He tells the boy everything there is to know about condoms and
<br /><br />sex.
<br /><br />* * * * * * * * *
<br /><br />At the register, the pharmacist asks the boy how many
<br /><br />condoms he'd like to buy, a 3-pack, 10-pack, or family
<br /><br />pack. The boy insists on the family pack because he
<br /><br />thinks he will be rather busy, it being his first time and all.
<br /><br />* * * * * * * * *
<br /><br />That night, the boy shows up at the girl's parents
<br /><br />house and meets his girlfriend at the door. &quot;Oh, I'm
<br /><br />so excited for you to meet my parents, come on in!&quot;
<br /><br />* * * * * * * * *
<br /><br />The boy goes inside and is taken to the dinner table
<br /><br />where the girl's parents are seated. The boy quickly
<br /><br />offers to say grace and bows his head.
<br /><br />* * * * * * * * *
<br /><br />A minute passes, and the boy is still deep in prayer,
<br /><br />with his head down.
<br /><br />* * * * * * * * *
<br /><br />10 minutes pass, and still no movement from the boy.
<br /><br />* * * * * * * * *
<br /><br />Finally, after 20 minutes with his head down, the
<br /><br />girlfriend leans over and whispers to the
<br /><br />boyfriend, &quot;I had no idea you were this religious.&quot;
<br /><br />* * * * * * * *
<br /><br />The boy turns, and whispers back, &quot;I had no idea your
<br /><br />father was a pharmacist.&quot;
<br /><br />* * * * * * * * *
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89b5606bc26f9a8f0ea242cc5792e302" url=""><![CDATA[invisible<br/><br/>I cry teras that nobody wants to see
<br />I cut, nobody seems to care
<br />I bleed and nobodies there for me
<br />I have scars that nobody see's 
<br />It doesn't matter what i do
<br />Because to them i am simply
<br />Invisible cut bleed, scar invisible
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9ba090c6346bae4f8deadd1f8818e1c" url=""><![CDATA[A Special World<br/><br/>A special world for you and me
<br />A special bond one cannot see
<br />It wraps us up in its cocoon
<br />And holds us fiercely in its womb.
<br /><br />Its fingers spread like fine spun gold
<br />Gently nestling us to the fold
<br />Like silken thread it holds us fast
<br />Bonds like this are meant to last.
<br /><br />And though at times a thread may break
<br />A new one forms in its wake
<br />To bind us closer and keep us strong
<br />In a special world, where we belong.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e24f7aeb00305593fa9b89a1f705824e" url=""><![CDATA[your name<br/><br/>Your Name
<br /><br />I wrote your name in the sky,
<br />but the wind blew it away.
<br />I wrote your name in the sand,
<br />but the waves washed it away.
<br />I wrote your name in my heart,
<br />and forever it will stay.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f16d5f7e0f119441f4e386759fce04a" url=""><![CDATA[Confusion of Love<br/><br/>Those simple words confuse me.
<br />For I thought I knew what they meant.
<br />Until I lost and won some,
<br />My love today is for rent.
<br /><br />I love you.
<br /><br />Those simple words I know so well.
<br />I wish for you to know.
<br />That just liking someone is so different.
<br />So I will say it real slow.
<br /><br />I L O V E Y O U
<br /><br />Those are the words of a million feelings.
<br />My hopes and dreams and joys.
<br />Little girls writing love letters.
<br />Chasing after boys.
<br /><br />I…L…O…V…E…Y…O…U
<br /><br />Those are the words that I say to you.
<br />I whisper them to your heart.
<br />You turn and look back at me.
<br />I loved you from the start
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ca39ab265acf56a2044c8bcc8d760092" url=""><![CDATA[You<br/><br/>You kissed my lips and I felt a flutter in my heart,
<br />You touched my hand and lit a spark in my body,
<br />You stared into my eyes and saw straight into my soul,
<br />You put your arms around me and I was finally complete.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c782bd2debb2bce7874aaee9df78bf4d" url=""><![CDATA[joke<br/><br/>A stoner walks into a pub and sees a sign hanging over the bar which reads:
<br />---------------------------------------
<br />| Cheese Sandwich .............. $1.50|
<br />| Chicken Sandwich ............. $2.50|
<br />| Hand Job .................... $10.00|
<br />---------------------------------------
<br /><br />Checking his wallet for the necessary payment, he walks up to the bar and beckons to one of the three exceptionally attractive blondes serving drinks to an eager looking group of men.
<br />&quot;Yes?&quot; she asks with a knowing smile, &quot;May I help you?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;I was wondering&quot;, whispers the man, &quot;are you the one who gives the hand jobs?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Yes&quot;, she purrs, &quot;I am.&quot;
<br /><br />The man replies &quot;Well wash your fucking hands, I want a cheese sandwich!&quot;
<br />lol
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>