<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="a59bc4b56f0327cbf0a3c6769f2e6d58" url=""><![CDATA[Some Of The Good And Bad Points Of Very Low Calorie Diets<br/><br/>Opinions is one thing that there are a lot of when it comes very low calorie diets. Some people claim that they are not healthy, but others say they are the best way to lose weight. You should talk to your doctor about this diet and get information on it, if you are considering trying one. There are lots of facts about very low calorie diets and here are some that will make a good starting point for your research.<br /><br />Whenever you make an intense modification to your body, you will be imposing possible negative effects as a result. With the reduction of calories, when dieting; you can sometimes have unwelcome results. Some of the health dilemmas may be nausea, fatigue, constipation, diarrhea, etc. Sometimes obese people who go on very low calorie diets develop gallstones, although this may be a result of rapid weight loss, rather then the diet itself. Always keep you local health provider tuned in to what your health objectives are and inform them of any abnormal symptoms. Medifast is a well known diet plan that has proven effective at helping many people lose weight. Meal replacements products are given to the users of the program to make sure they are staying within the limits of the calorie restrictions that are in place. Although you're supplied with set meals by Medifast on this diet, there's still variety in the meals as they can include things like eggs, lean meats, veggies and there are even desserts, such as puddings. Medifast is very close to being a very low calorie diet, but it isn't one technically due to it allowing a calorie intake of 800 to 1000 calories, which is slightly over the usual 800 calories of a very low calorie diet. One advantage to Medifast is that on this diet your intake of vitamins, minerals and other nutrients is calculated so that you won't be deficient in anything, which is always a risk if you try to restrict calories on your own.<br /><br />If you decide to attempt a food plan with very few calories, you are looking at two primary avenues. You can either go on a diet that gives you formula packets, so that you don't have to worry about counting calories, or you can restrict calories on your own. The second choice will offer you less restrictions; however you will need to be ever vigilant about the foods you eat. All of those tasty morsels you nibble on will be forbidden if they are full of calories. Instead, try low fat yogurt, rice cakes, carrots and fresh fruits and vegetables. As a substitute for refined flour, you would be better off to eat breads baked with sprouted wheat; if you think you need to eat carbohydrates at all. Refined sugars are not good, such as high fructose corn syrup. Picking the diet plan that's best for you can be difficult, and because very low calorie diets promise rapid weight loss they can be all too tempting. However, you ought to approach them with a lot of caution, unless of course your diet is being supervised by a doctor. Without the right advice and guidance, very low calorie diets can be very dangerous.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b533171a8f4dd56b6dda9900ba5ab68" url=""><![CDATA[Very Low Calorie Diets - The Things You Need To Understand<br/><br/>Because these diets cut your calorie intake to levels that are very low it's recommended that you consult a medical professional for advice. They are sometimes recommended by doctors for patients who need to lose a lot of weight quickly, but they are not safe for everybody. The features of very low calorie diets are what we shall be focusing on in the following article.<br /><br />The very low calorie diet has a big advantage for patients suffering from their weight due to them being obese because it can help them to shed their weight very quickly. It's possible to shed fives pounds per week on this type of diet, which equals twenty over a month. For anybody with a medical condition such as high cholesterol, hypertension or heart disease this can benefit them ever so much and it can sometimes save people's lives. Doctor guidance is rather important for this kind of weight loss and if you have a condition that's already being treated then it's crucial. To ensure you keep losing weight it's important to speak with your doctor to come up with a plan. A diet plan, by the name of Medifast, is rather well known and it has helped a lot of people lose weight. In order to assist the users in keeping within the calorie restrictions set by the program they're sent meal replacement products. Although you're supplied with set meals by Medifast on this diet, there's still variety in the meals as they can include things like eggs, lean meats, veggies and there are even desserts, such as puddings. Medifast is very close to being a very low calorie diet, but it isn't one technically due to it allowing a calorie intake of 800 to 1000 calories, which is slightly over the usual 800 calories of a very low calorie diet. The good thing about Medifast is that the diet already calculates and includes your required vitamin, mineral and other nutrient intake, meaning you won't be deficient in anything, which might not be the case if you do things yourself.<br /><br />If you decide to attempt a food plan with very few calories, you are looking at two primary avenues. You can go for a food regimen with a premixed formula, or you can curb your calorie intake by yourself. The latter option allows you more liberty; but you will need to be very conscious of what you consume. For instance, you will need to leave out treats with excessive calories. You can always replace those foods with healthier, low fat options like rice cakes, fruits and vegetables and such. You have to be careful with carbohydrates, so try eating bread made from sprouted wheat rather than refined flours. You should also stay away from refined sugar, including high fructose corn syrup. <br /><br />For short term weight loss very low calorie diets can be very useful, however their effects in the long term are certainly questionable. For people who are obese and under the supervision of a doctor this kind of diet may be appropriate. But for other people it's important that you are careful when it comes to the essential nutrients that are required by your body. After all, you don't just want to lose weight, you want to stay healthy too.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="752455eed072b2c7cf78f8b134fe7319" url=""><![CDATA[Prevent Outbreaks of Acne with Simple Tips Like These<br/><br/>The idea of preventing acne is certainly appealing to anyone who has ever had this condition. It is not always a straightforward thing to prevent the emergence of ghastly zits and in some cases, getting a hold of a medical professional is compulsory. However for the majority of individuals, being mindful of diet, personal cleanliness and other lifestyle decisions can make a magnificent difference. Supplement this with some valuable natural or OTC antidotes and pimples can generally be handled or entirely eradicated.<br /><br />Not only is exercise good for your health in general, but it is also good for preventing skin acne. When you exercise strenuously and sweat, you help to increase the blood circulation in your body and detox your body. You are also using more oxygen, which is wonderful for your skin and body. All exercise is advantageous, but the kinds of exercise that are backbreaking are especially good for the examples that we are using. Basically, any activity that makes you sweat is beneficial for the skin and can help prevent problems such as acne. There are certain herbs and other natural substances that can help clear up acne and prevent it from returning. One of the most powerful of these is tea tree oil, which has strong antibacterial properties. But with great power often comes great potency and tea tree oil is a little bit much for many people. One option that might be an attractive alternative to tea tree oil and is well worth a little research is aloe vera. You can find many skin products that use aloe vera as one of the main ingredients. If you're feeling a little daring or willing to take a risk in order to get rid of your acne for good, place a piece of papaya on your face, in the place where you are most acne-prone. When you're struggling to find a cure for your acne problem so you can present your best face to the world, papaya is a great place to get started.<br /><br />If you haven't heard, smoking has now been linked to acne in addition to its many other ills. Yes, along with all of the other well known health risks associated with smoking, it also constricts the blood vessels and can damage the skin. Painful outbreaks of acne aren't the only common skin complications that are related to smoking. For the most part your skin will begin to benefit as soon as you quit smoking but some of these benefits may take a little time before you can see them. Smoking is bad for you. There's no doubt about that. It's not even a stretch to believe that it's bad for your skin too. <br /><br />Acne can be a huge problem for some, but if you stick with a new strategy to combat it, you can get it under control. The best method for taking care of your skin involves taking care of your entire body. When you use some of these stated remedies or some others that you are familiar with, ensure that you track the results. This is because when you find the method that is most suitable for you, it will be wonderful.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.maidofhonorspeechesandtoasts.com%2Fsample%2Ffunny-maid-of-honor-speeches-make-em-laugh%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.maidofhonorspeechesandtoasts.com/sample/funny-maid-of-honor-speeches-make-em-laugh/</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.maidofhonorspeechesandtoasts.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.maidofhonorspeechesandtoasts.com/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a9ef6f784f29f964ab78404cc3442024" url=""><![CDATA[What You Need To Know About Regarding Very Low Calorie Diets<br/><br/>There are many types of diet plans to choose from, and very low calorie diets are one possibility. Ideally you shouldn't start one of these diets<br />without consulting a medical professional for some guidance because these diets restrict your calorie intake to levels that are severely low. Patients needing to lose a lot of weight quickly are sometimes recommended these diets by their doctors, however not everybody can do them safely. We'll be focusing on some of the features of very low calorie diets in this article.<br /><br />One thing you should know about very low calorie diets is that they can have side effects. When you embark on a new diet, by severely cutting calories, you may have adverse reactions. A couple of the ill effects may include fatigue, bowel issues or nausea. There have been known cases where gallstones build with extreme, rapid weight reduction; most likely caused by the pace with which the weight dropped off. If you go on such a diet and experience any serious side effects, you should keep your doctor informed concerning your symptoms. From research there have been no proven benefits of going on a very low calorie diet when compared with just a low calorie diet. The<br />regular low calorie diet lets you consume anywhere between 800 and 1500 calories every day, while a very low calorie diet will keep you below 800 calories. Fluid loss usually accounts for the great amount of weight lost initially with a very low calorie diet. It was found in a study that after a few months the effectiveness of a very low calorie diet wasn't any better than a low calorie diet for losing weight. A VLCD, furthermore, often has unpleasant side effects, including fatigue, dry skin, hair loss and headaches, to name a few. For those wanting to simply lose weight, a low calorie diet would be the more comfortable option, even though a VLCD might be best for somebody with underlying medical conditions.<br /><br />The dangerous thing about very low calorie diets is that they're appealing to not just obese people but to people who have eating disorders, like anorexia nervosa. This condition is where people really want to be thin and their view of themselves is very distorted. To people with these types of eating disorders they'll look fat, whilst to other people they will look very emaciated. These people will usually not eat anything but foods that are very low calorie, and nutritional deficiencies can be a result of this, bringing along many side effects such as hair problems, nail problems, depression and hypothermia, caused by their body temperature being lower than it should, making them feel cold. If you see someone on a very low calorie diet who already looks too thin, you should try to get them to seek help. There can be some benefits to very low calorie diets, especially for anyone who is extremely overweight and has medical problems because of this. Dehydration and malnutrition are some of the side effects and there are risks involved with such a diet, so getting medical supervision whilst on this diet is recommended.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/fuLafyqaveMariela/blog/blogid=4759409" target="_blank">http://en.pan.netcom/fuLafyqaveMariela/blog/blo...</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.democratandchronicle.com%2Fapps%2Fpbcs.dll%2Fsection%3Fcategory%3DPluckPersona%26amp%3BU%3D2d872f4d8a064a2e9a3932379ee6ea48%26amp%3BplckPersonaPage%3DBlogViewPost%26amp%3BplckUserId%3D2d872f4d8a064a2e9a3932379ee6ea48%26amp%3BplckPostId%3DBlog%253a2d872f4d8a064a2e9a3932379ee6ea48Post%253a1f3cbb51-266b-4f5e-9c68-0de24d273318%26amp%3BplckBlogItemsPerPage%3D5"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.democratandchronicle.com/apps/pbcs.dll/section?category=PluckPersona&amp;U=2d872f4d8a064a2e9a3932379ee6ea48&amp;plckPersonaPage=BlogViewPost&amp;plckUserId=2d872f4d8a064a2e9a3932379ee6ea48&amp;plckPostId=Blog%3a2d872f4d8a064a2e9a3932379ee6ea48Post%3a1f3cbb51-266b-4f5e-9c68-0de24d273318&amp;plckBlogItemsPerPage=5</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1365393209bec8c0cb92ad8d8f14871f" url=""><![CDATA[Very Low Calorie Diets - The Things You Need To Understand<br/><br/>It would seem to be logical that very low calorie diets would help you to lose weight, but before you try such a diet it's good to learn as much about them as you can. When choosing one of these diets, you should be cautious and if possible have a doctor monitor your progress; they may not be a healthy weight loss option. We will be taking an in depth view of these extreme diets, and figure out the plus side and see if there are any deficits as well.<br /><br />Whenever you make an intense modification to your body, you will be imposing possible negative effects as a result. When reducing your calorie intake, you may experience some effects that are less than pleasant. The list of possible harmful effects may be comprised of symptoms like fatigue, diarrhea, nausea and others. Sometimes obese people who go on very low calorie diets develop gallstones, although this may be a result of rapid weight loss, rather then the diet itself. Your doctor should always be included in making decisions on severe weight reduction diets, especially with an extreme diet plan. From research there have been no proven benefits of going on a very low calorie diet when compared with just a low calorie diet. A typical low calorie diet allows you to eat between 800 and 1500 calories per day, while a very low calorie diet keeps you under the 800 calorie mark. Due to fluid loss, the initial weight lost will be more if you're on a VLCD. However, studies have suggested that after a few months a VLCD isn't any more effective than a regular low calorie diet. In addition to this, headaches, dry skin, hair loss and fatigue can be some of the nasty side effects from a very low calorie diet. So, a VLCD might be best in some cases for medical reasons, however a traditional low calorie diet might be better for most people to lose weight.<br /><br />In England in the 1970s the Cambridge Diet, which is a very low calorie diet, was developed. If you go on this diet, you get pre-packaged foods, which calculate all of the necessary nutrients you need, as well as keeping your calorie intake down. They're usually in the form of soups, meal bars and shakes. While this diet has been around for a long time, and many people have had success with it, it does have some disadvantages. Exercise can only be done at very low intensity and drinking a lot of water is a must in order to avoid dehydration. A lot of people will also become very bored of eating just meals that are packaged. Before going on a diet like the Cambridge Diet you need to consult your doctor to find out whether it's safe for you. Very low calorie diets can carry benefits, especially in those people who are very overweight and as a result of this have medical problems. Dehydration and malnutrition are some of the side effects and there are risks involved with such a diet, so getting medical supervision whilst on this diet is recommended.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FWhats-New-about-the-3790T-GPS-by-Garmin-Nuvi%2F03EFBFFFF0246A6B70008015D0FFB"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://community.atom.com/Post/Whats-New-about-the-3790T-GPS-by-Garmin-Nuvi/03EFBFFFF0246A6B70008015D0FFB</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6c4b57f8d227760cdc2520ce6fe52010" url=""><![CDATA[Some Of The Good And Bad Points Of Very Low Calorie Diets<br/><br/>There are numerous diet plans to pick from and a very low calorie diet is just one of the many possibilities. Ideally you shouldn't start one of these diets<br />without consulting a medical professional for some guidance because these diets restrict your calorie intake to levels that are severely low. They're not safe for everyone and doctors will sometimes recommend them to people who must lose weight fast. In the following article we will focus our attention on some of the features of very low calorie diets.<br /><br />One problem is that people find it hard to stick to long term very low calorie diets. It is difficult for anyone to consume less than 800 calories a day, especially in the long term. Although people lose the weight when they are on the diet, when they come off they start to put it back on. That's why it's important to come up with a long term strategy for changing your lifestyle and eating a healthier diet. When you have finished the very low calorie diet this will stop you from going back to your old habits, and will help you to keep the weight off by having a modified diet and regular exercise. <br /><br />One diet used a lot is OPTIFAST as is is used globally by lots of hospitals. This diet started out for people that are about 50 pounds overweight or over 30 on the BMI scale. So if you are just a few pounds overweight then this diet is not for you. You will be monitored by professionals all the time on the OPTIFAST diet as it is in a medical setting which is an advantage. The program has such a solid track record because it started in 1974 and is deemed safe and effective, and millions of people have gone through it. Making serious changes to your life and diet are things you will have to do if you want to be serious about this diet.<br /><br />The hCG Diet combines both hormone injections and a very low calorie diet to promote weight loss.<br /><br />Women naturally produce the hormone hCG, Human Choriogonadotropin, when they're pregnant. This diet originated in the 1950s back when some fellow called Dr. Simeons created a book detailing the benefits of this hormone in helping people to eat less and not feel hungry. The hCG Diet is considered to be potentially unsafe and it's very controversial. If you're thinking about the hCG Diet then you really must find out what the opinions are on both sides before you try it. <br /><br />These diets are not for every person wishing to shed a few pounds, but if you have checked with your doctor and he gives you the OK; you just might give it a try. You now have a little information regarding the selections open to you. Regardless of the type of diet you choose, just make sure you study the information on the one you are thinking about and make sure it will fit into your lifestyle.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FWhats-New-about-the-3790T-GPS-by-Garmin-Nuvi%2F03EFBFFFF0246A6B70008015D0FFB"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://community.atom.com/Post/Whats-New-about-the-3790T-GPS-by-Garmin-Nuvi/03EFBFFFF0246A6B70008015D0FFB</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e4976c94a3b06f8b8d12fd87af35caef" url=""><![CDATA[Don't Hire a Home Improvement Contractor Without Considerin<br/><br/>Preceding the hire of a contractor, you might want to ensure that you have looked at every angle because you will not desire to have bad disappointments down the road. Supporting you in finding a contractor who tells you the truth and<br />who is dependable is what this piece is written for.<br /><br />The best way to find a contractor is through word of mouth. Learning about a good experience a neighbor or friend has had with a contractor, is really half the battle. Though you should speak with him to know beyond a shadow of a doubt that he is the man for the job you have, you will minimally be in possession of a recommendation you can count on. As expected, this can't constantly be the case, yet this is the first endeavor you should consider when looking for a contractor to hire. In addition, it is possible to discover copious amounts of information regarding individuals on line today. Despite the fact that not all people are aware of this, numerous local skilled laborers have evaluations written by local clients, published online. Certainly not all reviews can be trustworthy, yet you can get a pretty good idea provided there are enough of them. Subscribing to a service that charges a fee such as Angie's List is something you could do as well, this is a list of critiques independently given, and contractors are included in this. <br /><br />Before you hire a contractor for any project, it's a good idea to check to see if there are any complaints on record against him. One of the two most renowned spots to check someone out would be the Chamber of Commerce and the Better Business Bureau. A contractors history is important, but records provided by other people could be based on personal differences rather that professional quality. When you read a complaint, make sure to read between the lines; situations are not always what they seem. For example, a customer might change his mind or want additional word done in the middle of the project and then complain when the price goes up. So you have to look over any complaints and use your best judgment.<br /><br />Before you go out and hire a contractor, make sure you have a clear idea of what you want done. Failing to know what you're looking for leaves the doors wide open for an unscrupulous contractor to talk you into buying much more work than you had planned. On the other side of the equation you could be disappointed with the results if you didn't really think things through. Before you hire a contractor you need to know what you want the project to look like, the types of materials that will be used in the project, and have a budget in place for the sum total of the project. If you need a little help with inspiration or solidifying your goals, visit a home improvement store. Don't forget the countless books, magazines, and websites that exist on the subject of home improvement projects. Obtaining a reputable contractor is generally the smartest method to get a job for home improvement done in the manner you hoped for. Therefore, don't rush out and hire anyone, ensure that you discover the greatest person for the project.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F787821%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailystrength.org/people/787821/journal</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FHow-Jet-Airways-Got-Through-Rough-Times-And-Became-A-Reputable-Airline%2F03EFBFFFF0246A9370008015D1015"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://community.atom.com/Post/How-Jet-Airways-Got-Through-Rough-Times-And-Became-A-Reputable-Airline/03EFBFFFF0246A9370008015D1015</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8434fbbb49f54da071e0447003239f08" url=""><![CDATA[The Real Facts Regarding Very Low Calorie Diets<br/><br/>When a diet is restricted to just 800 calories per day or less then it's classed as a very low calorie diet (VLCD). While people's nutritional needs vary, most people find it quite challenging to restrict calories to this extent, which is why most diet programs of this sort give you prepared formulas to eat. You should consider a few of the following points before you embark on a very low calorie diet.<br /><br />You should not go on a very low calorie diet without talking to your doctor. For people with specific medical conditions, children, breastfeeding or pregnant women and the elderly, this type of diet can be dangerous.<br /><br />If you're taking of type of medication or if you fit into any of these categories then it's crucial that you consult your doctor regarding what kind of diet is appropriate for you. Whilst a very low calorie diet can aid you in losing weight, it may also deprive your body of the essential nutrients that it requires. That's why you have to be careful when choosing such a diet, and why it's best to only do so under medical supervision. <br /><br />A popular diet is the OPTIFAST which is used by lots of hospitals all over the world. If someone is over 50 pounds more than they are recommended to be or over 30 BMI then this diet is for them. You should not consider this diet if you are only slightly overweight. You will be monitored by professionals all the time on the OPTIFAST diet as it is in a medical setting which is an advantage. The program has such a solid track record because it started in 1974 and is deemed safe and effective, and millions of people have gone through it. Making serious changes to your life and diet are things you will have to do if you want to be serious about this diet.<br /><br />A very low calorie diet, called the Cambridge Diet, was produced in England back in the 1970s. Pre-packaged foods that provide you with the required nutrients, in addition to keeping your calories low, are given to you on this diet. They can come as shakes, meal bars and soups. Even though this diet has been in existence for a while, and a lot of people have had success on it, it does carry some disadvantages. On this diet you cannot do exercise that's very intense and you must drink plenty of water as to avoid dehydration. Also, people can find themselves fed up of consuming packaged meals. To find out whether a diet like the Cambridge Diet is safe for you or not you must ask your doctor. <br /><br />To sum things up, if you need to lose some weight and your local health care provider says you are healthy enough to do it; you may consider one of these low cal food regimens. We have covered some of the choices available, in this commentary. Regardless of the type of diet you choose, just make sure you study the information on the one you are thinking about and make sure it will fit into your lifestyle.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myindospace.com%2Fblog%2Fview_blog.php%3FBlogId%3D162835%23viewdetails"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.myindospace.com/blog/view_blog.php?BlogId=162835#viewdetails</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ziki.com%2Fen%2Fgail-bryant%2B284678%2Fpost%2FSimple-Ways-to-Elude-Acne%2B12880546"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.ziki.com/en/gail-bryant+284678/post/Simple-Ways-to-Elude-Acne+12880546</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8d89666d42392c35dc61df6136c3fa8a" url=""><![CDATA[Very Low Calorie Diets -How to Decide if They Will Work For<br/><br/>When you have the urge to lose a little weight, especially with an intense diet; you need to do some checking into the pros and cons before you delve into it. Some of these diets are quite effective, however they are not for everybody; it would behoove you to consult your physician. In this commentary, we will put the really low calorie diets under a microscope and compare the pros and cons.<br /><br />When you introduce any high impact diet to your body, you could be promoting an unhealthy outcome. Whenever you start a very different kind of diet, it's possible that your body will react in some way, and cutting back on calories can have certain effects. A couple of the ill effects may include fatigue, bowel issues or nausea. There have been known cases where gallstones build with extreme, rapid weight reduction; most likely caused by the pace with which the weight dropped off. Always keep you local health provider tuned in to what your health objectives are and inform them of any abnormal symptoms. Some research indicates that there are no proven benefits to a very low calorie diet as opposed to a merely low calorie diet. On a typical low calorie diet you can eat between 800 and 1500 calories each day, whereas a very low calorie diet limits you at 800 calories or less. If you're on a very low calorie diet you'll see a lot of weight loss to begin with, however a good amount of it is from the loss of fluids. After a few months, however, studies suggest that a VLCD is no more effective than a low calorie diet for losing weight. A VLCD, furthermore, often has unpleasant side effects, including fatigue, dry skin, hair loss and headaches, to name a few. Even though a very low calorie diet might be best in cases where there's a medical reason, a normal low calorie diet will probably be most comfortable for people looking to lose weight.<br /><br />People with disorders in eating, like those with anorexia nervosa, can be attracted to very low calorie diets just as much as obese people, which can be dangerous. This is a condition where people have a preoccupation with being thin, and have a distorted view of their own appearance. To people with these types of eating disorders they'll look fat, whilst to other people they will look very emaciated. Such people will often refuse to eat anything but very low calorie foods, and this can bring about nutritional deficiencies and many side effects such as depression, problems with the hair and nails, and hypothermia, which makes them feel cold because their body temperature is lower than it should be. Should you see a thin person on a very low calorie diet you must talk them into getting help. <br /><br />There are no guarantees when attempting any diet, some of these are intense and supervision from your physician would be a good idea; but if you doctor gives you the go ahead, then go for it. There are a couple of alternatives, some that we have viewed in this piece. Regardless of the type of diet you choose, just make sure you study the information on the one you are thinking about and make sure it will fit into your lifestyle.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myindospace.com%2Fblog%2Fview_blog.php%3FBlogId%3D162837%23viewdetails"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.myindospace.com/blog/view_blog.php?BlogId=162837#viewdetails</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FSimple-Ways-to-Elude-Acne%2F03EFBFFFF0246AA620008015D1497"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://community.atom.com/Post/Simple-Ways-to-Elude-Acne/03EFBFFFF0246AA620008015D1497</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e2a9b970465c81190151d561363afc57" url=""><![CDATA[Determine Whether a Low Cal Diet is the One for You<br/><br/>When you have the urge to lose a little weight, especially with an intense diet; you need to do some checking into the pros and cons before you delve into it. When choosing one of these diets, you should be cautious and if possible have a doctor monitor your progress; they may not be a healthy weight loss option. We will be taking an in depth view of these extreme diets, and figure out the plus side and see if there are any deficits as well.<br /><br />Some people believe that the key to living a long life is a very low calorie diet, but some experts will disagree and say that very low calorie diets are not healthy. According to one theory, based mainly on research done on animals, severely restricting your intake of calories can prevent many diseases and slow down the aging process. People who subscribe to this view may go on a very low calorie diet even if they're not overweight, because they believe it will help them live longer. The Calorie Restriction Society is an organization that's dedicated to this practice. Thus far there hasn't been any research done on humans to try and prove or disprove the theory in question, but it is worth looking into further. <br /><br />Some patients in the 1930s were treated with the Rice Diet, founded by Walter Kempner; this particular diet was made up of rice for the most part and was helpful for hypertension and kidney malfunction. If you are looking to loose a little weight; this diet could be helpful. This diet does not call for rice alone, but it is eaten with absolutely everything else you do eat; so you are up for a battle if you do not already like rice. The advantage of the Rice Diet is that it cuts out processed foods, and is extremely low in fat, salt and sugar. Most dieters may not wish to continue this food plan for any considerable amount of time; it is very intense.<br /><br />The Cambridge Diet is a very low calorie diet that was developed in England in the 1970s. If you go on this diet, you get pre-packaged foods, which calculate all of the necessary nutrients you need, as well as keeping your calorie intake down. Soups, shakes and meal bars are what form they are in. This diet does have some disadvantages, even though people have been successful with it and it has been around for a while. On this diet you cannot do exercise that's very intense and you must drink plenty of water as to avoid dehydration. Also, eating packaged meals every day can become tiresome for many people. To find out whether a diet like the Cambridge Diet is safe for you or not you must ask your doctor. <br /><br />The long term benefits of a very low calorie diet can be questionable, however they're useful for short term weight loss. For people who are obese and under the supervision of a doctor this kind of diet may be appropriate. However for other people it's important that they get the right amount of nutrients for their body. In addition to just losing some weight you also want to stay healthy too.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FSimple-Ways-to-Elude-Acne%2F03EFBFFFF0246AA620008015D1497"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://community.atom.com/Post/Simple-Ways-to-Elude-Acne/03EFBFFFF0246AA620008015D1497</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myindospace.com%2Fblog%2Fview_blog.php%3FBlogId%3D162837%23viewdetails"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.myindospace.com/blog/view_blog.php?BlogId=162837#viewdetails</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2f242c0bb3add2cba4b0e3256f0bf384" url=""><![CDATA[Useful Tips To Remember When Selecting The Best Diet<br/><br/>If you're going to go on a diet, you want to find one that's going to get you the results you want. You need to remember that your failure or success will be down to you, not your diet. You will need to follow your diet through, in this article we can only look at ways to help you choose your diet.<br /><br />The Mayo Clinic Diet is a diet that was put out there by the famous research organization. Many people have heard of the Mayo Clinic, and may have looked on their website for advice, but not everyone is aware that they have their own diet. You might have guessed already but the diet is about rigorous nutritional principles and research. Gradually you will start to make healthier choices with the Mayo Clinic Diet rather than counting calories or not eating certain foods. The advantage to this diet is that you have access to their online community, and the benefit of all the medical research that's behind this organization. <br /><br />Before you chose a diet you should consider how much structure, as well as guidance, you need. To get the most out of your diet you will have to be honest. Choosing your own food and counting calories is something you have to when it comes to some diets. But with other diets you are guided fully, with a specific allowance for what to eat for dinner, lunch and breakfast, and sometimes even between meals. To make sure people stick to the diet, some people like this structure but others find it way too restrictive, so they will quit the diet. It's not a question of one being better than the other, but which will work best for you.<br /><br />Before going on a diet it's often a good idea to visit the doctor. To begin with, your doctor can inform you about how much weight you ought to lose to get the optimum health. Your doctor can also point out any other problems you may need addressing, such as cholesterol and high blood pressure.<br /><br />Some diets can actually help sort out these issues in addition to helping you lose weight. Your doctor can also provide you with some guidance on which diets are good and which are bad. <br /><br />Everybody is different, this is why there is no diet that is best for everyone. Be patient with the diet and give it a chance to get working. If you want to keep your weight off once you have lost it, you should lose it gradually rather than with an extremely low calorie diet, which are seen as unhealthy.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ziki.com%2Fen%2Fervin-william-20%2B285111%2Fpost%2FLearn-About-the-Versatile-and-New-Garmin-Nuvi-3790T-GPS.%2B12885237"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.ziki.com/en/ervin-william-20+285111/post/Learn-About-the-Versatile-and-New-Garmin-Nuvi-3790T-GPS.+12885237</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5a06f31d520c42e4b1e609ea5b8adb08" url=""><![CDATA[Very Low Calorie Diets - Important Facts About Them<br/><br/>There are lots of different kinds of diets to choose from, and a very low calorie diet is just one of them. Due to these diets cutting your intake of calories to very low levels you really should speak to a medical professional for some advice before going on one. While doctors will sometimes recommend them to patients who need to lose weight quickly, they're not safe for everyone. We shall be looking at some of the things related to very low calorie diets in this article.<br /><br />It is often hard for people to stick to these diets long term, which is a problem. It's hard to maintain on a diet that for a long period of time restricts you to less than 800 calories a day. Once coming off the diet people tend to gain weight again, when they lost it on the diet. To help you in the long term, it is a good idea to come up with a strategy for eating healthier and changing your lifestyle. When you have finished the very low calorie diet this will stop you from going back to your old habits, and will help you to keep the weight off by having a modified diet and regular exercise. <br /><br />There are some natural diets out there that severely limit your calorie intake, however most very low calorie diets have specially prepared formulas to make sure you don't go over your calorie limit. One potential option is a raw foods diet, where the foods that you consume are unprocessed and uncooked. As you won't be eating any foods that are processed, all of the modern high calorie junk will be avoided, so a strict raw foods diet will normally be very low in calories.<br /><br />A raw foods diet will consist mainly of vegetables, fruits, nuts and sprouts, but you can make or buy raw food versions of foods such as bread using a dehydrator. Lots of people find it rather difficult to stay on track with this kind of diet because eating most everyday foods is forbidden, however this is considered to be healthy. If you aren't too keen on making your diet 100% raw then you may wish to add some more raw foods into your very low calorie diet.<br /><br />The hCG Diet combines both hormone injections and a very low calorie diet to promote weight loss.<br /><br />Human Choriogonadotropin is what hCG is, and it is a hormone that's produced by women who are pregnant. Simeons created a book back in the 1950s saying about how this hormone could be used to assist people in consuming less and not feeling hungry by simply having these hormones injected into them. The hCG Diet is considered to be potentially unsafe and it's very controversial. If you're considering the hCG Diet, you should research opinions on both sides before trying it. <br /><br />Very low calorie diets can be useful for short term weight loss, but their long term benefits are questionable. For the people who are obese and under the supervision of a medical professional this may be an appropriate kind of diet. For other people it's important that they get sufficient nutrients that their body requires. After all, you want to stay healthy in addition to losing weight.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="82dad3e6be0aaf424fc374a35188d00c" url=""><![CDATA[Locating Top Notch Contractors in Order to Improve Your Home<br/><br/>Some people think that finding a great home improvement contractor is difficult, but it's not. Stories about contractors scamming people, or leaving their homes in a right mess may be something you've heard, however these sorts of incidents are rather rare. If you just take some common sense steps you can ensure that something like this doesn't happen, and we'll be going over some of these steps in this article.<br /><br />Be advised that the builder you choose must have the license to do work in your area. Your local vicinity may have specific licenses that may be required to build or remodel; you can confirm this with your local agencies. For your own legal protection, you need to make sure the contractor has the right kind of insurance; whether it is legally necessary or not. The minimum requirement would be enough liability insurance to match the assessment of your house. You do not need the perils of a liable suit hanging over your head. Don't be afraid to ask a contractor for proof of licensing and insurance. The kind of builder that is a bad idea to hire is the type that approaches you through internet mail, coming to your house or calling you. Various scams are out there where a person insists on a retainer, vows to complete a job for the dwelling owner, and then disappears before the work is completed. Honest builders won't be attempting to make you hire them by knocking on your door or calling you. You need to be the one to get in touch with them first if it's a substantial job, however if someone desires to rake up your leaves or shovel your walk, that's different. Do not allow an individual to convince you to make any type of improvement on your dwelling where you don't check them out first.<br /><br />Carefully consider whether your project even merits that help of an actual contractor.<br /><br />Often times, you can do much of the work yourself or with limited assistance from a general handyman. With major renovations though or any work that warrants plumbers and/or electricians it's probable that you'll need a licensed and insured contractor. When work needs a permit you'll probably need a contractor as well. It's a huge risk for you not to hire a contractor for these tasks for you as well as those who are helping you. <br /><br />You won't have a hard time finding a solid and reliable contractor and if you use these tips you'll have a better overall experience than most people in your situation are able to have. There is a cost involved in hiring contractors for your home improvement projects. Letting someone with the skills and talent to do the skilled labor though is worth the price most of the time.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="902be2f92857b827a54f9ecce1165037" url=""><![CDATA[Easy and Proven Methods for Curing Stress Headaches<br/><br/>Headaches have become quite a common complaint due to the stressful world in which we live. You should not, however, convince yourself that having a raging headache every day or even every week. In this article we are going to look at some of the proven techniques that can help you prevent or even cure your stress headaches. Depending on what has been causing your headaches, some of these things will probably work better than others.<br /><br />The most common treatment for a stress or tension headache is to take aspirin or another over-the-counter medication. There are many choices here, and some will work better than others depending on the kind of headache you have and how severe it is. It is important to understand, however, that taking medication for your headache makes you more prone to something called the &quot;rebound&quot; headache. This occurs when the effects of the medication wear off and the headache comes back. That's why you shouldn't exceed the recommended doses of any medication you take for a headache and consult with your doctor if this isn't sufficient. <br /><br />One very common cause of a tension or stress headache is being dehydrated so the simple act of drinking water could be the solution you need. It's easy to get distracted and not realize that you are dehydrated. Try to remember that drinking caffeinated drinks isn't the answer; things like soda and energy drinks can make your headache worse. Water is your best bet and iced herbal tea and pure fruit juice will also work when you want to rehydrate yourself. When you eat too much salty food your dehydration can get worse so cutting back on the salt is a good idea.<br /><br />The things you eat and drink can sometimes cause headaches but not a lot of people are able to make this connection. What you think is a tension headache might actually just be a sensitivity or allergy to food. Lots of people find that alcohol, even in little doses, can cause headaches. Caffeine, especially for people who drink a lot of it, is another very common culprit behind headaches. If you want to stop these particular headaches, you need to dramatically reduce your caffeine intake. For some people, headaches are caused by the consumption of other foods like chocolate, dairy and peanuts or peanut butter...anything that you have a sensitivity to. See if there might be a connection between your headaches and the foods that you have been eating and drinking. <br /><br />Stress headaches can be cured in lots of ways including the methods in this article. If your headache is caused by tension, the most obvious solution is to lower the stress in your life but that can be very hard to do. You should still explore it though because stress is terrible for your body; headaches are just the tip of the iceberg.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e24480b1114c0c4634e7045bcb15fdf" url=""><![CDATA[Here Are The Pros And Cons Of Very Low Calorie Diets<br/><br/>Very low calorie diets are seen in different ways as there are many opinions on them. Some people claim that they are not healthy, but others say they are the best way to lose weight. You should gather information about these diets if you are planning to start one, and contact your doctor about it too. These facts can be a good starting point of your research for a very low calorie diet.<br /><br />You should not go on a very low calorie diet without talking to your doctor. For some people, like women who are pregnant or breastfeeding, children, the elderly or people with special medical conditions, this diet can be dangerous.<br /><br />If you're taking of type of medication or if you fit into any of these categories then it's crucial that you consult your doctor regarding what kind of diet is appropriate for you. While very low calorie diets can help you to lose weight, they can also deprive your body of nutrients that it needs. That's why you have to be careful when choosing such a diet, and why it's best to only do so under medical supervision. <br /><br />To make sure that you don't go over the allotted number of calories you can consume, most very low calorie diets will involve some prepared formulas, however there are some natural diets that also drastically limit your calorie intake. One choice is going on a raw foods diet, where the foods you eat haven't been processed or cooked at all. A strictly raw foods diet will tend to be very low in calories, because you'll be avoiding all modern processed, high calorie foods.<br /><br />A raw foods diet will consist mainly of vegetables, fruits, nuts and sprouts, but you can make or buy raw food versions of foods such as bread using a dehydrator. Because you have to avoid nearly all every day foods this is a very difficult diet to stay on track with, however it's considered to be very healthy by many people. Even if you really don't want to have a 100% raw diet you can still try to incorporate some more raw foods into your very low calorie diet.<br /><br />One danger of very low calorie diets is that they're appealing to not only people who are obese but also to those who have eating disorders, like anorexia nervosa. This condition is where people really want to be thin and their view of themselves is very distorted. A lot of people who suffer from such eating disorders will think of themselves as fat, whilst other people will see them as very thin. Nutritional deficiencies can happen because these kinds of people will usually refuse to consume foods that have higher calorie content, which can lead to side effects such as hair and nail issues, depression and hypothermia, which makes them feel cold due to their body's temperature being lower than what's deemed to be normal. If you see someone on a very low calorie diet who already looks too thin, you should try to get them to seek help. Choosing the best diet plan may seem to be a hard task, and with the promise of losing weight fast very low calorie diets may seem very tempting. Without the right advice and guidance, very low calorie diets can be very dangerous.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.flukiest.com%2Fmedia%3Ff_blog_id%3D182449"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.flukiest.com/media?f_blog_id=182449</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2eac6429e7f72b7b5766c4962403c803" url=""><![CDATA[Finding The Best Home Improvement Contractor - What You Must<br/><br/>Whenever you're planning to hire a contractor to help with home improvements or renovations you want to be sure to take your time and find one that will be reliable and honest. The good news is that there are plenty of great contractors to choose from, however, you might have to look a little bit to find the one for you. It doesn't have to be a long and arduous process if you follow these simple steps.<br /><br />The best way to find a contractor is through word of mouth. Provided a friend or someone nearby can recommend a contractor they have been pleased with, then you have already made great headway. You will at least have a recommendation that is trustworthy, yet you still need to discuss things with him to ensure he is the best for the job. This is the first method you might attempt to locate a contractor, though certainly this isn't always possible. Another way to find out facts about contractors currently is on the web. Multiple experts currently have cyber appraisals that were sent in by members of the community, though not everyone knows this. Even though you obviously cannot put your faith in all reviews, there are plenty of them to obtain a correct overview. An alternative could be subscribing to a service that charges a price to receive separate critiques of a wide variety of services, which includes contractors. <br /><br />Ask contractors to provide you with credit or bank references. Keep in mind that this person will be in your home and possibly around your family before you dismiss it as too extreme. If you don't know the contractor it's especially important to make sure he has credit in the area. This helps give you a little peace of mind that he isn't going to take the money and run as soon as you give him your down payment. Local business supply companies should have accounts for the contractor in question. Of course, we're referring to a licensed contractor here, not someone like a handyman or maybe a student who you hire to do a small job.<br /><br />When dealing with a contractor the two times that are most important are when the job is done and when the contract is being signed. It's very important to make sure everything is done and done well before you pay the contractor and sign off the job. Of course, you have to check that the promised work has been completed. The contractor should have taken away any debris and cleaned up the site, which should be mentioned in your contract. Finally, making sure the contractor can prove to you that all suppliers and any subcontractors have been paid is important, as these people could hold you to account if they don't get their money. <br /><br />Even small home renovations or improvements can increase the value of your home on the market as well as for your enjoyment of the home. When you find a highly skilled and qualified contractor you're more likely to get the results you're looking for so choose carefully. These principles will help you find the contractor most likely to give you the renovations you want.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.flukiest.com%2Fmedia%3Ff_blog_id%3D189487"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.flukiest.com/media?f_blog_id=189487</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="23774c7ce3e76f11c04c60af14f1d29f" url=""><![CDATA[Things to Consider Before Hiring a Home Improvement Contract<br/><br/>If you have some home improvement projects, you may be wondering if hiring a contractor is a good idea. You have more than one option available: you can do it yourself, get a general handyman, or hire a fully licensed contractor to do the work. Don't make a choice like this without keeping a few key factors, like these, in mind.<br /><br />The greatest avenue to locate a contractor is by reputation. Learning about a good experience a neighbor or friend has had with a contractor, is really half the battle. You will at least have a recommendation that is trustworthy, yet you still need to discuss things with him to ensure he is the best for the job. This isn't always possible, of course, but it's the first method of finding someone you should attempt. Another way to find out facts about contractors currently is on the web. Multiple experts currently have cyber appraisals that were sent in by members of the community, though not everyone knows this. Even though you obviously cannot put your faith in all reviews, there are plenty of them to obtain a correct overview. Another way is to pay for registration to a service similar to Angie's List, which shows autonomous criticism of contractors and all sorts of other services. You don't want to hire a contractor who attempts to promote your business via e-mail, knocking at your door, or email. Various scams are out there where a person insists on a retainer, vows to complete a job for the dwelling owner, and then disappears before the work is completed. A reputable contractor is not going to be knocking on your door or calling you up trying to get you to hire him. If someone offers to rake leaves or shovel snow, that's one thing, but if it's any kind of major project, you want to be the one who contacts them first. Do background checks first before you let anyone try to persuade you to let them do any sort of home improvement job.<br /><br />A contractor has quite a few responsibilities, and one of these is securing any work permits that are needed. This means if you want to have an addition built to your home, and a zoning permit is required, the contractor should be the one to take care of this. If an individual can't or won't do this for you, they most likely are not a contractor that is licensed. Consequently, if you have been contemplating a big job for improving your house, you might consider interviewing your contractors to ensure they are willing to secure all work permits that are required. You ought to go with another person if not, since a benefit of hiring a builder is that they are the one to manage those types of things. <br /><br />The tips we've shared on hiring a contractor aren't meant to talk you out of it, only to make sure you do your research and protect your interests. When it comes to home improvement projects, having a contractor do the work is a big step and can be costly. On the other hand, if you plan it properly, it can add lots of value to your home, and make it more comfortable and appealing.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.flukiest.com%2Fmedia%3Ff_blog_id%3D189520"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.flukiest.com/media?f_blog_id=189520</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7af2465c7d131b10045eb0a1f5d59758" url=""><![CDATA[Stress Headaches--How to Make Them Go Away<br/><br/>Headaches are a very common complaint, given the stressful world in which we live. It is not normal, however, to have a throbbing headache every day or even every week. Keep reading to learn some things you can do to prevent and sometimes even cure stress headaches. Depending on the cause of your headaches, some of these methods will probably work better for you than others.<br /><br />Tension headaches can be brought on by eye strain which is a common problem due to people spending most of their days staring at computer screens. When you add television and texting to this, you are straining your eyes quite a lot! While it is most likely that you aren't able to simply quit your job, there are still things that you can do to prevent or reduce your headaches if that is the main source of your eye strain. Take a few seconds, for example, to look away from your screen. Do this a lot so that your eyes aren't forced to continue staring at the screen for a long time without getting a chance to rest. It may also help to put a protective shield of some kind on your computer screen, which can reduce glare or, in some cases, radiation. <br /><br />You probably don't think that your posture plays into your headaches, but regular bad posture could be causing some of them. It's a fairly common problem with people who work at computer stations for long periods of time. A major problem is leaning forward so that your head puts more pressure down onto your back and your neck. Try to be aware of any tension you're holding in your shoulders or neck when you sit or walk around. Aside from working on sitting up straight, you may want to get regular massages or chiropractic treatments.<br /><br />The Alexander Technique and Feldenkrais Method that work really well to help you get a better posture. You can look for a professional practitioner of these methods or you can learn more about yourself by doing an internet search for videos that you can learn from.<br /><br />A foot bath with hot water is a remedy that's often effective if you frequently get stress headaches. You can use your own bathtub for this, a big bucket or you can fork over some money for one of the foot spas that you can find online or in most pharmacies. This is a fantastic treatment to do right before going to bed. If you purchase your own foot spa, you can set it to your comfort level but remember a good temperature is hot but not scalding. Let your feet stay in the bath for ten to fifteen minutes. As well as being great for your feet, it's great for your whole body and might even stop the headaches altogether. <br /><br />There are, as you can tell, a lot of ways to deal with stress headaches. You may want to use an instant cure, such as a pain reliever or cold caffeinated beverage if you have a bad headache, but you should really be looking at finding the cause of the problem and finding a way to manage it. Nobody should be forced to deal with stress headaches since they're typically a message from your body that it is time to lower your stress.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.flukiest.com%2Fmedia%3Ff_blog_id%3D185609"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.flukiest.com/media?f_blog_id=185609</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="73241ccfd2d9f1a85fcd4d1696a4225c" url=""><![CDATA[The Best Ways to Stop Stress Headaches<br/><br/>Stress headaches, especially in our fast paced society, are incredibly common and sure it's possible to fix them with aspirin or other pain relievers but it's better to search for a permanent solution. If you only get a headache once in a while, that's not a big problem, but if stress headaches are something that you frequently suffer from, you should try to find the cause. If you have severe headaches, you need to talk with your doctor and you might find some of these other remedies helpful too.<br /><br />Eyestrain is a common cause of tension headaches because people spend most of their days looking at computer screens. And, thanks to television, movie and smart phone screens, your eyes are under more strain than you probably think they are. Even though you can't just quit your day job, there are still things you can do to prevent headaches if that is the main source of your eye strain. It can help to look away from whatever screen you're looking at for a few seconds. Do this a lot so that you are not just staring at your screen for lengthy periods of time without giving your eyes a break. A protective shield that reduces glare and (sometimes) radiation is another solution to help protect yourself. <br /><br />One of the most common causes of the stress headache is dehydration so drinking more water might be a good solution for you. You may not know exactly when you are dehydrated especially if you are distracted by work or other things. Try to remember that you don't just want to drink more caffeinated drinks like soda or energy drinks because those can actually cause headaches. Water is your best bet and iced herbal tea and pure fruit juice will also work when you want to rehydrate yourself. Eating lots of salty food can make your dehydration worse so reducing your salt intake (and intake of junk and snack foods in general) can help too.<br /><br />If you experience stress or tension headaches, the best form of control over them is relieving the stress in your life. This is easier said than done but if you focus on it you will accomplish it. You can reduce your own stress levels by learning yoga and mediation. Relaxation exercises involving things like deep breathing don't just help you relax, they help you cure your headaches and preventing new ones from starting. If you are under lots of stress you might not be able to get rid of all of it at once, but you can take measured steps toward this goal. In conclusion, lots of people suffer from stress headaches and these headaches have a bunch of different causes like lack of sleep, too much caffeine or booze, etc. It is important to figure out the source of your headaches and take care of it, even if it means accepting changes that are inconvenient or not so pleasant. You don't want to have to live with headaches all the time, so it's worth it to to what's necessary to prevent them.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.flukiest.com%2Fmedia%3Ff_blog_id%3D185609"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.flukiest.com/media?f_blog_id=185609</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2da8e47fceefde4a056ca416cb45c2f" url=""><![CDATA[The Truth Regarding Very Low Calorie Diets<br/><br/>There are many types of diet plans to choose from, and very low calorie diets are one possibility. Ideally you shouldn't start one of these diets<br />without consulting a medical professional for some guidance because these diets restrict your calorie intake to levels that are severely low. They're not safe for everyone and doctors will sometimes recommend them to people who must lose weight fast. We shall be looking at some of the things related to very low calorie diets in this article.<br /><br />Some people believe that the key to living a long life is a very low calorie diet, but some experts will disagree and say that very low calorie diets are not healthy. Severely cutting your calorie consumption can make the aging process slower, as well as prevent diseases, according to one theory that is mainly based on animal research. People who believe this will probably go on a very low calorie diet, even if they're not overweight because they think that they'll live longer because of it. An organization that is fully dedicated to this practice even exists and it's called the Calorie Restriction Society. So far, there is no conclusive research done on humans to either prove or disprove this theory, but it's something worthy of further study. <br /><br />The Rice Diet is a diet that was developed in the 1930s by a doctor named Walter Kempner, who found that a diet that consisted mainly of rice could be useful for treating certain diseases such as hypertension and kidney diseases. This particular diet can also help some people shed a few pounds. You consume more foods than rice alone; however rice is eaten with every meal. The most positive aspect of the Rice Diet is the ability to do away with unhealthy processed foods and is nearly free of fat, sodium and sugars. Most dieters may not wish to continue this food plan for any considerable amount of time; it is very intense.<br /><br />When you try an extremely low cal diet, you really only have two alternatives. You can purchase products already prepackaged for you; or you can take it upon yourself to control your calorie consumption. The latter option allows you more liberty; but you will need to be very conscious of what you consume. For instance, you will need to leave out treats with excessive calories. You can always replace those foods with healthier, low fat options like rice cakes, fruits and vegetables and such. Carbohydrates are something to keep your distance from; if you need to eat bread; try a variety made with sprouted wheat flour rather than the processed ones. You should also stay away from refined sugar, including high fructose corn syrup. <br /><br />For short term weight loss very low calorie diets can be very useful, however their effects in the long term are certainly questionable. Such diets may be suitable for obese people under the supervision of a doctor. For other people it's important that they get sufficient nutrients that their body requires. You want to remain healthy and not only lose weight after all.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fjosephellis923.vieuxblog.com%2FThe-first-blog-b1%2FRiding-The-Technology-Wave-With-the-Garmin-Nuvi-3790T-b1-p53.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://josephellis923.vieuxblog.com/The-first-blog-b1/Riding-The-Technology-Wave-With-the-Garmin-Nuvi-3790T-b1-p53.htm</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.zimbio.com%2FGeneral%2Farticles%2FWFuP1BEPH5X%2FNew%2BTouches%2BGarmin%2BNuvi%2B3790T%2BGPS%3Fadd%3DTrue"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.zimbio.com/General/articles/WFuP1BEPH5X/New+Touches+Garmin+Nuvi+3790T+GPS?add=True</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be2cf9d6436c169096343a272b2a3d50" url=""><![CDATA[Useful Tips To Remember When Selecting The Best Diet<br/><br/>If you're going to go on a diet, you want to find one that's going to get you the results you want. You should know that your success or failure is down to you, not your diet. Although having the right diet will help, you will need to carry the diet through on your own, but we will look at ways to help you choose a diet.<br /><br />The famous research organization has put out a diet called the Mayo Clinic Diet. Even though people may have been on the Mayo Clinic website, they are probably unaware of their diet. You might have guessed already but the diet is about rigorous nutritional principles and research. You only need to make healthier choices with the Mayo Clinic Diet, not count calories or eat certain food. With the Mayo Clinic Diet you will have access to not only all the research behind the organization but also access to an online community. <br /><br />If you like the idea of a scientific approach to dieting, the Volumetrics Diet may appeal to you. This is all about the energy density of foods, how many calories a food has compared to how filling it is, and this was started by a nutrition professor called Barbara Rolls. Low density foods are better for losing weight, because they are high in volume but low in calories. These are foods such as fruits and vegetables. The opposite of this is high density foods, these will add lots of calories from only a small volume of the food, like sweets or cookies. Volumetrics divides foods into four categories, 1 being lowest density and 4 being highest. The first and second groups are what you want to eat the most of.<br /><br />Before you go on a diet is is normally a good idea to see your doctor. Firstly, you can be informed by your doctor on the amount of weight you must lose in order to have the optimum health. He or she can also point to any other issues you should be paying attention to, such as high blood pressure or cholesterol.<br /><br />Some diets can actually help sort out these issues in addition to helping you lose weight. Your doctor can also advise you on the wisdom of trying certain diets and how good or bad a new diet book or program is. <br /><br />Every diet is different for everyone, there is not one diet that's best for all. For starters you need to be patient and give the diet a chance to work. Except for extremely low calorie diets, which aren't usually considered healthy, it's best to lose weight gradually, as this gives you the best chance of keeping the weight off for good.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.zimbio.com%2FGeneral%2Farticles%2FT-mH_dUPUDm%2FJet%2BAirways%2BIndia%2BKnown%2BEverywhere%2BAmazing%3Fadd%3DTrue"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.zimbio.com/General/articles/T-mH_dUPUDm/Jet+Airways+India+Known+Everywhere+Amazing?add=True</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwallinside.com%2Fpost-219910.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://wallinside.com/post-219910.html</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="168b8121101763430c62a1657e8f248f" url=""><![CDATA[What You Need to Know Before You Hire a Home Improvement Con<br/><br/>If you are considering a few remodel jobs around your home, you are probably wondering about contractors. By hiring a competent builder to renovate your home; you can pretty much relax and watch the job unveil before your eyes. It is important to investigate the builders that are available to you and choose the one that will fit the bill. The following are some ways to make sure you get the right contractor for your needs.<br /><br />No matter how concerned you are over your budget, avoid the temptation to pick the cheapest contractor who bids on your project. Your home is probably among your highest value investments and you don't want to do anything to risk its value.<br /><br />Not only do you need to be sure you're getting someone who is capable of getting the job done but also someone who will use quality materials when doing the job. After you've received estimates from several contractors you might want to go with the cheapest; but only if there are no standout contractors in the group and if the prices are very similar. However, if one contractor claims he can do the job for a much cheaper price than the others, you should be suspicious, because it's likely that he's going to be skimping on something important. Asking to see a couple of references is a great way of determining if the contractor is right. This is a reasonable request, so you ought to cross off anybody who refuses to show references. Have a look at these references and ask to see what work the contractor has done. Also, you can have a word with some of the people on the list and ask some questions like if there were problems with the contractor or if they're happy with the work done. Asking them if they're ever hire the contractor again is probably the question that's most useful.<br /><br />Builders have a lot of things they are responsible for, like getting all job permits that are a necessity. This means if you want to have an addition built to your home, and a zoning permit is required, the contractor should be the one to take care of this. If an individual can't or won't do this for you, they most likely are not a contractor that is licensed. One needs to discuss with contractors whether or not they would take on responsibility for these permits, should you have a major home improvement job on their mind. Should they say no, you need to look somewhere else, because one benefit of securing a contractor is not being forced to take care of those things on your own. <br /><br />In addition to increasing the value of your home; home improvement projects can also make your home a more appealing place for you and your family to live. Getting the right contractor for the job will ensure you get the results you're after so take your time and choose wisely. These simple tips will have you hiring the contractor most likely to give you the renovation results you're after.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.zimbio.com%2FGeneral%2Farticles%2FZK3RnmlsOCq%2FHow%2BJet%2BAirways%2BGot%2BThrough%2BRough%2BTimes%2BBecame%3Fadd%3DTrue"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.zimbio.com/General/articles/ZK3RnmlsOCq/How+Jet+Airways+Got+Through+Rough+Times+Became?add=True</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fjosephellis923.vieuxblog.com%2FThe-first-blog-b1%2FThe-Goal-Strategy-and-Start-Up-of-Jet-Airways-b1-p56.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://josephellis923.vieuxblog.com/The-first-blog-b1/The-Goal-Strategy-and-Start-Up-of-Jet-Airways-b1-p56.htm</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a81247743c132481441ede6820e526e7" url=""><![CDATA[Easy and Proven Methods for Curing Stress Headaches<br/><br/>Headaches are day spoilers and make it really hard to concentrate on the things that you need to get done. You have lots of options for treating your stress headaches but if they happen frequently, you need to pay a visit to your doctor. Most of the time, though, some basic changes to your lifestyle and a few home remedies are sufficient to rid yourself of tension headaches.<br /><br />One of the common causes of stress headaches is not getting enough sleep. For the most part people need at least seven hours of sleep each night to feel really good. If you're getting much less than this, you're putting yourself at risk for a variety of problems, and headaches could be one symptom.<br /><br />Try to make some changes to your schedule so that you can go to bed earlier. You might need to drink fewer caffeinated drinks, turn off your TV or turn off your computer earlier as well. Your other option is to try to fit in a nap at some point during your day. Even when you can't sleep during the middle of the day, simply lying down and closing your eyes for a couple of minutes can be good therapy. You don't have to wait until a headache sets in to do this either, just by taking a little bit of time to relax each day you could prevent the headaches from happening altogether. Once in a while, tightness around your jaw is the cause of a tension or stress headache. There aren't that many people who understand just how tightly they clench their jaws when they are tense and this can cause a host of symptoms not the least of which is a headache. In some cases you can even give yourself TMJ which is a condition that causes any movement of your jaw to be extremely painful. Make sure that if you come down with this, and it happens more often than you might think, it is important to go see your dentist or doctor. However, even if you don't have TMJ, tightness of the jaw could be causing you to get stress headaches. The best remedy for this is to be aware of your jaw's tension and work to relax the muscles in the area. You could also try putting something like a pen or pencil (or similarly structured item) between your teeth. Don't bite down on your object of choice, instead, use it as a constant reminder to keep your jaw muscles loose and relax.<br /><br />Giving yourself a foot bath in hot water is also a great way to counteract the effects of a stress headache. You can use your regular bath for this or a bucket or one of the foot bath spas that are made specifically for this which are usually easy to find in the pharmacy or on the internet. This is a great treatment to use in the evening or nighttime before you head to bed. If you buy a foot bath spa, you can set it to your comfort, but if you prepare it yourself, use water that's hot but not scalding. You can try one of the methods listed in this article but if they don't prove effective you should talk to a doctor.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwallinside.com%2Fpost-219911.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://wallinside.com/post-219911.html</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.zimbio.com%2FGeneral%2Farticles%2F2peiNLbjUeA%2FSimple%2BWays%2Bto%2BElude%2BAcne%3Fadd%3DTrue"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.zimbio.com/General/articles/2peiNLbjUeA/Simple+Ways+to+Elude+Acne?add=True</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="100c6fd39dab5466743fe4811fbfef36" url=""><![CDATA[Very Low Calorie Diets - The Truth<br/><br/>A very low calorie diet (VLCD) is normally defined as a diet where the total calories consumed in a day are 800 or fewer. Most people will find cutting their calories to this level to be very difficult indeed, even though everyone's nutritional needs differ, which is why nearly all diet programs like this will provide prepared formulas for you to consume. Before going on a VLCD you ought to consider some of the points in this article.<br /><br />Sticking to a very low calorie diet is often something people struggle with, which is a problem. Consuming less than 800 calories a day is very difficult to maintain for a long period of time. Although people lose the weight when they are on the diet, when they come off they start to put it back on. To help you in the long term, it is a good idea to come up with a strategy for eating healthier and changing your lifestyle. This is so you keep the weight off that you have lost rather than going back to your old habits after the very low calorie diet. From research there have been no proven benefits of going on a very low calorie diet when compared with just a low calorie diet. A typical low calorie diet allows you to eat between 800 and 1500 calories per day, while a very low calorie diet keeps you under the 800 calorie mark. If you're on a very low calorie diet you'll see a lot of weight loss to begin with, however a good amount of it is from the loss of fluids. It was found in a study that after a few months the effectiveness of a very low calorie diet wasn't any better than a low calorie diet for losing weight. A VLCD, furthermore, often has unpleasant side effects, including fatigue, dry skin, hair loss and headaches, to name a few. For those wanting to simply lose weight, a low calorie diet would be the more comfortable option, even though a VLCD might be best for somebody with underlying medical conditions.<br /><br />The Cambridge Diet is a very low calorie diet that was developed in England in the 1970s. Due to you receiving foods that are pre-packaged on this diet, your calorie intake will be low in addition to having all of the essential nutrition you need calculated for you. These are in the form of shakes, soups and meal bars. Even though this diet has been in existence for a while, and a lot of people have had success on it, it does carry some disadvantages. You must drink plenty of water to avoid being dehydrated, and you can only do exercise at a very low intensity. Also, eating packaged meals every day can become tiresome for many people. Before going on a diet like the Cambridge Diet you need to consult your doctor to find out whether it's safe for you. Very low calorie diets can carry benefits, especially in those people who are very overweight and as a result of this have medical problems. At the same time, it's not usually a good idea to go on such a diet without medical supervision, as there are some risks involved, such as side effects, malnutrition and dehydration.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwallinside.com%2Fpost-214192.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://wallinside.com/post-214192.html</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fjosephellis923.vieuxblog.com%2FThe-first-blog-b1%2FWays-to-Take-Charge-before-an-Acne-Outbreak-b1-p59.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://josephellis923.vieuxblog.com/The-first-blog-b1/Ways-to-Take-Charge-before-an-Acne-Outbreak-b1-p59.htm</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>