<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="2a628f5b0bffa30d10aac0c4c7d704b7" url=""><![CDATA[HEY HO, LET'S GO!<br/><br/>HEEEY PEOPLES! 
<br />I'm in school now, I can not post any photos in my profile D: It's very annoying that, the computers here are all blocked, shit!
<br />But, I'm new here and I am looking for many foreign friends, cool! 
<br />I liked it here, is quite different.
<br />So, take care. :*
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7669afdb9f3c49a78dddf3b092dc4fea" url=""><![CDATA[WOW! It's perfect!<br/><br/>OMG, Times Square is the most beautiful thing I've ever seen! The southern end of Times Square at night. 
<br /><br />Well I love Flickr, it's a cool place where you put a lot of pictures <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br />And this guy, took several great pictures, here you will like, I liked YAAAY!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1869d463029cc57f964d2fb04d85cc0f" url=""><![CDATA[Nothing Personal.<br/><br/>Well, I'm still here at school, library, and it is already 2:10 pm, and I have not walked away, my dad will kill me! Taking all this, I'm not doing anything tonight, except maybe get on the internet, one thing I'm finding it very difficult, I have to help my sister, tomorrow has 2 health class with the asshole Paulo Grillo, that life more boring, hmm. At least the weekend I go shopping, hang out with some friends and go to the movie <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
<br />For today, nothing else. Take caaare, see ya.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a9ea72ec0b1591df55a7eab7c8e85ddc" url=""><![CDATA[Love, love, love.<br/><br/>I finished posting the photos here, add a kitten to aim, pack my things and sleep! tomorrow has a lot to come! 
<br />BFF's: Diina, Nina, Naná, Letty, Mel, Thay *-* I MISSED YA SWEETHEARTS ):
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4accf8025c40cd81ece72c799ddd88ce" url=""><![CDATA[Good Nightttt <3<br/><br/>Hey Everyone!
<br />Well, today I put in my two new photo albums, view and comment on if they want! I have nothing to say except good night, now it's 03:56am, I'm tired, sleepy, dying. Soooooo, up shortly, taaake care lovers, and see ya! I love u guys &lt;33
<br /><br />xoxo, B!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6ac73be7e3aee1076a87537a0f8d6413" url=""><![CDATA[Rio de Janeiro - Brazil WINS! *-*<br/><br/>World, are welcome to Brazil ;D
<br />It will be an honor to have you here in Rio de Janeiro for the 2016 Olympics, is sure to be the best party of all that you've seen. It will be remembered in the history of the Olympics, of course being the only country in South America to give in one Olympics.
<br />Because we Brazilians yes, we do a party! No wonder that Reveillón and Carnaval of Rio are the best parties in the world! 
<br />Hope you here in 2014 and 2016 - World Cup &amp; Olympics. haha.
<br />See ya guys, take caaaaaaare :*
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="36a34509331d4a4cb8455cbc63bbb58d" url=""><![CDATA[Life's what you make it.<br/><br/>Lets get crazy, get up and dance, take a swing do your thing, If were taking a chance lets get crazy, yeah just kick up your heels, dont miss out, time to shout always keeping it real, lets get crazy! crazy. our songs, our style, our hair, our smile, our laughs, our heart, our grace, our smarts.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="75a20800e124cd3d7c4542fb337309a3" url=""><![CDATA[LOL!<br/><br/>Help! I need somebody, Help! not just anybody, Help! you know I need someone, help. When I was younger, so much younger than today, I never needed anybody's help in any way. But now these days are gone, I'm not so self assured, Now I find I've changed my mind I've opened up the doors (8) Help! - The Beatles. I LOOOOOOOOVE THE SONG, I hear it every day at school! /yeah, I'm stuped. #JohnLennon, ever &lt;3
<br />YEEEEEEEEEEEP, take care, see ya &lt;33' B.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fc1b339a0dc8be767b59acd103e411a" url=""><![CDATA[-.- (?)<br/><br/>HEEEY THERE! When you are a person who does nothing, that's what gives, blog only makes boring, and pointless (<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> WELL, WELL .. I'll change it, yeah! I'm tired of so much study, mimimi, missing 2 months to finish the classes, and I can not stand it. I'll see if I do something good today, I'm a children's party, I do not know what to do next. I'm on twitter, orkut and msn now <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
<br />Take care guys, see ya &lt;3
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fa91be7ea7ae842e35c37e2ec8750431" url=""><![CDATA[I was think about you,<br/><br/>I throw all of your stuff away, then I clear you out of my head I tear you out of my heart, and ignore all of your messages, I tell everyone we are through, cause I'm so much better without you, but it’s just another pretty lie, cause I break down, every time you come around. so how did you get here, under my skin swore that I'd never let you back in should have known better, than trying to let you go cause here we go, go, go again, hard as I try I know I can't quit, something about you, Is so addictive, we're falling together, you'd think that for now I know, cause here we go again. you never know what you want, and you never say what you mean but I start to go insane, every time that you look at me, you only hear half of what I say and you're always showing up too late and I know that I should say goodbye, but it's no use can't be with or without you. I throw all of your stuff away and I cleared you out of my head and I tore you out of my heart so how did you get here under my skin swore that I'd never let you back in should have known better than trying to let you go, cause here we go, go, go again, hard as I try I know I can't quit, something about you Is so addictive, we're falling together, you'd think that for now I know, cause here we go, go. here we go again, here we go again! should have known better, than trying to let you go, cause here we go, go, go again, again, again ?
<br />Wish you were all in my life, but wanted too, you were just a dream and nothing more, I love you.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c17ac87803d76becbfbb07e740b90d9b" url=""><![CDATA[Hey peopless!<br/><br/>I'm back, it's really a long time since I did not come here, and so long that I do not speak with anyone else here! But now I'm back, I'll always be coming here when I can, is that Twitter, Orkut, Msn will not let me go, more fortunately I'm back. So that's it, xx. With love, B.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fd274573577fe4ec932cf54216bb405e" url=""><![CDATA[I'm happy.<br/><br/>Hello everyone! I am writing another blog! Today I am very happy, have few reasons. Some are: today is the anniversary of my cousin, and tomorrow my best friend Nini, this week is coming Christmas, I think this year I will not make these, I'm kinda sad about it, but okay. But I'm also happy because next year I do 18 years, and by other reasons. I do not know if I can get VERY here this week, but I will do my best. I'm leaving, I'll see if I watch a movie that's on tv, then give it back again. I'm sorry for my English very bad, I'm still learning. See ya peopless, xx. With love, B.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>