<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="73154001ac11aad9d1982d21b1ffdc98" url=""><![CDATA[pix<br/><br/>check my new pix out ppl, leme  no wot u fink
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6e39a3500ea495b45e6f6e3771c2f51d" url=""><![CDATA[pickles<br/><br/>Bill worked in a pickle factory. He had been employed there for a number of years when he came home one day to confess to his wife that he had a terrible compulsion. He had an urge to stick his penis into the pickle slicer. His wife suggested that he should see a sex therapist to talk about it, but Bill indicated that he'd be too embarrassed. He vowed to overcome the compulsion on his own. One day a few weeks later, Bill came home absolutely ashamed. His wife could see at once that something was seriously wrong. 
<br /><br />&quot;What's wrong, Bill?&quot; she asked. 
<br /><br />&quot;Do you remember that I told you how I had this tremendous urge to put my penis into the pickle slicer?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Oh, Bill, you didn't.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Yes, I did.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;My God, Bill, what happened?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;I got fired.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;No, Bill. I mean, what happened with the pickle slicer?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Oh... she got fired too.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dab74553443cf301c52e87927aef5401" url=""><![CDATA[ear or finger?<br/><br/>While having drinks a man and a woman got into an argument about who enjoyed sex more. The man said, &quot;Men obviously enjoy sex more than women. Why do you think we're so obsessed with getting laid?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;That doesn't prove anything,&quot; the woman countered. &quot;Think about this: when your ear itches and you put your finger in it and wiggle it around, then pull it out, which feels better-your ear or your finger?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="db8288ac333dfcde2d7666bed17eaa3e" url=""><![CDATA[speech for the deaf...<br/><br/>An Englishman, a Scotsman and an Irishman are all to give speeches to the Deaf Society. All are keen to make an impression on their audience.
<br />The Englishman goes first and to the surprise of his colleagues starts by rubbing first his chest and then his groin. When he finishes the Scotsman and Irishman ask him what he was doing.
<br /><br />'Well' he explained' By rubbing my chest I indicated breasts and thus Ladies and by rubbing my groin I indicated balls and thus Gentlemen. So my speech started Ladies and Gentlemen'.
<br /><br />On his way up to the podium the Scotsman thought to himself I'll go one better than that English fool and started his speech by making an antler symbol with his fingers above his head before also rubbing his chest and his groin. When he finished his colleagues asked what he was doing.
<br /><br />'Well' he explained' By imitating antlers and then rubbing my chest and groin I was starting my speech by saying Dear Ladies and Gentlemen'.
<br /><br />On his way up to the podium the Irishman thought to himself I'll go one further than those mainland fools and started his speech by making an antler symbol above his head, rubbing his chest, and then his groin, and then masturbating furiously. When he finished his colleagues asked him what he was doing.
<br /><br />'Well' he explained,' by imitating antlers, rubbing my chest and then my groin and then masturbating I was starting my speech by saying 'Dear Ladies and Gentlemen, it gives me great pleasure.......'
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d34146a56636ebf05e81b79e0187b0c4" url=""><![CDATA[no chocolate???<br/><br/>A lady walks into an ice cream parlor and order's a scoop of chocolate ice cream. The proprietor quickly responds &quot;I'm sorry mamm, but we are all out of chocolate.&quot; The lady looks confused and gazes down through the glass of the ice cream case and then looks back up at the man and asks for a pint of chocolate. The man replies a little annoyed stating once again that he is out of chocolate ice cream. The lady then seems to get the point and walks down to the end of parlor. She then looks back up and says &quot;excuse me sir?&quot; &quot;Can I get a gallon of chocolate?&quot; At this point the owner becomes upset. &quot;Mamm. Do me a favor please?&quot; &quot;O.k.&quot; The woman replied. &quot;Can you spell the straw in strawberry?&quot; &quot;Sure. S T R A W.&quot; &quot;Good mamm.&quot; The owner said gently. &quot;Can you spell the Van in Vanilla?&quot; &quot;Yes. V A N.&quot; The lady said confidently. &quot;Now can you spell the Fuck in chocolate?&quot; The owner said smartly. The lady looked up at the ceiling in thought then replied, &quot;There is no Fuck in chocolate.&quot; &quot;Well Mamm.&quot; The owner said. &quot;That's what I have been trying to tell you.&quot; &quot;There is NO FUCKIN' CHOCOLATE.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e7a48908b2d3579ebdd3390dee4b561b" url=""><![CDATA[lying to the cops<br/><br/>A police officer pulls a guy over for speeding and has the following exchange:
<br /><br />Officer: May I see your driver's license? 
<br />Driver: I don't have one. I had it suspended when I got my 5th DUI.
<br /><br />Officer: May I see the owner's card for this vehicle? 
<br />Driver: It's not my car. I stole it. 
<br /><br />Officer: The car is stolen? 
<br />Driver: That's right. But come to think of it, I think I saw the owner's card in the glove box when I was putting my gun in there. 
<br /><br />Officer: There's a gun in the glove box? 
<br />Driver: Yes sir. That's where I put it after I shot and killed the woman who owns this car and stuffed her in the trunk. 
<br /><br />Officer: There's a BODY in the TRUNK?!?!? 
<br />Driver: Yes, sir. 
<br /><br />Hearing this, the officer immediately called his captain. The car was quickly surrounded by police, and the captain approached the driver to handle the tense situation: 
<br /><br />Captain: Sir, can I see your license? 
<br />Driver: Sure. Here it is. 
<br /><br />It was valid. 
<br /><br />Captain: Who's car is this? 
<br />Driver: It's mine, officer. Here's the owner's card. 
<br /><br />The driver owned the car. 
<br /><br />Captain: Could you slowly open your glove box so I can see if there's a gun in it? 
<br />Driver: Yes, sir, but there's no gun in it. 
<br /><br />Sure enough, there was nothing in the glove box. 
<br /><br />Captain: Would you mind opening your trunk? I was told you said there's a body in it.
<br /><br />Driver: No problem. 
<br /><br />Trunk is opened; no body. 
<br /><br />Captain: I don't understand it. The officer who stopped you said you told him you didn't have a license, stole the car, had a gun in the glovebox, and that there was a dead body in the trunk. 
<br />Driver: Yeah, I'll bet the lying s.o.b. told you I was speeding, too!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3aef2c704b169855c2335714d9fdf3d" url=""><![CDATA[giving up drugs<br/><br/>Two guys were picked up by the cops for smoking dope and appeared in court before the judge. 
<br /><br />The judge said, &quot;You seem like nice young men, and I`d like to give you a second chance rather than jail time. I want you to go out this weekend and try to show others the evils of drug use and pursued them to give up drugs forever. I`ll see you back in court Monday.&quot; 
<br /><br />Monday, the two guys were in court, and the judge said to the first one,&quot;How did you do over the weekend?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Well, your honor, I persuaded 17 people to give up drugs forever.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;17 people? That`s wonderful. What did you tell them?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;I used a diagram, your honor. I drew two circles like this: O o and told them this (the big circle) is your brain before drugs and this(small circle) is your brain after drugs.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;That`s admirable,&quot; said the judge. &quot;And you, how did you do?&quot; (to the 2nd guy) 
<br /><br />&quot;Well, your honor, I persuaded 156 people to give up drugs forever.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;156 people! That`s amazing! How did you manage to do that!&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Well, I used the same two circles. I pointed to the small circle and told them, `This is your asshole before prison...`&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7b50f709eb0dedc4e0809486394ec00b" url=""><![CDATA[gods plan<br/><br/>A middle-aged woman had a heart attack and was taken to the hospital. While on the operating table she had a near death experience. Seeing God she asked, &quot;Is my time up?&quot; God said, &quot;No you have another 43 years, 2 months and 8 days to live.&quot; 
<br /><br />Upon hearing this, the woman decided to stay in the hospital and have a face lift, liposuction and a tummy tuck. She even had someone change her hair color. Since she had so much more time to live, she figured she might as well make the most of it. 
<br /><br />She was released from the hospital but while crossing the street on her way home, she was killed by a car. 
<br /><br />Arriving in front of God, she demanded, &quot;I thought you said I had another 43 years?! Why didn't you pull me out of the path of that car?&quot; 
<br /><br />God Replied,&quot;I didn't recognize you.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6959d2c539d2ad996b47ae156676f427" url=""><![CDATA[life in hell<br/><br/>One day a guy dies and finds himself in hell as he is wallowing in despair he has his first meeting with the devil. Devil: Why so glum, chum? 
<br /><br />Guy : What do you think? I'm in hell. 
<br /><br />Devil: Hell's not so bad. We actually have a lot of fun down here, you a drinking man? 
<br /><br />Guy: Sure I love to drink. 
<br /><br />Devil: Well you're gone love Mondays than. On Mondays that's all we do is drink. Whiskey, Tequila, Guinness, Wine coolers, Diet tab, and Fresca. We drink till we throw up and then we drink some more. 
<br /><br />Guy: Gee that sounds great. 
<br /><br />Devil: Do you smoke? 
<br /><br />Guy: You better believe it. 
<br /><br />Devil: Alright you're gonna love Tuesdays. We get the finest cigars from all over the world and smoke our lungs out. If you get cancer, no biggie. You're already dead. 
<br /><br />Guy: Wow thats awesome. 
<br /><br />Devil: Do you like to gamble? 
<br /><br />Guy: Why yes, as a matter of fact I do. 
<br /><br />Devil: Wednesday you can gamble all you want. Craps, Black Jack, Roulette, Poker,Slots. If you go bankrupt, well your dead anyhow. 
<br /><br />Devil: You do drugs? 
<br /><br />Guy: Are you kidding. I love drugs. 
<br /><br />Devil: Thursday is drug day. Help your self to a bowl of crack, or Smack. You can do all the drugs you want, and if you over-dose that's all right you're dead who cares? Guy: Yawzall I never realized hell was such a swinging place. 
<br /><br />Devil: You Gay? 
<br /><br />Guy: No. 
<br /><br />Devil: oooh.(grimaces) You're gonna Hate Fridays
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="88d596074e0ef6b510ecf75706ac4456" url=""><![CDATA[drunk bet<br/><br/>There were these two guys in a bar, which was on the 20th floor of a building. The first man said &quot; I bet you $100 I can jump out that window and come straight back in!&quot; The second man says &quot;Ok, sure.&quot; and the barman holds the bet. The first man jumps out the window and disappears for a second before jumping straight back in. Disappointed about losing the $100, the second man says: &quot; I'll bet you another $100 you can't do it again.&quot; So the barman holds the bet. Sure enough, the first man jumps out the window, disappears for a second, then jumps straight back in. Thinking he must have caught a freak gust of wind, the second man says &quot;Ok, I bet you $300 I can jump out the window and come straight back in.&quot; The first man says&quot; Ok, sure.&quot; The second man jumps out the window and falls to the footpath below. He is dead. Back up in the bar, the barman says to the first man &quot; Gee, you can be a bastard when you're pissed, Superman.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="18c93fdc0604dcacf899dd227687b8c1" url=""><![CDATA[do something<br/><br/>A husband is at home watching a football game when his wife interrupts, &quot;Honey, could you fix the light in the hallway? It's been flickering for weeks now.&quot; 
<br /><br />He looks at her and says angrily, &quot;Fix 
<br />the light? Now? Does it look like I have a G.E. logo printed on my forehead? I don't think so.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Well then, could you fix the fridge door? It won't close right.&quot; 
<br /><br />To which he replied, &quot;Fix the fridge door? Does it look like I have Westinghouse written on my forehead? 
<br />I don't think so.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Fine,&quot; she says, &quot;Then could you at least fix the steps to the front door? They're about to break.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;I'm not a damn carpenter and I don't want to fix the steps,&quot; he says. &quot;Does it look like I have Ace Hardware written on my forehead? I don't think so. I've had enough of you. I'm going to the bar!&quot; 
<br /><br />So he goes to the bar and drinks for a couple hours. He starts to feel guilty about how he treated his wife, and decides to go home and help out. As he walks into the house, he notices the steps are already fixed. As he enters the house, he sees the hall light is 
<br />working. As he goes to get a beer, he notices the fridge door is fixed. &quot;Honey, how'd this all get fixed?&quot; 
<br /><br />She said, &quot;Well, when you left, I sat outside and cried. Just then a nice young man asked me what was wrong, and I told him. He offered to do all the repairs, and all I had to do was 
<br />either screw him or bake him a cake.&quot; 
<br /><br />He said, &quot;So, what kind of cake did you bake him?&quot; 
<br /><br />She replied, &quot;Hellooooo... Do you see jamie fucking oliver written on my forehead?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="59600cddff4cada4c71a936d4544265c" url=""><![CDATA[torah scholar<br/><br/>A young woman brings home her fiance to meet her parents. After 
<br />dinner, her mother tells her father to find out about the young 
<br />man. 
<br /><br />The father invites the fiance to his study for a drink. &quot;So what 
<br />are your plans?&quot; the father asks the young man. 
<br /><br />&quot;I am a Torah scholar,&quot; he replies. 
<br /><br />&quot;A Torah scholar. Hmmm,&quot; the father says. &quot;Admirable, but what 
<br />will you do to provide a nice house for my daughter to live in, as she's 
<br />accustomed to?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;I will study,&quot; the young man replies, &quot;and God will provide for us.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;And how will you buy her a beautiful engagement ring, such as she 
<br />deserves?&quot; asks the father. 
<br /><br />&quot;I will concentrate on my studies,&quot; the young man replies, &quot;God 
<br />will provide for us.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;And children?&quot; asks the father. &quot;How will you support children?&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;Don't worry, sir, God will provide,&quot; replies the fiancee. 
<br /><br />The conversation proceeds like this, and each time the father questions, 
<br />the young idealist insists that God will provide. 
<br /><br />Later, the mother asks, &quot;How did it go, Honey?&quot; 
<br /><br />The father answers, &quot;He has no job and no plans, but the good news 
<br />is he thinks I'm God.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="29696b3e4e34dc30d4cb3431f4dde561" url=""><![CDATA[nuclear johnny<br/><br/>A stranger was seated next to Little Johnny on the plane when the stranger turned to the Little Johnny and said, &quot;Let's talk. I've heard that flights will go quicker if you strike up a conversation with your fellow passenger.&quot;
<br /><br />Little Johnny, who had just opened his book, closed it slowly, and said to the stranger, &quot;What would you like to discuss?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Oh, I don't know,&quot; said the stranger. &quot;How about nuclear power?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;OK,&quot; said Little Johnny. &quot;That could be an interesting topic. But let me ask you a question first. &quot;A horse, a cow, and a deer all eat grass. The same stuff. Yet a deer excretes little pellets, while a cow turns out a flat patty, and a horse produces clumps of dried grass. Why do you suppose that is?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Jeez,&quot; said the stranger. &quot;I have no idea.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Well, then,&quot; said Little Johnny, &quot;How is it that you feel qualified to discuss nuclear power when you don't know shit?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7a820aa15383e59f927cce05819ffcb9" url=""><![CDATA[couple of funnies<br/><br/>A well dressed business man was walking down the street when a little kid covered in soot said to him respectfully, &quot;Sir, can you tell me the time?&quot; The portly man stopped, carefully unbuttoned his coat and jacket, removed a large watch from a vest pocket, looked at it and said, &quot;It is a quarter to three, young man.&quot; &quot;Thanks,&quot; said the boy. &quot;At exactly three o'clock you can kiss my ass.&quot; With that, the kid took off running, and with an angry cry, the outraged businessman started chasing him. He had not been running long when an old friend stopped him. &quot;Why are you running like this at your age?&quot; asked the friend. Gasping and almost incoherent with fury, the business man said, &quot;That little brat asked me the time and when I told him it was quarter to three he told me that at exactly three, I should kiss his ass!&quot; &quot;So what's your hurry,&quot; said the friend. &quot;You still have ten minutes.&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />A man hasn't been feeling well, so he goes to his doctor for a complete check-up. Afterward, the doctor comes out with the results. &quot;I'm afraid I have some very bad news,&quot; the doctor says. &quot;You're dying, and you don't have much time left.&quot; &quot;Oh, that's terrible!&quot; says the man. &quot;How long have I got?&quot; &quot;Ten,&quot; the doctor says sadly. &quot;Ten?&quot; the man asks. &quot;Ten what? Months? Weeks? What?!&quot; The doctor interrupts, &quot;Nine...&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />A group of girlfriends are on vacation when they see a 5-story hotel with a sign that reads: &quot;For Women Only&quot;. Since they are without their boyfriends and husbands, they decide to go in. The bouncer, a very attractive guy, explains to them how it works. &quot;We have 5 floors. Go up floor by floor, and once you find what you are looking for, you can stay there. It's easy to decide since each floor has a sign telling you what's inside.&quot; So they start going up and on the first floor the sign reads: &quot;All the men on this floor are short and plain.&quot; The friends laugh and without hesitation move on to the next floor. The sign on the second floor reads: &quot;All the men here are short and handsome.&quot; Still, this isn't good enough, so the friends continue on up. They reach the third floor and the sign reads: &quot;All the men here are tall and plain.&quot; They still want to do better, and so, knowing there are still two floors left, they continued on up. On the fourth floor, the sign is perfect: &quot;All the men here are tall and handsome.&quot; The women get all excited and are going in when they realize that there is still one floor left. Wondering what they are missing, they head on up to the fifth floor. There they find a sign that reads: &quot;There are no men here. This floor was built only to prove that there is no way to please a woman.&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />Little Johnny's kindergarten class was on a field trip to their local police station where they saw pictures, tacked to a bulletin board, of the 10 most wanted criminals. One of the youngsters pointed to a picture and asked if it really was the photo of a wanted person. &quot;Yes,&quot; said the policeman. &quot;The detectives want very badly to capture him.&quot; Little Johnny asked, &quot;Why didn't you keep him when you took his picture?&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />A man in his 40's bought a new BMW and was out on the interstate for a nice evening drive. The top was down, the breeze was blowing through what was left of his hair, and he decided to open her up. As the needle jumped up to 80 mph, he suddenly saw flashing red and blue lights behind him. &quot;There's no way they can catch a BMW,&quot; he thought to himself and opened her up further. The needle hit 90, 100.... then the reality of the situation hit him. &quot;What the heck am I doing?&quot; he thought and pulled over.
<br /><br />The cop came up to him, took his license without a word, and examined it and the car. &quot;It's been a long day, this is the end of my shift, and it's Friday the 13th. I don't feel like more paperwork, so if you can give me an excuse for your driving that I haven't heard before, you can go.&quot; The guy thinks for a second and says, &quot;Last week my wife ran off with a cop. I was afraid you were trying to give her back.&quot; &quot;Have a nice weekend,&quot; said the officer.
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />Two guys and a union worker were fishing on a lake one day, when Jesus walked across the water and joined them in the boat. When the three astonished men had settled down enough to speak, the first guy asked humbly, &quot;Jesus, I've suffered from back pain ever since I took shrapnel in the Vietnam war...could you help me?&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;Of course, my son&quot;, Jesus said, and when he touched the man's back, he felt relief for the first time in years. The second man, who wore very thick glasses and had a hard time reading and driving, asked if Jesus could do anything about his eyesight. Jesus smiled, removed the man's glasses and tossed them in the lake. When they hit the water, the man's eyes cleared and he could see everything distinctly.
<br /><br />When Jesus turned to heal the union worker, the guy put his hands up and cried defensively, &quot;Don't touch me! I'm on long term disability.&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />The new employee stood before the paper shredder looking confused. &quot;Need some help?&quot; a secretary, walking by, asked. &quot;Yes,&quot; he replied, &quot;how does this thing work?&quot; &quot;Simple,&quot; she said, taking the fat report from his hand and feeding it into the shredder. &quot;Thanks, but where do the copies come out?&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />Tom had this problem of getting up late in the morning and was always late for work. His boss was mad at him and threatened to fire him if he didn't do something about it. So Tom went to his doctor who gave him a pill and told him to take it before he went to bed. Tom slept well, and in fact, beat the alarm in the morning. He had a leisurely breakfast and drove cheerfully to work. 
<br /><br />&quot;Boss&quot;, he said, &quot;The pill actually worked!&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;That's all fine&quot; said the boss, &quot;But where were you yesterday?&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a654b14e80e626d9c54e5bdf813d76b" url=""><![CDATA[0-200 in 6 seconds<br/><br/>Bob was in trouble. He forgot his wedding anniversary. His wife was
<br />really pissed.
<br /><br />She told him &quot;Tomorrow morning, I expect to find a gift in the
<br />driveway that goes from 0 to 200 in 6 seconds AND IT BETTER BE THERE !!&quot;
<br /><br />The next morning he got up early and left for work. When his wife woke
<br />up, she looked out the window and sure enough there was a box
<br />gift-wrapped in the middle of the driveway.
<br /><br />Confused, the wife put on her robe and ran out to the driveway, brought
<br />the box back in the house.
<br /><br />She opened it and found a brand new bathroom scale.
<br /><br />Bob has been missing since Friday.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="73538fde85f49f3b0f8ee97803b71dc5" url=""><![CDATA[how did u know?<br/><br/>A woman was shopping at her local supermarket where she selected: 
<br /><br />2 Litres of low fat milk 
<br />6eggs 
<br />2 litres of orange juice 
<br />A lettuce 
<br />half a dozen tomatoes 
<br />a 500g jar of coffee 
<br />a 250g pack of bacon 
<br /><br />As she was unloading her items on the conveyor belt to check out, a drunk was standing behind her watching. While the till operator was ringing up her purchases, the drunk calmly said &quot;You must be single.&quot; 
<br /><br />The woman was a bit startled by this, but she was intrigued by the derelict's intuition, since she was indeed single. She looked at her six items on the belt and saw nothing particularly unusual about them that could have tipped off the drunk to her marital status. Curiosity getting the better of her, she said, &quot;Well, you know what, you're absolutely correct. But how on earth did you know that?&quot; 
<br /><br />The drunk replied, &quot;Cos you're fucking ugly.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1d1bea62e87a06f23549983f97ef3cec" url=""><![CDATA[q's and a's<br/><br/>Q. What is the difference between a drug dealer and a hooker? 
<br />A. A hooker can wash her crack and sell it again. 
<br /><br />Q. What's a mixed feeling? 
<br />A. When you see your mother-in-law backing off a cliff in your new car. 
<br /><br />Q. What's the height of conceit? 
<br />A. Having an orgasm and calling out your own name. 
<br /><br />Q. What's the definition of macho? 
<br />A. Jogging home from your vasectomy. 
<br /><br />Q. What's the difference between a G-Spot and a golf ball? 
<br />A. A guy will actually search for a golf ball 
<br /><br />Q. Do you know how New Zealanders practice safe sex? 
<br />A. They spray paint X's on the back of the sheep that kick! 
<br /><br />Q.Why is divorce so expensive? 
<br />A. Because it's worth it! 
<br /><br />Q. What is a Yankee? 
<br />A. The same as a quickie, but a guy can do it alone. 
<br /><br />Q. What do Tupperware and a walrus have in common? 
<br />A. They both like a tight seal. 
<br /><br />Q. What do a Christmas tree and priest have in common? 
<br />A. Their balls are just for decoration. 
<br /><br />Q.What is the difference between &quot;ooooooh&quot;and &quot;aaaaaaah&quot;? 
<br />A. About three inches. 
<br /><br />Q. Why do Gay men wear ribbed condoms? 
<br />A. For traction in the mud. 
<br /><br />Q: What's the difference between purple and pink? 
<br />A. The grip. 
<br /><br />Q. How do you find a blind man in a nudist colony? 
<br />A. It's not hard. 
<br /><br />Q: How do you circumcise a hillbilly? 
<br />A: Kick his sister in the jaw. 
<br /><br />Q: What's the difference between a girlfriend and a wife? 
<br />A: 45 pounds. 
<br /><br />Q: What's the difference between a boyfriend and a husband? 
<br />A: 45 minutes. 
<br /><br />Q: Why do men find it difficult to make eye contact? 
<br />A: Breasts don't have eyes. 
<br /><br />Q: If the dove is the bird of peace, what is the bird of true love? 
<br />A. The swallow. 
<br /><br />Q: What is the difference between medium and rare? 
<br />A: Six inches is medium, eight inches is rare. 
<br /><br />Q. Why do women rub their eyes when they get up in the morning? 
<br />A . They don't have balls to scratch!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cead11f4596feb06b3137c4c45beef7" url=""><![CDATA[gone fishing<br/><br/>A fellow went off on his honeymoon, and after returning meets up with a friend for a beer and conversation. The friend, being single and a pervert to boot, begins to inquire as to the festivities of the honeymoon. &quot;So, Bob, big married man, did ya get any while you were out there?&quot; the friend asks. Bob just shakes his head. &quot;Ah, you know me. I like to fish. So I just fished.&quot; His friend gasps. &quot;You mean you didn't have no sex? C'mon, Bob, tell me at least got a blowjob!&quot; Bob again shakes his head. &quot;Naw, she had pyorrhea, so I just fished. You know I like to fish.&quot; His friend replies, &quot;Bob, she's your god damn wife! She's gotta give it up when you say! You should just made her do it!&quot; Bob replies, &quot;Nah, she had gonorrhea, and you know me. I like to fish, so I just fished.&quot; His friend, now quite upset, says, &quot;What?! Why didn't ya just pork it up her ass?&quot; &quot;Well,&quot; says Bob, &quot;she had diarrhea...and you know me, I like to fish. So I just fished.&quot; His friend, totally exasperated by this point, shouts at him, &quot;Jesus! Why'd you marry this sick bitch anyway?!&quot; Bob replies, &quot;Well, she got worms, and you know how I like to fish...&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e9c66f0d8da292c40219f81d8fe5fb41" url=""><![CDATA[politics<br/><br/>A little boy goes to his dad and asks, &quot;What is politics?&quot;
<br /><br />Dad says, &quot;Well son, let me try to explain it this way: I'm the breadwinner of the family, so let's call me capitalism. Your Mom, she's the administrator of the money, so we'll call her the Government. We're here to take care of your needs, so we'll call you the people. The nanny, we'll consider her the Working Class. And your baby brother, we'll call him the Future. Now, think about that and see if that makes sense.&quot; So the little boy goes off to bed thinking about what dad had said.
<br /><br />Later that night, he hears his baby brother crying, so he gets up to check on him. He finds that the baby has severely soiled his diaper. So the little boy goes to his parents' room and finds his mother sound asleep. Not wanting to wake her, he goes to the nanny's room. Finding the door locked, he peeks in the keyhole and sees his father in bed with the nanny. He gives up and goes back to bed. The next morning, the little boy says to his father, &quot;Dad, I think I understand the concept of politics now.&quot; The father says, &quot;Good son, tell me in your own words what you think politics is all about.&quot;
<br /><br />The little boy replies, &quot;Well, while Capitalism is screwing the Working Class, the Government is sound asleep, the People are being ignored and the Future is in deep shit.&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="593815a612c4df2a659c18a3236329ab" url=""><![CDATA[best death<br/><br/>Three men were standing in line to get into heaven one day. Apparently it had been a pretty busy day, though, so Peter had to tell the first one, &quot;Heaven's getting pretty close to full today, and I've been asked to admit only people who have had particularly horrible deaths. So what's your story?&quot; 
<br /><br />So the first man replies: &quot;Well, for a while I've suspected my wife has been cheating on me, so today I came home early to try to catch her red-handed. As I came into my 25th floor apartment, I could tell something was wrong, but all my searching around didn't reveal where this other guy could have been hiding. Finally, I went out to the balcony, and sure enough, there was this man hanging off the railing, 25 floors above ground! By now I was really mad, so I started beating on him and kicking him, but wouldn't you know it, he wouldn't fall off. So finally I went back into my apartment and got a hammer and starting hammering on his fingers. Of course, he couldn't stand that for long, so he let go and fell -- but even after 25 stories, he fell into the bushes, stunned but okay. I couldn't stand it anymore, so I ran into the kitchen, grabbed the fridge and threw it over the edge where it landed on him, killing him instantly. But all the stress and anger got to me, and I had a heart attack and died there on the balcony.&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;That sounds like a pretty bad day to me,&quot; said Peter, and let the man in. 
<br /><br />The second man comes up and Peter explains to him about heaven being full, and again asks for his story. 
<br /><br />&quot;It's been a very strange day. You see, I live on the 26th floor of my apartment building, and every morning I do my exercises out on my balcony. Well, this morning I must have slipped or something, because I fell over the edge. But I got lucky, and caught the railing of the balcony on the floor below me. I knew I couldn't hang on for very long, when suddenly this man burst out onto the balcony. I thought for sure I was saved, when he started beating on me and kicking me. I held on the best I could until he ran into the apartment and grabbed a hammer and started pounding on my hands. Finally I just let go, but again I got lucky and fell into the bushes below, stunned but all right. Just when I was thinking I was going to be okay, this refrigerator comes falling out of the sky and crushes me instantly, and now I'm here.&quot; 
<br /><br />Once again, Peter had to concede that that sounded like a pretty horrible death. 
<br /><br />The third man came to the front of the line, and again Peter explained that heaven was full and asked for his story. 
<br /><br />&quot;Picture this,&quot; says the third man, &quot;I'm hiding inside a refrigerator...&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5b9fd2b51fe7eaf5d6b6332c9d84d60d" url=""><![CDATA[building site blunder<br/><br/>An Italian, an Irishman and a Chinese fellow are hired at a construction site. The foreman points out a huge pile of sand and says to the Italian guy, ‘You're in charge of sweeping.’ He then turns to the Irishman. ‘You're in charge of digging.’ Finally, he turns to the Chinaman. ‘And you're in charge of supplies. Now, I have to leave for a little while. I expect you guys to make a dent in that pile.’ Two hours later, the foreman returns to find the pile of sand untouched, and the Italian and Irishman standing nearby looking sheepish. ‘Why didn't you sweep any off it?’ he asks the pair. The Italian looks at him. ‘We didn’t have a broom or shovel. You said the Chinese guy was in charge of supplies, but he disappeared and I couldn't find him.’ Annoyed, the foreman storms off to find the errant Oriental. Just then, the Chinaman leaps out from behind the pile of sand. ‘Supplies!’ he yells.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3f960b50537477485cfaafce0b0474e4" url=""><![CDATA[you make me laff<br/><br/>A cowboy rode into town and stopped at a saloon for a drink. Unfortunately, the locals always had a habit of picking on strangers, which he was. When he finished his drink, he found his horse had been stolen. He went back into the bar, handily flipped his gun into the air, caught it above his head without even looking and fired a shot into the ceiling. 
<br /><br />&quot;Which one of you sidewinders stole my horse?!?!?&quot; he yelled with surprising forcefulness. No one answered. &quot;Alright, I'm gonna have another beer, and if my horse ain't back outside by the time I finish, I'm gonna do what I dun in Texas! And I don't like to have to do what I dun in Texas!&quot; Some of the locals shifted restlessly. The man, true to his word, had another beer, walked outside, and his horse has been returned to the post. 
<br /><br />He saddled up and started to ride out of town. The bartender wandered out of the bar and asked, &quot;Say partner, before you go... what happened in Texas?&quot; The cowboy turned back and said, &quot;I had to walk home.&quot; 
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />A guy sticks his head in the barber shop and asks, &quot;How long before I can get a haircut?&quot; The barber looks around the shop and says, &quot;About two hours.&quot; The guy leaves. A few days later, the same guy sticks his head in the door and asks, &quot;How long before I get a haircut?&quot; The barber looks around the shop full of customers and says, &quot;About two hours.&quot; The guy leaves. A week later, the same guy sticks his head in the shop and asks, &quot;How long before I can get a haircut?&quot; The barber looks around the shop an says, &quot;About an hour and half.&quot; The guy leaves. The barber looks over at a friend in the shop and says, &quot;Hey Bill, follow that guy and see where he goes.&quot; In a little while, Bill comes back into the shop laughing hysterically. The barber asks, &quot;Bill, where did he go when he left here?&quot; Bill looked up and said, &quot;To your house.&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />A man walked into the office of the eminent psychiatrist Dr. Von Bernuth, and sat down to explain his problem. &quot;Doctor, doctor!&quot; he started. &quot;No need to repeat yourself, my good man,&quot; replied the doctor. &quot;One 'doctor' is enough.&quot; &quot;Yes, well, you see, I've got this problem,&quot; the man continued. &quot;I keep hallucinating that I'm a dog. A large, white, hairy Pyrenees mountain dog. It's crazy. I don't know what to do!&quot; 
<br /><br />&quot;A common canine complex,&quot; said the doctor soothingly. &quot;Come over here and lie down on the couch.&quot; &quot;Oh no, Doctor. I'm not allowed up on the furniture.&quot; 
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />Once there was a millionaire, who collected live alligators. He kept them in the pool in back of his mansion. The millionaire also had a beautiful daughter who was single.
<br /><br />One day, the millionaire decides to throw a huge party, and during the party he announces, &quot;My dear guests, I have a proposition to every man here. I will give one million dollars, or my daughter, to the man who can swim across this pool full of alligators and emerge unharmed!&quot; As soon as he finished his last word, there was the sound of a large splash in the pool. The guy in the pool was swimming with all his might, and the crowd began to cheer him on. Finally, he made it to the other side of the pool unharmed.
<br /><br />The millionaire was impressed. He said, &quot;That was incredible! Fantastic! I didn't think it could be done! Well, I must keep my end of the bargain. Do you want my daughter or the one million dollars?&quot; The guy catches his breath, then says, &quot;Listen, I don't want your money! And I don't want your daughter! I want the asshole who pushed me in the pool!&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />The teacher of the Earth Science class was lecturing on map reading. He spent the class explaining about latitude, longitude, degrees, and minutes. Towards the end of class, the teacher asked his students, &quot;Suppose I asked you to meet me for lunch at 23 degrees, 4 minutes north latitude and 45 degrees, 15 minutes east longitude...&quot; A student's voice broke the confused silence, and volunteered, &quot;I guess you'd be eating alone, sir.&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />Two women that are dog owners are arguing about which dog is smarter.... First Woman : &quot;My dos is so smart, every morning he waits for the paper boy to come around and then he takes the newspaper and brings it to me. Second Woman : &quot;I know...&quot; First Woman : &quot;How?&quot; Second Woman : &quot;My dog told me.&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />A woman in Brooklyn decided to prepare her Will and make her final requests. She told her rabbi she had two final requests. First, she wanted to be cremated, and second, she wanted her ashes scattered all over Bloomingdales. &quot;Why Bloomingdales?&quot; asked the rabbi. &quot;Then I'll be sure my daughters visit me twice a week.&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />There was a boy who worked in the produce section of a super market. A man came in and asked to buy half a head of lettuce. The boy told him that they only sold whole heads of lettuce, but the man replied that he did not need a whole head, only half. The boy explained that he would have to ask the manager and so he walked into the back room and said, &quot;There is some jerk out there who wants to buy only a half a head of lettuce.&quot; As he finished saying this, he turned around to find the man standing right behind him, so he quickly added, &quot;And this gentleman wants to buy the other half.&quot; The manager okayed the request and the man went on his way. Later on the manager said to the boy, &quot;You almost got yourself in a lot of trouble earlier, but I must say I was impressed with the way you got out of it. You think on your feet and we like that around here. Where are you from, son?&quot; The boy replied, &quot;Minnesota, sir.&quot; &quot;Oh, really? Why did you leave Minnesota?&quot; inquired the manager. The boy replied, &quot;They're all just whores and hockey players up there.&quot; &quot;My wife is from Minnesota&quot;, exclaimed the manager. The boy instantly replied, &quot;Really! What team did she play for?&quot;
<br /><br />--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
<br /><br />A man went to a pet shop and bought a talking parrot. He took the parrot home, and tried to teach the parrot how to say a few things, but instead the parrot just swore at him. After a few hours of trying to teach the bird finally the man said &quot;If you don't stop swearing I'm going to put you in the freezer as punishment.&quot; The parrot continued, so finally the man put the bird in the freezer. About an hour later the parrot asked the man to please open the door. As the man took the shivering bird out of the freezer it said &quot;I promise to never swear again. Just tell me what that turkey did!&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6a16fc5e3c49b0420b8945b78df622d3" url=""><![CDATA[qualify 4 heaven<br/><br/>Recently a teacher, a garbage collector, and a lawyer wound up together at the Pearly Gates. St. Peter informed them that in order to get into Heaven, they would each have to answer one question. 
<br /><br />St. Peter addressed the teacher and asked, &quot;What was the name of the ship that crashed into the iceberg? They just made a movie about it.&quot; 
<br /><br />The teacher answered quickly, &quot;That would be the Titanic.&quot; St. Peter let him through the gate. 
<br /><br />St. Peter turned to the garbage man and, figuring Heaven didn't *really* need all the odors that this guy would bring with him, decided to make the question a little harder: &quot;How many people died on the ship?&quot; 
<br /><br />Fortunately for him, the trash man had just seen the movie. &quot;1,228,&quot; he answered. 
<br /><br />&quot;That's right! You may enter.&quot; 
<br /><br />St. Peter turned to the lawyer. &quot;Name them.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4c585de3aa0154185c9912cb18bb14c9" url=""><![CDATA[can you spare just £2???<br/><br/>Zani is a 9 year old boy living in namibia. he only has 1 arm and 1 leg, each day he goes along a path full of craters from land mines, on a bike with a broken frame, 1 pedal and no brakes. if you can find it in your heart to spare £2, yes just £2....... we will send you the video, its fucking hillarious!!!!!!
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>