<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="14">
		<document id="b89f701044c0091243c06104dc24332e" url=""><![CDATA[How nice to feel you are not alone...<br/><br/>How nice is to feel u r not lonely everynight
<br />U have a date..everynight..
<br />no more darkness u live ur night
<br />just a real light u catch by your heart
<br />u feel so wonderful inside..
<br />so in love..so nice..
<br />Everynight I be with you...
<br />It is everynight i forget the darkness of my day ...
<br />so nice to lay by your light bb
<br />so nice to have ur touch warmth...
<br />so nice the dream that i share with u
<br />and i tell u ..
<br />again and again..
<br />how much ur love is inside me
<br /><strong></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3b4bd70e4ebc72850fd451ae2c6dd040" url=""><![CDATA[I need you<br/><br/>Tonight's the night,for me and you,
<br />The night to prove we were meant to be.
<br />You mean the world to me,and so much more,
<br />I would give my life for you,the one I adore.
<br />You're the one I think of,when I'm happy or sad,
<br />You're the one i think of,and am very glad to have.
<br />Your touch is so gentle,your smile is so sweet,
<br />Everytime I'm with you,my heart skips a beat.
<br />Together, Forever,
<br />I know it's meant to be,for you to only be with me.
<br />When we hold hands,my heart fills with joy,
<br />Just to hear you tell me,I'll always be your boy.
<br />When we hold eachother close,
<br />the world seems to move fast,
<br />And it seems like forever,though much time has past.
<br />When we hug eachother,and i look into your eyes,
<br />Your sweet adorable smile,catches me by surprise.
<br />Your kisses are so sweet,when our lips begin to meet.
<br />To hear you say, I Love You,means so much to me,
<br />And I hope and pray that you,will always be with me. <strong></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f01e1ce08c442bc57e68f7d1b02894ae" url=""><![CDATA[I miss you...<br/><br/>I miss you more, than you could ever know 
<br />I can only hope, you miss me too 
<br />Hope that you haven't moved on 
<br />And that you still think about me 
<br />That I'm the only one for you 
<br />I miss you so much, that I weep 
<br />I miss you so much, that I ache 
<br />My heart aches so much, that it could break 
<br />But it's not your fault, it's mine 
<br />I'm sorry and i hope you know, 
<br />I miss you more, than you could ever know.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a5ae80224b03ccbebb576aca21d5c200" url=""><![CDATA[Sad ...<br/><br/>Outside I look fine 
<br />But on the inside I'm not 
<br />Lonely, sad and confused 
<br />Falling and not caught. 
<br /><br />Without you I am lost 
<br />I don't know where to turn 
<br />With you is ever thing I am 
<br />Without you my emotions have burned. 
<br /><br />I want to hold you 
<br />I want to kiss you 
<br />I want to hug you 
<br />I want to be near you 
<br /><br />I would love to see you 
<br />But we are so far apart 
<br />And that's what gets to me 
<br />It's what tears me apart  <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" /> <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b11da87c4dd1007ff3cd5d5dd13d3e1b" url=""><![CDATA[“13 PHRASES FOR LIVING”<br/><br/>1.I love you not for whom you are, but who I am when I’m by your side. 
<br /><br />2.No person deserves your tears, and who deserves them won’t make you cry. 
<br /><br />3.Just because someone doesn’t love you as you wish, it doesn’t mean you’re not loved with all his/her being. 
<br /><br />4.A true friend is the one who holds your hand and touches your heart. 
<br /><br />5.The worst way to miss someone is to be seated by his/her side and know you’ll never have him/her. 
<br /><br />6.Never stop smiling, not even when you’re sad, someone might fall in love with your smile. 
<br /><br />7.You may only be a person in this world, but for someone, you’re the world. 
<br /><br />8.Don’t spend time with someone who doesn’t care spending it with you.. 
<br /><br />9.Maybe God wants you to meet many wrong people before you meet the right one, so when this happens, you’ll be thankful. 
<br /><br />10.Don’t cry because it came to an end. Smile because it happened. 
<br /><br />11.There will always be people who’ll hurt you, so you need to continue trusting, just be careful. 
<br /><br />12.Become a better person and be sure to know who you are before meeting someone new and hoping that person knows who you are. 
<br /><br />13.Don’t struggle so much, best things happen when not expected.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ddba7438286fc01fbf3b6d0b68941ee3" url=""><![CDATA[Shadows of Destiny ...<br/><br/>My tears are shivering souless
<br />My voice is lost of so much coldness
<br />My passion whispers something just for you
<br />A word that you don't even know 
<br />You don't remeber my name 
<br />And I remain embraced by the darkness
<br />In a world where the wind breathes endless 
<br />Telling me the mystery of the survial 
<br />I step on the shadows of that memories
<br />I wake up in the cruelty of the morning
<br />And the rain drops little sparkles in my hair 
<br />I feel a pain and the wishes make me remember...
<br /><br />I wished I could hear just one last time that sweet words that give me thrills 
<br />I wished I would never loose the burning trace of your sight
<br />I wished I would never loose the smell of our desire 
<br />I wished I would never loose the soft touch of your kiss
<br />I just wished I could tell you that my entire world were you ...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a7207c1af6865e17b4c595d6a652f78b" url=""><![CDATA[Just remember<br/><br/>Throw me just a last smile ... Let my sight lose itself in the blue sheens ... Drown yourself in dead dreams ... Give me back the green of the stars ... Sleep in your own deep pain ... Throw me in the abyss of the colors ... Look at the white of the snowflakes ... Burn me in the pain of your eyes and maybe this way you will make the distance between you and me disappear... 
<br />Remember who I am ... remember the death of the dreams, 
<br />let me believe you didn't forget ... remember the flight of the music in our world, let me believe I still have wings ... remember the sweet symphony of the sea, let me believe that my illusions drowned in its deepness ... remember the road of our sights, let me believe that the memory of your look still hurts ... remember the dance of love between you and me, let me believe you didn't lose the rhytm ... remember my smile, let me believe that the sadness doesn't kill ... remember our dates, let me believe you still understand the time's ireversibility ... remember my tears, let me believe you still watch the sky ... remember I loved you, let me believe your soul is missing me ... remember how much I suffered, let me believe you could remember any of these things someday ...
<br /><br /><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/40756812_2942209_12212577.jpg" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b1125248786b0a9a6732e6fce5b04ff8" url=""><![CDATA[One of my fears...<br/><br/><strong></strong>First of all I am human and I have many fears ... and one of them is saying &quot;I love you&quot; ...
<br /><br />I know it's strange ... nowadays you hear these words everywhere...sometimes even when it's not the case ... and when I look around me and I see how easily seems to the others saying these words I start having some doubts about me ...
<br /><br />At first I thought I can't spell them perhaps because I'm not able to love anyone ... but then I thought better and I realised that actually I am afraid of spelling them because I am afraid of getting hurt. I have always been afraid of that because people often let me down and this is why I chose not to trust them and to wear a cold mask which make me not seem vulnerable... 
<br /><br />It's so sad doing that but I have no choice ... I would like be myself anywhere anytime ... I would like to be able to say to the people from my life that I love them before it's too late but I don't want to finish the story here because I don't want this end for it ...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="900eec3f9ea21ae8c2c0293f3c5e1b87" url=""><![CDATA[Simple words<br/><br/><strong></strong>So many words told with no sense, so many meaningful words ... so much indifference ... so much carelessness...
<br /><br />Seconds ... minutes ... hours ... days ... weeks ... months ... years ... all of them pass nearby and all of them put their careless print on me. I have wishes ... I can't just stop. Time should see that I exist that I'm not just invisible. I want to melt myself like the sunrays, I want to spoil myself like the breath of the wind, I want to drain myself like the rain's avasts, I want to fly like the travelling birds ... and I want just one more thing ... the most important ... always to feel your warm look ... 
<br /><br />So many misunderstood feelings, so many broken thoughts, so many heart-rending words... 
<br /><br />just a lost thought <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="48a6e17a07c9fe5efcb9d042d555dc60" url=""><![CDATA[Selfish love<br/><br/>I don't know what you are doing ... I don't know where you are ... I don't know if you ever think of me ... I don't know if you suffer in the same way I do ... I don't know if you feel that encumbrance inside as I do .... I don't know if you remember my smile because ... I search inside of my mind and I can't find yours ... unreasonable ... because usually it is always there ... 
<br />Time stops when you're not with me ... your steps lose in your trace...
<br />You tell me what you feel but I can't be sure of anything ... our love is like a labyrinth and I lost myself but at least I know what I truly feel ... 
<br />Sometimes it seems that we are just two parts of a whole that complete and destroy each other ... forever we will search and eternal we will chase each other like the Sun and the Moon ... doomed to loneliness for eternity ... you angel, I temptation ... you a mountain of security, I an unbridled sea of incertitude ... 
<br />You don't see me ... you don't feel me ... you don't hear me ... just indifference ... the burning traces of my tears are deeper and deeper ... the shadow of my soul becomes intenser and intenser ... 
<br />I am a thought ... I am a sunray ... I am cloud ... I am a flower ... I am a butterfly ... I am everything you love and everything you hate .... I AM NOTHING! But do you know something? ... From this nothing you could have done everything you wanted ... 
<br />Oh and ... something more ... do you remember that smile that disappeared from my mind? .... well ... I have just found it ... it was in my soul ... 
<br /><img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/40756812_13368941_12212476.jpg" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="940765e35d8a7695e45228d4428cdf2a" url=""><![CDATA[Bet With Life !<br/><br/>It's raining ... I can feel drop by drop ... 
<br />Among the heaps of my memories and the black-white words, just one thought is rising in my entire body: I miss ... 
<br />It seems that years and years passed since the sun's light didn't fill through my small window... It's so hot! And my tears flow along my cheeks ... yes ... life is unfair ... I even lost my memories. I thought nothing could harm me anymore, I thought I was not able to love anymore ... to feel something and suddenly the coldness penetrates me so deeply that touches the marrow of my bones. I'm gathering myself in a corner and I'd like to hide somewhere but I don't have how to run ... I am still chained ... I even lost the last piece of my hope...
<br />I step on the cold floor as a ghost, everything is black and white and I just can't breathe anymore, I can't feel the air ... I feel I stifle myself and suddenly I tread on a small shining marble. I lift it up and I look at her with my eyes fixed on it ... shall I dare? ... I watch my reflexion in the window and my eyes are glittering ... I can feel the air heavier and heavier ... yes I can do it ... I must do it ... and in a second my cage is breaking and the sunrays penetrate timidly my room. I am falling on my knees and I can finally breathe the fresh air. I gather my heart that has broken and my hands are filling with blood ... I stroke a memory ... 
<br />Freedom ... I locked everything that means past so deeply in my heart ... 
<br />Now everything has sense ... I used tu run away from this world ... I closed myself in my own solitude ... I thought I could forget ... I gathered inside me a huge dissappointement and a great hate and finally my heart ... turned into pieces ... but do you want to know something? ... I continued loving you with each part of my soul, body and mind. Now I'm hiding my memories in a box and I'm buring it. I felt my past didn't want to let me go so ... I let it go ... 
<br />I'm rewarding the hate with love ... the betrayal with friendship ... the dissappointment with hope ... the sadness with hapiness ... the tears with a smile ... the pain with a caress ... 
<br /><br />I MADE A  BET WITH LIFE AND I WON !
<br /><strong></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="df732f051bf8edb9ca282ea4374acbef" url=""><![CDATA[Irrational Foolish<br/><br/>Everything you tell me now ... there are just words with no meaning. I didn't forget, and I will never be able to forget what happened between us ... nonsense... you act and think in a perverse way just for youself. You insist to keep me just for you but I don't feel you just for me. In my mind arises an horizon of indifference or at least ... this is what I tend to believe. I build a defensive shield between you and me ... otherwise I just don't have the power to understand you anymore. 
<br />What is happening to me? It hurts me physical but it starts from inside. I am just an emotional child, affected by what happens around me ... I blame you for all the suffering you caused me ... for everything I suffered and I still suffer. Perhaps I tend to ask worthless things, now I am just confused blocked in a world that seems to have no sense. 
<br />Now my tears are too rose ... colour that flows from the depth of my drab soul ... 
<br />Once you painted me in the shades of love ... we were dreaming mounted on the rainbow of the immortality ... of the eternal love ... 
<br />Now I walk through the night with the flash stired up, searching the heart you broke ... Now there are just words lost by the wind .... burnt by the sun ... drowned by the rain and everything I spell seems to be now so irrational ... 
<br />It's so strange the way I keep you in my mind even when I don't try to think, when my mind is invaded by nothing. I don't even know what I am writting ... I waste the ink ... I swot the brush of my suffering, sharing to this piece of paper nothing more than mortal remains ... than fragments of my desires ... Nothing has any sense and I smile ... but that is just apparently because inside of me that is my way of cursing you ... of cursing you tacitly to happines ... 
<br />You hurt me but I wish only the best for you ... I want to cry, but you to laugh .... I want to be quiet, but you to sing ... I want to die, but you to fly! 
<br />I ADORE YOU! Overwhelming happiness ... that's all I want for you ... why? ... because I still love you irrational foolish !!!
<br /><strong></strong>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bcd81c88eca31f23b03bcc65f12ba03c" url=""><![CDATA[My Disappointment<br/><br/>I'm an innocent girl, born by accident or not ... I am not who I seem to be, I never smile with the soul, but rarely, very rarely, when you spoiled me like a drop of rain. I am nothing of what I wanted to be, but I have many roles and films that I will be playing ... what a great director life is. Everything I loved ... I loved it by my own ... I loved from the bottom of my heart. 
<br />I step quietly, I do not want to wake up any other feeling ... I turn off the last light which was burning ...it's dark ... hopes, dreams, love, wishes ... all ... but all are transformed into disappointment. I step quietly ... I am in my universe ... here I am and here I am going to remain ... just me ... now I am no longer full of dreams, I try to turn them off as I already extinguished the light ... 
<br />Having new dreams? Just when someone will prove me that he really deserves. 
<br />Fallen somewhere ... I stay down, because I do not want to get up, I am alone down there ... but I was alone also up there where everyone used to look at me. You ... stay away from me... I close myself in my own disappointment, I remain down there ... and if you meet me... I will smile ... I promise I'll use that mask called happiness!
<br />I have no more dreams, and the ones I dreamed last night I will forget, and I will try not to load my nights waiting for a sign ... an answer to 2 or 3 thoughts, that's it ... I just don't wish anything anymore ... because you can't offer me anything but ... disappointment. I will still use that music that relaxes me, I will fall alseep on it ... I will spend the nights with the songs I like ... but nothing more I want. 
<br />Disappointed, I withdraw myself in solitude remaining down there ... 
<br />And I still remained the same innocent girl I always used to be.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cce76125907e8009c50e1595f0c7385" url=""><![CDATA[The7th day...<br/><br/>Today he is still disappear,the 6th month.
<br />Maybe he is begining to face the reality,maybe he is married,or maybe he is going to be a father soon,whatever.
<br />But I am still waitting.
<br />Even I don't know what am I waitting for.
<br />I don't want to tell him, I don't want him to know
<br />That my love for him can't seem to let go
<br />I want to be with him, but I know that I can't any more
<br />I don't want him to know, how I long for his kiss
<br />How I long to feel his touch, to have him hold me close
<br />I still feel that love when I look in his eyes
<br />It still takes my breath away when I see him smile
<br />I lie awake at night in my bed thinking
<br />What happened, our love was so strong
<br />I don't understand it, what the hell went wrong
<br />I was so happy, now I sit here alone
<br />I just can't do it, I don't have the strength
<br />It hurts to lose him, it hurts that never see his face
<br />My heart breaks everytime I read those mails
<br />Everything reminds me of him, I can't get away
<br />I just want all of this hurting and pain to leave
<br />My heart is beating faster, all the blood is rushing to my head
<br />It's getting harder to breathe
<br />I wish I didn't love him, I wish I didn't care
<br />Should I let him go, or should I try again?
<br />Doesn't really matter, either way I get hurt in the end
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>