<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="13">
		<document id="b2e20549d80a6fc7e5a27e6fbd6d7405" url=""><![CDATA[Website Styles For Low-cost - How to Get it Accomplished Wit<br/><br/>People started buying, selling, and trading links like it was their job. And for some, it was. Today, the link industry is worth more than one billion dollars. Even after the purity of the Google founders’ system was disturbed, it was tremendously innovative for its time. In fact, that same link-based system, called PageRank, is still the foundation of the most popular search engine in the world. But nowadays, dozens of restrictions apply to which links can count as legitimate votes. PageRank works in very much the same way as popularity in grade school.<br /><br />Generally speaking, the more friends you have (and the cooler they are), the better. So if you have six friends who are sort of cool, you’re pretty comfortable. If you have only three friends, but they happen to be the coolest kids in the school, you’re even higher in the pecking order. But of course, the most enviable situation of all is to be the most well-liked kid in the whole school. It is exponentially more difficult to achieve higher PageRanks in each successive bracket, and most websites never get past a 4 or 5. PageRanks of 6 are hard to come by, and 7s are downright rare. 8s and higher are reserved for the Apple.coms and Microsoft.coms of the world, and there are fewer than a dozen PageRank 10 websites on the entire Internet, including Facebook, the World Wide Web Consortium, and Google itself. You can see a site’s PageRank by downloading the Google toolbar and enabling the PageRank bar.<br /><br />As in the grade school analogy, PageRank is based on how many other sites like you—that is, link to you. More important, if the sites that link to you are very popular— that is, well-linked—themselves, you get an even higher PageRank. So even if only one website links to your page, if it’s a super-high PageRank site like, say, Huffingtonpost.com, your page will get a much higher PageRank than one that has 20 links but all from lesser-known sites. And of course, the best situation of all is to be that universally liked kid in school and have many websites of varying<br />PageRanks linking to you. That gives you the highest aggregate PageRank of all. A shining example of a site that everyone seems to like is Wikipedia, which is why it has a PageRank of 9.<br />The analogy goes even further when you consider the special rules that Google has imposed on PageRank. You know how it stinks to be the new kid in school—how it takes a few months to make friends and establish a reputation?<br />Well, it’s exactly the same with new websites. Even though Google assigns a PageRank to a new site pretty quickly, they won’t allow it to enjoy the value of that PageRank—that is, rank well in the search results—until the site has been around for a couple of months.<br />A second important rule of PageRank is this: You are who you hang out with. If you have an inner page on your website that gains a higher PageRank than your home page, you should place an ad for your product or service on that page because it is more likely to rank highly in the search results.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Flatest-premium-wordpress-template-on-the-web%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/latest-premium-wordpress-template-on-the-web/</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Fpopular-cheap-plugins-for-wordpress%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/popular-cheap-plugins-for-wordpress/</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6b8cd4cbfdaf20bc4331dfa8cb2e5f96" url=""><![CDATA[ChillDownload.com - All you want to find<br/><br/>But the big G likes to have all sorts of data available so that it can return relevant web pages for highly specific searches such as why does my dog like watching baseball? After all, most searches are specific. General searches such as dog make up a relatively tiny slice of the search pie.<br />As a website owner or marketer, you don’t need to worry about the more arcane data points that Google analyzes. Your focus should be on the three most important factors for ranking on Google:<br />Links <br />Page title <br />URL<br />Understanding how to optimize these factors allows you to rank for popular search terms, which causes you to get the most visitors to your website in the shortest time. But before I show you how to do that, you need to understand how Google looks at the Web.<br />When Larry Page and Sergey Brin set out to organize all the Web’s information as eager, bushy-tailed grad students at Stanford, they made one concept the foundation of their entire algorithm: links. Links, they hypothesized, were the currency of a new, democratic World Wide Web, just as votes are the currency of an election.<br />After all, a voter only casts his ballot for the candidate he believes in, and similarly, a website owner only links to another website if he finds it genuinely valuable… right?<br />Nope. Not in a free-market economy. The moment people figured out that Google ranked websites based on links, a new cottage industry was born. People started buying, selling, and trading links like it was their job. And for some, it was. Today, the link industry is worth more than one billion dollars. Even after the purity of the Google founders’ system was disturbed, it was tremendously innovative for its time. In fact, that same link-based system, called PageRank, is still the foundation of the most popular search engine in the world. But nowadays, dozens of restrictions apply to which links can count as legitimate votes. PageRank works in very much the same way as popularity in grade school.<br /><br />Generally speaking, the more friends you have (and the cooler they are), the better. So if you have six friends who are sort of cool, you’re pretty comfortable. If you have only three friends, but they happen to be the coolest kids in the school, you’re even higher in the pecking order. But of course, the most enviable situation of all is to be the most well-liked kid in the whole school. Then you have more aggregate coolness than anyone.<br />Now let’s turn to the way Google looks at PageRank. Technically, PageRank is a predictor of how relevant a web page will be for any given search. It is similar to popularity, which could be said to be a predictor of how much a person will be liked by any other given person. Every web page on the Internet is assigned a PageRank, which is a number from 0 to 10. The higher the PageRank, the more relevant Google considers the page to be, and the better its chance of showing up at the top of the search results. It is exponentially more difficult to achieve higher PageRanks in each successive bracket, and most websites never get past a 4 or 5. You can see a site’s PageRank by downloading the Google toolbar and enabling the PageRank bar.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F21134319%2Fchilldownloadcom-all-you-want-to-find"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/21134319/chilldownloadcom-all-you-want-to-find</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenmacias724.mywapblog.com%2Fwhy-website-templates-are-well-worth-it.xhtml"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenmacias724.mywapblog.com/why-website-templates-are-well-worth-it.xhtml</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogster.com%2Fstevenmacias724%2Fwebsite-models-for-cheap-how-to-get-it-accomplished-with-no-having-to-pay-a-ton"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.blogster.com/stevenmacias724/website-models-for-cheap-how-to-get-it-accomplished-with-no-having-to-pay-a-ton</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bb427bbc9229790cfc7d4d5471746acb" url=""><![CDATA[ChillDownload.com - All you want to find<br/><br/>As you will soon see, only a few factors ultimately determine the order of search results. But the big G likes to have all sorts of data available so that it can return relevant web pages for highly specific searches such as why does my dog like watching baseball? After all, most searches are specific. General searches such as dog make up a relatively tiny slice of the search pie.<br />As a website owner or marketer, you don’t need to worry about the more arcane data points that Google analyzes. Your focus should be on the three most important factors for ranking on Google:<br />Links <br />Page title <br />URL<br />Understanding how to optimize these factors allows you to rank for popular search terms, which causes you to get the most visitors to your website in the shortest time. But before I show you how to do that, you need to understand how Google looks at the Web.<br />When Larry Page and Sergey Brin set out to organize all the Web’s information as eager, bushy-tailed grad students at Stanford, they made one concept the foundation of their entire algorithm: links. Links, they hypothesized, were the currency of a new, democratic World Wide Web, just as votes are the currency of an election.<br />After all, a voter only casts his ballot for the candidate he believes in, and similarly, a website owner only links to another website if he finds it genuinely valuable… right?<br />Nope. Not in a free-market economy. The moment people figured out that Google ranked websites based on links, a new cottage industry was born. People started buying, selling, and trading links like it was their job. And for some, it was. Today, the link industry is worth more than one billion dollars. Even after the purity of the Google founders’ system was disturbed, it was tremendously innovative for its time. In fact, that same link-based system, called PageRank, is still the foundation of the most popular search engine in the world. But nowadays, dozens of restrictions apply to which links can count as legitimate votes. PageRank works in very much the same way as popularity in grade school.<br /><br />Generally speaking, the more friends you have (and the cooler they are), the better. So if you have six friends who are sort of cool, you’re pretty comfortable. If you have only three friends, but they happen to be the coolest kids in the school, you’re even higher in the pecking order. But of course, the most enviable situation of all is to be the most well-liked kid in the whole school. Then you have more aggregate coolness than anyone.<br />Now let’s turn to the way Google looks at PageRank. Technically, PageRank is a predictor of how relevant a web page will be for any given search. It is similar to popularity, which could be said to be a predictor of how much a person will be liked by any other given person. Every web page on the Internet is assigned a PageRank, which is a number from 0 to 10. The higher the PageRank, the more relevant Google considers the page to be, and the better its chance of showing up at the top of the search results. You can see a site’s PageRank by downloading the Google toolbar and enabling the PageRank bar.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ziki.com%2Fen%2Falberto-bishop-16%2B273317%2Fpost%2FWebsite-Templates---Common-Mistakes-to-Steer-clear-of-When-Making-use-of-a-Template%2B12832058"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.ziki.com/en/alberto-bishop-16+273317/post/Website-Templates---Common-Mistakes-to-Steer-clear-of-When-Making-use-of-a-Template+12832058</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F21134319%2Fchilldownloadcom-all-you-want-to-find"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/21134319/chilldownloadcom-all-you-want-to-find</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcheapwebsitetemplate46.blog.com%2F2011%2F09%2F02%2Fweb-templates-the-least-expensive-way-to-develop-a-website%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://cheapwebsitetemplate46.blog.com/2011/09/02/web-templates-the-least-expensive-way-to-develop-a-website/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a8cd05cd5f8d0adab1677c21f066a27" url=""><![CDATA[New, Refreshing & Remarkable Site Templates<br/><br/>If you are not familiar with this form of giveaway that <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mojo-themes.com%2F%3Fr%3Draffael211"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.mojo-themes.com/?r=raffael211</a>  has, it is easy, it implies is that every time there is a new signup we will deposit a No cost $ten in your account. No queries asked. If you have been pondering of getting a WordPress theme you now only devote $20 on common!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5718811a5c63c2f84b227fc8de1d1e28" url=""><![CDATA[New, Fresh & Amazing Website Templates<br/><br/>New collection of theme and template that can easily be used on any type of website, giving a new fresh look to your online business and interact more with your customers for a better quality. I’ve added and something that will make the new guys very happy … A new deal from Mojo Themes, were only be registering a make a small depozit of minimum 10$, you will be automated include in the list of users to win the big prize. Good luck all!!!<br />$10,000 Marketplace Credit Giveaway. Get $10 Deposited into your new MOJO Account!<br /><br />If you’re not familiar with this type of giveaway that Mojo Theme Market has, it’s simple, it means is that whenever there is a new signup we will deposit a FREE $10 in your account. No questions asked. If you were thinking of buying a WordPress theme you now only spend $20 on average!<br />Here are the details:<br /><br />We have allotted $10,000 for this giveaway and will run it until the money is all spent!<br />Each new account will be deposited $10. Unfortunately, this is only for new accounts<br /><br />We thought with a big giveaway like this, along with our another announcements, we could be sure everyone in the MOJO community was being taken care of.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Fnew-fresh-amazing-website-templates%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/new-fresh-amazing-website-templates/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="78394b911d95d22805f44bb9ce2a37da" url=""><![CDATA[New, Fresh & Amazing Website Templates<br/><br/>New collection of theme and template that can easily be used on any type of website, giving a new fresh look to your online business and interact more with your customers for a better quality. I’ve added and something that will make the new guys very happy … A new deal from Mojo Themes, were only be registering a make a small depozit of minimum 10$, you will be automated include in the list of users to win the big prize. Good luck all!!!<br />$10,000 Marketplace Credit Giveaway. Get $10 Deposited into your new MOJO Account!<br /><br />If you’re not familiar with this type of giveaway that Mojo Theme Market has, it’s simple, it means is that whenever there is a new signup we will deposit a FREE $10 in your account. No questions asked. If you were thinking of buying a WordPress theme you now only spend $20 on average!<br />Here are the details:<br /><br />We have allotted $10,000 for this giveaway and will run it until the money is all spent!<br />Each new account will be deposited $10. Unfortunately, this is only for new accounts<br /><br />We thought with a big giveaway like this, along with our another announcements, we could be sure everyone in the MOJO community was being taken care of.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Fnew-fresh-amazing-website-templates%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/new-fresh-amazing-website-templates/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8d67f179744ca4476a7a1a6f1fff9822" url=""><![CDATA[New, Fresh & Amazing Website Templates<br/><br/>New collection of theme and template that can easily be used on any type of website, giving a new fresh look to your online business and interact more with your customers for a better quality. I’ve added and something that will make the new guys very happy … A new deal from Mojo Themes, were only be registering a make a small depozit of minimum 10$, you will be automated include in the list of users to win the big prize. Good luck all!!!<br />$10,000 Marketplace Credit Giveaway. Get $10 Deposited into your new MOJO Account!<br /><br />If you’re not familiar with this type of giveaway that Mojo Theme Market has, it’s simple, it means is that whenever there is a new signup we will deposit a FREE $10 in your account. No questions asked. If you were thinking of buying a WordPress theme you now only spend $20 on average!<br />Here are the details:<br /><br />We have allotted $10,000 for this giveaway and will run it until the money is all spent!<br />Each new account will be deposited $10. Unfortunately, this is only for new accounts<br /><br />We thought with a big giveaway like this, along with our another announcements, we could be sure everyone in the MOJO community was being taken care of.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Fnew-fresh-amazing-website-templates%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/new-fresh-amazing-website-templates/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b94646ee39f07233b15de9ce63052926" url=""><![CDATA[New, Fresh & Amazing Website Templates<br/><br/>New collection of theme and template that can easily be used on any type of website, giving a new fresh look to your online business and interact more with your customers for a better quality. I’ve added and something that will make the new guys very happy … A new deal from Mojo Themes, were only be registering a make a small depozit of minimum 10$, you will be automated include in the list of users to win the big prize. Good luck all!!!<br />$10,000 Marketplace Credit Giveaway. Get $10 Deposited into your new MOJO Account!<br /><br />If you’re not familiar with this type of giveaway that Mojo Theme Market has, it’s simple, it means is that whenever there is a new signup we will deposit a FREE $10 in your account. No questions asked. If you were thinking of buying a WordPress theme you now only spend $20 on average!<br />Here are the details:<br /><br />We have allotted $10,000 for this giveaway and will run it until the money is all spent!<br />Each new account will be deposited $10. Unfortunately, this is only for new accounts<br /><br />We thought with a big giveaway like this, along with our another announcements, we could be sure everyone in the MOJO community was being taken care of.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Fnew-fresh-amazing-website-templates%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/new-fresh-amazing-website-templates/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="439df43ad4faa8fcba837d678c9e77b0" url=""><![CDATA[New, Fresh & Amazing Website Templates<br/><br/>New collection of theme and template that can easily be used on any type of website, giving a new fresh look to your online business and interact more with your customers for a better quality. I’ve added and something that will make the new guys very happy … A new deal from Mojo Themes, were only be registering a make a small depozit of minimum 10$, you will be automated include in the list of users to win the big prize. Good luck all!!!<br />$10,000 Marketplace Credit Giveaway. Get $10 Deposited into your new MOJO Account!<br /><br />If you’re not familiar with this type of giveaway that Mojo Theme Market has, it’s simple, it means is that whenever there is a new signup we will deposit a FREE $10 in your account. No questions asked. If you were thinking of buying a WordPress theme you now only spend $20 on average!<br />Here are the details:<br /><br />We have allotted $10,000 for this giveaway and will run it until the money is all spent!<br />Each new account will be deposited $10. Unfortunately, this is only for new accounts<br /><br />We thought with a big giveaway like this, along with our another announcements, we could be sure everyone in the MOJO community was being taken care of.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Fnew-fresh-amazing-website-templates%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/new-fresh-amazing-website-templates/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2e08dfe4c0c5cb065d80ef7677484f61" url=""><![CDATA[New, Fresh & Amazing Website Templates<br/><br/>New collection of theme and template that can easily be used on any type of website, giving a new fresh look to your online business and interact more with your customers for a better quality. I’ve added and something that will make the new guys very happy … A new deal from Mojo Themes, were only be registering a make a small depozit of minimum 10$, you will be automated include in the list of users to win the big prize. Good luck all!!!<br />$10,000 Marketplace Credit Giveaway. Get $10 Deposited into your new MOJO Account!<br /><br />If you’re not familiar with this type of giveaway that Mojo Theme Market has, it’s simple, it means is that whenever there is a new signup we will deposit a FREE $10 in your account. No questions asked. If you were thinking of buying a WordPress theme you now only spend $20 on average!<br />Here are the details:<br /><br />We have allotted $10,000 for this giveaway and will run it until the money is all spent!<br />Each new account will be deposited $10. Unfortunately, this is only for new accounts<br /><br />We thought with a big giveaway like this, along with our another announcements, we could be sure everyone in the MOJO community was being taken care of.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Fnew-fresh-amazing-website-templates%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/new-fresh-amazing-website-templates/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="978d1f5b729ff4b33d39f0769c023bd7" url=""><![CDATA[World wide web Templates - The Most affordable Way to Genera<br/><br/>Your focus should be on the three most important factors for ranking on Google:<br />Links <br />Page title <br />URL<br />Understanding how to optimize these factors allows you to rank for popular search terms, which causes you to get the most visitors to your website in the shortest time. But before I show you how to do that, you need to understand how Google looks at the Web.<br />When Larry Page and Sergey Brin set out to organize all the Web’s information as eager, bushy-tailed grad students at Stanford, they made one concept the foundation of their entire algorithm: links. Links, they hypothesized, were the currency of a new, democratic World Wide Web, just as votes are the currency of an election.<br />After all, a voter only casts his ballot for the candidate he believes in, and similarly, a website owner only links to another website if he finds it genuinely valuable… right?<br />Nope. Not in a free-market economy. The moment people figured out that Google ranked websites based on links, a new cottage industry was born. People started buying, selling, and trading links like it was their job. And for some, it was. Today, the link industry is worth more than one billion dollars. Even after the purity of the Google founders’ system was disturbed, it was tremendously innovative for its time. In fact, that same link-based system, called PageRank, is still the foundation of the most popular search engine in the world. But nowadays, dozens of restrictions apply to which links can count as legitimate votes. PageRank works in very much the same way as popularity in grade school.<br /><br />Generally speaking, the more friends you have (and the cooler they are), the better. So if you have six friends who are sort of cool, you’re pretty comfortable. If you have only three friends, but they happen to be the coolest kids in the school, you’re even higher in the pecking order. But of course, the most enviable situation of all is to be the most well-liked kid in the whole school. Then you have more aggregate coolness than anyone.<br />Now let’s turn to the way Google looks at PageRank. Technically, PageRank is a predictor of how relevant a web page will be for any given search. It is similar to popularity, which could be said to be a predictor of how much a person will be liked by any other given person. Every web page on the Internet is assigned a PageRank, which is a number from 0 to 10. The higher the PageRank, the more relevant Google considers the page to be, and the better its chance of showing up at the top of the search results. It is exponentially more difficult to achieve higher PageRanks in each successive bracket, and most websites never get past a 4 or 5. PageRanks of 6 are hard to come by, and 7s are downright rare. 8s and higher are reserved for the Apple.coms and Microsoft.coms of the world, and there are fewer than a dozen PageRank 10 websites on the entire Internet, including Facebook, the World Wide Web Consortium, and Google itself. If you have an inner page on your website that gains a higher PageRank than your home page, you should place an ad for your product or service on that page because it is more likely to rank highly in the search results.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Fpopular-cheap-plugins-for-wordpress%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/popular-cheap-plugins-for-wordpress/</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chilldownload.com%2Flatest-premium-wordpress-template-on-the-web%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.chilldownload.com/latest-premium-wordpress-template-on-the-web/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fca414485f4ed82a30fa12890d9c7d34" url=""><![CDATA[ChillDownload.com - All you want to find<br/><br/>Google analyzes unimaginable amounts of data from millions of websites and whittles it down to the ten most relevant results for your search. As you will soon see, only a few factors ultimately determine the order of search results. But the big G likes to have all sorts of data available so that it can return relevant web pages for highly specific searches such as why does my dog like watching baseball? After all, most searches are specific. General searches such as dog make up a relatively tiny slice of the search pie.<br />As a website owner or marketer, you don’t need to worry about the more arcane data points that Google analyzes. Your focus should be on the three most important factors for ranking on Google:<br />Links <br />Page title <br />URL<br />Understanding how to optimize these factors allows you to rank for popular search terms, which causes you to get the most visitors to your website in the shortest time. But before I show you how to do that, you need to understand how Google looks at the Web.<br />When Larry Page and Sergey Brin set out to organize all the Web’s information as eager, bushy-tailed grad students at Stanford, they made one concept the foundation of their entire algorithm: links. Links, they hypothesized, were the currency of a new, democratic World Wide Web, just as votes are the currency of an election.<br />After all, a voter only casts his ballot for the candidate he believes in, and similarly, a website owner only links to another website if he finds it genuinely valuable… right?<br />Nope. Not in a free-market economy. The moment people figured out that Google ranked websites based on links, a new cottage industry was born. People started buying, selling, and trading links like it was their job. And for some, it was. Today, the link industry is worth more than one billion dollars. Even after the purity of the Google founders’ system was disturbed, it was tremendously innovative for its time. In fact, that same link-based system, called PageRank, is still the foundation of the most popular search engine in the world. But nowadays, dozens of restrictions apply to which links can count as legitimate votes. PageRank works in very much the same way as popularity in grade school.<br /><br />Generally speaking, the more friends you have (and the cooler they are), the better. So if you have six friends who are sort of cool, you’re pretty comfortable. If you have only three friends, but they happen to be the coolest kids in the school, you’re even higher in the pecking order. But of course, the most enviable situation of all is to be the most well-liked kid in the whole school. Then you have more aggregate coolness than anyone.<br />Now let’s turn to the way Google looks at PageRank. Technically, PageRank is a predictor of how relevant a web page will be for any given search. It is similar to popularity, which could be said to be a predictor of how much a person will be liked by any other given person. You can see a site’s PageRank by downloading the Google toolbar and enabling the PageRank bar.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F775363%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailystrength.org/people/775363/journal</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcheap-website-template46.tumblr.com%2Fpost%2F9707285229%2Finexpensive-site-design-software-program"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://cheap-website-template46.tumblr.com/post/9707285229/inexpensive-site-design-software-program</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcheapwebsitetemplate68.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F09%2F07%2Finternet-site-models-for-low-cost-how-to-get-it-done-with-out-having-to-pay-a-ton%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://cheapwebsitetemplate68.wordpress.com/2011/09/07/internet-site-models-for-low-cost-how-to-get-it-done-with-out-having-to-pay-a-ton/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="adcfd4983632df4a3c4dbdf3c2336b06" url=""><![CDATA[ChillDownload.com - All you want to find<br/><br/>But the big G likes to have all sorts of data available so that it can return relevant web pages for highly specific searches such as why does my dog like watching baseball? After all, most searches are specific. General searches such as dog make up a relatively tiny slice of the search pie.<br />As a website owner or marketer, you don’t need to worry about the more arcane data points that Google analyzes. Your focus should be on the three most important factors for ranking on Google:<br />Links <br />Page title <br />URL<br />Understanding how to optimize these factors allows you to rank for popular search terms, which causes you to get the most visitors to your website in the shortest time. But before I show you how to do that, you need to understand how Google looks at the Web.<br />When Larry Page and Sergey Brin set out to organize all the Web’s information as eager, bushy-tailed grad students at Stanford, they made one concept the foundation of their entire algorithm: links. Links, they hypothesized, were the currency of a new, democratic World Wide Web, just as votes are the currency of an election.<br />After all, a voter only casts his ballot for the candidate he believes in, and similarly, a website owner only links to another website if he finds it genuinely valuable… right?<br />Nope. Not in a free-market economy. The moment people figured out that Google ranked websites based on links, a new cottage industry was born. People started buying, selling, and trading links like it was their job. And for some, it was. Today, the link industry is worth more than one billion dollars. Even after the purity of the Google founders’ system was disturbed, it was tremendously innovative for its time. In fact, that same link-based system, called PageRank, is still the foundation of the most popular search engine in the world. But nowadays, dozens of restrictions apply to which links can count as legitimate votes. PageRank works in very much the same way as popularity in grade school.<br /><br />Generally speaking, the more friends you have (and the cooler they are), the better. So if you have six friends who are sort of cool, you’re pretty comfortable. If you have only three friends, but they happen to be the coolest kids in the school, you’re even higher in the pecking order. But of course, the most enviable situation of all is to be the most well-liked kid in the whole school. Then you have more aggregate coolness than anyone.<br />Now let’s turn to the way Google looks at PageRank. Technically, PageRank is a predictor of how relevant a web page will be for any given search. It is similar to popularity, which could be said to be a predictor of how much a person will be liked by any other given person. Every web page on the Internet is assigned a PageRank, which is a number from 0 to 10. The higher the PageRank, the more relevant Google considers the page to be, and the better its chance of showing up at the top of the search results. You can see a site’s PageRank by downloading the Google toolbar and enabling the PageRank bar.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F775363%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailystrength.org/people/775363/journal</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F775363%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailystrength.org/people/775363/journal</a> , <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstevenmacias724.mywapblog.com%2Fwhy-website-templates-are-well-worth-it.xhtml"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://stevenmacias724.mywapblog.com/why-website-templates-are-well-worth-it.xhtml</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>