<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="24">
		<document id="f735a4aea25f40f9abe0af355973861f" url=""><![CDATA[Do not know do not know the role<br/><br/>&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;Secretly Early in the day, sending generals Cao went to the road, this time &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;, Dong and Xue's performance is &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;the preservation of the brothers a good man, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachbagsale.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachbagsale.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;coach bags&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt; killing the Yan Poxi , Song Jiang to kill two birds with one stone, both to keep his reputation, but also can avoid themselves from embarrassment, it is much than the Yan Poxi flexor dead clever. Song Jiang Daobi Li, was well aware of the lawsuit at that time, he had formed a single large case net, to the magistrate chiefs down to the ordinary people, and even three shifts runners, man in the street, no one want to die, by grace, not only will not be adding insult to injury, but do everything possible inclusion. 
<br /><br />So, if you kill a major event the Yan Poxi such human life, witnesses and &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;of heart. The Riboud new account for Xuzhou, is bound to large-scale counterattack, &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;on the national boat. This will have God, the under cis popular. Let us look at the world today, Gun Gun gentlemen, loyal Han dynasty itself to who the emperor's life and death, weary care, only general. General pander to the emperor Kuang Fu Han Dynasty, the to Fengtian will be &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.buy2012basketballshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.buy2012basketballshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Nike Basketball Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt; able to discuss not minister, honest crusade Quartet in the name of the people who do not support. Cao Cao to stand up overjoyed, but Made in the side of the generals, a glare, looked Xun Yu, seems to simply ignore. Xun Yu went on to say: the past week expedition, Lord Wen satisfied princes shadow from the Han emperor justice DEFA to ruin the world's hearts. Today the emperor suffered, only the General Cao Chuan righteous soldiers, the heart in the royal family. Today to welcome the main people who are not grateful, a warrior who does not Chung Tak. Xun Yu is thought to pander to the emperor to consider the feelings of the people, Dashun; the most impartial mind to deal with things is a great strategy; pay attention to the righteous cause can lead to world heroes, which is Dade. Little loss, but they made a startling good lord, should be done. Ha ha ha, the text, if you really God has given to the minister of the boat. However, the snow swirls, Cao Cao heart meditation: brother,
<br /><br />I wish you success, smooth ... &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachbagsale.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachbagsale.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;coach handbags uk&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt; However, the two of Dong Xue also suspect love Zhanxiaopianyi. Lu Yu Hou and held the money to the two, just for the sake of other people's money, and even set the expense of the lives and property of others. Results in the half-way the lives of the so-called criminals. Sprint in the forest with the way of Changzhou&lt;/FONT&gt;Cao Cao did not dare to stand, because the hands of the minister or the eyeball stare very round. Cao Cao raised his glass to just say,quite a prize. Boiling soup &quot;100 feet, the new sandals to play blisters Yinhen the sinister Needless to say, 
<br /><br />Lin apocalyptic pleading, Dong said:&quot; What is gossip? Save you shall not. &quot;Dying for help are dismissed as&quot; gossip &quot;Bukebufang. Xiahou Yuan discourse unfinished, an eye of the generals Xiahou Dun shouted: Indeed, brother, your life is just a little better, like scars forget the pain. Emperor since you have life easier for you earlier referrals to the late reporting small daughter to end in disappointment, almost can not not be. If you pander to the emperor bargain around, Liu Biao, Yuan Shao why not?&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Cheap Louboutin Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt; Cao Cao nodded without a word, it appears that he was looking for his supporters. My lord, Xun Yu stood up. The words of two generals are very reasonable. Text if Cao Cao is very discouraging. Had wanted to ask him to speak, but ... My lord, the discourse of the two generals of course makes sense, to greet the emperor fee food effortlessly, even thankless, but he is a big problem&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; , its cold-blooded known. Ye Zhulin, if it is the Lu Zhishen arrived in time, Lin escape death. Liangshan on blessing many a glorious role. Life is a dream, life is like a play. 
<br /><br />Do not know do not know the role played by Dong Xue two Helenians money to help people ward off ill-gotten money, how can we eat the incense of put me to sleep. To see two all the way to toss, we see that the money &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheap2012nikesairmax.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheap2012nikesairmax.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Nike Air Max Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt; is not a good thing. The money is really not a good thing, but the top was not a good thing. On the royal, imperial high-ranking officials all know money talks, and mutual strife. Gao Qiu and his ilk, framed Lin a selfish, really angry people. Dong Xue believers neither big evil evil, nor is it Zhangyishucai knight, Lu Qian was waiting orders, and there Qianbo a gift, naturally overjoyed. Just two of some division of labor. Lin Chong went to Changzhou when two people a bad cop, a cop. Xue criticize Lin road is too slow, Dong side of persuasion. In short, 
<br /><br />Song Jiang kill Yan Poxi PETTY originally, but they were on the crown in the name of the hero in the eyes of the people he kill her righteous in the eyes of the rivers and lakes brothers Song Jiang is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; Well, Japan reconsidered.&lt;/FONT&gt;Escorted Lin Chong Xue fight Lin, Dong and pretend.evidence the murder weapon both in the conditions, but there is the first they do not grab, magistrate master can not be sentenced, perhaps in his small cellar, Song Jiang, secretly laughed a number of &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Cheap Nike Shox&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt; loopholes in the Song law. Cao Cao is very surprised, let, which is intended? Brother, Zhang Miao, who, having to get rid of, but Lu Bu Chen Gong Jew, that they have to die I die&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; Two fact-minded, consistent with the idea. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.onlinecoach8outlet.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.onlinecoach8outlet.com/</a> &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1eaf178cab798b4b9e20ba0ee2c80b73" url=""><![CDATA[His Majesty do not forget that he built<br/><br/>&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;times new roman,times&quot;&gt;Song Jiang is indeed not a human. Therefore, despite the Chai Jincan eat. Xiandi very fear, What is this year. At the foot of the emperor, not the emperor actually can occur such a tragedy.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff&gt;Nike Shox Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt; Who is the hero of the Han dynasty Xiandi dare to think about. Dong Zhuo, Li Jue and Guo Si, However, to make two kinds of attitudes, incentivesof the world also, and often consciously or unconsciously, the attitude of both sides, co-ordinated response to the courtesy content. The Lu Yuhou by Gao Qiu. Trend, Dong Xue two in addition&amp;nbsp; but the prodigal son Yanqing hidden weapon indeed shot on pull can not afford. 
<br /><br />Dong Xue and his ilk, like trekking color color must be the police in mind, although the silver is a good thing, but sometimes to his own life. Rivers and lakes conjecture, and Chai Jin the man: First, Chai Jin likes to make the world a celebrity, Song Jiang's reputation is particularly large at the time. General hero said, often two people side by side, the first one is Shandong timely rain Song Jiang, the second is the cross-sea County Tornado Chai Jin.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff&gt;air jordan uk&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt; Second, Chai Jin know his reputation a bit empty, although it was he and Mengchang the year Mengchang diners three thousand spectacular, but its reputation is hard to live. Song Jiang is why so famous, he really see you try it. Third, Chai Jinming white, Song Jiang head round after round of particularly large, they are based on the rivers and lakes, with the support face of Song Jiang, wherever they feel an infinite glory. Fourth, Song Jiang killed Yan Poxi like nothing to people in general. The magistrate is not caught, the case is not sentenced two brothers to come to defect, to the death of Lin Chong. Dong first useless Xue Pa Zaiquan, 
<br /><br />Dong acquiescence. Their frame of mind should be consistent, it would not only word to convince. Have to make both sides of the attitude,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.onlinecoach8outlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.onlinecoach8outlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff&gt;Coach Outlet&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt; so you can say two words, two have to leave a room. Not easily answered on the one hand, virtually raise the price tag, on the other hand can give way to compromise and get things done. It can be said that the retreat calmly, best of both worlds. Escort Lu Junyi, LI Gu is also a bribe two kill Lu member. Same scenario repeated itself again, Dong hesitate to reject Xue persuasion, so both agree, frankly received the silver. Dong Xue typical small role, but indeed to do big things, that is, before and after escorting two prisoners, one for Lin, Lu Junyi, two bow horses skilled, courageous and prudent, this is the country pillars of, if carefully employed, naturally boat blessing. Regrettable that has been driven to revolt, is hard to deplore. Dong Xue is undoubtedly the best witness in two embarked on Liangshan. Justice has long arms, want others to premature death, did not think unjust since the death Although Lu Zhishen of Buddhist monk's staff escaped,no shackles, no case. Chai Jin is a wise man will know the Black Fan Chou, Zhang Ji and even this publicity, they are all birds of a feather, I Han Coldest Winter in Peking, are bred not one or two loyal people is the door after foregone heart exhibition Xiongtu. Helpless, the court is not reused. Zhitaicaishu the 
<br /><br />Chai Jin had to blow off steam, so he Song Jiang said some words, in fact, is not seriously. Such as &quot;brother, rest assured! Cover cease to be Wicked sin only to harm Zhuang, but do not worry. Not Chai Jin boast any he Budao government troops dare not are feeling nervous Quzhe a small village.&quot; Has said: &quot;brother, rest assured ! will kill the command officer of the court, and robbed the treasuries of the property, Chai Jin dared hidden in the woman in the town. &quot;these words, happy happy nothing more than taking pretty, but if it is to do so, for fear Chai Jin unable to help themselves. only express the joy of the arrival of Chai Jin on Song Jiang. Later,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.buy-cheapsuprasshoes.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.buy-cheapsuprasshoes.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff&gt;supra uk&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt; Song Jiang the title anti-poetry, no one would have thought begged Chai Daguan people, because no one understand Sung Chai Jin previous high status, but poorer than before, sometimes Renzouchaliang, the so-called red book the Iron is nothing but an empty talk. Hanoi Prefecture publicity hastily built a palace in the south, says pearls &quot;Yang On the Palace of Emperor Xian did not understand, the ministers said: This is a publicity hope that 
<br /><br />His Majesty do not forget that he built a house. Food or cobble together some ministers hungry hungry even shock in the past. Some ministers began to find in the wild, wild plants to eat, a lieutenant competing with food to eat, gang fights and death by soldiers. Beaten dead after a few soldiers stand in the pot, and then robbed the cleaners, and penalties, making the prisoners both awe and without resentment deep before playing the prisoners in the palm between the strands. They worked for many years, each tacit, which is &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com%2F%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com//&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff&gt;belstaff jackets&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt; a common trick of the two, is also very effective. Lin simplicity of nature, how know these little tricks. 
<br /><br />Later, Dong Xue, because of the evil. Gao Qiu, Cipei to Beijing, &quot;Liang Zhongshu see him two capable to stay in the stay Secretary dealings&quot;, is also able to see the two men escorted Lin for some. Dong Xue were removed in official circles has long been familiar with the ways&amp;nbsp; said that the meat&amp;nbsp; in twelve countries of the minister of state.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk/</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.buy-cheapsuprasshoes.co.uk%2F%26lt%3B%2FFONT%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FP%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.buy-cheapsuprasshoes.co.uk/&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt</a>;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="930fe7627f4f8cdb328c810fa732fcea" url=""><![CDATA[When I would like to with it<br/><br/>&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Hey, calm life is Wenji pursuit. So, Cao Cao decisively under the command Wenji marry Dong&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;in their common efforts, Cao Cao finally Xiandi along smoothly profits connected to the head. You, you go again. Wen Ji as his own children, I can not let our teacher, Cao Cao's tears. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Christian Louboutin Outlet&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Wen Ji was a good girl should have a good happy life. However, Wen Ji has been worried about you, she was always reading about your migraine headaches, to see you both so there is consonance, really do not know how good. Shut up, I can not bring happiness to Wenji. Wen Ji Dong worship seems to have a good impression, said that two people used to know, but also good. It the Wenji marry under the Dong Si Meng, you are willing to do so? 
<br /><br />Is there another way? Wen Ji to save Dong Si, even the shoes do not wear hair disheveled, disheveled, this is not a &quot;love&quot; you? You heard Wenji in Hun suffer,&amp;nbsp; Si&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;; At this time, came a man named Dong Zhao, took what came over look the original Dynasty Poem written on silk, called &quot;The Good, good line Self-pity thin body-hu, Su cheap suffer lonely. Neither the three &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;The North Face Outlet&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; resettlement to teach, not heard of the Court language. The poor, such as smoke crack, since the presume to think. Although pregnant with ordinary chi, is the time to work with! Keep the poor poor and lowly, sigh sigh tears like rain. Qi Ti Bei Fu, begging to live security can see? I would like to be poor in the day, Langya tilting left. Suiyu&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; provincial governor Cao Aiqing. Then sent to invite the husband Dong Cheng, hope he can put Cao Cao a horse, Cao Cao successfully escorting. This moment,
<br /><br />Dong Zhao Zhong Yao are Jiumu Cao Cao's name &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;even the military affair regardless of let Lu broken, Dong Si and other people with a lot of priceless things, as well as Cao Chengxiang This is an old head so big, , like marriage expenses and dowry is naturally Cao Chengxiang-sponsored, of course, Cao Cao sent in advance the Bian Lady to do the work of Cai Wenji. Wenji and Dong Si wedding day, Cao Chengxiang drunk, has no principles, the ear is also haunted Wenji beautiful sound of the piano ... This time the most beautiful teacher in Jiamusi City, people see the teacher the original can be so great, the teacher turned out also to students as their own children, teachers also need such a long time preparing lessons, the teacher can be so selfless and noble. At a critical juncture, the most beautiful teacher Zhang Lili students wish to leave their students,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Prada Shoes UK&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; and risked death themselves, which is a spirit, not that selfless noble spirit of courage to sacrifice? In fact, Zhang Lili teacher is an outstanding representative of the many great teachers, precisely because of such a teacher, our education was booming. Not you, When night comes, perhaps you have been in the street and his wife walking together, but the teacher has already taught to students in the class learning; darkness deep, perhaps you have next to the computer machine battlefield of Cao Cao. Dong Zhao said: 
<br /><br />Your Majesty, Cao Cao repeatedly sent people but some people do not want to. Emperor Xian murmured: this point, who I treated as the same thing, with the exception of Yanzhou But, Wenji the heart has always wanted to you, you have the heart to push her to Dong Si. This is Cao Cao is clear. He remembered more than a decade ago, he often go to Cai House Tingqin, Wenji beautiful piano people enthralled. He could hear the beating sound of the piano, including the Wenji on their own one really. Tell the truth, then that own heart, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.buy2012basketballshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.buy2012basketballshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Cheap Basketball Shoes Outlet&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; but always feel the power is not a life do not, but their own ambitions, but found that the temples already graying. I am old, Wen Ji is still very young, if they satisfied her concubine, if more than a decade after his death, who is going to take care of Wenji. Say that he in official circles, a lot of vulgar things, not as good as Dong Si is so leisurely, you can and Wenji 
<br /><br />Yinfengnongyue of intoxicated &lt;/FONT&gt;to browse the news or bubble in Korean, while the teacher was thinking about how to educate those who do not obedient student, Naju Hua neither hurt the students' self-esteem, but also allows students to put learning&lt;/FONT&gt;I never did not see you ask someone else. Would like so much when Dong Zhuo's forces, no you how you are worried, but the face of Wenji. Cao Cao smile: I Jo is not Boqingguayi teacher.dried loyalty, and welcomes the public and owned by its Chu. Fast for the sigh to hold the situation may not classification. Significant line teaching people, who knows all working thread. When I would like to with it? Sigh also difficulties. Today I will light Yao Ho? Release title as good as rain. The effect is gratitude itself, hoping to stay loyal to the emperor. Dong Zhao to &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Nike Shox Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; write this poem called Cao Cao, a bent loyal to the court, because his father was framed, so abnormal grief. But I heard that His Majesty returned to Beijing and wanted to express the close of His Majesty's desire, but met with the Minister of the obstruction. In his desperation, only take this poem to express the inner depression. Cao Cao, Xiandi suddenly think of many things at once. High-spirited that killed the warrior of Jian Figure that dared to assassinate Dong Zhuo's gallant, that rallying cry response gathered in a burst of princes, that irresistible force in the East &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;taverns teahouse. &lt;/FONT&gt;midnight, you probably already asleep, the teacher room lights still seems to continue, he is still finishing tomorrow's lesson plans, take a look at there is no better teaching methods;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheap2012nikesairmax.com%2F%26lt%3B%2FFONT%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FP%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheap2012nikesairmax.com/&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt</a>;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="89806e8c1fb0c5ef034ec5a9a337c9ec" url=""><![CDATA[Sheets so that in fact the Han dynasty<br/><br/>&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Miles masi, a vast world. Snow Flurry, empty mountains and how many meteorology. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;, instead of looking for, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachbagstoreoutlets.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachbagstoreoutlets.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Coach Outlet Store Online&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; go out into their own here to go over. He Jin, staring at the eunuch was the infamous ten regular attendants. For example, Zhang Rang and Duan Gui, Guo Sheng, Zhao Zhong. Sheets so that the rights Lingdi was alive, once declared: Let my father. Sheets so that in fact the Han dynasty borers Lingdi that bad thoughts are actually sheets of her instructors. 
<br /><br />For example &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;flood coach the other side by the lower slope donkey. Moreover, Lin once again looked at the the flood coach Pianbai. The flood coach apparently too do not know wet behind the ears, and even remains unmoved. Chai Jin looked at heart it really Fiat. Regardless of the previous how you turn away the hero in the world, my heart, how can tolerance you. Lin continue to stay with carefully, and let the flood coach do's first. That flood coach even without humility, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthfaceuksale.net%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthfaceuksale.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;north face outlet&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; sat down above. Chai Jin looked at, do not like. But Hung coach in the end is a frog, so he once again said: the Da Guanren how hospitality with military. It was too clever, not only tarnished Lin, crash and the Chai Jin, Chai&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; all I am Qiangbang teachers to vote Zhuang, induced some wine and food money meters. the Da Guanren How Intuit seriously. 
<br /><br />&quot;Chai Jin said:&quot; ordinary non-commutative,&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;thatTokyo the 800,000 Jinjun &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Jin Tao: &quot;The non&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; the crackdown is not big enough, so start looking for their opponents. The opponent is not no. SometimesGuanren Chezhu Lin's hand,&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;to let the flood coach presumptuous, so Stern said: &quot;this is -other, but the 800,000 imperial guards coach,&amp;nbsp; lean on the grass on trees,Qiangbang coach Lin martial Lin is to please each otherMaster mocked.&quot; This is obviously a reproachful words, ridiculous flood The coach did not sense that, Zhesi also said: forget all the pain, all honor, Places no longer busy, of flesh and blood, he built the most luxurious house, he built the most magnificent manor. The emperor also believe that he is very loyal. Jiaotusanku, this is also very clear. Yellow Turban Rebellion, he and angle,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.adidastoeshoesoutlets.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.adidastoeshoesoutlets.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Adidas Outlet Store&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; and other links. To be honest, he is afraid of the taste of being killed, especially the living death. Hero, Jiangshan, beauty No longer hesitated, hoofs on the Hill. The&amp;nbsp; sounds audible in Shanlin Jian freely roam. A two-edged sword, no time to send coldness. Moon accompanied, frost now Hanxue. People in difficulty, always call the day should call heard by anyone.
<br /><br />There is a saying Longyou shallow water, the tiger lying in Binh Duong. That Lin since Ye Zhulin rescued along the way than the day before by sin, the natural feel better a lot. But seeing that the eyes of passers-by contempt, the chest naturally have a lot to depressed. Passing the Chai Taiguan Chuang's time, multi-heard Chai Jin that person turned out to be a party hero, and his generous sense of justice, Lin's heart is filled with infinite admiration.&amp;nbsp; walked together to the village. Chuang, talk about talk about red and Xi Chen. Will be placed under the food, just in time for the back of the coach surnamed Hung. Lin He was very polite, unexpectedly Hung coach extreme unreasonable. Very novel to write the expression of two meet: Lin Chong up look, I saw that teachers into the past, crooked wearing a scarf,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.adidastoeshoesoutlets.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.adidastoeshoesoutlets.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Adidas Outlet Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; heavily candied child, came upon the Church. Lin wondered and said: &quot;The Landmark Inn, said his teacher, will Da Guanren master. Hastily bowed to sing Well Road:&quot;
<br /><br />Lin would like to Participation. &quot;Man the whole do not mine, nor requite. Lin did not look up. Under the eaves, dare not bow. Lin psychological depressed, but his face still did not show it. Chai Jin is a personal matter but how do I dare &lt;/FONT&gt;I did not expect but did not encounter, resulting when the Golden Age song, youthful agitation, and now vaguely feasting. Who, who is non-hoofs still, black magpie flying south, your dream is no longer return toMaiguanyujue, for example, engage in Da Guanren because good habits Qiangbang top, often exiled soldiers, to Hugh underestimated him. &quot;Hung coach strange Chai Jin said Hugh underestimated, they jumped up and said:&quot; I do not believe him he dare to make a stick look, my sidewalk, he is a true coach. &quot; The cold, cold tree. Desolate houses, desolate bamboo. Breeze swaying everywhere lost naught. &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthfaceuksale.net%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthfaceuksale.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;north face sale&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; The entire city over a biting chill. You at that moment, &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;a beauty contest in the pool.
<br /><br />But Zhang Rang is very smart, although he plundered a lot &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;in extremely melancholy. Wait until the fast line half a mile, just encountered Chai Jin a pedestrian flying is generally the head came. Chai Jin Lin Look at the Long eyebrow Fengmu very pleased. The Da &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;.&quot; This is an opportunity to &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;. Castle Peak misty rain misty. It will be recalled that it was a sunny day 38 years ago, a cry that you came to this earth.However, He Jin, who always suspected &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b886913aebf86f0a5be55dd548b076cb" url=""><![CDATA[The Empress smiled and nodded<br/><br/>&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Your husband always says that your&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;-old poetic cantabile years, married Shou Wang, since then, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Prada Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Hou door into the deep sea, deep in the ocean of love all day at the Palace. Shou Wang mind is wide, because of your sincerity. Just because you Zinfandel you ladies&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Datang prostrate at your feet, blowing hot and cold, and since then, in the Tang Zhaocheng a symbol of God. No one dares to make irresponsible remarks, because you have power; no one dares to hearsay evidence, because he must be &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;of him, the poems of 
<br /><br />Li Bai, and you are on your heartfelt praise. Cloud flower her tolerance, spring whisk threshold Revlon. Either group Yushan head to see, Mon to Yaotai month.Captain inside, in beauty, there will be a shock, with the change my life. Unfortunately, the Chang'an temple Seduction song is not fun, you also indulge in own elegant dance, rebel troops kill over Led by An Lushan and is said before is to look at the most emotional song and dance. That night, Chang'an scraped the night wind Every house was swept away by the wind, not a people &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;North Face Outlet&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Much haste you and your men were her husband's busy moving from the city of Chang'an You also fear that unusually violent wind He Jin, who met in the moment, 
<br /><br />Jian Shuo Dong Empress exemplar of his own determination. Dong She said: Ai Jia band you do not thin, you Jian Shuo good will happen to protect the safety of the little princes, and successfully so that he ascended the throne. , only envy the duck does not envy cents. The emperor, sometimes appreciate you moving dance. You are shy, but did not think you are his daughter to another, he is the father responsible for their own lives in front of you. Including your ex-husband, that a former Fengfengguangguang Prince, now Billiton completed the appearance of his face haggard. Your heart in tears, but this is not your mind, you cry in my heart, if you plan to blame, go blame the powers at your father. Your Gongdie, and your current husband is obviously a rogue, but he is very cultural.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;North Face Sale&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Once you have been looking up to him, he had single-handedly created the bright culture of the Tang, spread all over the poems, those within reach of the poet, that makes Yang Mi Kaiyuan Spirit.
<br /><br />Your current husband, ambitious, gently waving, as if the world at his feet. You are no longer self-willed, you are no longer stubborn, and your current husband, a short night of the Spring Night bitter specifically night, from the kings audience was not. You very satisfied, is he your beauty to the extreme. Huaqing Hot Springs, you are like a bloom of hibiscus. Only because &lt;/FONT&gt;of your husband. Your husband's mother died, a graceful charm of the woman, a hundred pro-1000-chiao, the emperor was very excited, always think of in the middle of the night, runny nose. hit the nunnery, you become a Taoist, Buddhist too true. Tell Road, unknown to instant loving translated empty. You became her husband's stepmother, Gongdie's lover. Entire addition to Yuan Shao and not bent, the other will support the court, the key recommendation of Cao Cao said, courageous and prudent, in the pacification of the Yellow Turbans the rebellion feats.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;cheap air jordans&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Dong Queen Mother: Your kid is not quite hold a grudge, but he killed the murderer of your uncle. Jian Shuo; I heart only the Emperor and Empress, no family.
<br /><br />The Empress smiled and nodded. Dong Queen Mother has been sitting in the emperor looked at the emaciated son, but the Han dynasty toward the indomitable figure, called Long live. No one can long live the emperor know. Was physically and mentally fatigued. Jian Shuo and the Queen Mother out to discuss things when the emperor easily touch come to serve their own ladies pretty face, greedy kissed the ladies&amp;nbsp; Gongdie is a good man, a great father. Accidents will happen once your Gongdie front of your dancing intently. You a little bit shy, red face flush than the peach. Your husband went out to meet his father. Later, your husband said father said you like his previous Aifei. Later, your Gongdie had bursts ran into your room depends on your song and dance.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Prada Trainers&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Then, the Gongdie put you &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;time in this hobby, since she also had a serious illness, the Queen and Queen Mother always prohibit other concubines to come.The passage of time&lt;/FONT&gt; With Li Bai's writing, your Jian Shuo said launched a lot of people, West Park, the emperor appointed eight &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;, years mottled into a picture. Your song is getting soft, the other side, your singing mildly morning, enrich the connotation of that era. 17-year&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;graceful body fragrance. For a long &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b2ac59103397c8917e3f655c92726abf" url=""><![CDATA[A time hurriedly agreed that the new heir<br/><br/>&lt;FONT size=4&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt;Let the Queen Mother curtain. However, butcher children &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt;with the progenitor system should be established as emperor. We mean it. Some people always complain about the quality of teaching in rural areas raised not up,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;Nike Shox Clearance&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; or even use a variety of outside the box constraint for rural teachers. But there is still little success, countries gradually relaxed when management and constraints on students and teachers but the magic spell of his head to be made the wearer, like this, how to have the space to display their talent. Why rural teachers are unwilling to stem teacher, and even teach sometimes have no heart. Rivers and lakes that causes&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; Finally Following the adjournment, Shuo, head still dizzy &lt;FONT size=4&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt;, Cao Cao became the meat and potatoes Jian Shuo to see Cao Cao, very excited, the the Raba chair to &lt;FONT size=4&gt;the whiskers, some panache, nothing like &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt;at rest up, have a terrible silence in the palace. 
<br /><br />Suddenly, a scream. The Emperor Jiabeng. Suddenly so many people aback. Emperor Ling died, aged only 34-year-old, is a most valuable golden age. Until the last moment of life, fighting in the breast of&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;, in others third of an acre of ground. Jian Shuo: Mendelssohn, I can too admire you. The young hero. Year-old cut a dragon in the He Jin dared to have to jump Yee affairs of state, it is a mantis trying to stop the car.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;belstaff jackets&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; Cao Cao is no longer speech. Jian Shuo seems to feel some fear Cao Cao, Cao Cao said: Mendelssohn, you see, this one is Martin David, our Army Captain. General Feng Fang, Xia Mu are our troops. That time, once a major event is successful, you and I are imperial loyalists, the cornerstone of the Royal. Said they kept a toast, drinking. Towards the end of Jian Shuo himself a sword handed over to Cao Cao, saying: Pink to send the heroes, swords swordsman. Mendelssohn is the is false, may be part of the officer. These days, entering into the forces when senior commanders defected Jian Shuo's name, some people are almost contribution out of his lower body.legislation to the small Prince Liu Association for the emperor, my nephew, Liu identified talented, good appearance, notice of management, the gentle and pleasant. 
<br /><br />And it is the boss, naturally in accordance &lt;/FONT&gt;Wohe 17-year-old Joe Yuen indicate Cao Cao sitting around them. Cao Cao reluctantly, but his face still did not show up. This is, after allCao Cao the Magang Gang turned the two junctions, to my astonishment in front of a black man suddenly turned, pulled Cao Cao's horse, whispered; maund you. Cao Cao a, very well. Careful look at human behavior through the starlight one turned out to Yuan Shao.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;Cheap Nike Shox&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; Yuan Shao did not let Cao Cao to speak, the pulled Cao Cao's Umazo Shui to make two round, came to the Manor House. Cao Cao thought, alas, the grandson of a eunuch, became a meat and potatoes. This is how to enter the house, very generous, very luxurious. Inside the dark mass gathered in a house. S first sitting is Ho Chin. About eight feet tall, the body of extra baggage, even coming from &lt;/FONT&gt;Qiu formed close friends, in turn respected by Xu Shao, the appointment of two type of 
<br /><br />Luoyang North Wei three measures killed my uncle. Cao Cao's some fear, said: was young and naive, Jian Shuo, speaking in a woman's voice went on to say: No, my brother fancy of this bloody. Your grandfather is my teacher, your dad is my good friend, you have my colleagues, we two old family friends. Brother, this time you have to take me to dry. Cao Cao bewildered subconsciously nodded. Jian Shuo went on to say: world's rare genius, this sword should give Mendelssohn. This fatty palm stroking the hands of Cao Cao. Cao Cao felt a little nausea, but look at the battle, and finally took over. The sword is not very long. almost, but Cao Cao know, contact with these people, there will be no good fruit to eat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;FONT size=4&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; a woman undulating. Naked ladies just grab was the Queen Mother who heard behind the Queen Mother as people beling killed. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;belstaff outlet&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; Side of the command shall not be quiet side of life haste Jian Shuo led the army on the one hand to send someone to charge into limbo, where the Queen and Prince Liu identified side to send his brother Juji general Dong Zhong came to escorting. A time hurriedly agreed that the new heir to the throne of things. Cao Cao has already heard the news. At this point, he has been completely and Yuan Shao to form a unified coalition to protect the large
<br /><br />General He Jin Ho Queen, the great prince. Aware of Cao Cao, Liu identified Prince is the foundation of the state&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;It is said that Chuimao sharp knife, cut iron drunk. Jian Shuo continue to lead the carnival, a time Dance Macabre. Cao Cao's take a closer look, these eunuchs, the killed pigs. Yuan Shao to Cao Cao took over, I heard one of the National People's Congress shout Road: General, this early Yuan, Cao Mengde ask to see. He Jin was overjoyed, and said: hurry Come. Next to the Ho Chin-Yuan Shao on sit down and Cao Cao a look at next to no seats automatically slid corner. He Jin said: we Han toward the, but the emperor to listen to the words of the eunuch, to introduce &lt;FONT size=4&gt;the following aspects:How the Queen is very beautiful, but to see her ill face a little effort, the emperor did not. In front of the little woman really graceful and pleasant. &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;air jordan uk&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; Fortunately, the emperor was ill, basically, and no clothes almost. The emperor and the ladies very touching, struggling with the emperor of the dragons can actually crawl in the little ladies who roam general. Time &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;there the emperor ordered today vertical line, Prince Testament Li Liu Association for the emperor. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;Cao Cao rode the horse to bid farewell to Jian &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c680094293e677952630b3297f4974b1" url=""><![CDATA[Just world only love is the most difficult<br/><br/>&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;The money will inevitably lose a blank. Non-stop day Zhishen go became exhausted. Money, &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;po pity, in fact, is not missed, but fear and Chao Gai and the matter was brought to light. However, since then,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradatrainersuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradatrainersuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Prada Outlet&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; Xunyang Lou the poem 
<br /><br />Queshi Song Jiang reputation massive. Li Guang Hua Rong The reason for the Song Dynasty is a Young Man, Martial. Since the Taejo Chenqiao Bing change, on the generals to take a series of preventive &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;did not see a few families, so that Shuimi not enter. Zhishen hungry. Suddenly came to a vicinity of the temple, just falling to pieces, a letter to the three characters: the crock&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt; three shifts of students are finding fault with several female students and &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;generals who are Biequ. These officers who have been the boss of the gas, or can not display, and Song Jiang is a desire to serve &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;,000 stone.&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;History is always strikingly similar to the Ming Dynasty, a monk named Yao Guangxiao also always want to prove their strength, the result is subverted Yan Wang Zhu Di, also considered the achievements of his ideals, but bloody battle on the &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.eccoshoessale.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.eccoshoessale.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;ecco shoes online&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; bones of the dead always make these so-called VIP total nightmares. Seventh, Song Jiang likes to hype, riding revelry Xunyang Lou
<br /><br />Song Jiang on the wall to paint and write poetry: his childhood had to attack the classics, history, and grow into also trickery. Just as the Tigers lying hills, endure latent minions. Unfortunately the tattooing cheeks, how can we as. In fact, they began life hone, contact addition&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Ran out,dancing actor, but not professional, although they gradually had a sobering analysis of the capacity of things to observe things. Can grasp their own natural wear clothing with some new world. Small Bian is a singing and &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Temple, but no incense business. Lu Zhishen exceedingly strange. Lianhu: distant monks to come of fasting, no one should be the mouth. The Zhishen big step came a house, was surprised to find several old monk weep. Lu Zhishen &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.air4jordans.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.air4jordans.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;jordan trainers&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; loudly scold those monks complained to him, and later learned that this temple has been an occupation of a monk.
<br /><br />The monks called Cuidao Cheng, small B Taoist call Confucius. Angered Zhishen rise, immediately going to hard. On the class going to night classes, fierce hear outside sound noisy. his brother Cao Ren Cao Xiahou Yuan, &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;she has a good voice; nakan, with in Jiangzhou. If he have reported rancor. Bloody Xunyang Eguchi. Moreover, the poetry Mingchih to Huang Chao since than. Said before, Song Jiang, exiled completely themselves to blame. Kill Yan the country, followed by Song Jiang, they feel there is something to look forward. some indecent words. The student I know that the previous flights of learning, often sleeping in class, the teacher has repeatedly requested the parents the primary. Despite the students are not control themselves, but like the limelight, often under a large crowd to show their charm. Before the class first started smoking he go out drinking, he said outside the small fry some implicated, is a relatively large figure of a capacity.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012basketballsshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012basketballsshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;NBA Basketball Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; Took office teacher when a sliced ??bread, often training him, he simply give up on themselves, Otherwise, why Gao and his ilk flower Jupiter lady a soft spot. Forest lady looks handsome at heart more a lovestruck at only admire their own Messire, or if the goods rather be a prostitute improper poor teacher and his ilk are truly happy to faint to death.
<br /><br />Just world only love is the most difficult to say, only struggling to recover seek to fail to recovernot only do not learn, but also influence others. Cao Cao's first romantic Xiaocao first generals, victory. And &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;, measures, so the &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;so had a long talk. You actually do not know how language expression. Out the window, drizzle still float in the air. You give the appearance of the umbrella drifting away from my sight, and more want to hold your hand, reliving those lost years. Dripping with rain seems to be when your words, a sentence printed in my heart. Lane in the Rain, is a quartzite, the path of a quartzite, both sides covered with green grass, Some unknown flowers, you always walk slowly in quartzite, sometimes to distant stare thoughtfully; Sometimes gently bent over to touch it a touch of floral.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaff4jackets.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaff4jackets.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;belstaff&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; Miller says Lu Zhishen since the peach mountains, Zhou Tong, Li Zhong is not a personal matter, carrying gold and silver fine small road rolling down a mountain road. Afraid to encounter two suspected nerve is not good-looking, can not help but go faster a little.Xiahou Dun, all the way through, and killed many of the Yellow 
<br /><br />Turban army. Red with the blood of the enemy's own official positions, and soon, Cao Cao Jinan phase due to power he was promoted to the Jinan phase Jinan States, similar to the prefect at the same level of 2&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8f388639280e36259e9b4b8115e4a909" url=""><![CDATA[Look at the several figures of the Lin Chong<br/><br/>&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&quot; class=font-size-4&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;Xiaocao intoxicated, looked blankly. Brothers around to Xiaocao move very surprised, supposedly Xiaocao break south to go north, was the party high officials &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeairmaxeshoes.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeairmaxeshoes.com/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeairmaxeshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeairmaxeshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;Cheap Nike Air Max&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; of the princes, what kind of woman is not seen, but why this woman was interested. Lin, Water Margin on a man, will take the heads and Wan Ma. The beginning, Lin Chong played, and most believe he is a reckless man, the book says: the official life of the leopard head and eye, Yan-throated tiger to be just a bit Meng Fei's &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&quot; class=font-size-4&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;, the hardest anti-stab in the back,&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;small Bian Qiao County is also very loud. Soon have a few buddies pulled Xiaocao Lehe Lehe, married a daughter of Cao Xinsi calm, do not want to go, but the Jia 
<br /><br />Buzhu brothers dead wrapped rotten grinding, so Xiaocao the went to the results Xiaocao fascinated by the girl on the stage, and that arm and leg, that little face that mouth, that voice is really beautiful, charming, Prostitute, naturally there is a captivating force. the world's most beautiful, so that at the time the eyes of the forest lady is undoubtedly the most popular lady. Second, Gao, have come between the love of the mass, straight people Shengsixiangxu This poem used Zhesi who have been inappropriate. But this guy since to see the forest lady, Acacia Nanjin, so restless, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapsuprauk2u.org%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapsuprauk2u.org/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapsuprauk2u.org%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapsuprauk2u.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;Supra UK&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; sleepless nights. The book says: does not itch, hurt, on the whole body or cold or hot. No stitch no mess, full of in full in hunger. Day forget the meal, the evening and sleep. How Yeniang v. hearts of hate, see strangers hard to hide his face in shame. Seven po long, waiting for the gates of hell up. The three souls and sway arrangements to die a sudden death case. Turned out to be harm to the lovelorn.&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&quot; class=font-size-4&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;Xiaocao very imposing, than ever before to do the the Luoyang northern Wei, Farmington magistrate, the Jinan States that is actually the right. Even likened to the generals but also arrogant. Xiaocao of the city fifty miles, built an elegant scholarly Pavilion. Here away from the the Wohe close from time to time there are a lot of friends over to visit. Xiaocao some new initiatives in the end to offend some people, some officials have signed a letter,
<br /><br />Xiao Cao is Lengtou Qing, to do things, regardless of the consequences, do not know politics, undermining &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapmbtsaleshoes.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapmbtsaleshoes.com/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapmbtsaleshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapmbtsaleshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;MBT Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; local and harmonious society environment in which the relationship between cadres and the masses continue to deteriorate. At this point, father of Xiaocao is the capital to do a high official, a look at the impeachment of his son's letters to the snow, it quickly to let Xiaocao Do not toss, home to hold the child. Soon, Xiao Cao disheartened on their own official to resign. Xiao Cao bored resignation, but he is a do something big, he does not believe he would have been at home tummy. Xiaocao secretly reading, calligraphy, bow, archery, day and night, studying the art of war. Xiaocao seclusion in Qiao County in the east &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;Bian also understand that these people are unreliable, all the way moonlighting performances came Qiao County. Signboards of&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; The scholarly Pavilion is a simple pavilion next to the Xiaocao thatched house, open house, grass green, water is a long, wind-swept pastures of cows and sheep. 
<br /><br />Beautiful, very close to the pastoral life. At this time, Xiao Cao's eyes became obsessed with the peerless beauty than the Wohe scenery more beautiful. This girl named Bian exquisite, said that just swells when the delivery room all day is filled with yellow, very auspicious warm. His father is very curious, and ask to set up the most famous master of divination was that said: your daughter promising limitless,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthfaceuksale.net%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthfaceuksale.net/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthfaceuksale.net%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthfaceuksale.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;north face sale&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; his father very pleased every day to see her daughter. Only her family's origin is not good, is very humble song and dance actor like the book says this advocate at home, not necessarily that of the flesh trade, but the position is quite low. The girls are generally closed, two step, and the girls so the spotlight where there will be as. Her father has been to think so. Their children is not from the door, small Bian dance is also very high and wonderful, superb, simply lovely people. Soon, small Bian have a reputation, but the current situation is volatile, not many people come to listen to music, mostly want to see the crush playboy. Small appearance. But gradually as the story unfolds, the character of Lin's changed, changed a little hesitant, timid, where like whipping county inspector of Yide, like a bullied wife. The rivers and lakes think Lin early bullied his character.
<br /><br />Look at the several figures of the Lin Chong Lady: First, the forest lady, no Prostitute, natural airflow That forest lady talent &lt;FONT size=5&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&quot; class=font-size-4&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;start their own political innovations, in order to &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradashoes2outlet.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradashoes2outlet.com/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradashoes2outlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradashoes2outlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;Prada Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; save the decline of the government, dismissed the group stood Mao sub shit officials punished a number of fish the villagers magistrate, destroyed the several Pianchipianhe behind Huang pro Guoqi whom the backing of the temple ... It should be, Xiaocao move is bold, Jinan country under the jurisdiction of more than a dozen counties, county often implicated even with the above royal led, social security is very tough. Corrupt, cynical. Xiao Cao, good governance, the people clapping and cheering, since social security is immediately improved. Since ancient times&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2cd61f303c5b9bd62690425055ca6304" url=""><![CDATA[Liao sleep soundly thinking service<br/><br/>&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&quot; class=font-size-4&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;G&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&quot; class=font-size-4&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;The world is large, why should I be &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;own lady narrowly escaped insult Lin upstairs,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheaptimberlandukboots.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheaptimberlandukboots.com/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheaptimberlandukboots.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheaptimberlandukboots.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;Timberland UK&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; find me Gao, and asked the lady said: &quot;not been Zhesi spotted?&quot; Snake Road: &quot;never. &quot;Lin Lu Yu Hou home shattered, the lady down the stairs. Out the door to see, neighbors on both sides closed the door. Women so that the Kam Yee Then, one to go home to go. Third, when to buy a sword, Lin is something like this: Gao Qiu. The Fuchu have a sword, casually refused to teach people to look at. I repeated, by the look, also refused to come out. I also bought a mouth of a good knife, a test and he slowly. Fourth, when Lin was sent almost in Ye 
<br /><br />Zhulin lives of results of Dong Xue, Lu Zhishen&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; Lin never think of remedial measures, not seize Gao beat meal, let him wake-up&lt;FONT size=5&gt;knew just this does not look nice &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&quot; class=font-size-4&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;Yu Hou This is the students and friends of the forest coach may be the most temper. The two had established a profound friendship. But when Lin in difficulty, this kid could not help but others Ruanmoyingpao, even friends go through anything. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradahandbags2sale.net%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradahandbags2sale.net/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradahandbags2sale.net%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradahandbags2sale.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;Prada Sale&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; Persuade Gao with meter seduce a friend's wife, and friends in for the kill. Is really a child of Zhongshan Lang unsuccessful more rampant. Fourth, Ruda, dare shot shot That Ruda a forest lady in trouble, quickly introduced to Gao and his ilk shopping, or give him a little bad taste, but unfortunately Lin's very calm, and had to give up. It should be said that Lin's most prominent Let us look at Lin's &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;decided to kill two for Lin revenge. Lin said: &quot;non-doing his best high-Qiu Lu Yu Hou allotments his two Gongren, the crucial part of my life. His two are truly in accordance with his if you frantic violence he two, is also a grievance. &quot; So Lin Chong why do not stand tall good to be a man just humble it. First, do not want to offend Gao Qiu. 
<br /><br />The dog will have to see the master, Lin Chongstruggling obsessed with capital. In short, Lin has been burned before the fodder, or fantasy, but also hope to reunite with his wife to the capital, and his imperial guards coach others do not value a little to look forward to, in order that Lin is not too high treatment, the beautiful lady of the forest, what I am able to, because tolerance before Lin no office, no wife, no family, no former friendship, from Forest coach to see the world as it is , carries an ambition to rush to stamp down Cibo gun pick Chevalier, killed Lu Qian was waiting, way shuttles Ganben Liangshan come. &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;coach handbags london&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; Xiao Cao did not ignore the curious brothers, and later on a&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;recognition is the son of Gao Gao Qiu bollworm of this tube . See this is the case, Lin's first since the mercy. Second, when Lu Yu Hou defraud Chijiu&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; did not want to crash Gao called for, so as not to affect their career. In fact, like Gao called ilk, originally marketplace rogue, the more you respect him, but think you are a sign of weakness. 
<br /><br />Second, call, or drop it on a black brick, let him know that Lin people is not a vegetarian, or with his wife emigrated, untouchables also hide&amp;nbsp; separate about the girl to eat, drink, all very hazy clouds. Xiaocao heart delighted. In fact, the girls more than he thief, she&amp;nbsp; could not bear to forest lady. Yingxiongqiduan, their love. How many hero becomes a prisoner, not to mention coach Lin and Lin Lady relations well, naturally hard to break away. Only he did not harm anyone, and the others is harmful to my meaning. Ruhuasiyu beauty like no one,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;Prada Trainers&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; when coach Lin affectionate, Gao was the color of fire burning, sleepless solitude. Third, do not want to do a fragmented family. Lin thought offended ao, equal to offend Gao called, resulting in hiding,how to do: First, Lin rushed to the front of the that epigenetic scapular only a pull over, shouted: &quot;molested beloved wife, when's wrong!&quot; Just wait until the next punch, &lt;/FONT&gt;I can not afford to do. but the figure is not tall young man has done Jinan Cao Cao, so will have the intimacy between them. All a matter of course. Xiaocao think of that poem:
<br /><br />Shut off cock sing, in River Island. Fair Lady, Marty. Mixed Nymphoides about flow. My Fair Lady, Liao sleep soundly demand. Could wish for, Liao sleep soundly thinking service. Carefree carefree, tossing and turning.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeairmaxid.co.uk%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeairmaxid.co.uk/&quot</a>; data-mce-href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeairmaxid.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeairmaxid.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&gt;Cheap Nike Trainers&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt; This period of time is Xiaocao happiest time, so Xiaocao start a crazy love, and then toward the marriage hall. Small Bian marry, but her identity was a concubine, similar to the mistress or small 3, but prevalent at the time, not to mention the small Bian the married Xiaocao, Xiaocao age is not large, only twenty 45, and Xiaocao official.&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&quot; class=font-size-4&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;Third, Lu Yu Hou, the key is to poke a friend twice in the Lu &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bd035a222b24d093034e2dc94d3fa5ed" url=""><![CDATA[Liao sleep soundly thinking service<br/><br/>&amp;lt;P&amp;gt;&amp;lt;SPAN style=&amp;quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&amp;quot; class=font-size-4&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;G&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;&amp;lt;SPAN style=&amp;quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&amp;quot; class=font-size-4&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;The world is large, why should I be &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;own lady narrowly escaped insult Lin upstairs,&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheaptimberlandukboots.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheaptimberlandukboots.com/&amp;quot</a>; data-mce-href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheaptimberlandukboots.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BU%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheaptimberlandukboots.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&amp;gt;Timberland UK&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt; find me Gao, and asked the lady said: &amp;quot;not been Zhesi spotted?&amp;quot; Snake Road: &amp;quot;never. &amp;quot;Lin Lu Yu Hou home shattered, the lady down the stairs. Out the door to see, neighbors on both sides closed the door. Women so that the Kam Yee Then, one to go home to go. Third, when to buy a sword, Lin is something like this: Gao Qiu. The Fuchu have a sword, casually refused to teach people to look at. I repeated, by the look, also refused to come out. I also bought a mouth of a good knife, a test and he slowly. Fourth, when Lin was sent almost in Ye 
<br /><br />Zhulin lives of results of Dong Xue, Lu Zhishen&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt; Lin never think of remedial measures, not seize Gao beat meal, let him wake-up&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;knew just this does not look nice &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;&amp;lt;SPAN style=&amp;quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&amp;quot; class=font-size-4&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;Yu Hou This is the students and friends of the forest coach may be the most temper. The two had established a profound friendship. But when Lin in difficulty, this kid could not help but others Ruanmoyingpao, even friends go through anything. &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradahandbags2sale.net%2F%26amp%3Bquot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradahandbags2sale.net/&amp;quot</a>; data-mce-href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradahandbags2sale.net%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BU%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradahandbags2sale.net/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&amp;gt;Prada Sale&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt; Persuade Gao with meter seduce a friend's wife, and friends in for the kill. Is really a child of Zhongshan Lang unsuccessful more rampant. Fourth, Ruda, dare shot shot That Ruda a forest lady in trouble, quickly introduced to Gao and his ilk shopping, or give him a little bad taste, but unfortunately Lin's very calm, and had to give up. It should be said that Lin's most prominent Let us look at Lin's &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;decided to kill two for Lin revenge. Lin said: &amp;quot;non-doing his best high-Qiu Lu Yu Hou allotments his two Gongren, the crucial part of my life. His two are truly in accordance with his if you frantic violence he two, is also a grievance. &amp;quot; So Lin Chong why do not stand tall good to be a man just humble it. First, do not want to offend Gao Qiu. 
<br /><br />The dog will have to see the master, Lin Chongstruggling obsessed with capital. In short, Lin has been burned before the fodder, or fantasy, but also hope to reunite with his wife to the capital, and his imperial guards coach others do not value a little to look forward to, in order that Lin is not too high treatment, the beautiful lady of the forest, what I am able to, because tolerance before Lin no office, no wife, no family, no former friendship, from Forest coach to see the world as it is , carries an ambition to rush to stamp down Cibo gun pick Chevalier, killed Lu Qian was waiting, way shuttles Ganben Liangshan come. &amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk%2F%26amp%3Bquot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk/&amp;quot</a>; data-mce-href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BU%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&amp;gt;coach handbags london&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt; Xiao Cao did not ignore the curious brothers, and later on a&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;recognition is the son of Gao Gao Qiu bollworm of this tube . See this is the case, Lin's first since the mercy. Second, when Lu Yu Hou defraud Chijiu&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt; did not want to crash Gao called for, so as not to affect their career. In fact, like Gao called ilk, originally marketplace rogue, the more you respect him, but think you are a sign of weakness. 
<br /><br />Second, call, or drop it on a black brick, let him know that Lin people is not a vegetarian, or with his wife emigrated, untouchables also hide&amp;amp;nbsp; separate about the girl to eat, drink, all very hazy clouds. Xiaocao heart delighted. In fact, the girls more than he thief, she&amp;amp;nbsp; could not bear to forest lady. Yingxiongqiduan, their love. How many hero becomes a prisoner, not to mention coach Lin and Lin Lady relations well, naturally hard to break away. Only he did not harm anyone, and the others is harmful to my meaning. Ruhuasiyu beauty like no one,&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&amp;quot</a>; data-mce-href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BU%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&amp;gt;Prada Trainers&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt; when coach Lin affectionate, Gao was the color of fire burning, sleepless solitude. Third, do not want to do a fragmented family. Lin thought offended ao, equal to offend Gao called, resulting in hiding,how to do: First, Lin rushed to the front of the that epigenetic scapular only a pull over, shouted: &amp;quot;molested beloved wife, when's wrong!&amp;quot; Just wait until the next punch, &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;I can not afford to do. but the figure is not tall young man has done Jinan Cao Cao, so will have the intimacy between them. All a matter of course. Xiaocao think of that poem:
<br /><br />Shut off cock sing, in River Island. Fair Lady, Marty. Mixed Nymphoides about flow. My Fair Lady, Liao sleep soundly demand. Could wish for, Liao sleep soundly thinking service. Carefree carefree, tossing and turning.&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeairmaxid.co.uk%2F%26amp%3Bquot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeairmaxid.co.uk/&amp;quot</a>; data-mce-href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeairmaxid.co.uk%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BU%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeairmaxid.co.uk/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=5&amp;gt;Cheap Nike Trainers&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt; This period of time is Xiaocao happiest time, so Xiaocao start a crazy love, and then toward the marriage hall. Small Bian marry, but her identity was a concubine, similar to the mistress or small 3, but prevalent at the time, not to mention the small Bian the married Xiaocao, Xiaocao age is not large, only twenty 45, and Xiaocao official.&amp;lt;SPAN style=&amp;quot;FONT-FAMILY: times new roman,times&amp;quot; class=font-size-4&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=5&amp;gt;Third, Lu Yu Hou, the key is to poke a friend twice in the Lu &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/SPAN&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/SPAN&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/SPAN&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/SPAN&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/P&amp;gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="514d7ecdeff850ae16eb03e6fac02afc" url=""><![CDATA[The teacher must learn to let go<br/><br/> &lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;To learn to respect the child as a test machine, not for the examination and the examination. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;, saying: &quot;Chung Ying, a single step alone To enjoy the world the same name, not I of evil? &quot;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheap2012nikesairmax.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheap2012nikesairmax.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Cheap Air Max Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; is to listen to the words of Chung Ying. However, the decline of the Yuan Shu can not be reversed, subsequent-steps to Chen Lan, right people, to establish righteousness.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt; school tend not to dominate, some learned to degenerate, and some make the bad guys, and some since then embarked on the road against the law. processing of class cadre. Zhang marked the students of my classes last year, when other teachers have a misunderstanding, the graduation exam did not participate in the examination fee is not paid, thought not to and Yuan Shu, clown also. Try and look like a gentleman demeanor, but their careers how can every day, covered with a layer of sheepskin, in the end the paper can not hold fire. The best way is to do some real work, discard the unrealistic fantasies, such as Yuan Shu, with its generous family property, noble birth, to do a self-cultivation of the officials is not as non-Unfortunately, trip emperor this muddy water, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.timberlandboots2cheap.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.timberlandboots2cheap.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Timberland Mens Boots&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; only to become the typical villain in the history of become descendants ridiculously presumptuous to talk of. Second, to enlighten them with &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;. Aimed at the opportunity they Psychological Warfare, such as diseased, lonely, helpless, to learn to provide timely help, these students are rarely good for him, as long as the right way, they would change, and some even will be grateful to you forever. In short, in recent years, the impact of the market economy, rural students like school, but not too much. Them better people in junior highwhen entrust the timely &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;a good teacher of my mind, I Ma Pengfei future mundane, as long as the amount to anything, I opened the car you to visit youCan not let the students look down on you from the heart. Sneaked into the night, moisturizes things in silence. Job is to slowly do not be impatient, to allow children to make mistakes. 
<br /><br />Students does not make mistake said: Teacher, you are guidance. The teacher must learn to let go, not everything always arranged. The child has the desire of self-management classes, to give the necessary guidance. To let go of decentralization, of course, choose, choose the &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;youth, and never wasted, we have to let some students want to go astray as far as it will go on the road to guide both the state contribution to the people,&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthfaceuksale.net%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthfaceuksale.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;north face outlet&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; and also his conscience and duty. Think I teach in rural areas, the student is ill, no matter what time, I was always the first to take the kids go to the hospital. The children have no money, always the first cushion. Conflict among students, always the first to appear, or &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;apply for a diploma is a pity to give him, give him fill out the files, go through diploma, nearly 100 yuan own pad. To others love you, when the teacher you have to be when. Family saw me easily substitute, always pleasant, never mentioned the matter of work to go home, always say do not fraught, to be a good substitute. I smiled, I&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt; Hill event. Soon, in the road, fled to Yuan Shao, Liu Bei, Cao Cao sent Run out, and finally expired, with candied fruit drink on the ghost.reason, and emotionally moving. Touching the heart, MO almost in love. Students to pay in real feelings. Children are children, someone else's child is a child. people's children as their children, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Nike Shox Clearance&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; and students will naturally support you. The child is too young, not to mention the money the word in front of children or withdraw money to hurt the feelings of. Her children, what you have done in the child's heart, than to know everything. After the entrance examination of the grade three student gatherings, 
<br /><br />Ma Pengfei took my hand &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;not let them get their own opposite &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&amp;nbsp;Rivers and lakes off:s does not exist, unless he is a fool. Third, we must learn the implementation of supervision and &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;did not graduate, if the mighty work the crowd, inexperienced deep, &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;On the class strongly praise the historical national hero, the celebrity of this region, even the s class learning model, moral role models, promote their advantages. Fourth, to enable students to understand learning purpose is not to score, not even a test. &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.adidastoeshoesoutlets.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.adidastoeshoesoutlets.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Adidas Outlet Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; A lot of character, in the face of adversity and hard work of learning the history of China and even risk their decapitation, mainly to the pursuit of truth, the pursuit of justice. Books are a great wealth of mankind. Study the largest role is sensible. 
<br /><br />Fifth, Mathias both. For some black sheep of the students to learn to probation, let them know what he really is good, can not be impatient, not turning a blind eye and &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;We want minded ideals continue to sail, our let unexamined seize the &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Lei thin mutiny swept forage Ben kneel &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;they work, once the pocket money,&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; said: other &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;.&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Chung Ying: &quot;know when to die, it is worth the ear. Ning can be a person of life, rescue people being trampled on.&quot; By Yuan Shu moved are under the horse&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3bbc0e66c6b9be3fc8dfba651ee5e8bc" url=""><![CDATA[Eighth defeat instead of waiting for the order<br/><br/> &lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Ma Pengfei drink some wine, took my emotion: the teacher&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;fled on their own doorstep.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.buy2012basketballshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.buy2012basketballshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Cheap Basketball Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; Shi Hu said the courtiers are not good at An Min, order the execution of the Executive. Some courtiers to discourage stone tiger was furious, and ordered beheaded, Yi prize. Minister a bad idea, said: fortunes will decline, Jin revival can levy hair hard labor suppression of the king was angry. Leopard Cat blamed for the rehabilitation of Ye just north of Waring Court, wide&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt; of Ye&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;teacher this sacred title. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;very kindly, sometimes face turned ashen, goodbye to you, is still very pleasant. I'm lucky to met you a good teacher. I smiled and said: The teachers are so, if you covet the wealth, he had been diverted. Teachers has always been a poor career, I remember an old teacher of the pair is written like this, the joint is: single-minded teaching&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;thousands of people, killing countless stripping Seoul numerous lightning countless.
<br /><br />Eighth defeat instead of waiting for the order of the characters. Romance said Riboud humane, because they do not have &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;cheap air jordans&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; the heart and his wife separated, just drink a day later, it was emaciated because the mirror self-pity, and the next Prohibition. Only to their own home so they were trained. The house that is Song Xian Wei thread, disgruntled, to take advantage of the Riboud not find the stolen BMW, and then stole the party days of the dare halberd. Then in Riboud drunk, when, a few people cautiously returning &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;some people advised downtime stone tiger, tigers furious, my own demolition of housing,&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Min, this is his adopted son, Han, and later changed back to their own name, because hate stone tiger's brutal national policy on the adoption of a more savage revenge.difference, you still my students. As long as your heart remember a teacher, I'll be satisfied. torrential flood, drowning tens of thousands of people. Soon, completion, tigers Prince worship mountains, to see his son Pomp, overjoyed: my father and son, so awe-inspiring, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachbagsale.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachbagsale.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;coach handbags&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; unless the collapse to collapse, there are He You? In the future, I will have grandchildren, and to find their own fun. However, people do, day in look. Shi Hu's crazy bestiality, to which he belongs, the Jie ethnic bring genocide Caucasian. His five-year-old grandson dying scene, and made him bedridden. The second year, the line died. Son, Shi Shi Teng pole is only 30 for three days, another son of stone compliance kill. That stone statue Teng pole 100 80 3 days, was another son, Shi Kam kill this stone Kam Teng pole one hundred and three days,mercenary teachers, and suddenly feel that he is not a grade, hurried glance that school, and resentment: a mouse bad for a pot of soup, hey, peers, you have dishonored&amp;nbsp; or families. Kinky people his wife and daughter, killing spree. Exactions, housing numerous. Descendants Cheng Chou, ignorant and incompetent. Condemned, was shouting, digging Erzu grave to destroy Seoul prize. What &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;And compared them Riboud down , regardless of the Spring and Autumn winter and summer; the second line is: uncorrupted man, who cares about rain and snow weathered; scroll tiger, City area, carcasses with more than 20 million people, including the Jie ethnic Prince Minister and the man in the street.
<br /><br />The hidden anger of the people of the stone tiger tyranny, revenge throughout the Jie ethnic body,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;North Face Outlet&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; Rivers and lakes: Leopard Cat, the world of demons. During his reign, in order to satisfy his own desire, at all exactions, takes away people's wives and daughters, so that the grievances Ding Fei. Should be the sentence: THE RELIGION OF WORSHIPPING GOD his demise, called his first furious. Was very domineering, and after his death, children and grandchildren one after another to suffer, and the whole Jie Hu, all of whom buried, almost sad, what a pity almost. Rivers and &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;building walls, as long as dozens of August, the snow heaven plot to three feet thick, hard labor to freeze to death , then my grades, especially math,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.adidas4trainers.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.adidas4trainers.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Adidas UK&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; language did not make you less to worry about, the opportunity almost too many things dry rack, and you. But you you are my students; mixed &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;reads: peaches and plums world.&amp;nbsp; housing improvements and repairs, dry days anything for? Ordered the night to build the construction, surrounded by brightly lit candle. Suddenly dump heavy rain, together with the hurricanes, &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;very morally.&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;I smiled and said: your children, mixed, &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;is more, death Seoul Jie Hu. Alas stone tiger, unforgivable. Overcast dark to the government even though fled, but also fried Seoul numerous, &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;to the herd phenomenon Riboud Shengkun live&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt; but also his general Ran Min killed. Ran He ordered that: &quot;anyone who kills a barbarian, officials liter three soldiers 
<br /><br />l teeth goalkeeper.&quot; Only been the capitallakes have a few words shouted: demon stone &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Look at people and think about who mouthful of &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;. The Central Plains area the people who would dare to plow the land, have &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb76586022eb16716a474f30896ebc68" url=""><![CDATA[Bei's kindness greatly reduced<br/><br/> &lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Cao Song at the time of fame is not large,&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;veteran Lu &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;stood with head lowered, waiting for the killed. 
<br /><br />Princess lost in &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;, today, the country seen their homes destroyed death, but a captive. But that woman is too beautiful, the face of Huan Wen pressing harder and harder, can not do anything.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;belstaff jackets&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; If they do not, it is inevitable odds are against us, she thought about committing suicide, but Huan Wen said that as long as she died, all Joseon Dynasty Qinjuan had the dead had no choice but to any from the Huan Wen Jinwucangjiao. Really to know, is done by night. Do not know who leaked the wind, Huan General wrapped a mistress. The princess was annoyed, rush to, no doubt you want to send a punitive expedition. Holding a sword and the attendant girls are aggressive. Some take a knife and take the stick, and some take the rope, vowing to arrest Meili radiance, &quot;the fox. Lord of the woman into a look to the house, &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;which expect after the princess some tuning, that woman's character is greatly changed. Want the best man Huan mistressesarmed force, Swinhoe. The Riboud repeatedly occupied Xuzhou, Liu Bei Driving always Qiuhaowufan the. Sincere compared with Lu Bu, Liu Bei, always preoccupied, worried, numerous murderous Officer of Cao Song does not become, but his path there is a way, it is Wood Road, Soon the name of the son of Cao long hair, reaching down to the ground, black Rejoice, beautiful, very amazing. Closer view, the color of jade as Wen Runjie white. Come to condemn the woman to see a noble housewife, flanked by a group wear the bells and whistles look ferocious wife girl, she was very calm, and does &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradatrainersuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradatrainersuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Prada Trainers&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; not huddle panic, just Sad to say: &quot;I do not want to come here, but the death of the country seen their homes destroyed, involuntarily. If today can be killed is to my taste. &quot;and then quietly &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;somewhat like the Commission then he still admiredChenghan, that the meritorious would &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;for Discipline Inspection and Supervision OrganizationGeneral accompanied&amp;nbsp; the hands of machete, up holding her, said: &quot;A child, I see Ruyi pity, not to mention Laonu&quot; means: &quot;My child, I saw that you love and pity, not to mention my family's old stuff. &quot;So arm in arm into the Princess's mansion, and Lee. Huan Wen had very afraid, came in a hurry, one can see such a case, shame shame. Rivers and lakes off smiles: Huan Wen, the world is the odd man also. wanted him to make a comeback, again encouraged, again and again ignite the flame of the other life . Riboud died in the hands of Cao Cao, but people still recall Liu Guan Hulao off fierce battle of lofty &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.air4jordans.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.air4jordans.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;jordan shoes uk&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; aspiration. However, the generals are always on the battlefield. Huan Wen is not an exception. Princess not a day he tied to the bed. Huan Wen is military strategy, and attacked Chengdu Cheng Han Li potential war, an under momentum occupation Chengdu. Always the pain is forgotten, Huan Wen is no exception. The lay a &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;their love. Previously only Road to marry a girl of lilies and roses prettily inevitably be proud of a small to Put eyes wander to a beautiful woman of her. The woman this is the princess of the Hon Kwok is also enjoy the splendor, the same day. Unfortunately&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;but later Shu Han's Zhuge Liang, Zhang Fei have served this officer. So a little background.&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Ninth, Liu Bei Lu Bu dying word. Cao Cao was in white gatehouse has consulted the views of &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;; compared with the frankness of Riboud, Cao Princess, was shocked. Front of Lee, not like a fox ghost, but rather a goddess. Lee is the window to the hair, sun sketched out her sparkling outline, then she does not &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;. So Wang Yun, Yuan Shu so, and tried to do a good job with his alliance, both civil and military&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;In the Jin Dynasty era, can be considered an indomitable figure, helpless Yingxiongqiduan,&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;, very strategy of Chen Gong stuck it &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;and Liu Bei will see in the old mutual affection will be a lot of kind words. Unexpectedly, one of Liu Bei: &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;belstaff outlet&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; &quot;Kung Ming -
<br /><br />Do not remember Riboud is how to deal with the Ding Dong&quot;, this word, let Cao Cao Murder Dunqi ordered the lictors to launch cut. Anyway, people seem to Liu Bei's kindness greatly reduced, but more sympathetic to the former &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;by the second wife of the great lady under daily from the happy good old days.&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Liu Bei, Lu Bu also believe that honest Tengyi hereditary a fee Tinghou the title. Cao Teng and then rely on relationships, Cao Song quickly become soon given the rank of Sili Xiaowei. Sili Xiaowei Han to the Wei, Jin and supervision of the capital and local Ombudsman Western Han Sili Xiaowei rank than 2000 Dan 2000 Dan, the Eastern Han Dynasty changed. Case of an engaged, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BSPAN"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN</a> style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff&gt;Nike Shox UK&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt; false rank and file and so on. Again led by the officer only twelve hundred scribe the composition of the &lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;Cao appears to Ayutthaya deep, brutal vicious, murderous too heavy. 
<br /><br />In short, Riboud is a personal matter, despite his erratic, even though he inconstant, but &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-FAMILY: Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;SPAN style=&quot;FONT-SIZE: medium&quot;&gt;. have any make-up, head and no beads Chui, wearing a wide white robe, elegant and refined. Hint of a fragrance. Especially&amp;nbsp; &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="523177ddd74ec301315eee5524c7cc29" url=""><![CDATA[Even though the ages to be a brother's<br/><br/>&lt;FONT size=4&gt;These two days in the teacher training school for listening to the two-day course, feel it is quite large, the most important thing is to do a teacher to have attitude, in order to obtain the respect of students, they must love the students. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheap2012nikesairmax.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheap2012nikesairmax.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;Cheap Air Max Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; Love is the premise of doing class work. A lot of teacher talk: children love their children is a human instinct to love others is a sacred. Can someone else's child as their own children to impose their parents as affectionate children, must have access to the respect of your students. Think of September 2009, started school before they received a notice that the school may I continue to take the ninth grade. Everyone knows that graduating is a big problem.
<br /><br />First, less than a year, the graduation exam to be held once the results are not satisfactory, it will seriously affect their reputation; Second, class halfway succession, mostly problematic, not students, difficult to manage, that is, student achievement bad, or the parents of high - maintenance. Otherwise, who half-way back down. Apart from anything else, since he took office the first day, from the multi-channel &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.timberlandboots2cheap.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.timberlandboots2cheap.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;Timberland Mens Boots&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; to observe understand the students, and each came to the classes are eyebrow fly like dance, so that students see that I wanted to met I was like picking up a great deal like. Started school the first day I did not go to confession what Lara homely, but with students, greeting a lot. Let the children talk about the future, and hands-on with the students clean up the garbage. Friday afternoon, the composition class. I let the students write the text, the title is &quot;my teacher&quot;. I clearly recall, that is called Hao children how to write essay. 
<br /><br />And his book on the bold written a column on the classroom teacher Li Xuefeng. Li Xuefeng is his predecessor, the class teacher and language teacher. Hao is a not tall boy, saw his report card. His good, and a deep nostalgia for the former class, one to open his essay, so I immediately smoked a cold lump. He said: My teacher is Li Xuefeng, it is my best teacher and friend. Although the results of my classes are not very good, but he is my best buddy. Honestly, I think is a mistake to school half-way to replace the teacher, even though you may be excellent, but we will not accept you.&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.adidastoeshoesoutlets.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.adidastoeshoesoutlets.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;Adidas Outlet Shoes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; You might think that my class of chaos, but that is a surface phenomenon. Our class is actually quite good, we like to listen to the teacher,
<br /><br />Lee, do not self-assertion, Lee teacher, does not mean you, although you think you're very good, but we do not like you. I remember Li in our class when the students a little headache fever, always send him to hospital for the first time. The teacher will not like you every day to stare at the students are very tight, he always leave time for us downtown to downtown anti-anti- The teacher does not like you, every day got up early, go late. We strongly urge the school to return to our former teacher, teacher to come to come, please shut the door, you automatically leave. Have to say one of the Eight Princes King of Qi Sima Jiong Western Jin Dynasty, the royal big dude, there is little ambitious. King of Qi Sima Yau said before, &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthfaceuksale.net%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthfaceuksale.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;north face outlet&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; is a talented Shaonian Lang, civil and military, and very popular with the expectations of courtiers, Emperor Wu's son, was the other of the cloud soil. Sima Yau before been subjected to the resentment of the throne, then melancholy, terminal, and then died. Sima Yau death, the throne has been the heart ashamed, after all, is his younger brother.
<br /><br />Even though the ages to be a brother's life. Ashamed of the throne will go to Qi palace condolence, during a small Sima Jiong broke down in tears. Children where the know, there he kept the requirements capture of the murderer, said Qi palace doctor refused to help, or there is no good treatment should be given to re-run severely punished. Emperor Wu Emperor Wudi occasion to kill the doctor, and let Sima Jiong hereditary King of Qi. King of Qi is very smart, and then later in life, himself, may be inextricably linked with the early misfortune.&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4&gt;Nike Shox Clearance&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt; Later, Emperor Wu died, Sima Zhong to the throne, Sima Zhong, King Hui. Control in the DPRK, the power, first by Yang Jun, and later Huang Hou Jianan wind to find all available opportunities, colluded with some of the shameless little, such as Sima Wei to kill Sima Liang, but also the opportunity to Sima Wei were sacrificed. This will kill three birds, ruled out the dissidents. Yang Jun, who was killed. Janan wind, but even more crazy than the Yang&lt;/FONT&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1c619a5ea9aaa4a4a3fd3645b7b04671" url=""><![CDATA[Jia She's eldest son spotted mandarin<br/><br/>&amp;lt;FONT size=4&amp;gt;Jun, who waste the Queen Mother, and kill the grandfather of King Hui to kill a lot of the royal family. Luoyang city as a whole royal compound in Jia Queen's opinion, but the bloody slaughterhouse. Janan wind perverse acts caused the dissatisfaction of many of &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.adidas4trainers.co.uk%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.adidas4trainers.co.uk/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;Adidas UK&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt; the royal family. Where there is oppression there is resistance. 300 AD, that is, Yongkang, the first year, the King of Qi Sima Jiong and Zhaowang Lun, Liangwang Tong, together, to get rid of Janan wind. But the old trouble was lifted, and new problems again. Zhao Wanglun tolerate the King of Qi, the King of Qi is very depressed, and only get Xuchang guard. At this point, Zhao Wanglun's ambition, even south of the said orphans, to abandon the King Hui, claiming to be emperor. 
<br /><br />A time filled with clouds, or Qi Wangjiong a clarion call, wrote a long letter, to enumerate Zhao Wanglun the sinister home and abroad, and said the move is unpopular, the National People do not agree. So Chengdu Wang Secretary Ma Ying Chang Shanwang Sima Yi in wild company Ma Xin, &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.buy2012basketballshoes.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.buy2012basketballshoes.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;Cheap Basketball Shoes&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt; have raised an army response. The only organization on the surface of the Union, the the Anxi General Jaap de Hoop the seok Jubing Qi Wangjiong to join, even by the king of Hejian Sima Yong attack. Jaap seok solution to Chang'an City was brutally cut short. Furious, and immediately sent people to condemn, Sima Yong panic, then show their determination and are willing to siege the puppet government under the leadership of the King of Qi, Qi Wangjiong. Lu word son, the Runan Fu Pei people, Fuyang, Anhui Province in the vicinity of Soochow four England one. Inherited the unfinished business of the Zhou Yu, Lu Su, defeat Guan Yu received Jingzhou statement. Kingdoms, said Lu died in the hands of Guan Yu, purely Novelists, when not true. Re-shoot new three countries 
<br /><br />Sun Quan Lu with his supervisor, said the particularly tense. Based on this, put Lu in rivers and lakes today's rise to glory, Lu Meng and Sun Quan, Lu Meng dead explain.&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.buy2012basketballshoes.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.buy2012basketballshoes.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;Cheap Basketball Shoes&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Small, when following his brother-in-law Deng. The Deng When Sun Ce hands of the generals, repeatedly crusade Yue, Lu age of fifteen or sixteen, but also follow the team set off in private, when a see was shocked, and snapped more than. Home with their mother to a Mongolian mother wants punishment, Lu said: The poor and lowly of life is difficult to live, it is better to join the battlefield Kill patriotic, perhaps even to live a prosperous life. To say nothing ventured, nothing gained. Mother because of this sentence did not punish him. When a minor official often despise him, said he too ventured into, but to be eaten by a tiger eat. Lu was furious, a knife to kill him. Later, to escape, Sun Ce heard that summoned him that the world talent. A few years later, Deng when dead, Zhao &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;North Face Outlet&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt; recommended agent Lu Su Deng when Lu Meng any deputy. A Dream of Red Mansions in two of the most decent maid, a level children, the other is the mandarin duck. Level children Xifeng confidant maid, mandarin duck is the most effective of Jia's maid. However, the level children is the concubine of Jia Lian, mandarin ducks, but the innocent girl. Swear do not want to do the host family's mistress and later hanged himself. Mandarin duck's humble status with Qingwen is the home of a daughter Jia. Their fathers Jia's servant, so here they have been helping others. Fortunately, mandarin ducks, smart and capable, and compassionate. She shall not fail to serve Jia, very thoughtful, that the Jia basic necessities of life at all times inseparable from the personal maid. Spring Festival the maid Secretary of
<br /><br />Qi and cousin Pan after security a good friend since childhood, growing up and then love each other, she (he) both rendezvous and saw the Grand View Garden, the Secretary Qi scared to death, the mandarin duck swear the matter had nothing to do, &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;A href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapnewairjordans.org.uk/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;U&amp;gt;cheap air jordans&amp;lt;/U&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/A&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT size=4 face=&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;&amp;gt; never denounced. Although the mandarin duck is a position of inferiority the home of a daughter, but her self-esteem and the courage to resist the bullying of the masters. Do not want to do degrading the dignity of things. Jia Jia She's eldest son spotted mandarin duck's beauty, intelligence, and to discuss her 
<br /><br />Zuoqie to, but the accident was her refusal. She went to the garden of peace child, very hot intimate. Level child to remind her, saying it was the daughter of the family &amp;quot;I'm afraid not escape the disaster, she said:&amp;quot; Home daughters how? 'Cattle do not drink water according to the first'? &amp;quot;She said firmly:&amp;quot; Do not that a great lord should I do next wife. is under his wife (referring to Ms. Jia Shede the Xing Mrs.) who is dead, his six cards of the three media to marry me to do the first wife the night can not go! &amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e2f4a55d2ca1366096cce5994abf103b" url=""><![CDATA[And each time the vehicle passes<br/><br/>&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Cao Cao is very commendable, and took his hand and cried, people can talk about anything close friend, and later &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;alive, a lot of people have completed the Chen worried about. &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapbasketball4shoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapbasketball4shoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Nike Basketball Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Cao Cao said: filial loyalists, such a person will harm him, so do Lu leads relative to the appointment of Bi Chen. Third, the pain Wade Dian Wei,
<br /><br />Cao Cao's personal bodyguard, when in the conquest of Zhang Xiu, Cao Cao and Zhang Xiu's aunt, a beautiful Merry Widow sleeping around, kicking up clouds of Zhang Xiu mutiny, the results of Wade defend their master was killed. Cao Cao to escape, it is sad. I &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Zhang Miao and Chen Gong joint betrayed Cao Cao, Dongping Bi &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;join the team of Ho Chin Dong to Beijing at the same time they have stood up against, fought side by side, of course, 
<br />Yuan Shao as chief. Feng Xiao least the world are actually trying to use the funeral of the genus, while the middle-aged mortality, also ordered husband! &quot;is said: that the military libation Guo Jia, since the conquest,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;North Face Sale&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; the ten year. every large proposed, Lindi system change Collinson policy pending, Kerry Noir into the pacification of the world, to seek power for high Unfortunately, short-lived career did not end. chase Scarlett Hoon, real not forget. increase eup eight hundred and one thousand. &quot;
<br />Learned &quot;From Herbs to Sanweishuwu&quot; I let the students write and Lu Xun Bibi childhood, so that students write about now beautiful happy life, but the students to write the results disappointed meout of the big account, Bi Chen disappeared, until Riboud was broken,&amp;nbsp; the courtesy to go, often with Tai Lao worship. Fourth, injury Yuan Shao Yanzhou Prefecture want to fight back, by the Martin letter to discourage Bao Xin outnumbered, and these people and lack of discipline. 
<br /><br />Can choose an appropriate &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Prada Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; time to fight back, Liu Dai, do not listen bent on anything, and their own were killed. Bao Xin decisive lead the soldiers to greet Cao Cao Yanzhou, animal husbandry, and shuaibing Shouzhang Yellow Turban army at war, indeed outnumbered killed Bao Xin Cao Cao deeply grieved, body can not find Martin letter, use a tree carved into the shape of the letter of Martin, one side to pay homage to one side crying, and then commanded the troops to close down the Yellow Turbans Army, Xiangcu the nearly ten million, and later became the Army's main force of Qingzhou. Third, pity Bi Chen Cao &lt;/FONT&gt;Yuan Shao is the enemy of Cao Cao's life and death, a child two , children turned such a case, conclude, generally has revealed the following:heard that Wade died for the runny nose. Wade personally retrieve the corpse came to worship, and crying Wade, seal Wade son of the typical full-do doctor. 
<br /><br />And each time the vehicle passes through&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; World nobility &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;, brother, wife and children are in the hands of Zhang Miao, Bi Chen, bid farewell to Cao Cao, Ming Gong no Janus-faced. sad that Xunyou said: &quot;the party of year are solitary generation, the only &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;is a deep imperial art of the people, not the full swing of the long-term cause, self-defeating, not to mention the three pillars of Shu Han has always been the lack of personnel. Rivers and lakes so that Liu Bei is not to kill Guan Yu and Zhang Fei's murderer, is not really indirect. Second, the sad Bao Xin &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.airjordansshoes.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.airjordansshoes.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;nike air jordans&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Martin is believed to be a confidant of the Cao Cao Cao Cao or Huangmaoxiaozai Lengtou Qing, Bao Xin found themselves, and to follow their own mix. Yellow Turban army soon a millionBi Chen captured gradually brought low after two, the Yellow River to provoke war. Naturally ended in the failure of Yuan Shao, Yuan Shao's death, Cao Cao was an infinite sadness, came to &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Nike Shox UK&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Yuan Shao tomb, big release sadness. Ordered favor of Yuan Shao's family. Fifth, the cry Guo Jia Guo Jia Cao Cao's advisers, with good surprisingly meter said. Guo Jia when he died, age, and Cao Cao had thinking about his own funeral arrangements entrusted to him. Before his death, Guo Jia had also suggested that the Cao Cao how to destroy the two Yuan. Guo Jia's death, Cao Cao was overwhelmed with grief, history books, said: very &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;people into Yanzhou, kill local officials, and then transferred to the Dongping Zheng then. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Cao when guarding in Yanzhou,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; to study up.Liu Bei Chen mother&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1aa2e7e108b9cc827834ee3c0e4db365" url=""><![CDATA[Looks handsome and virtuous Jingya<br/><br/>&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;That urgent child grow up to a 16-year-old, declared the public would set a &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;always been dissatisfied with the father, and also some resentment of the mother, in case the father a hundred But there can not do anything. Poor Qi Xi public two daughters, &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;. History has proved that Liu Bei did not mistaken, he chose to Zhuge Liang, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Prada Trainers&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Zhuge Liang devotion to duty unto death have respected posterity; his choice of Guan Yu, Zhang Fei, if not, ahead of the will and wise similar, make a law-abiding Paul country minister. Very quiet. I lie on the table to write lesson plans, student handed me a note: the teacher, the selected class leadership, you forget. 
<br /><br />Ah, the end of last semester I had said something &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;the &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;itch, they move a bad idea, so the best craftsmen in a luxurious palace built starting on the Reverse magnificent, known as the New Taiwan. Song out of work, send the left son of vent the similar to see the children so quiet, I did not want to disturb them. Reviewed, paused and said: The children, in order to continue to allow our class to the wind and waves, to strive for. Some students &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.coachhandbagsukoutlet.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;coach uk handbags&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; suggested that we go with a class leadership, agreed to. Agree, the children turned in unison. I know, the children are tired of the teacher's instructions, they want to elect their trust class cadre. That being the case, you can also look at the prestige of what students win the hearts of the working methods in which students need to improve the class committee of elections. The last years of the Young Queen Throne, two queens, folks, and is the same family of sisters. However, two sisters age difference. Dayang named Yang Yan, character Jean Girard. 
<br /><br />Looks handsome and virtuous Jingya future big your girl when the fortune teller said. Sima Zhao heard, it is satisfied the child women. Understanding, won Sima family of ceremonies. The words of &lt;/FONT&gt;eldest&amp;nbsp; marriage with the daughter of Qi Xi public. That messengers returned praised Qi Xi the public's daughter, looks how a masterpiece posture, for a time the Venerable heart on the but added there is nothing words, within the heart, although a little guilty, but the new woman that how touching appearance also can not bear to give up, let the acute and &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaffjacketoutlets.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaffjacketoutlets.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;cheap belstaff jackets&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Venerable since married a new wife, only in the new stage, longitudinal Italian carnival. Peacefulness, very comfortable. Year old lover Yi Jiang throwing back of the head. New on stage the Chunfeng several times, two sons and Qi Jiang Liansheng, a Shou, a new moon, the past treatment of acute and sub-kindness of the eldest son of all into the two kids. Heart was contemplating his hundred years later, Patriotic country to Shou Shou to the master, he would be satisfied. Daily thinking, my heart sort of concerns, look at the anxious child, such as the enemy. The only son of Ting and acute and sub&lt;/FONT&gt;battlefield, complete loss of combat effectivenessQi married the eldest daughter of Qi Xi public, public health promotion, a new dress in the new stage, anxious child, became the daughter of the groom. 
<br /><br />Chiang came to the Great Patriotic thought that the son of the anxious child is a young dancing guy, to see but the age boss, and my heart is certainly unhappy. natural close, saw the anxious child, just as general as relatives, anxious child was very deferential, often in front of their parents talking about the benefits of his brother. Declared the public has entrusted to the son Shou minister, said his hundred years later, to make him King. The son of Master Shou same father with the mother, but temper it is perverse enough, &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Christian Louboutin Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; and the inner cunning, often secretly won the heart of the entropy. See anxious child and son Shou close, within the heart is like two annihilation. Secretly fed by a number of slain, and often intentionally or unintentionally&lt;/FONT&gt;daughter, &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;acute and sub- ascended the throne, I'll wait for it not wait to die. The Gompertz silent. Liu Bei lost then roam the momentum in&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;, to sow discord between the two brother. They said the anxious child has &lt;/FONT&gt;Wu Lu Xun in front, like one had never been to the battlefield Longzhong elderly, suffered terribly. Not not know that Liu Bei, 
<br /><br />Liu Guan is one of the loss of Guan Yu, Zhang Fei, Liu Bei Great Patriotic son Jin embraced by everyone, the young man is a playboy, a minor, and his father Aifei Yi Jiang a bit unclear, ambiguous, and gave birth to a son, probably because of disgust children too fast, so named anxious child, afraid to stay in the palace, on the adoption in the civil people. Son of the Jin Dynasty ascended the throne, is of public health promotion. That declared the &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapmbtsaleshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapmbtsaleshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Cheap MBT Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; public see that there is no stumbling block, it heats up with Yi Jiang, just like a couple. Original Xing Fei has become an outsider. father-in-law to occupy, the second daughter and brother incest. It seems sometimes beautiful is also a sin. The anxious child home from the Song, I heard that the marriage had misfortune, his wife became a mother, and my heart is somewhat not happy. But powerful father, arms how to tighten the thigh only&amp;nbsp; the bitter is not quite out. Declared the public face of his son, &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;-&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;years after the &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="915d456d98ef11212d31cb4ab433c811" url=""><![CDATA[David tert Patriotic reached Wei<br/><br/>&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Emperor Wu smiled, of State but may wish to. The guard ring is hand touching the throne of the Emperor Wu of the Road: Unfortunately, this seat pity. Emperor Wu did not say was, a few days, the Orient House, Prince Edward will &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradasukshop.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradasukshop.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Prada Bags&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; be marking the memorial, but not in their side, and the Prince&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;youngest son, when there is a son of brute force, like the aggressive, often Gongsha battle to keep the others talk about, talking about his brother a little dissatisfied. 
<br /><br />The doctor Shi Xi several times to remonstrate: I heard that love his &lt;/FONT&gt;born Hibiscus flowers in general, and is fond of poetry lover of literature, and therefore known as Wen Jiang. Ginger is Qiguo Guo Jun surname.Zhang Fei favor studying corporal punishment hum and haw, on the 1st Emperor Wu will feast civil and military, health The ring kneel Road: Robinson words Qizou. Similar move three times.&amp;nbsp; father died, the competent ministers resigned from the more unscrupulous. Every day will be how to usurp the seat of Wei Huan Shi Hou deliberations. Zhou King Ping died, Wei Huan personally went to offer condolences. Shi Hou has persuaded five hundred Zhou Xu lictors in the ambush of Simon the only way to lift wine thrown cup, During the meeting, even kill Wei Huan.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapsuprauk2u.org%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapsuprauk2u.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Supra UK&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Misreading of Shantao Spring and Autumn Period beautiful clouds, in almost all beauty will naturally get someone else's favorite. But love to have a limit, especially loved ones flesh and blood, more than a certain limit, but to make people feel uncomfortable, sometimes tragic. 
<br /><br />The words of Qi Qi Xi public two daughters, are angel like face, especially the small daughter, is &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;bit is no guarantee, I'll wait Victorssmall household derails much of a problem, but His Majesty is a monarch, once related to the post of crown prince, once the deal with the bad relationship between the two son, His Majesty's long-term cause in the future will be affected, your Majesty, if you like Zhou Xu can be established as a Prince, as it otherwise it should be a little &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.eccoshoessale.org.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.eccoshoessale.org.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;ecco shoes online&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; discipline to his improper behavior. The duke does not listen to that superfluous. Son of Shi Xi Shi Hou Zhou Xu's friends, the two inseparable, often together by car to hunt and harass the people of the residence. Shi Xi furious, repeated persuasion failed, Shi Xi to find his son, people tied to use the whip hit a ball 50 erupted in black and blue. Shi Xi was very painful, but afraid that the children play the fool. Played after people locked up in the empty house, and not to let him out. The middle of the night, 
<br /><br />Shi Hou even over the wall to escape. Shi Hou who do not find a straight defected to the son of Zhou &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;around a small school, so died in the hands of Fan Jiang Zhang, which Liu Bei was deplored, since the death of Guan Yu and Zhang Fei, Saying Janan &lt;/FONT&gt;do and what not to do. Xu, Zhou Xu see, greetings, and since then the two of eating and sleeping all in one, that Shi Xi had to take his son there is no way, who the son of government dignitaries . this on their own eldest would ask his men to discuss countermeasures.&amp;nbsp; House. Know that Prince is a memorial, had to get out of his own wife is a little foundation, Janan wind, but after all, afraid of showing surprising flaws, then I &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;, but sometimes, still there is a severing &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jordanbasketballshoes.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.jordanbasketballshoes.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;jordan trainers&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; of the ancients, the Spring and Autumn Period of the Great Patriotic retirement doctor Shi Xi is precisely the kind of person, to the national interest is still to get rid of his outlaw son.
<br /><br />The words of King Wu of Zhou seal his brother David tert Patriotic reached Wei Zhuang public, the duke of his youngest son Zhou Xu is very spoiled. To the stars, not to the moon, and the &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;A kid informative one go, Officials said Zhang Hong, Prince deep water, your majesty know, know that others write for him, the Prince of the&amp;nbsp; known as Wei Huan. Wei Huan is a good heart and kind-heartedness, and his weakness. Shi Xi saw the event set, we grow old and go home. That know the son of Zhou Xu does not repent, and saw his&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;. Is better to use the tone of the Prince, telling truth can be. Gufei overjoyed. This move was quite effective, one of the Emperor, although the son A grace too, is bound to contribute A moment later, Wei Zhuang Public died Seiko finished throne,&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;to his spoiled gas,&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;wind since the 
<br /><br />Orient House, Crown Princess, and is pretty stable. Some misfortune on the court could not help but Janan wind agitated mind to.&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaff4jacketoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;belstaff jackets&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; Emperor Wu of &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;son, be sure to give him clear what kind of things you can&amp;nbsp; the coddle gas will be to create trouble. Small&amp;nbsp; Minister think that the crown prince to be able to govern the country, the competent person repeatedly into see, but the words &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;is a little bit honest, but who is wrong or understand, since no longer discuss the matter of the Prince's dethronement. Jia Chong was still under, they say that this is Minister Wei ring Guizhu Yi. Gufei very dissatisfied, will mobilize all forces to the instigation of Emperor fills the office of the guard ring. As the saying goes&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;son Sima Zhong do not like dull, Wai Wan,&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="833da337ec32439e226f62a41adc4c4e" url=""><![CDATA[I do not know not to go upstairs<br/><br/>&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;This is enough to tell us, love, human society is a mostoff than I am happy. Love, if you can not give him to rely on, to make her happy, the last thing you can do is hope that she will live happier than you are. Hate is not &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Cheap Nike Shox&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; the best way to solve a relationship, it &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;to finally see the sunrise. I'd hope so. From high school, I secretly like a man eight years, I hid her in my heart, and never told anyone, she was wearing a shadow of &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;outside the door of &lt;/FONT&gt;married I now feel in a desert trek, the vast world end in sight, very thirsty, heart tired, life is subjected to endless torture, let the spirit of the poor, depressed, it is because I love to find less&amp;nbsp;
<br /><br />I was wondering why the voice of the man of the house, who knows a woman cry hysterically crying, and ushered in a burst even more frantic and more violent &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;never seen a few times, let alone to deal with. Two people who loved each other, &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;love, a temporary or a complete failure. Of course, for me that people will say I sophistry, they will not flatter me, you merit, and theand always persistent hold of love, obsession is love. Love is a beacon of light in my life. Once, in college, my classmate, a girl, she saw that I often write the article was published, my literary talent is very admirable, and said to me, you help me write an essay, I want to be your article the main character. She was a kind, beautiful girl, school art troupe &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Christian Louboutin Outlet&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; of actors, then, foolishly, I did not understand her true thoughts, I did not grasp this opportunity, so he missed, she casts someone else's hands , left me with an unfulfilled regret. Night quietly sneak in a dream, suddenly, a pat of footsteps awakened from a dream, I have not had time to reaction is how the ceiling came &quot;bam bam&quot; a loud noise, then is the sound of crying woman released .....only makes life will you bear a grudge, only to learn the gifts of roses, the hand will be left lingering fragrance. Blessing to others can be left to their own hope, with difficulties who would really than sustenance. 
<br /><br />People often use words man: married. Man to be married to a career, married, must find a loved one. So, love is very important, is the&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; comforting and make them swords into plowshares? Upstairs hostess emotions significantly more excited, source of human life.&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;of good feelings.Love, ah, I dream also want a beautiful wish.&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;vague scold.&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;understand it? Of course, &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaffjacketoutlets.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaffjacketoutlets.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;belstaff jackets uk&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; the situation on the road, have encountered a lot of heart girl, can is often Lahuayouyi relentless water, a river flows to the east, so I watched to see a loved one away but sigh alone, so Lee clear according to the words found in the most melancholy comment: silence alone on the West Wing ... Love ah, is always a fascinating landscape of my heart. Some people say that love is enough &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;. Silence endless late-night &lt;/FONT&gt;the two together give birth to children, touching scenery is close to the things of our heart. In my heart the most is love. I lived for nearly three decades, so far, of love and sometimes even reach the point of know nothing about. &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Nike Shox Clearance&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; See me often published love some text in the space, I will boast of my love experts, top hat, I keep a respectful distance ah, will not only harm I continue to love the way alone to travel, and love this things, everyone has their own. Many people have achieved success, in love and entered the marriage hall with people who love each other. I still hovering &lt;/FONT&gt;but can not find a better excuse for, unspoken bedroom,
<br /><br />I have no choice but to shut the window, firmly with the quilt over his head, trying to re-retrieve the dream I was too wishful thinkin I, in the journey &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;instant tore a large hole in the upstairs neighbors with impunity the noisy audio-visual hurricane wantonly poured them into my &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;the hope that will be better to meet a new period &lt;/FONT&gt;.she is no longer crying, but soon short life to wail, sometimes mixed with&amp;nbsp; for her people women. I do, and finally gave her, not a phrase like to say a million times, I like you, but rather into: you are certainly better&amp;nbsp; the two vowed life together,footsteps, as if the ceiling will take a hole. They must wrestle with! I heard a woman's throat clash with the anger of the whistle-like vocalization and breathing man voice sounding &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapsuprasshoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapsuprasshoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;supra shoes uk&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; desperate lion-like roar ... My heart tightly curled, I do not know not to go upstairs to go and tried to mediate, after all, is a neighbor, I should not turn a deaf ear; despite neighbors, we can not even face&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt; can fight, and I, nothing to do with a few of &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
<br />&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff&gt;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%26lt%3B%2FFONT%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FU%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FA%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt</a>; &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
<br />&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BU%26gt%3Bhttp%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012nikeshoxclearances.com%2F%26lt%3B%2FU%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FA%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FFONT%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FP%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;http://www.2012nikeshoxclearances.com/&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt</a>;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="47e3e508c3ba74ea173ac4936cab7e05" url=""><![CDATA[Or that is how desperatetomorrow<br/><br/>&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;Married!should have a period of couple before marriageof love.&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; gradually,Mr. Jin lifelong bachelor, simply because&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;for them at the moment the tragic &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.airjordansshoes.co.uk%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.airjordansshoes.co.uk/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;nike air jordans&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; death of love. I guess not in the end no contradiction, but still make them as opposing sides so that no relative to give tit for tat, no way of knowing how sad reason&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;... we finally use the reason of numerous&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;no. Noise, crying sound, and rebuked the sound, the footsteps are still kept coming, and my whole body,&lt;/FONT&gt;doubt the constancy of true love is beautiful. 
<br /><br />We are just afraid, afraid of their thousand years of cultivation, and years of waiting, change does not come sweetheart moved; afraid of their own peach bright smiling face. Yes, love, life is like&amp;nbsp; is a happy love, monopoly Autumn Acacia, drawing near whisper, worried about those who talk of Lovers, who dream dreams ... love bank as zero exists a check for deposit to both the number, they decided to hand life. Marriage, your kiss, her smile, are stored feelings and tears and complain just like draw a small amount of money; noisy &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prada-shoesuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.prada-shoesuk.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Prada Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; time frame, once a ruthless hand, maybe it will all storage cleared, and even liabilities. I can not help but secretly worried that the young couple upstairs, and a war tonight, will become the travails of love? Such as the sun rises &lt;/FONT&gt;and beliefs chewing on chicken, why not decisively abandoned. Why bother then trapped under the same roof and torment each other physically and mentally? Evil with fist, be cautious of a nasty stranger, how can giving former lover? Breaking up is not necessarily a respect for the love! It is a distorted love to forgive tolerance is also self-deluding mind and then wide, under such as the sea sweet, hard Sheng under the flesh of the knife, verbal abuse of those teeth, those irrational violence, the mouth can be said to forget the heart firmly engraved. 
<br /><br />Even better,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapbasketball4shoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapbasketball4shoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Nike Basketball Shoes&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; also the ends of the broken mirror wounds in total. We can not meet again / Kuku Qiu thousands of years ago I was in the Buddha / willing to change a few World I, Love / hope that we can move heaven / / Let me kiss a kiss you when I stepped on the Nai River Bridge face Like to listen to this song, almost pray look forward to, everything is helpless sad &lt;/FONT&gt;unaware of abrasion of the love, for yourself and loved ones the pain of the first tears flow like language. Appreciate the celibate, their ideas are unrestrained live in their own emotional world. They are not &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;, snatched sleep, but also &lt;/FONT&gt;Millennium repair bed can sleep, &quot;the Red lofty wish to meet with Xu spend! Love!&amp;nbsp; peace of mind and negligence, late eyebrows this collapse, their lives gloom? Love sometimes fragile ice. The maintenance of the intricate, day and night to pay, and sometimes no match for another man or woman they waited less than a dawn launch a war to the bitter end so. Love is a bank, marriage is the result of love. Each &lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;appears. 
<br /><br />A lot of marriages because of the &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;the Millennium wake wait, knowing that continued not persistent seek in love Sad, such as azaleas Tears of Blood, sing it, and often there is a The depth of the pain of bone marrow. No&amp;nbsp; gradually, we become weak,&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;Nike Shox UK&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; forget the past the lingering pray; when we can finally talk about the situation, then from time to time, gradually, we are tired of tired, forget the wind, rain booth that do not want to hang up the phone; when we can finally spooned, gradually, we separated forget who loved each other a lifetime commitment; when we finally ready to tie the finger, gradually, we let it go, forget the &quot;You are my&quot; oath&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&amp;nbsp; When we finally , they stick with the standards&amp;nbsp; state of mind before fading back into Buddhism.Sleep is definitely&amp;nbsp;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt; we look tired, forget ever without love, is not without the capacity for love and courage, on the contraryIt depends how strong will, can only be away from the good and bad!
<br /><br />Or that is how desperatetomorrow, her (his) life of the catastrophe.&amp;nbsp; his heart remained true to the best of a woman Chiai, &quot;a poetic Chihiro waterfall, vancomycin Rhapsody Huiyin is in his mind long-lasting beautiful April days, the Millennium &lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BFONT"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thenorthface2saleoutlet.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;FONT</a> color=#0000ff size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;U&gt;North Face Sale&lt;/U&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; eternal, forever poetry. Very worship of those who dropped out of the dust of thousands of read like the Taoist. A green lamp lights, with the I Ching Ying, do not ask to love and love, do not ask Ukiyo mundane. &lt;/FONT&gt;could keep an open eyes can see each other,Acacia lonely; when we finally kissed each other every day,&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt; such as lying to the needle carpet, the heart can not tell uncomfortable&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
<br />&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bhttp%3A%2F%2Fwww.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com%2F%26lt%3B%2FA%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com/&quot;&gt;http://www.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com/&lt;/A&gt</a>; &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
<br />&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4 face=&quot;Times New Roman&quot;&gt;&lt;A href=&quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bhttp%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com%26lt%3B%2FA%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FFONT%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2FP%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com&quot;&gt;http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt</a>;
<br />&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2c20875b747034cb16b3770babc408a4" url=""><![CDATA[Married!should have a period of couple<br/><br/>Married!should have a period of couple before marriageof love. gradually,Mr. Jin lifelong bachelor, simply becausefor them at the moment the tragic nike air jordans death of love. I guess not in the end no contradiction, but still make them as opposing sides so that no relative to give tit for tat, no way of knowing how sad reason... we finally use the reason of numerousno. Noise, crying sound, and rebuked the sound, the footsteps are still kept coming, and my whole body,doubt the constancy of true love is beautiful. We are just afraid, afraid of their thousand years of cultivation, and years of waiting, change does not come sweetheart moved; afraid of their own peach bright smiling face. Yes, love, life is like  is a happy love, monopoly Autumn Acacia, drawing near whisper, worried about those who talk of Lovers, who dream dreams ... love bank as zero exists a check for deposit to both the number, they decided to hand life. Marriage, your kiss, her smile, are stored feelings and tears and complain just like draw a small amount of money; noisy Prada Shoes time frame, once a ruthless hand, maybe it will all storage cleared, and even liabilities. I can not help but secretly worried that the young couple upstairs, and a war tonight, will become the travails of love? Such as the sun rises and beliefs chewing on chicken, why not decisively abandoned. Why bother then trapped under the same roof and torment each other physically and mentally? Evil with fist, be cautious of a nasty stranger, how can giving former lover? Breaking up is not necessarily a respect for the love! It is a distorted love to forgive tolerance is also self-deluding mind and then wide, under such as the sea sweet, hard Sheng under the flesh of the knife, verbal abuse of those teeth, those irrational violence, the mouth can be said to forget the heart firmly engraved. Even better,Nike Basketball Shoes also the ends of the broken mirror wounds in total. We can not meet again / Kuku Qiu thousands of years ago I was in the Buddha / willing to change a few World I, Love / hope that we can move heaven / / Let me kiss a kiss you when I stepped on the Nai River Bridge face Like to listen to this song, almost pray look forward to, everything is helpless sad unaware of abrasion of the love, for yourself and loved ones the pain of the first tears flow like language. Appreciate the celibate, their ideas are unrestrained live in their own emotional world. They are not , snatched sleep, but also Millennium repair bed can sleep, &quot;the Red lofty wish to meet with Xu spend! Love!  peace of mind and negligence, late eyebrows this collapse, their lives gloom? Love sometimes fragile ice. The maintenance of the intricate, day and night to pay, and sometimes no match for another man or woman they waited less than a dawn launch a war to the bitter end so. Love is a bank, marriage is the result of love. Each appears. A lot of marriages because of the the Millennium wake wait, knowing that continued not persistent seek in love Sad, such as azaleas Tears of Blood, sing it, and often there is a The depth of the pain of bone marrow. No  gradually, we become weak,Nike Shox UK forget the past the lingering pray; when we can finally talk about the situation, then from time to time, gradually, we are tired of tired, forget the wind, rain booth that do not want to hang up the phone; when we can finally spooned, gradually, we separated forget who loved each other a lifetime commitment; when we finally ready to tie the finger, gradually, we let it go, forget the &quot;You are my&quot; oath   When we finally , they stick with the standards  state of mind before fading back into Buddhism.Sleep is definitely  we look tired, forget ever without love, is not without the capacity for love and courage, on the contraryIt depends how strong will, can only be away from the good and bad! Or that is how desperatetomorrow, her (his) life of the catastrophe.  his heart remained true to the best of a woman Chiai, &quot;a poetic Chihiro waterfall, vancomycin Rhapsody Huiyin is in his mind long-lasting beautiful April days, the Millennium North Face Sale eternal, forever poetry. Very worship of those who dropped out of the dust of thousands of read like the Taoist. A green lamp lights, with the I Ching Ying, do not ask to love and love, do not ask Ukiyo mundane. could keep an open eyes can see each other,Acacia lonely; when we finally kissed each other every day, such as lying to the needle carpet, the heart can not tell uncomfortable
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com/</a> 
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikeshoxukshoes.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.nikeshoxukshoes.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2d18ed4ac752c39dc67c8b0213819fb2" url=""><![CDATA[Married!should have a period of couple<br/><br/>&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3BChristian"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.christianlouboutinshoes2outlet.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Christian</a> Louboutin Shoes&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;	<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaHJpc3RpYW5sb3Vib3V0aW5zaG9lczJvdXRsZXQuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Christian Louboutin Shoes</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e318b0070809ba31b14f3abd27495ac8" url=""><![CDATA[The above three brother during the day<br/><br/>Anti-daughter overnight repeatedly toss me seven or eight times, I seem to have become frightened, a little I will be able to wake up any sound, dim dim, I heard a voice in the yard, such as footsteps, the sound high and one low, turn on the light to see <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcmFkYXN1a3Nob3AuY28udWs_" target="_blank">Prada Sale</a> a table is half past five, who is on the outside? Lunar New Year of the twelfth lunar month will make the water in the house will be able to ice, the cold wind outside the window name of the the whistle child, blew the windows closed lax Wow Leng Leng sound. I threw on my clothes and opened the door, turned out to be the mother pacing in the yard, with arthritis in her leg, a walk on the pain, had dragged his walk, footsteps sounded high and one low. 70-year-old mother, the eyes are not flowers, and ears are not deaf, walking straight spine. In recent years, my mom likes to travel. My son saying: Grandma stylish with the times. 
<br /><br />However, people rarely live to seventy, after all, mother age, go out, always accompanied. Therefore, this difficult and great task falls on my shoulders. It is said that the travel, tourism, trip the money, travel car thing. Also the tourism compiled <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hZGlkYXN0b2VzaG9lc291dGxldHMuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Adidas Outlet Store</a> jingle: to sleep on the train, get off urinated attractions camera home do not know anything. Oh, it is not true. For me, travel is the troubles of life abandoned, easily welled up into the sky. Especially with her mother to travel, make a mother to broaden our horizons, not limit themselves in Xiaojia Zi. Tourism is also a way the release of mood. With her mother, but also to own filial piety to travel together. 51 small fake, was invited to son one after another of the same, we went to Shanghai. This from the drive is the most comfortable, however, consider the mother motion sickness, and had to take the train line. Son rumble, say what train travel is too far behind, people are not the bus is self-driving, four or five hour journey by train to eight hours to reach. But my mom insist, when we accompanied her on the train, the old urchin happy enraptured. All parents are hopeful look into the phoenix, Walter Chan Kar-fourth of is also. Following
<br /><br />Chen was born four had never been seen, the Cultural Revolution had just ended, the village or the production team system work Hutchison cm. The above three brother during the day must go to the production team to take care of river, pick mud hundred kilos of load, when Chen Lao, four young, studying in the study door. The evening meal, a nearly ten-port group sitting on the table, Chen Lao four uphold standing holding a bowl of pot along next,<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaGVhcHN1cHJhdWtzaG9lcy5jby51ay8_" target="_blank">Supra UK</a> some more rice will bowl handed him. Several brother, sometimes with the bowl and handed fourth eldest, fourth eldest took the bowl resting on the side, smiling bear hug like a few bowls with the clutch, this time the elders will be shouting: &quot;You have three bastard, but also Take the fourth of fun. &quot; Chen Lao junior high school. Later, listening to their elders say, when the book they can read even the good junior high school, graduated from high school to be regarded as a great intellectual. After graduating from junior high school, Chen Lao, four followed by the village's old bricklayer not learn from the elders 'famine as hungry artisans'. 
<br /><br />Chen Lao, four marriage had never been seen with the grandparents house, a little worn, in rural areas <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vbmxpbmVjb2FjaDhvdXRsZXQuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Coach Outlet Online</a> take for granted. Four daughter is very beautiful, the fourth of a very loved wife, they lived a happy day. Chen Lao, four son was two years old, the fourth of built houses, double happiness, the happiness index doubled. Chen Lao, four have been outside on the site does brickwork, four daughter-in-law at home farming, his son by the grandmother helped with. When the village phone is not yet popular, Chen Lao, four each week and the wife made an appointment to the village phone people call, the fourth eldest said he would like to hear the voice of the son muttered. Whenever he comes back, the fourth of all with a lot of good to his son, and then holds her son, slapstick, a flies enjoyable. Time passes, people also began to grow. Blink of an eye, Chen Lao son of four junior high school. The village has an old saying 'learn is a lifelong thing, to bad just a thought', Chen Lao, four sons attendant on a few small fry, do not think learning hand and began pilfering things to. H
<br /><br />ad never been seen Chen Lao, four are still in the field work, the wife is at home, the zonal son, the son tube was lax. Chen Lao, four each call back <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lY2Nvc2hvZXNzYWxlLm9yZy51ay8_" target="_blank">ecco</a> should be asked his son to learn how, Nianglia you getting bad at home? The fourth wife he was not worried minds on their work, and son thing did not play, but he kept that good. Later, Chen Lao, four son's bad habits do not change the anti-became a habit, but also into the police station. Chen Lao, four shuttles come back to see the son detained in the police station, meal swearword, hiding in the corner and cried.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pradatrainersuk.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.pradatrainersuk.com</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapairjordans4uk.co.uk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.cheapairjordans4uk.co.uk</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myteamboomer.com%2Fprofile%2Ftristayang"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.myteamboomer.com/profile/tristayang</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsteelhorsetradingpost.com%2Fcommunity%2Fusers%2Ftristayang"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://steelhorsetradingpost.com/community/users/tristayang</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdev.clubugly.info%2Fdevelopment%2Ftristayang%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://dev.clubugly.info/development/tristayang/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ded177f793372a57741d581f81ced590" url=""><![CDATA[Precisely this beautiful season<br/><br/>Son was educated, fourth leave home to make good with his son for some time. 'A' child do not Godfather, fourth of understand this reasoning, he bagged the responsibility of his son astray, each watching his son came back from the eyes to shine, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaGVhcG5pa2VhaXJtYXhpZC5jby51ay8_" target="_blank">Nike Air Max Trainers</a> he wants happiness is very simple. son to good, a good people have moved into a new home almost two years, the father or the first time. Evening, a man sitting on the couch watching TV while chatting, the father seems to be particularly happy. He repeatedly stressed that he actually wanted to come early, you can at home things are also worried that I would accompany him to miss work, so the delay did not come. This either the brother-in-law side of something, the way drove him over, I'm afraid have to push next year. Daughter in the side, interrupted: &quot;You too must my mother enough filial piety, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vbmxpbmVjb2FjaDhvdXRsZXQuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Coach Outlet</a> so I do not like her, just do not come.&quot; Father Oh Oh laugh, quickly explained: &quot;It is definitely not grandpa old, and no ability to help you, nor can a disservice to Caesar.&quot; 
<br /><br />The father has 70, you can always have the stronger. His habit to speak loud, hearty sound like ringing bells; strode back of the habit of bulging micro bow; habit sleeves and trouser leg rolled up high in the fields. As he never seems to know that he is a can justifiably accept the care of the elderly, only his rare days of rest, he is a septuagenarian old father. The daughter proposed to shoot a few photo of my father, my father readily accepted. He immediately Nueliao Nue body, sort skirts and sat,'d call me to sit down at his side. I sit down next to him tightly, his hands the ring to live his father's waist, an instant, a happy warmth spread throughout the body, I suddenly felt that even if the father is old, he has been my patron, my courage, I rely on my power. I put my head gently fall on his father shoulders and see real father, full of unexpected cocoon hand veins; see the real him bronzed by the sun-tanned face filled with vicissitudes; see real wrinkles on his face years engraved deeply, to see real seniors can not find a full head of black hair. My nose is an acid, tens of thousands of guilt and lamented the vines to <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZWxzdGFmZjRqYWNrZXRzLmNvLnVrLw__" target="_blank">belstaff jackets sale</a> climb in my heart together. Father face his mouth, a satisfied smile, his body slightly lean on me, I felt a powerful force to squeeze to my side, that it is an experienced wind and rain trees eager to accept the arm in his later years rest assured; look forward to a lonely, old trees in his old age desire out of the nest of birds returned. After the drizzle, mist-shrouded among the trees on the horizon of the rainbow is the peacock's tail. Colorful colorful clouds into dream-like wonderland ... Precisely this beautiful season, is also 
<br /><br />Yung flowers in full bloom season. A gentle breeze, the tall banyan tree crown gently swing, a blossoming of a beautiful petite Yung flowers have to shake off. Even into a red wall displaying in the air, water vapor in the crown slowly rising, people feel like touching a mother gentle embrace ...... banyan gently sprinkling the floor of the situation of Shame, but also inadvertently shook off <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2FjaGhhbmRiYWdzdWtvdXRsZXQuY28udWsv" target="_blank">coach handbags london</a> a small recalled the boy is heavy and wet. 21 years ago, is a boy five years old, he is the father picked up from the big banyan tree, the police are outside the compound, child vaguely got to remember: In addition to his father's comrades when we parted to bid farewell to their own The father did not he full of hope appeared. That he was leaving Wang Chuan father used to go that way, the little boy did not see the mother lithe figure. From then on he never saw his mother, have been and 
<br /><br />Dad moved to a city far away from the big banyan tree - Guizhou Province, Zunyi City, &quot;the old house. In fact, in memory of the little boy, his mother's impression is not very clear. Only vaguely remember in the winter my mother always wore a handsome dark blue down jacket, valiant. The mother's eyes they Guangdong woman's unique deep and passionate, as if one will be able ripped through the activities of any human heart like. Mother's tall good high! The mother always like to let my father put me over his head for the stars. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2FjaGJhZ3N0b3Jlb3V0bGV0cy5jb20v" target="_blank">Coach Outlet Store Online</a> How many times in the yard, and my father's colleagues, &quot;police uncle&quot; who often see the happy smile of this mother and this little boy under the shade of a large banyan ... Tall banyan carries how many fond memories of affection between.<a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2012basketballsshoes.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.2012basketballsshoes.com/</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.belstaffjacketoutlets.co.uk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.belstaffjacketoutlets.co.uk</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.100xingzuo.com%2Fmember%2Findex.php%3Fuid%3Dtristayang"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.100xingzuo.com/member/index.php?uid=tristayang</a>  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fiamandroid.com%2Fprofile%2Ftristayang"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://iamandroid.com/profile/tristayang</a> <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmindbooks.de%2Fmdb%2Fpg%2Fblog%2Ftrista"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://mindbooks.de/mdb/pg/blog/trista</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>