<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="16">
		<document id="d090522375418fea0cb3bd40d26acfb3" url=""><![CDATA[Duquesa Apartment Rentals<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment in Puerto de la Duquesa<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment on Costa Blanca - Information:<br /><br />Kitchen consists of fridge freezer, microwave and washing machine plus every little thing you will need. 32' flat screen Television together with Sky and Spanish Tv, music centre, games, puzzles and books. All principal rooms have ceiling fans. The fact is every little thing for a excellent holiday young or old.<br />Luxury 3 bedroom apartment together with substantial terrace and spectacular sea views towards Gibraltar &amp; Africa. Situated in Puerto de la Duquesa together with its wonderful port and near to numerous golf courses which includes Duquesa Golf, Valderama, San Roque &amp; Sotogrande. Fantastic gardens surround the communal swimming swimming pool, children's swimming pool &amp; Paddle Tennis court. The beaches of Puerto de la Duquesa &amp; Estepona are really close by.<br /><br />Rent Apartments in Duquesa - Spot:<br /><br />Closest Restaurant : Monte Duquesa Square at 0.25 Km's<br />Car: recommended <br />Location: La Duquesa in Manilva region<br />Car: recommended<br /><br />The beaches of Puerto Duquesa &amp; San Luis de Sabinillas are within a 2min drive or 10min stroll. Estepona's extensive beaches are a 10min drive. The attractive port of Puerto Duquesa together with restaurants and bars are a 10 minute stroll. Numerous more Restaurants and Bars are nearby from excellent value chringuitos (Beach Restaurants) to fine dining. Golf courses which includes Duquesa Golf, Valderama, San Roque &amp; Sotogrande are within a 10 minute drive. Wonderful Andalusian white towns of Casares, Gaucin &amp; Jimena de la Frontera are within 1/2 hour drive. Marbella, Puerto Banus, Ronda are within 1 hour’s drive. Surfing/windsurfing beaches at Tarifa and the Costa de la Luz are 45 min's away. North Africa is a 15 mile crossing from Tarifa together with regular services. Dolphin observing boat excursions from Gibraltar, Estepona or Tarifa are highly recommended along with the magnificent train ride from San Roque to Ronda. The airports of Malaga &amp; Jerez are within 1 hour and Gibraltar is 20 min's away. <br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Rent - Rental Information<br /><br />Golf: About 5 min's stroll takes you to the club house at Duquesa Golf. This is an fantastic course together with impressive views of the Mediterranean. two Other courses are within 5-10 minutes drive, such as the new Don Julia complex together with its proposed six star spa holiday resort. Valderama is approximately 20 minutes drive ( 1 of the greatest courses in Europe. Our agents can organise special deals and discounts on numerous courses. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fduquesaapartmentrentals04.wetpaint.com%2Fpage%2FDuquesa%2BApartment%2BRentals%2B%252820%2529"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://duquesaapartmentrentals04.wetpaint.com/page/Duquesa+Apartment+Rentals+%2820%29</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fduquesaapartmentrentals04.wikispaces.com%2FRent%2BDuquesa%2BApartment"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://duquesaapartmentrentals04.wikispaces.com/Rent+Duquesa+Apartment</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fduquesarentalapartment61.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F10%2F09%2Frent-apartments-in-duquesa%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://duquesarentalapartment61.wordpress.com/2011/10/09/rent-apartments-in-duquesa/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b3b25cd870540fb42bc1f9e51300a980" url=""><![CDATA[Rent Duquesa Apartment on Costa Blanca<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment &quot;Haven in the Sun&quot; in Puerto De La Duquesa<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment on Costa Blanca - Info:<br /><br />Wonderful apartment on the beach, walking distance to bars and restaurants<br /><br />Directly off the promenade just about the corner and away from the hustle of the Duquesa Harbour you will see this apartment which feels extra like a Spanish casita than an apartment. Ground floor, you stroll out directly to the beach, it has excellent views from the living room and master bedroom. The apartment is cool together with ceiling fans and has been recently modernised.<br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Let - Spot:<br /><br />Closest Motorway : N340/AP7 - Manilva at five Km's<br />Closest Beach : Puerta De La Duquesa at 800 M<br />Closest Barpub : Fino's at 150 M<br /><br />Located suitable on the beach this wonderful 2 bedroom apartment looks out on the wonderful Mediterranean sea. It is a 2 minute stroll into the popular Duquesa Port which has a multitude of bars and restaurants and has become a popular choice for families, couples and golfers. Duquesa is a idyllic port together with a friendly atmosphere, you are spoilt for choice together with the variety of restaurants. This apartment which has the feel of a Spanish casita is in a excellent location, you can also stroll to Duquesa Castillo, a tiny village together with some excellent restaurants. For those wanting to while away the hours on the beach then you hardly need to pack a bag. For those wanting to explore some of the great Andalucian countryside then this is a excellent base from which to explore the area. <br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Rent - Further Details<br /><br />Golf: Duquesa Golf and Country Club across the road, about a dozen courses together with in half an hours drive, such as Valderamma, the Ryder Cup venue.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fduquesaapartmentrentals04.wikispaces.com%2FRent%2BDuquesa%2BApartment"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://duquesaapartmentrentals04.wikispaces.com/Rent+Duquesa+Apartment</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fduquesarentalapartment61.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F10%2F09%2Frent-apartments-in-duquesa%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://duquesarentalapartment61.wordpress.com/2011/10/09/rent-apartments-in-duquesa/</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fduquesaapartmentrentals04.wetpaint.com%2Fpage%2FDuquesa%2BApartment%2BRentals%2B%252820%2529"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://duquesaapartmentrentals04.wetpaint.com/page/Duquesa+Apartment+Rentals+%2820%29</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5722c4f0c9ac4103cbbfdfb41ad12ca1" url=""><![CDATA[Duquesa Apartment Rentals<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment &quot;Los Granados de la Duquesa II&quot; in Duquesa<br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Let - Info:<br /><br />This Luxury 3 Bedroom Apartment in a tranquil location is inside easy walking distance from the hustle and bustle of the Puerto de la Duquesa Harbour and Beach. Located 50 min's from Malaga Airport, or 25 min's from Gibraltar Airport, on the Duquesa Golf Course. The complicated has below ground auto parking together with direct access towards the apartment via a lift. The holiday accommodation is furnished to a high normal and provides air-conditioning, heating and marble levels throughout, 2 bathrooms (1 en-suite), modern kitchen which includes oven &amp; hob, fridge freezer, washing machine, dishwasher, microwave, toaster &amp; kettle. The roomy living room comprises of 2 sofas, Radio, CD, DVD &amp; Tv which receives satellite channels, patio doors lead onto a significant terrace. The terrace is perfect for eating Al Fresco, relaxing together with a drink following a game of golf or observing the sunset following a day sunbathing on  of the numerous sunloungers by 1 of the 2 beautiful pools<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain - Spot:<br /><br />Closest Motorway : N340/AP7 - Manilva at 5 Km's<br />Closest Beach : Puerta De La Duquesa at 800 M<br />Closest Barpub : Fino's at 150 M<br /><br />This luxury apartment is in a tranquil location a short stroll from vibrant Puerto de la Duquesa which is a well kept secret along this coastline and is referred to as the new 'Golden Mile' on the Costa Del Sol. The Harbour boasts numerous restaurants catering for all preferences, beaches can be found either side of the harbour where  can enjoy beach cafes for a snack or lunch looking over the sea. A wonderful stroll along a promenade joins Duquesa Harbour together with the tiny village of Sabinillas. Fifteen min's by car will take you to the village of Estepona along with a further ten min's will take you to Marbella. Gaucin &amp; Casares famous Andalucian white villages within the hills are also only a short drive away. Golf courses are in abundance along the coastline and numerous are within 15 min's drive. These include Duquesa, Dona Julio, Valderrama, San Roque, Marbella Golf Holiday resort, Marbella Golf &amp; Country, Sotogrande, Alcaidesa, Estepona and La Canada. <br /><br />Duquesa Apartment Rentals - Rental Information<br /><br />Golf: The area is a haven for golf enthusiasts, you have over 50 golf courses to choose from within an hours drive. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fjacquesshann922.livejournal.com%2F835.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://jacquesshann922.livejournal.com/835.html</a> ,
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4bdd6421f10281cdbb860c5a3bf2d038" url=""><![CDATA[Duquesa Apartments to Rent<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment &quot;Las Gaviotas&quot; in Duquesa, Manilva<br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Let - Summary:<br /><br />The living room has flat screen Tv and DVD. There is also a breakfast bar and kitchen. Both bedrooms have fitted closets. The bathroom has a bath together with a shower above. The 2nd bedroom has a double and a single bed so this apartment can accommodate 5. A patio region would be to the back of the property. The entrance towards the property is gated.<br /><br />Duquesa Holiday Apartments - Location:<br /><br />Closest Golf : Golf de la Duquesa at 300 M<br />Closest Restaurant : Kelly's at 150 M<br />Car: recommended<br />Closest Airport : Malaga/Gibraltar at 100 Km's<br /><br />Ideally situated for access to Malaga and Gibraltar, and Jerez airports. Adjacent to Duquesa Golf, together with Valderrama and Sotegrande golf courses a brief drive away. Venture inland towards the historic 'white villiages' of Ronda and Casares, along to Gibraltar, or even a day trip to Morocco. Selwo National Park is 15km away. Based on an African safari park, it houses 2000 animals in semi-wild conditions. Windsurfing off the beach or 45 min's by car to Tarifa on the Atlantic coastline - the premier windsurfing venue in Europe. <br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain - Summary<br /><br />Golf: Duquesa Golf and Country Club across the road, about a dozen courses together with in half an hours drive, such as Valderamma, the Ryder Cup venue.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogster.com%2Fjacquesshann922%2Fapartment-rent-in-duquesa"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.blogster.com/jacquesshann922/apartment-rent-in-duquesa</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thoughts.com%2Fblog%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thoughts.com/blog/</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frefugiohardy12.bravejournal.com%2Fentry%2F72040"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://refugiohardy12.bravejournal.com/entry/72040</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="959e6d30fb9f1ec25188416b93c2616f" url=""><![CDATA[Rent Apartment in Duquesa<br/><br/>Our property, acquired in 2005 boasts numerous luxury features, including full air-conditioning (hot/cold), marble flooring throughout, totally fitted kitchen, separate utility, en-suite to the master bedroom together with spa bath, significant living room, TV (Together with Sky digital), DVD/CD/Radio, fitted closets &amp; built-in hotel style safe, roomy south facing patio, secure below ground car auto parking, 24hr Concierge, BBQ area, 3 pools together with separate children's swimming pool and play area, two paddle tennis courts, 15,000m2 landscaped gardens, automatic lifts to all levels. Perfect for all year round rentals, we offer total peace and relaxation in a luxury well appointed apartment (See our recent guest reviews below)<br /><br />Apartment Rent in Duquesa - Spot:<br /><br />Closest Motorway : A7 Toll motorway at six Km's<br /><br />Puerto de la Duquesa is situated between 2 great tourist centres of Marbella and Sotogrande and is the Costa del Sol's greatest kept-kept secret, situated within easy reach of airports at Malaga (50mins) or Gibraltar (30mins). Local shops/bars/cafe are located in a courtyard within a 5min stroll, a stroll further down to the marina/beaches will take approx 15mins. The harbour is flanked together with fine sands and clean and crystalline water beaches which have been awarded together with the European Blue flag status. For golfers there is the Robert Trent designed Duquesa golf and country club which boasts an 18-hole course, which features wonderful sea and mountain views, 3 tennis courts, snooker &amp; covered swimming swimming pool. Other golfing challenges are close at hand, Alcaidesa, Valderrama, Sotogrande and San Rogue courses are all within easy driving distance A relaxing atmosphere is teamed together with an array of first-class amenities which makes La Duquesa a really desirable location for your relaxing holida <br /><br />Rent Apartments in Duquesa - Summary<br /><br />Golf: La Duquesa Golf and Country Club right next to the complex boasts an 18 holes course designed by Robert Trent Jones Sr., a technical masterpiece together with wonderful sea and mountain views. In addition to golf, the club offers numerous amenities including tennis, squash, and a totally fitted gym together with a qualified resident trainer. Estepona Golf, Atalaya Golf Club, El Coto Golf Club, El Paraiso Golf Club, Los Flamingos Golf Club, Guadalmina Golf Clu, Monte Mayor Golf Club, Marbella Club Golf Holiday resort, La Quinta Golf Club, Los Arqueros Golf Club, La Zagaleta Golf Club, La Duquesa Golf Club, Los Naranjos Golf Club, Royal Las Brisas Golf Club, Aloha Golf Club, La Canada Golf Club, La Dame de Noche Golf Club, Valderrama, Sotogrande Golf Club, Almenara Golf Club, Rio Real Golf Club, Marbella Golf &amp; Country Club to name but a few you will find plenty more!!.<br />Other Activities: Dolphin and whale observing boat excursions<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.spainrentalsdirect.co.uk%2Fsearch%2Fproperties%2Flist.cfm%3FTownID%3D158"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.spainrentalsdirect.co.uk/search/properties/list.cfm?TownID=158</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4e83f9d483c343f9e0268fdda420b023" url=""><![CDATA[Duquesa Rental Apartment<br/><br/>Luxury Secluded Apartment together with substantial sunny terrace looking over wonderful gardens<br /><br />Rent Apartments in Duquesa - Info:<br /><br />three Bedrooms, two Bathrooms, Sleeps five, two Pools<br /><br />Duquesa Holiday Apartments - Place:<br /><br />Closest Airport : Malaga at 70 Km's<br />Closest Ferry : Gibraltar at 35 Km's<br /><br />Ideally situated for access to Malaga and Gibraltar, and Jerez airports. Adjacent to Duquesa Golf, together with Valderrama and Sotegrande golf courses a short drive away. Venture inland to the historic 'white villiages' of Ronda and Casares, along to Gibraltar, or even a day trip to Morocco. Selwo National Park is 15km away. Based on an African safari park, it houses 2000 animals in semi-wild conditions. Windsurfing off the beach or 45 min's by car to Tarifa on the Atlantic coastline - the premier windsurfing venue in Europe. <br /><br />Duquesa Apartment Rentals - Further Details<br /><br />Other Activities: Selwo Nature Park, Prado World Water Park<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.squidoo.com%2Fduquesaapartmentrentals65"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.squidoo.com/duquesaapartmentrentals65</a> ,
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3738ebf3342e6a9ea1388e3c519b996" url=""><![CDATA[Rent Apartment in Duquesa<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment in Puerto de la Duquesa<br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Rent - Information:<br /><br />Spend your holiday in an exclusive self catering holiday apartment in Duquesa, Costa del Sol, Spain. The holiday accommodation contains modern quality furnishings, full hot and cold air conditioning, marble levels, en-suite spa bath, free broadband and a 47 inch LED Television. In your holiday apartment you have your own huge (68m) private terrace together with sea views, its south west orientation means you also benefit from all day hot sunshine literally from sunrise (out of the sea in front of you) to sunset (to the mountains behind). The apartments position is perfect, its 50m of the beach and 50m of the port, whilst also being pleasantly detached and elevated from those around you. Located alongside the charming port, you can unwind on the apartments private terrace, swim in the swimming pool or lay on the beach. You can have a game of golf, maybe go fishing, or just wander through the port at your leisure, the choice is yours at No 1 Mikonos Playa Duquesa, Costa del Sol, Spain.<br /><br />Rent Apartments in Duquesa - Place:<br /><br />Closest Airport : Malaga at 80 Km's<br /><br />Located 100 m from Duquesa Harbour, and adjacent to Duquesa Golf and Sabinillas and Duquesa blue flag beaches. 25 min's from Gibraltar, 50 min's from Malaga. Puerto Banus and Marbella within easy reach. Rail journey from San Roque to Ronda is a must. Casares white village 15 min's away. Granada and Seville about two.five hours away. For young children the Selwo Safari park is only 15 min's away. Water parks and other theme parks are also within easy reach. Golfers have an fantastic course on their doorstep, plus Dona Julia six star golf holiday resort and Estepona Golf 5 min's away. 50 courses in total within easy reach. The port has a multitude of quailty international restaurants and bars. A further five minutes stroll past the harbour will take you to the tiny Spanish village of Castillo together with its castle and number of fish and Tapas restaurants. Casillo has its own fishing fleet and has some of the greatest fish on the coastline.<br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Let - Rental Information<br /><br />Golf: About five min's stroll takes you to the club house at Duquesa Golf. This is an fantastic course together with impressive views of the Mediterranean. two Other courses are within 5-10 min's drive, which includes the new Don Julia complex together with its proposed six star spa holiday resort. Valderama is approximately 20 min's drive ( 1 of the greatest courses in Europe. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FDuquesa-Holiday-Apartments%2F03EFBFFFF024B2881000801663A6E"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://community.atom.com/Post/Duquesa-Holiday-Apartments/03EFBFFFF024B2881000801663A6E</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F899645%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailystrength.org/people/899645/journal</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eb2706dc470e9f992c4bf3d521c75395" url=""><![CDATA[Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment &quot;Haven in the Sun&quot; in Puerto De La Duquesa<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain - Summary:<br /><br />This Luxury 3 Bedroom Apartment in a tranquil location is within quick walking distance from the hustle and bustle of the Puerto de la Duquesa Harbour and Beach. Located 50 min's from Malaga Airport, or 25 min's from Gibraltar Airport, on the Duquesa Golf Course. The complicated has below ground auto parking together with direct access to the apartment via a lift. The holiday accommodation is furnished to a high regular and delivers air-conditioning, heating and marble  all through, 2 bathrooms (1 en-suite), modern kitchen such as oven &amp; hob, fridge freezer, washing machine, dishwasher, microwave, toaster &amp; kettle. The roomy living room comprises of 2 sofas, Radio, CD, DVD &amp; Tv which receives satellite channels, patio doors lead onto a significant terrace. The terrace is perfect for eating Al Fresco, relaxing together with a drink after having a game of golf or observing the sunset following a day sunbathing on 1 of the numerous sunloungers by  of the 2 beautiful pools<br /><br />Duquesa Apartments to Rent - Location:<br /><br />Closest Golf : Golf de la Duquesa at 300 M<br />Closest Restaurant : Kelly's at 150 M<br />Car: recommended<br />Closest Airport : Malaga/Gibraltar at 100 Km's<br /><br />Ideally situated for access to Malaga and Gibraltar, and Jerez airports. Adjacent to Duquesa Golf, together with Valderrama and Sotegrande golf courses a short drive away. Venture inland towards the historic 'white villiages' of Ronda and Casares, along to Gibraltar, or even a day trip to Morocco. Selwo National Park is 15km away. Based on an African safari park, it houses 2000 animals in semi-wild conditions. Windsurfing off the beach or 45 min's by car to Tarifa on the Atlantic coastline - the premier windsurfing venue in Europe. <br /><br />Apartment Rent in Duquesa - Summary<br /><br />Golf: Duquesa Golf and Country Club across the road, about a dozen courses together with in half an hours drive, including Valderamma, the Ryder Cup venue.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F899645%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.dailystrength.org/people/899645/journal</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FDuquesa-Holiday-Apartments%2F03EFBFFFF024B2881000801663A6E"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://community.atom.com/Post/Duquesa-Holiday-Apartments/03EFBFFFF024B2881000801663A6E</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7fc392bd89256f05a3b7824a60c9e7c7" url=""><![CDATA[Rent Duquesa Apartment on Costa Blanca<br/><br/>In truth every little thing for a excellent holiday young or old.<br />Luxury 3 bedroom apartment together with substantial terrace and spectacular sea views towards Gibraltar &amp; Africa. Situated in Puerto de la Duquesa together with its fantastic port and near to numerous golf courses which includes Duquesa Golf, Valderama, San Roque &amp; Sotogrande. Fantastic gardens surround the communal swimming swimming pool, children's swimming pool &amp; Paddle Tennis court. The beaches of Puerto de la Duquesa &amp; Estepona are really close by.<br /><br />Rent Apartment in Duquesa - Place:<br /><br />Closest Airport : Gibraltar at 25 Km's<br />Closest Beach : beach at 1 Km's<br />Closest Golf : Golf Duquesa at 0.5 Km's<br /><br />The beaches of Puerto Duquesa &amp; San Luis de Sabinillas are within a 2min drive or 10min stroll. Estepona's extensive beaches are a 10min drive. The attractive port of Puerto Duquesa together with restaurants and bars are a 10 minute stroll. Numerous more Restaurants and Bars are nearby from excellent value chringuitos (Beach Restaurants) to fine dining. Golf courses which includes Duquesa Golf, Valderama, San Roque &amp; Sotogrande are within a 10 minute drive. Wonderful Andalusian white towns of Casares, Gaucin &amp; Jimena de la Frontera are within 1/2 hour drive. Marbella, Puerto Banus, Ronda are within 1 hour’s drive. Surfing/windsurfing beaches at Tarifa and the Costa de la Luz are 45 min's away. North Africa is a 15 mile crossing from Tarifa together with regular services. Dolphin observing boat excursions from Gibraltar, Estepona or Tarifa are highly recommended along with the magnificent train ride from San Roque to Ronda. The airports of Malaga &amp; Jerez are within 1 hour and Gibraltar is 20 min's away. <br /><br />Duquesa Apartments to Rent - Further Details<br /><br />Nearby Attractions: The typically Spanish village of Sabinillas has a good variety of restaurants and hosts a market on Fridays. 'Art in the Street' is an art show on the Paseo Maritimo every Sunday from 7pm to midnight until 21 September. Banks, supermarkets, pharmacy etc are all accessible. The beaches at Sabinillas, La Colonia &amp; Puerto de la Duquesa have been awarded Blue Flag status. You will find several beaches at Estepona such as the beach at Cristo Bay which is beautiful for families. The harbour at Duquesa is an attractive Port with numerous restaurants and beaches and you will find good seafood restaurants in the Castillo location of Puerto de la Duquesa. You will find numerous prestigious golf clubs in the location such as the La Duquesa Golf and Country Club together with its 18 hole course designed by Robert Trent Jones Sr which has been totally refurbished and has a brand new spa, gym and tennis amenities and is next to the 5* Hotel Duquesa Golf. Valderrama and Sotogrande courses are only 10 min's away.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fjacquesshann922.sosblog.com%2FThe-first-blog-b1%2FApartment-Rent-in-Duquesa-b1-p5.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://jacquesshann922.sosblog.com/The-first-blog-b1/Apartment-Rent-in-Duquesa-b1-p5.htm</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fjacquesshann922.posterous.com%2Frent-duquesa-apartment"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://jacquesshann922.posterous.com/rent-duquesa-apartment</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwallinside.com%2Fpost-381291.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://wallinside.com/post-381291.html</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="f49036ae7099cc953b84e259d7f5fa2d" url=""><![CDATA[Apartment Rent in Duquesa<br/><br/>two bed two bathroom apartment on the beach 100 m to Harbour<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain - Info:<br /><br />Hot and cold air conditioned two bed two bathroom apartment on beach and short stroll to bars and restaurants. Partial sea view and view of swimming pool and garden. four pools 1 occasionally heated. Paddle tennis and gym on-site. Fantastic golf course 5 min's stroll. Substantial sunny terrace for alfresco dining. Acceptable for wheelchairs and grab rail in bath. Disabled friendly. Lifts to all . Auto parking space offered. Fantastic and tranquil harbour location together with plenty of good bars and restaurants but not acceptable for clubbers. Wonderful beach bars. Assistance offered from local agents. Excursions available such as Gibraltar, Morocco, Ronda, Selwo Safari, individuals observing in Puerto Banus and white villages in mountains. Boat employ from Harbour.<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment - Location:<br /><br />Closest Beach : beach at 50 M<br />Closest Barpub : Duquesa at 60 M<br />Closest Restaurant : Duquesa at 60 M<br />Car: not necessary <br /><br />The beaches of Puerto Duquesa &amp; San Luis de Sabinillas are within a 2min drive or 10min stroll. Estepona's extensive beaches are a 10min drive. The attractive port of Puerto Duquesa together with restaurants and bars are a 10 minute stroll. Numerous more Restaurants and Bars are nearby from excellent value chringuitos (Beach Restaurants) to fine dining. Golf courses such as Duquesa Golf, Valderama, San Roque &amp; Sotogrande are within a 10 minute drive. Fantastic Andalusian white towns of Casares, Gaucin &amp; Jimena de la Frontera are within 1/2 hour drive. Marbella, Puerto Banus, Ronda are within 1 hour’s drive. Surfing/windsurfing beaches at Tarifa and the Costa de la Luz are 45 min's away. North Africa is a 15 mile crossing from Tarifa together with regular services. Dolphin observing boat excursions from Gibraltar, Estepona or Tarifa are highly recommended along with the magnificent train ride from San Roque to Ronda. The airports of Malaga &amp; Jerez are within 1 hour and Gibraltar is 20 min's away. <br /><br />Duquesa Apartment Rentals - Further Details<br /><br />Day Excursions: Dolphin observing day excursions from Tarifa into the Strait of Gibraltar are accessible as are excursions to Tangiers where visitors can go to the Caves of Hercules, the Medina &amp; the Souk &amp; be entertained at the Berber Arabian Fantasia Show. Visiting Ronda by train is a great experience through the Andalusian countryside to the amazing village of Ronda. The wonderful Andalusian towns of Jerez, Cordoba, Seville, Granada are all accessible from Duquesa. The shops of Marbella &amp; Puerto Banus are less than an hour away. The old village of Marbella is a really attractive place to have a meal. The Gibraltar Rock tour incorporates St Michael's Caves, the Upper Rock and the Barbary Apes &amp; provides spectacular views of the surrounding area. Passports are required when visiting Gibraltar.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.getjealous.com%2Fblog.php%3Faction%3Dshowdiaryentry%26amp%3Bdiary_id%3D2234611%26amp%3Bgo%3Drefugiohardy12"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.getjealous.com/blog.php?action=showdiaryentry&amp;diary_id=2234611&amp;go=refugiohardy12</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.zimbio.com%2FGeneral%2Farticles%2F23t2aj5il9V%2FDuquesa%2BApartments%2Bto%2BRent%3Fadd%3DTrue"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.zimbio.com/General/articles/23t2aj5il9V/Duquesa+Apartments+to+Rent?add=True</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fduquesarentalapartment88.qapacity.com.qapacity.com%2Fmy-blog%2F196241%2Fduquesa-apartment-rentals%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://duquesarentalapartment88.qapacity.com.qapacity.com/my-blog/196241/duquesa-apartment-rentals/</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="74c686dbef3b78404fe8a15486084d6a" url=""><![CDATA[Rent Apartments in Duquesa<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment &quot;Haven in the Sun&quot; in Puerto De La Duquesa<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain - Information:<br /><br />Beautiful apartment on the beach, walking distance to bars and restaurants<br /><br />Directly off the promenade just about the corner and away from the hustle of the Duquesa Harbour you will see this apartment which feels additional like a Spanish casita than an apartment. Ground floor, you stroll out directly to the beach, it has excellent views from the living room and master bedroom. The apartment is cool together with ceiling fans and has been recently modernised.<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment on Costa del Sol - Place:<br /><br />Closest Golf : Golf de la Duquesa at 300 M<br />Closest Restaurant : Kelly's at 150 M<br />Car: recommended<br />Closest Airport : Malaga/Gibraltar at 100 Km's<br /><br />Located correct on the beach this wonderful 2 bedroom apartment looks out on the wonderful Mediterranean sea. It is a 2 minute stroll into the popular Duquesa Port which has a multitude of bars and restaurants and has become a popular choice for families, couples and golfers. Duquesa is a idyllic harbour together with a friendly atmosphere, you are spoilt for choice together with the variety of restaurants. This apartment which has the feel of a Spanish casita is in a excellent location, you can also stroll to Duquesa Castillo, a tiny village together with some excellent restaurants. For those wanting to while away the hours on the beach then you hardly need to pack a bag. For those wanting to explore some of the superb Andalucian countryside then this is a excellent base from which to explore the location. <br /><br />Duquesa Rental Apartment - Further Details<br /><br />Other Activities: Selwo Nature Park, Prado World Water Park<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.getjealous.com%2Fblog.php%3Faction%3Dshowdiaryentry%26amp%3Bdiary_id%3D2234611%26amp%3Bgo%3Drefugiohardy12"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.getjealous.com/blog.php?action=showdiaryentry&amp;diary_id=2234611&amp;go=refugiohardy12</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fduquesarentalapartment88.qapacity.com.qapacity.com%2Fmy-blog%2F196241%2Fduquesa-apartment-rentals%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://duquesarentalapartment88.qapacity.com.qapacity.com/my-blog/196241/duquesa-apartment-rentals/</a> ,  <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.zimbio.com%2FGeneral%2Farticles%2F23t2aj5il9V%2FDuquesa%2BApartments%2Bto%2BRent%3Fadd%3DTrue"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.zimbio.com/General/articles/23t2aj5il9V/Duquesa+Apartments+to+Rent?add=True</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b7c6aea9ae9451a8398beec0158c59e1" url=""><![CDATA[Duquesa Apartment Rentals<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment &quot;Los Granados de la Duquesa II&quot; in Duquesa<br /><br />Duquesa Rental Apartment - Summary:<br /><br />three Bedrooms, two Bathrooms, Sleeps 5, two Pools<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain - Place:<br /><br />Closest Barpub : Duquesa Harbour at 0.two Km's<br />Closest Golf : Duquesa Golf at 1 Km's<br />Closest Restaurant : Duquesa Harbour at 0.two Km's<br />Car: not necessary<br /><br />This luxury apartment is in a peaceful location a short stroll from vibrant Puerto de la Duquesa which is a well kept secret along this coastline and is referred to as the new 'Golden Mile' on the Costa Del Sol. The Port boasts numerous restaurants catering for all preferences, beaches can be found either side of the port where  can enjoy beach cafes for a snack or lunch looking over the sea. A beautiful stroll along a promenade joins Duquesa Harbour together with the tiny village of Sabinillas. Fifteen min's by car will take you to the village of Estepona along with a further ten min's will take you to Marbella. Gaucin &amp; Casares famous Andalucian white villages within the hills are also only a short drive away. Golf courses are in abundance along the coastline and numerous are within 15 min's drive. These include Duquesa, Dona Julio, Valderrama, San Roque, Marbella Golf Holiday resort, Marbella Golf &amp; Country, Sotogrande, Alcaidesa, Estepona and La Canada. <br /><br />Duquesa Apartment Rentals - Summary<br /><br />Golf: Duquesa Golf and Country Club across the road, about a dozen courses together with in half an hours drive, including Valderamma, the Ryder Cup venue.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.friendsreunited.co.uk%2Fblog%2Fread%2F719788915%2F174006"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.friendsreunited.co.uk/blog/read/719788915/174006</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="950bd0644c1198b63798671dfd5f3d54" url=""><![CDATA[Duquesa Apartment to Rent<br/><br/>Luxury substantial new 3-bedroom apartment looking over Puerto De La Duquesa<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain - Information:<br /><br />Kitchen includes fridge freezer, microwave and washing machine plus every little thing you need. 32' flat screen Television together with Sky and Spanish Television, music centre, games, puzzles and books. All key rooms have ceiling fans. The fact is everything for a excellent holiday young or old.<br />Luxury three bedroom apartment together with substantial terrace and spectacular sea views towards Gibraltar &amp; Africa. Situated in Puerto de la Duquesa together with its fantastic port and near to numerous golf courses such as Duquesa Golf, Valderama, San Roque &amp; Sotogrande. Wonderful gardens surround the communal swimming swimming pool, children's swimming pool &amp; Paddle Tennis court. The beaches of Puerto de la Duquesa &amp; Estepona are really close by.<br /><br />Duquesa Apartments to Rent - Area:<br /><br />Closest Airport : Malaga at 80 Km's<br /><br />Whilst staying a No 1 Mikonos Playa in Puerto de la Duquesa, the harbour is agreat area to stroll through, explore, and rest in whilst taking in the the views and scenery or you can visit Gibralter for your tax free shopping, Marbella and Puerto Banus for a big night out, or go and stroll through the harbour at Sotogrande at you leasure. <br /><br />Duquesa Rental Apartment - Rental Information<br /><br />Local Historial Attractions: The surrounding area of Puerto de la Duquesa has numerous historic places to visit - the Castillo de la Duquesa, built in 1767 is currently being adapted to house a museum celebrating the local village of Manilva's rich Roman history. The Torre Alemenarade Chullera is a watch tower built at the end of the 15th Century and is located at Punta Chullera, on the border together with the province of Cádiz between the sea and the CN-340 at km 137. The Hedoinda Roman Baths are on the Rio Manilva road and the healing powers of the sulphuric waters are still popular today where numerous visitors also indulge in the mud baths! The remains of Los Castellejos de Alcorrin, a Bronze Age fort is located on a hill just about 1.5km inland from Aldea Beach and is an archaeological web page of exceptional interest. In Manilva the Iglesia de Santa Ana dates from the 18the Century &amp; is a focal point for the towns festivals &amp; fiestas.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.quechup.com%2Fblog%2Fentry%2Fview%2Fid%2F319559"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.quechup.com/blog/entry/view/id/319559</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fc663d8eb1a2c148c60c072a622dedc3" url=""><![CDATA[Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment &quot;Haven in the Sun&quot; in Puerto De La Duquesa<br /><br />Rent Duquesa Apartment in Spain - Summary:<br /><br />Beautiful apartment on the beach, walking distance to bars and restaurants<br /><br />Directly off the promenade just about the corner and away from the hustle of the Duquesa Port you will discover this apartment which feels more like a Spanish casita than an apartment. Ground floor, you stroll out directly to the beach, it has excellent views from the living room and master bedroom. The apartment is cool together with ceiling fans and has been lately modernised.<br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Rent - Location:<br /><br />Closest Golf : Golf de la Duquesa at 300 M<br />Closest Restaurant : Kelly's at 150 M<br />Car: recommended<br />Closest Airport : Malaga/Gibraltar at 100 Km's<br /><br />Ideally situated for access to Malaga and Gibraltar, and Jerez airports. Adjacent to Duquesa Golf, together with Valderrama and Sotegrande golf courses a short drive away. Venture inland towards the historic 'white villiages' of Ronda and Casares, along to Gibraltar, or even a day trip to Morocco. Selwo National Park is 15km away. Based on an African safari park, it houses 2000 animals in semi-wild conditions. Windsurfing off the beach or 45 min's by car to Tarifa on the Atlantic coastline - the premier windsurfing venue in Europe. <br /><br />Apartment Rent in Duquesa - Summary<br /><br />Golf: Duquesa Golf and Country Club across the road, about a dozen courses together with in half an hours drive, including Valderamma, the Ryder Cup venue.<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.quechup.com%2Fblog%2Fentry%2Fview%2Fid%2F319559"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.quechup.com/blog/entry/view/id/319559</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="64218aef6d47160ea15dd35a01cf4318" url=""><![CDATA[Duquesa Apartment Rentals<br/><br/>two bed two bathroom apartment on the beach 100 m to Port<br /><br />Duquesa Rental Apartment - Info:<br /><br />Hot and cold air conditioned two bed two bathroom apartment on beach and short stroll to bars and restaurants. Partial sea view and view of swimming pool and garden. four pools 1 at times heated. Paddle tennis and fitness center on-site. Fantastic golf course 5 min's stroll. Substantial sunny terrace for alfresco dining. Acceptable for wheelchairs and grab rail in bath. Disabled friendly. Lifts to all levels. Auto parking space out there. Wonderful and peaceful harbour location together with a lot of good bars and restaurants but not acceptable for clubbers. Fantastic beach bars. Help obtainable from local agents. Excursions accessible which includes Gibraltar, Morocco, Ronda, Selwo Safari, people observing in Puerto Banus and white villages in mountains. Boat employ from Port.<br /><br />Duquesa Apartment to Let - Area:<br /><br />Closest Airport : Malaga at 80 Km's<br /><br />Located 100 m from Duquesa Harbour, and adjacent to Duquesa Golf and Sabinillas and Duquesa blue flag beaches. 25 min's from Gibraltar, 50 min's from Malaga. Puerto Banus and Marbella within easy reach. Rail journey from San Roque to Ronda is a must. Casares white village 15 min's away. Granada and Seville about two.5 hours away. For young children the Selwo Safari park is only 15 min's away. Water parks and other theme parks are also within easy reach. Golfers have an fantastic course on their doorstep, plus Dona Julia six star golf holiday resort and Estepona Golf 5 min's away. 50 courses in total within easy reach. The port has a multitude of quailty international restaurants and bars. A further five minutes stroll past the harbour will take you to the tiny Spanish village of Castillo together with its castle and number of fish and Tapas restaurants. Casillo has its own fishing fleet and has some of the greatest fish on the coastline.<br /><br />Duquesa Apartments to Rent - Rental Information<br /><br />Golf: About 5 min's stroll takes you to the club house at Duquesa Golf. This is an wonderful course together with magnificent views of the Mediterranean. two Other courses are within 5-10 minutes drive, which includes the new Don Julia complex together with its proposed six star spa holiday resort. Valderama is approximately 20 min's drive (  of the greatest courses in Europe. Our agents can organise special deals and discounts on numerous courses. <br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmyanimelist.net%2Fblog.php%3Feid%3D200311"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://myanimelist.net/blog.php?eid=200311</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b300d5f1f772e26a770896d9313afdea" url=""><![CDATA[Duquesa Rental Apartment<br/><br/>La Duquesa holiday apartment &quot;Los Granados de la Duquesa II&quot; in Duquesa<br /><br />Duquesa Apartment Rentals - Summary:<br /><br />This Luxury three Bedroom Apartment in a tranquil location is within straightforward walking distance from the hustle and bustle of the Puerto de la Duquesa Port and Beach. Located 50 min's from Malaga Airport, or 25 min's from Gibraltar Airport, on the Duquesa Golf Course. The complex has below ground auto parking together with direct access to the apartment via a lift. The holiday accommodation is furnished to a high normal and gives air-conditioning, heating and marble  throughout, 2 bathrooms (1 en-suite), modern kitchen including oven &amp; hob, fridge freezer, washing machine, dishwasher, microwave, toaster &amp; kettle. The roomy living room comprises of 2 sofas, Radio, CD, DVD &amp; Television which receives satellite channels, patio doors lead onto a significant terrace. The terrace is perfect for eating Al Fresco, relaxing together with a drink following a game of golf or observing the sunset after having a day sunbathing on 1 of the numerous sunloungers by  of the 2 wonderful pools<br /><br />Duquesa Apartments to Rent - Spot:<br /><br />Closest Golf : Golf de la Duquesa at 300 M<br />Closest Restaurant : Kelly's at 150 M<br />Car: recommended<br />Closest Airport : Malaga/Gibraltar at 100 Km's<br /><br />Ideally situated for access to Malaga and Gibraltar, and Jerez airports. Adjacent to Duquesa Golf, together with Valderrama and Sotegrande golf courses a brief drive away. Venture inland to the historic 'white villiages' of Ronda and Casares, along to Gibraltar, or even a day trip to Morocco. Selwo National Park is 15km away. Based on an African safari park, it houses 2000 animals in semi-wild conditions. Windsurfing off the beach or 45 min's by car to Tarifa on the Atlantic coastline - the premier windsurfing venue in Europe. <br /><br />Rent Apartments in Duquesa - Further Details<br /><br />Other Activities: Selwo Nature Park, Prado World Water Park<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmyanimelist.net%2Fblog.php%3Feid%3D200311"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://myanimelist.net/blog.php?eid=200311</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>