<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="11">
		<document id="9d131d7e7045b2ecf5f7f3173b210c7b" url=""><![CDATA[Using Real Estate to Generate BIG BUCKS<br /><br/><br/>About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50dWxzaWFuaWludmVzdG1lbnRzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcml2YXRlaW52ZXN0bWVudGNsdWIuYml6L2VudHJlcHJlbnVlcnNoaXAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> believes that wealth-development is one particular of the most highly effective signifies there is on transforming our earth. Modern society progresses because it runs on funds and the demands it helps make, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cHM6Ly9wbHVzLmdvb2dsZS5jb20vMTE0MjU4NjY2MDcyMzkzMjg1NDMy" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> claims, the additional people there are with a lot more money the increased the standards a civilized culture has.<br /><br />My desire to invest and be financially free led me to Tulsiani Investments. I was lucky to have Sunil's knowledge and guidance at every step, which gave me confidence to overcome my FEAR for Real Estate Investing. Finally I made the decision to invest in my first property in Kitchener, which is below market value, positive cash flow, AAA location in downtown Kitchener, No property management, ROI of 30%. -Manmit Singh<br /><br />Acquire Good Deals - This goes together with acquiring motivated property or homeowners. Just because the person is motivate/distressed does not mean it is the right situation for you. You need to assess the property so as to be sure it will be an effective venture for you. Take into consideration what you want to do with the property for the long term. Have a plan to progress as well as a strategy to exit.<br /><br />Unsuccessful people find other reasons to procrastinate. They end up not investing. Successful people, on the other hand, are decisive and know to act immediately. When they find a property that can potentially make them thirty to one hundred thousand dollars or more, they put in an offer right away with proper conditions.<br />Think about it: If you have an offer in on a property with the following conditions:<br />=&gt; Conditional upon legal approval<br />=&gt; Conditional upon getting appropriate financing<br />=&gt; Conditional upon evaluation of the property<br />=&gt; Conditional upon your due diligence<br />(Note: Please receive proper legal advisement on all terminology used in your contracts)... then you have generally driven that property off the real estate market, no one else can have it. You have afforded yourself the time to assess everything properly, research the numbers and costs, get rental comparables for that area, etc. If the information does not look promising, you simply get out of the deal... period. The most important point here is to seek out and take advantage of money making opportunities or someone else will.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7ca7e7db44e73c2870066038b1374e4" url=""><![CDATA[Goals - Invisible to Visible<br/><br/>He who fails to plan, plans to fail. (Ancient prover<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" />	   <br /><br />Nearly all motivational speakers are advocates for the importance of goal setting. Tony Robbins has said: &quot;Setting goals is the first step in turning the invisible into the visible.&quot; To bring goals out of your thoughts and into the realm of being clearly visible many experts in the field of motivation use the S.M.A.R.T. acronym for goal setting.<br /><br />S - specific - details, a definite must for achievable goals<br />M - measurable - assessment of your progress<br />A - attainable -  within the reach of your current situation<br />R - relevant - a reflection of your aspirations and purpose<br />T - time-sensitive - milestones to mark your progress	   <br /><br />Specific - Be particular about the details of your goals. As you journey through life a detailed map can bring you to your destination. Knowing as much as possible about your objectives can ensure a greater chance of success in reaching them.	   <br />Measurable: Goals that are not measurable and recorded are little more than wishes.<br />Keeping track of the steps taken towards attaining your goals helps you to stay focussed and more able to reach deadlines. <br />&quot;When performance is measured, performance improves. When performance is measured and reported, the rate of improvement accelerates.&quot; Thomas S. Monson.<br />Experiencing and recording your progress towards your goals can generate a real sense of euphoria and can give you the confidence needed to continue on your path towards your goals.	   <br />Attainable - Don't let this part of the S.M.A.R.T. acronym dissuade you from setting goals that may seem unattainable at first. You will find that as you progress toward your goals your capacity to achieve will enlarge. Through working towards your goals you will enhance and develop the skills and abilities that will allow you to take advantage of opportunities. Perhaps even opportunities that were previously overlooked or that seemed unreachable.	   <br /><br />Relevant - Who are you, really? What is your purpose in life? Your goals reflect the underlying purpose of your life. Goals are the means by which you will achieve your purpose. It is best to be sure that your goals are relevant to who you are and what you want your efforts to be focused on.	   <br /><br />Timely - Beginning a project or steps towards a goal without a deadline can be detrimental to the end of that goal. Having a clear conclusion enables you to say &quot;Yes! That goal has been achieved.&quot;	<br /><br />Adhering to the practices found in the S.M.A.R.T. goal setting techniques will cultivate the ability to achieve your goals. Then, as Socrates had counseled, you will be well on your way to success. There is no other secret.	 <br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcml2YXRlaW52ZXN0bWVudGNsdWIuY2EvdHJhaW5pbmcvMjEtc3VuaWwtdHVsc2lhbmktZWJvb2stb24tY2FzaC1jb3ctcHJvcGVydGllcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNwYWNlLmNvbS90dWxzaWFuaWludmVzdG1lbnRz" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> is a committed citizen who strongly believes in socially responsible policies <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcml2YXRlaW52ZXN0bWVudGNsdWIuY2E_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> sees both equally PIC and TI as the ideal instruments to assist other individuals develop the prosperity they want.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42d71d12c32f38f22bc725685fdb0b80" url=""><![CDATA[Find Good Property as Investor<br/><br/>With all the gloom and doom we hear on television, you might think that investing in real estate is not such a great bargain right now. Actually, the reverse is true. The market will correct itself as it always does. Real estate is the first to suffer when things go away, but is the first to make a comeback, and in a huge way. <br /><br />Investment companies research economic and population projections to identify metropolitan areas with favorable growth outlooks, then we drill down to the community and neighborhood levels to forecast likely directions of growth and new construction. <br /><br />When you are considering purchasing a property for real estate investing, there are generally two ways to make money on the property you purchased. One, for instance, is from capital appreciation. This is where the value of the property increases, and the other is from renting your property out. <br /><br />Distressed real estate presents... a unique and temporary opportunity that has resulted from the tidal wave of residential (and expected commercial) foreclosures. The dramatic downturn of the housing market and simultaneous collapse of credit markets have created a demand for mechanisms that help return the massive inventory of foreclosed properties from the possession of the banks back to the market. Far from being a &quot;vulture&quot; in this space, investing joint ventures allow investors to participate in a systematic, proprietary methodology that allows nationwide assets to be sold back into the marketplace.<br /><br />The location of the investment property is also an important factor. Regardless of whether or not you purchase a rental property well below its market value, if you can't find tenants for the property, it won't matter. Make sure you choose a property in a location where there is a demand for housing. Researching the market can save you the hassle of a poor choice in real estate investing. Also, you want to make sure the property you choose will appeal to the masses.<br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzdGFyLmNvbS9CdXNpbmVzcy9JbnZlc3RpbmcvYXJ0aWNsZS81MzM0Njc_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3R1bHNpYW5paW52ZXN0bWVudHMucWFwYWNpdHkuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> is 'The Wealthy Cop' - a former Canadian policeman who's manufactured good in real estate investing he has become a prosperity-generating guru for hundreds of traders who flock to him to assist them attain the very same benefits for on their own. By way of the twin, but separate vehicles of Private Expense Club (PIC) and Tulsiani Investments (TI), <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50dWxzaWFuaWludmVzdG1lbnRzLmNvbS9zdWNjZXNzLnBkZg__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> has designed the perfect environment to enable unfold his own difficult-won know-how.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="90e7df747edf5fee22c6a7f30a5dec2c" url=""><![CDATA[Investment Ideas for Beginners<br/><br/>Is Real Estate Investment Wise For Retirement? Yes, it is. But first you must understand the real estate market. Don't be taken in by the so-called invest &quot;gurus&quot; that you see so often on early Sunday television. Real estate investment is a tough subject to learn because of all the laws and different aspects of the market.<br /><br />Wealth building, through real estate investment, is one of those areas where you get to work with highly motivated people who are prepared to work hard and work intelligently in order to get where they want and that provides a lot of satisfaction at a personal level.<br /><br />The network of external contacts helps specific possible acquisitions on which the companies perform initial due diligence and economic analysis. Only those select projects that demonstrate superior potential move to the next step of the process. Above all, the advisors invest in every project with you so both parties have a vested interest in the outcome.<br /><br />Distressed real estate presents... a unique and temporary opportunity that has resulted from the tidal wave of residential (and expected commercial) foreclosures. The dramatic downturn of the housing market and simultaneous collapse of credit markets have created a demand for mechanisms that help return the massive inventory of foreclosed properties from the possession of the banks back to the market. Far from being a &quot;vulture&quot; in this space, investing joint ventures allow investors to participate in a systematic, proprietary methodology that allows nationwide assets to be sold back into the marketplace.<br /><br />Obviously, one of the most important factors in determining whether a property is a good investment or not, is to consider the price of the property. If after you've made the initial down payment and your mortgage payment is over and above what you can rent the property out for, you will find that to be a poor investment. One of the most important factors is determining whether or not the property will bring in a positive monthly cash flow for you.<br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcml2YXRlaW52ZXN0bWVudGNsdWIuY2EvdHJhaW5pbmcvMjEtc3VuaWwtdHVsc2lhbmktZWJvb2stb24tY2FzaC1jb3ctcHJvcGVydGllcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcml2YXRlaW52ZXN0bWVudGNsdWIuYml6L2VudHJlcHJlbnVlcnNoaXAuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> believes that prosperity-development is a person of the most strong means there is on shifting our globe. Society progresses mainly because it runs on income and the demands it makes, <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NhLmxpbmtlZGluLmNvbS9wdWIvc3VuaWwtdHVsc2lhbmkvMTgvMjA4Lzc1" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> claims, the far more people there are with much more dollars the larger the expectations a civilized culture has.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="265efb53fb97e604822221adb27753ba" url=""><![CDATA[How to Search for Good Property to Invest in<br/><br/>With all the gloom and doom we hear on television, you might think that investing in real estate is not such a great bargain right now. Actually, the reverse is true. The market will correct itself as it always does. Real estate is the first to suffer when things go away, but is the first to make a comeback, and in a huge way. <br /><br />Investment companies research economic and population projections to identify metropolitan areas with favorable growth outlooks, then we drill down to the community and neighborhood levels to forecast likely directions of growth and new construction. <br /><br />The network of external contacts helps specific possible acquisitions on which the companies perform initial due diligence and economic analysis. Only those select projects that demonstrate superior potential move to the next step of the process. Above all, the advisors invest in every project with you so both parties have a vested interest in the outcome.<br /><br />Wealth making should not be an exclusive club, the more people become involved and benefit from it the better it is for our communities and the world we live in. Wealth building tips should never be something we keep to ourselves, and a society in which everyone has the opportunity to become wealthy is a society which is more equitable and has the potential to have far fewer problems than one in which there are inherent inequalities which cannot be overcome. <br /><br />Just because you like the uniqueness of a house, doesn't mean someone else will and you may have trouble renting or selling when the time comes. <br />If the investment property you are considering is a fixer-upper, you may want to bring a contractor with you to determine the cost for repairs as well as renovations. You will want to figure this into the cost of the property and if it will not yield you a return on your money, whether you plan to sell or rent, you are taking the risk that it may be a very poor investment.<br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50dWxzaWFuaWludmVzdG1lbnRzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3R1bHNpYW5paW52ZXN0bWVudHMucWFwYWNpdHkuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> is a dedicated citizen who strongly believes in socially responsible insurance policies <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3VyaG9tZS5jYS9ob21lcy9hcnRpY2xlLzU0Mjk5Mw__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> sees each PIC and TI as the excellent instruments to assist other people develop the prosperity they need to have.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="df4a8fe9d049740e0e84014892677255" url=""><![CDATA[Investment Techs in the Gloomy Market<br/><br/>With all the gloom and doom we hear on television, you might think that investing in real estate is not such a great bargain right now. Actually, the reverse is true. The market will correct itself as it always does. Real estate is the first to suffer when things go away, but is the first to make a comeback, and in a huge way. <br /><br />Wealth building, through real estate investment, is one of those areas where you get to work with highly motivated people who are prepared to work hard and work intelligently in order to get where they want and that provides a lot of satisfaction at a personal level.<br /><br />We saw it as a vehicle which would allow investors to come on-board and leverage the expertise and advice from experts to their benefit. Investing is never risk-free of course. There are always difficulties involved because the real estate market, like every other market you can invest in, is subject to volatility from external factors no one can control.<br /><br />Distressed real estate presents... a unique and temporary opportunity that has resulted from the tidal wave of residential (and expected commercial) foreclosures. The dramatic downturn of the housing market and simultaneous collapse of credit markets have created a demand for mechanisms that help return the massive inventory of foreclosed properties from the possession of the banks back to the market. Far from being a &quot;vulture&quot; in this space, investing joint ventures allow investors to participate in a systematic, proprietary methodology that allows nationwide assets to be sold back into the marketplace.<br /><br />The location of the investment property is also an important factor. Regardless of whether or not you purchase a rental property well below its market value, if you can't find tenants for the property, it won't matter. Make sure you choose a property in a location where there is a demand for housing. Researching the market can save you the hassle of a poor choice in real estate investing. Also, you want to make sure the property you choose will appeal to the masses.<br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcml2YXRlaW52ZXN0bWVudGNsdWIuY2EvdHJhaW5pbmcvMjEtc3VuaWwtdHVsc2lhbmktZWJvb2stb24tY2FzaC1jb3ctcHJvcGVydGllcy5odG1s" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a>As a outcome <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNwYWNlLmNvbS90dWxzaWFuaWludmVzdG1lbnRz" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a>'s 'secret' mission is to transform a small part of the earth. The a lot more profitable we turn into and the a lot more men and women we aid, the higher the odds that their earth will also be much better and what they do will positively impact their quick contacts and communities. It really is challenging to feel that real estate traders can be agents of alter but <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcml2YXRlaW52ZXN0bWVudGNsdWIuY2E_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> provides the exception which may well properly demonstrate the rule.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ba8deea044930136411f3751cc24f60f" url=""><![CDATA[Search for Real Estate for Investment<br/><br/>Having experience needed to accomplish the numerous complex tasks leading to success is a key, as well as solid relationships with developers and builders that further enable you to realize the optimal value of projects.<br /><br />Whether you plan to flip houses or rent them out, real estate can be a very profitable business for yourself. While determining whether or not a property will make a good investment or not can be difficult, the important thing to remember is to always do your research. <br /><br />The competition is a rife and spreading your name, let alone your company in such a large area, can be a big challenge. This market is more cut-throat and possibly requires a sales person with comprehensive client canvassing strategies and is, by nature, is determined and competitive.<br /><br />It is very important to negotiate what you believe to be favorable terms for acquiring the land or other underdeveloped real estate assets, by utilizing inspection periods, deposits, options, conditional offers and elements of seller financing to structure transactions in ways that reduce the exposure to possible market shifts or hidden property defects.<br /><br />The acquisition of properties with high yield allows us to increase the level of financial independence, thus allowing a better quality of life. The realization of your life's objectives is one of the most important goals. Financial security is something that every family deserves especially in a time of need.<br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzdGFyLmNvbS9CdXNpbmVzcy9JbnZlc3RpbmcvYXJ0aWNsZS81MzM0Njc_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcmxvZy5vcmcvMTA4MjM4MDMtc3VuaWwtdHVsc2lhbmktdGVzdGltb25pYWxzLW9mLXR1bHNpYW5pLWludmVzdG1lbnRzLXByb3ZpZGVkLWJ5LXN1bmlsLXR1bHNpYW5pLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> is a dedicated citizen who strongly believes in socially accountable policies <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3VyaG9tZS5jYS9ob21lcy9hcnRpY2xlLzU0Mjk5Mw__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> sees equally PIC and TI as the perfect instruments to support other individuals produce the prosperity they will need.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="19f983458c5675b58bc1fba88b0b54a5" url=""><![CDATA[How to Identify Good Property for Investment<br/><br/>When it comes to wealth making advice it is always preferable to listen to the experts and follow their lead as it is their expertise which makes the difference between advice that's 'out there' and targeted tips which really work. The markets are always volatile and you can never predict what will happen from month to month, but with the kind of targeted, specific advice necessary to help you make better informed decisions.<br /><br />When you are considering purchasing a property for real estate investing, there are generally two ways to make money on the property you purchased. One, for instance, is from capital appreciation. This is where the value of the property increases, and the other is from renting your property out. <br /><br />Obviously, one of the most important factors in determining whether a property is a good investment or not, is to consider the price of the property. If after you've made the initial down payment and your mortgage payment is over and above what you can rent the property out for, you will find that to be a poor investment. One of the most important factors is determining whether or not the property will bring in a positive monthly cash flow for you.<br /><br />Whether you plan to flip houses or rent them out, real estate can be a very profitable business for yourself. While determining whether or not a property will make a good investment or not can be difficult, the important thing to remember is to always do your research. <br /><br />Advises for your project-based capital placements should be focusing on communities that feature:<br />* High population growth projections and favorable demographics<br />* Strong local job development trends and community plans<br />* Master planning and infrastructure investment that facilitate development<br />* Availability of prime raw land for conversion to residential and commercial uses<br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1bmlsdHVsc2lhbmkuY2E_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3R1bHNpYW5paW52ZXN0bWVudHMucWFwYWNpdHkuY29tLw__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> is 'The Wealthy Cop' - a former Canadian policeman who's created excellent in real estate investing he has become a wealth-earning expert for hundreds of investors who flock to him to aid them realize the exact same benefits for on their own. As a result of the twin, but separate vehicles of Personal Investment Club (PIC) and Tulsiani Investments (TI), <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3VyaG9tZS5jYS9ob21lcy9hcnRpY2xlLzU0Mjk5Mw__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> has produced the ideal environment to assist pass on his very own challenging-won expertise.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2609447e7bc34c123edc6608c3b8b4f6" url=""><![CDATA[An Evidenced Way of Choosing Success<br/><br/>Every day there are choices to be made. Making a choice is like picking up a stick. When you pick up one end of a stick the other end of the stick logically comes along with it. When a choice is made a consequence always comes with it.  As I write this I feel as if I am a parent warning my children of an impending punishment for bad behavior. Yet this is has nothing to do with punishments. It is just a fact. That is all.<br /><br />The unknown can be diminished though. Quality advice from someone who has already made these kinds of changes can diminish the unknown. Someone that can advise you as to the consequences of your decisions is invaluable. I believe my shy childhood friends would have enjoyed the game of drawing straws if they could have had someone to coach them through their choices.<br /><br />In this light, it seems reasonable that everyone would want use the most effective way to become successful. During the years that I have trained people no one has ever argued with this fact. This is a blueprint for success. Those who are not successful in their life’s purposes may understand this blueprint but they will not use it to build their own success. Many people who are achievers follow this design. Achievers find mentors to guide them.<br /><br />It may be a challenge to find such an individual, a great mentor. Yet if you are strategic about this choice it will make all the difference in the world. <br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50dWxzaWFuaWludmVzdG1lbnRzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNwYWNlLmNvbS90dWxzaWFuaWludmVzdG1lbnRz" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> is a committed citizen who strongly believes in socially liable policies <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cHM6Ly9wbHVzLmdvb2dsZS5jb20vMTE0MjU4NjY2MDcyMzkzMjg1NDMy" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> sees equally PIC and TI as the best instruments to help other individuals generate the prosperity they need to have.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3489f09401b095175e9f1b24d881855" url=""><![CDATA[Secrets to success<br /><br/><br/>Keep the positive thoughts at the fore front of your mind. This is an important tool in goal achievement. We all know the saying “Be careful what you wish for... you might just receive it.” It is this way with our thoughts. When we dwell on positive things we will be more likely to see opportunities to make those positive things become reality.<br /><br />Pay attention to the details. This does not mean micro-managing. You can be aware of the small facts and daily minutia without letting them overwhelm you. <br />It is better to learn from these details and respond by making adjustments than to ignore them until they become a crisis.<br /><br />Reliability and honesty. Without these two keys already in place there is no point to the rest of these success tips. Be responsible for your own actions, otherwise nothing else matters.<br /><br />Ask yourself “What would I do if I knew I would succeed?” What new things would you institute that would set you apart from everyone else? If you have an innovative idea follow it!<br /><br />Associate only with positive, focused people who you can learn from and who will not drain your valuable energy with complaining and uninspiring attitudes. By developing relationships with those committed to constant improvement and the pursuit of the best that life has to offer, you will have plenty of company on your path to the top of whatever mountain you seek to climb.<br /><br />About <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cHM6Ly9wbHVzLmdvb2dsZS5jb20vMTE0MDY4MTA5NTYyMzg4MjEwNzAx" target="_blank">Mr Tulsiani</a><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzdGFyLmNvbS9idXNpbmVzcy9pbnZlc3RpbmcvYXJ0aWNsZS81MzM0NjctLWludmVzdG1lbnQtZ3JvdXBpZXM_" target="_blank">Sunil</a> - There can under no circumstances be any guarantees in any form of investing. The markets are often unstable and you can in no way predict what will take place from thirty day period to month. <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcmxvZy5vcmcvMTA4MjM4MDMtc3VuaWwtdHVsc2lhbmktdGVzdGltb25pYWxzLW9mLXR1bHNpYW5pLWludmVzdG1lbnRzLXByb3ZpZGVkLWJ5LXN1bmlsLXR1bHNpYW5pLmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Sunil</a> claims: but by means of Personal Investment Club (PIC) and Tulsiani Investments (TI) you can, at least, get the kind of targeted, specific suggestions essential to enable you make much better informed choices.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8c704d4c18dfa46a59f4b2ef0b2a0a5c" url=""><![CDATA[Keys to great outcomes<br /><br/><br/>Keep the positive thoughts at the fore front of your mind. This is an important tool in goal achievement. We all know the saying “Be careful what you wish for... you might just receive it.” It is this way with our thoughts. When we dwell on positive things we will be more likely to see opportunities to make those positive things become reality.<br /><br />Learn and practice effective communication skills. Written and  oral communication skills are a must have for the success-oriented person. These talents will help you understand and motivate others, which will in turn, help you develop a network of supportive people.<br /><br />Reliability and honesty. Without these two keys already in place there is no point to the rest of these success tips. Be responsible for your own actions, otherwise nothing else matters.<br /><br />Learn to enjoy the journey. Regularly take the time to   measure your progress toward your goals. Plan to celebrate and  take pride in what you have accomplished as you reach mile stones along your pathway to success.<br /><br />No one can insult or hurt you without your permission. One of the golden keys to happiness and great success is the way you interpret events which unfold before you. Highly successful people are master interpreters. People who have attained greatness have an ability which they have developed to interpret negative or disempowering events as positive challenges which will assist them in growing and moving even farther up the ladder of success. There are no negative experiences only experiences which aid in your development and toughen your character so that you may soar to new heights. There are no failures, only lessons.<br /><br />About Sunil Tulsiani <br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcml2YXRlaW52ZXN0bWVudGNsdWIuY2EvYWR2ZXJ0aXNlbWVudC1vcHRpb25zLzIxLXN1bmlsLXR1bHNpYW5pLWVib29rLW9uLWNhc2gtY293LXByb3BlcnRpZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank">Sunil Tulsiani</a> is really a dedicated citizen who strongly emphasizes from social responsible guidelines. Sunil Tulsiani considers both the PIC and also TI as being the ideal recources to assist other folks generate the riches they'll desire. Need know more about <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1bmlsdHVsc2lhbmkuY2E_" target="_blank">commercial real estate investors</a>, remember to click on the link - <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzdGFyLmNvbS9idXNpbmVzcy9pbnZlc3RpbmcvYXJ0aWNsZS81MzM0NjctLWludmVzdG1lbnQtZ3JvdXBpZXM_" target="_blank"><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thestar.com%2Fbusiness%2Finvesting%2Farticle%2F533467--investment-groupies"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.thestar.com/business/investing/article/533467--investment-groupies</a></a>, or visit public web sites - suniltulsiani.ca.
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>