<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="12">
		<document id="19dbe53fc768be7ffb710ae0092b2241" url=""><![CDATA[Artist Interview<br/><br/>Today, when my mother visited the company, met a painter by accident. Is a well-known landscape painters. I conducted an interview with him.
<br />  According to him, his favorite painting is the landscape, his main studio to ink painting,he was very much like the Chinese landscape.His name was Chun-Ling Wang, born in Nanjing. He is a native of Nanjing.He took me to a tour of his exhibition. Original exhibition of his company in building next to my mother's work building.His exhibition not only has many beautiful pictures, and a teahouse inside the exhibition hall.He not only likes to draw, he likes tea.His exhibition called &quot;View of River Museum of Art&quot;, in Nanjing is a famous Museum of Art.Because at that time had just opened his exhibition, and we ended the interview. My farewell him.
<br />  This interview, I learned what a painter.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e626453119ddae53c687e3f63d951b81" url=""><![CDATA[Restaurant<br/><br/>Today is the day of holidays, grade three students to lead us to a company called &quot;Hello, Italy&quot; in the hotel dining.
<br />  The restaurant is small, there are many foreigners gathered here meal. We set a bench as our dinner location. Although this restaurant is small but has the atmosphere of Italy.Food prices are expensive here, just a small noodles to spend my 60 dollars. Really very scary.Here are the dishes are done, so we waited a long time.We all feel a little disappointed, the food there was very little weight.But waiting so long, we all hungry. So we ate all the food. Flavor of the food here can only be general. We do not feel good to eat.I also ordered a dessert, a little ice cream actually worth 30 dollars, it is too expensive.I do not think that this restaurant is ideal for our students, this restaurant needs to consume the high consumption group.And I do not really enjoy the food, the food here is not my taste.But after this event I learned that what is Italian cuisine.This is a good practice.
<br />  After this event, I understand what is Italian cuisine.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="42ccaf58ed2605f5c52b4bd4ea22383d" url=""><![CDATA[club<br/><br/>I am honored to join a lot of clubs, badminton clubs is one of them.
<br />  Above the General Assembly on Friday, the club decided to host a list of activities, so we went to Nanjing Normal University on Saturday to play badminton in the gym.It is a cloudy day, but  we rented indoor space, so did not affect our enthusiasm of playing badminton.I like to play badminton, this is one of my favorite hobbies,Because I think badminton is beneficial to health.I started playing badminton a long time ago, I first encountered  badminton is at my school.But at that time  I did not know how to play badminton, but now I've got good technology.I arrived early in the badminton hall, they had packed a lot of venues where we played a very wonderful time. I would like to have such sports once every week, and my body will be more healthy.A few hours passed quickly, and we bid farewell to each other and went home. This is a meaningful event.
<br />  I really like this activity, I would like to take part in this club activities.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="16148c136937e569ed2ecfc91d068530" url=""><![CDATA[University<br/><br/>In the winter, I went to Nanjing University to volunteer to help the researcher in doing the experiments.
<br />  The temperature was very low those days, and it was very cold, I came to University's Research center and I joined researchers in doing experiments. I feel that members are very hard at their tests, because they have to handle such a cold day sticking out their hands into the cold test containers. Although they had the protection of rubber gloves, but gloves were thin layers.  What is the use? I quickly joined the ranks of laboratory assistant.Water was too cold, barbing with our hands. In that afternoon my hand  received the &quot;harm&quot; and at last they had no feeling, which made me very tired and weary. I fully understand as a researcher, no matter what kind of weather it is, and no matter how difficult they are, they have to complete their experiments. Becoming a researcher really was not easy.I continued to work there for many days, met a lot of good researchers. They said to me: &quot;This is holiday now, we do not have a lot of experiments to do, if not in the holiday, we will do much more experiments.&quot; But to me they do too many experiments in the holiday, so researchers is a hard job.
<br />  A few days of volunteer work let me know becoming a good  researcher is really not easy.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="b00eddfaf283cd75daa586cf9b04621" url=""><![CDATA[Lunch with students<br/><br/>Today is Sunday, I and my classmates JOHN, JEFFEREY went to a restaurant called &quot;Henry House&quot; to have lunch.
<br />  It was only 11 o'clock when we came to &quot;Henry House&quot; restaurant . This restaurant is not large, with gray lighting show It has a kind of atmosphere of Western restaurant. The price of food is not expensive, but it is much more than those ordinary Chinese restaurants. Though we had ordered only several things, it cost us several hundred renminbi. This is not an inexpensive lunch, but I like the atmosphere here. The food is very romantic, very delicious. Although it is a relatively small place, but I still love eating here. Ater the past few tens of minutes, a pizza and a bowl of  rice was placed in front of me. I have to say that it taste good, but it is very little. I ate all the food, but I was not fully enough to eat. The food tastes great, I like the taste.Because food is delicious, we ate a long time and ate all of it .After dinner was done, because the environment here is very good, we stayed there for a longer time and enjoyed ourselves. Then we left the restaurant happily.
<br />  This is a very fun trip, I miss the actiivity.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7c905cd39f83265dcf7d3f86ac4a4f4b" url=""><![CDATA[Zheng<br/><br/>Zheng is an ancient Chinese String instruments, &quot;Cheng-chu&quot; can move freely, a string of a sound, press the pentatonic arrangement, the first maximum of 25 string zither.
<br />  My mother organized a learning unit Zheng's cultural activities, I am honored to be invited to take part in activities,This is a great event, a lot of young people came to the site to visit or participate in the event.Zheng is the name of our ancient family of musical instruments.I'm very interested in Zheng.I like Zheng's melodious voice and classic tunes.This is so intoxicated with the people.But Zheng is not very easy to learn,Professional zither player must use the fake nails to play the zither. No matter how it is cold, or how hot it is, the player should practise it every day. I learned it for a long time, and it injured my fingers. Though I am still not good at learning the use of zheng, I will not give it up, I will take more efforts to study the zheng.
<br />  Good instruments are difficult to use, so a Chinese want to learn the classical instruments is not a very easy thing!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="aaf238a79f44afb370238da514bf1ab5" url=""><![CDATA[Art exhibition<br/><br/>My mother's company organized a large-scale exhibition. Because my mother is the unit's staff, so we are honored to receive the two exhibition tickets.
<br />  This is a lively exhibition, many of the important leaders in the local came to visit this exhibition. There are many works from well-known Chinese contemporary and ancient artists , In accordance with the scale of the exhibition, these paintings should all be authentic. It can not imagine how much time and how much money cost to prepare for this exhibition! It is very surprising and admirable.I have basically unheard of these paintings before, but I like these paintings, these paintings have a charm of Chinese classical. The characters looked very much  comfortable. The most landscape on exhibition confirms the title of China's great rivers and mountains.Although only two-storey exhibition, but the exhibition hall is 1,000 square meters, and full of many works on the gallery floor, this is how great a show!
<br />  The exhibition was my first experience to see a lot of famous paintings, which also cultivated my sense of art.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c1820334908b8e25f44a680940f0188c" url=""><![CDATA[Art exhibition2<br/><br/>Today, I and my classmates went to the Caojun's exhibition.By exhibition I understand the modern artist's painting style.
<br />  It was 10 am when I and my classmates came to the Yangtze River Road Gallery,It is a large 3-storey exhibition hall. We visited each floor of the exhibition.Unfortunately, some good art are not allowed visitors to take photographs, I can not record all these beautiful pictures.Caojun is a painter based in ink.So his paintings are basically ink.He loved painting the lion, we could see a lot of lions in ink .He always likened a robust Chinese lion.He also painted some abstract paintings, in his paintings, we can see his love of Chinese landscape.I like his paintings.His words are very classical and the people looked very comfortable, His paintings also give people a sense of three-dimensio, and very magical.I was attracted by his works so much that I forget to return, and his style conbines classic elegance with a very modern.
<br />  It was a spectacular event, I understand the significance of Chinese ink painting.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="24625462087d9af4ad809325f5efc60f" url=""><![CDATA[Church<br/><br/>Today, my classmates and I went to Jiangsu Road Church, there is a very spectacular place, where we understand what is religion.
<br />  I and my classmates arrived at the church door at 7 am.Many church people had ended their worship today. Many priests and bishops guided the many Christians to sing holy songs.We entered the cathedral with some of the clergy. There is a spectacular place. There were  many pastors in front leading singing sacred songs. Inside the church, it was filled with the sacred air .Activities still continued, we slowly exited the Cathedral and then posed for pictures outside.I believe in God, although my family do not believe in any one religion.This is not the first time I came to this church, but it still gave me a fresh feeling.It is a good place to pray to God.
<br />  This is an exciting travel, the event let me know the church's sacred and there are many people who believe in God.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2a6352bc7f34c6feb6e441a080fde225" url=""><![CDATA[Nursing home<br/><br/>I and my fellow students to do volunteer work to the nursing home, this is a fun activity to help the elderly because we have  a lot of things to do.
<br />  Nursing home is in the suburb of Nanjing, and it is a very remote place, where we met a lot of vicissitudes in the elderly. An old man said he was born before the last century, which is really fantastic. The old man is more than 100 years old.Most old people here are not taken care by friends and their children. Many of them are at the same age here, and they take care of each other. This is a very tragic and sad thing. We brought some fruit for these old people. They were very happy to chat with us, told us their stories, and also share pictures with us. When we came here they were very excited.We accompanied the old people in the whole afternoon. At last  we had to bid farewell to these miserable old man.
<br />  We will miss the memory. This allows us to know how to treat the elderly.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="59d78dbac3c80c4d6a69720f2d3b18f6" url=""><![CDATA[Temple<br/><br/>This is a sunny weather, I and my classmates to visit Jiuhuashan Park.
<br />  This is an ancient temple, despite it has experinced many times' reconstruction, but still preserved temple has venerable chill breath.But it is said inside the temple there are ancient monk &quot;Xuanzang&quot;'s dressed and staves, this are very rare rare things. Journey story believe everyone already clear understanding passed when we met Journey items in will have a fresh feeling.Temple also retained other monasteries characteristics incense rampant. Many believers are came to this ancient temple burning incense and Buddha for this ancient temple adds many lively breath.We  visited whole Jiuhuashan park have uncanny workmanship Luohan hole thrills limit sports center, bustling prosperous temple. Standing at Jiuhua Peak, we overlooked entire Nanjing city not only seeing Xuanwu Lake but also seeing Zijinshan, two Nanjing symbols.We also try to pray with believers together. But we have no feeling, because we do not believe this religious.Time flies, we left the Jiuhuashan Park.
<br />  The event made me realize the sense of Buddhist, I have learned the art of Buddhism.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="448a3c231228fe45556af18f4969e9d3" url=""><![CDATA[Concert<br/><br/>This is a beautiful night, and I alone went to Nanjing music to listen to Shen was the concert hall.
<br />  Great concert halls, and a large concert hall stand in front of signs. Soon, the concert will begin, and I entered the concert hall. Inside the seat is made of wood.Shen was a pianist, he was born in the mountain city of Chongqing. He was known as the piano genius from childhood. When he was 11 years old as the piano more get a national first prize.The concert started, because voice and Shen afraid of the camera flash to disturb him, so forbidden to take pictures.He is good at big musician Beethoven, from the soft music heard fortitude.I unknowingly intoxicated in  his music.Several hours passed quickly, I am reluctant to leave the music hall.The concert ended?
<br />  I love the piano, I also like the music he played
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>