<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="19">
		<document id="5d04cc5d5bfa1ce8696b9754eb9e2056" url=""><![CDATA[Rich people constantly learn and grow<br/><br/>We are all born with a vast capacity to explore and learn. Unfortunately, many of us never discover what we are truly capable of because we never fully unleash the power of learning. As kids, we perpetually keep learning from everything and everybody due to our inquisitiveness. But as we grow old, we start taking many of the things around us for granted. An important rule of leadership is to rediscover the joy of learning so that we could expand our capabilities and productivities.
<br />Full Story here: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53b3Jrd2l0aG1jLmNvbS8yL3Bvc3QvMjAxMS8wNC9yaWNoLXBlb3BsZS1jb25zdGFudGx5LWxlYXJuLWFuZC1ncm93LXBvb3ItcGVvcGxlLXRoaW5rLXRoZXktYWxyZWFkeS1rbm93Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank">Rich people constantly learn and grow poor people think they already know</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="be50246ea84ef1a299b57afe81cdec48" url=""><![CDATA[My links<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dvcmt3aXRobWFya2Nob28uY29tL2xlYWQtZ2VuZXJhdGlvbg__" target="_blank">FREE Training on how to Start Making Money w/ FaceBook!</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dvcmt3aXRobWFya2Nob28uY29tL291ci1uYXRpb25hbC05MTEtZmxhZw__" target="_blank">Our National 9/11 Flag is now part of History</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mcmVld2Vla2x5dHJhaW5pbmcuaW5mbw__" target="_blank">How to Get on the Google Search Engine in 72 Hours PROOF!</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dvcmt3aXRobWFya2Nob28uY29tL2Z1bmRyYWlzaW5nLXByb2dyYW0_" target="_blank">Looking for a FREE Fundraising Program for your Organization</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29ubHl3aXJlLmNvbS9yLzQ1NzMwMDU3" target="_blank">Why we all need a PLAN-B in todays economy!</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29ubHl3aXJlLmNvbS9yLzQ1NTExNzQ2" target="_blank">Why we all need a PLAN B in todays economy</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29ubHl3aXJlLmNvbS9yLzQ1NTExMTY0" target="_blank">The Difference between the Rich and the Poor</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29ubHl3aXJlLmNvbS9yLzQ1MzU4NzM0" target="_blank">Rich people constantly learn and grow while poor people think they already know</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29ubHl3aXJlLmNvbS9yLzQ1MTgxOTM1" target="_blank">Creating your Success with Luck</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29ubHl3aXJlLmNvbS9yLzQ0NzU2NTMy" target="_blank">So is College a Waste of time in Todays World</a>
<br /><br /><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5Xb3JrV2l0aE1DLmNvbQ__" target="_blank">Welcome to Mark Choo Online - HOME</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3f3fba04ec5fc5fe4aa356dae040f727" url=""><![CDATA[How to Build a Website Webinar Training Series<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Fmark-choo-recommends%2Fhow-to-build-a-website"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/mark-choo-recommends/how-to-build-a-website</a> 
<br /><br />My First 80 Guest get this class for FREE! There are still a few seats left but you should hurry! How to build a website just like this one that will brand you and your business!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1cc62026e6d4ea30fd4f3cd32951179f" url=""><![CDATA[Exactly how he’s been able to help so many marketers achie<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeweeklytraining.info"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.freeweeklytraining.info</a> 
<br /><br />This Wednesday Night YOU are invited to join us as we welcome Mark to our Wednesday Webinar platform and get a chance to grill him on exactly how he’s been able to help so many marketers achieve success! Register NOW!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="eb521085ef7b0d27a057767360629546" url=""><![CDATA[Tonights FREE Webinar - How to Absolutely Crush It In Your B<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeweeklytraining.info"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.freeweeklytraining.info</a> 
<br /><br />John Tonight at 9PM they’re going to work with you on overcoming some of these major hurdles and challenges that are holding you back.<br />For more info on the poster Mark and more FREE Training visit: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Flead-generation"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/lead-generation</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1e68c753942fddf64331482ef55be98f" url=""><![CDATA[GOOD NEWS - The Recording of the FIRST CLASS in now up!<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Ffirst-session"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/first-session</a> 
<br /><br />I am happy share this valuable info with you and to inform you that if you missed it, the recording for the First Class (How to Build a Website to Brand YOU and YOUR BUSINESS) has been uploaded and is now available for everyone to view. We still have a few seats left if you would like to join us next week!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="4f69c638033e781bec27751e5e822d3" url=""><![CDATA[TONIGHT - FaceBook Marketing Queen Reveals Some Tricks<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeweeklytraining.info"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.freeweeklytraining.info</a> 
<br /><br />If you’re tired of watching everyone else make a fortune on FaceBook but you, this webinar will ease your pain!<br />If you’re ready to finally see what the FB “gurus” have been hiding from you, We’ll see you Wednesday at 9 PM SHARP. Click here to register: ==&gt; <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeweeklytraining.info"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.freeweeklytraining.info</a> and for more info you can also visit my other website here: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a1aeb17e16d0fd0eaa3d43e969d21f7b" url=""><![CDATA[FREE Training Tonight -The Secret of SOLO ADS - 100+ Leads<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Flead-generation%2Ffree-wednesday-night-training"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/lead-generation/free-wednesday-night-training</a> 
<br /><br />Here is another FREE class for tonight!<br />Here is what will be covered on this webinar TONIGHT: <br /><br />These leaders are INCREDIBLE!<br />Where else does such a group of leaders unite<br />to form this type of community and culture to<br />provide the BEST training on the internet<br />to you for F*R*E*E every single Wednesday?! Read on...<br />*******<br /><br />100, 200, 300, even 400+ Leads PER DAY Mark!<br /><br />Yup.<br /><br />That's right. Another MLM leader CRUSHING<br />it in the field.<br /><br />His secret: SOLO ADS<br /><br />And YES he's agreed to share his secrets<br />with YOU this Wednesday, December 7th at<br />9 PM EST!<br /><br />UNBELIEVABLE.<br /><br />You see, SOLO ADS are a great paid advertising<br />method for non-techie people, and people who<br />don't have a lot of time to spend on content marketing.<br /><br />It also gives people yet another simple option for<br />paid traffic, and ANYBODY CAN DO THIS!<br /><br />Take a look at some of what Jaime's about to unveil<br />to you this Wednesday:<br />•  What are SOLO ADS <br /><br />* How you can leverage solo ads to explode<br />your list overnight<br /><br />* How you can get your offer
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="8ff504f85b44fc909f154c77ff4de6ba" url=""><![CDATA[Master Sponsoring Strategy will be Revealed TONIGHT LIVE!<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Flead-generation%2Ffree-wednesday-night-training"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/lead-generation/free-wednesday-night-training</a> 
<br /><br />His HIGHEST YIELDING Skill-Set: Sponsoring. And it gets better...Not only is this guy a proven Master Prospector, but he only recruits LEADERS. You MUST attend this webinar if you're looking to be the &quot;#1 INCOME EARNER in YOUR company&quot; and only work with leaders who will BUILD your business and create for you a TRUE WALK-AWAY, RESIDUAL INCOME?! I will see you tonight....This is going to be a GOOD one!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3616c20de66ca022efcd69290f2214ce" url=""><![CDATA[PLEASE HELP A family in Dire Need!<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdeservingfamily.chipin.com%2Fa-family-in-dire-need"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://deservingfamily.chipin.com/a-family-in-dire-need</a> 
<br /><br />Please take a moment and read this story. If you cannot HELP, PLEASE pass it on. Keep passing it on. Please help us help them into a small rental home for Christmas.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="dff92c733415ea6e4ce3f532db7f8b03" url=""><![CDATA["How a Real Estate guy in Foreclosure Sponsored 28 Peo<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmarkchoo.mysponsoringsecrets.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://markchoo.mysponsoringsecrets.com</a> 
<br /><br />FREE 89 Minute Training Webinar Reveals… &quot;How a Real Estate guy in Foreclosure Sponsored 28 People in 21 Days at a Minimum $500 Buy-In, and Today Regularly Enjoys Multiple $5-Figure Months in Residual Income Thanks to ONE Skill-Set He Mastered...&quot; His Best-Kept Sponsoring Secrets Are Inside This FREE Training...
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="71f7c41dce4c58cc680da6dad9e24ef6" url=""><![CDATA[THE 3 TYPES OF INCOME YOU SHOULD GENERATE IN 2012<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Ffree-wednesday-night-training"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/free-wednesday-night-training</a> 
<br /><br />Let's face it, sometimes this can be a frustrating business, can't it? Rob can relate. He started out just like you Mark. So how did Rob go from zero to $100,000 in only 14 months, become a top 20 Income Earner with a team of over 10,000 active distributors worldwide, earning six figures as a PART-TIME affiliate marketer?<br />Tune in Wednesday, Dec. 21, 9PM EST to find out.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="bf61605f3b5cc43ed16453acbe52adec" url=""><![CDATA[Happy New Year Let's Connect on Facebook<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffacebook.com%2Fmarkychoo"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://facebook.com/markychoo</a> 
<br /><br />Happy New Year my Friends! ~ Let's Connect on Personal Facebook Profile: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffacebook.com%2Fmarkychoo"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://facebook.com/markychoo</a> Remember, if you do what you've always done, you'll get what you've always gotten. This is your opportunity to make the most important decision you will ever make. Forget your past and let's focus on who you have decided to become in 2012? Make this decision consciously. Make it carefully. Make it powerfully.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c06019f4a7f3ae513fa20006bd841536" url=""><![CDATA[2012 - The Next Chapter in YOUR Life is Here! Join us and we<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Ffree-wednesday-night-training"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/free-wednesday-night-training</a> 
<br /><br />There are secrets that 100% of the top leaders and income earners will embrace in 2012 to double, triple, and even quadruple their incomes.<br /><br />Will this be the year you finally break free from the chains of corporate America and take your life back?<br /><br />It can be. But you have to START 2012 OFF PROPERLY, OR IT WILL BE EXACTLY LIKE 2011 (or worse).<br /><br />Join us this Wednesday, January 4th at 9 PM EST for a mind-bending, MUST ATTEND, brutal wake-up webinar that you must experience to MAKE SURE 2012 IS NOT LIKE 2011!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cb4a9d576cbecebdf872770748d50c2c" url=""><![CDATA[My buddy has tapped into the YouTube Secret<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Ffree-wednesday-night-training"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/free-wednesday-night-training</a> 
<br /><br />This is Unbelievable! Tonight My buddy who has tapped into the YouTube Secret is going to show you how he’s extracting hundreds of leads from this media giant! He's easily ranking videos in the top 5 positions on Google to get FREE Lead for Life! Click Here to Register for this FREE Training tonight: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Ffree-wednesday-night-training"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/free-wednesday-night-training</a>
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e8d1aa59fec672024330cb8aab9d32a8" url=""><![CDATA[Mind-Blowing MLM Success Strategies<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Fmindblowing-mlm-success-strategies"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/mindblowing-mlm-success-strategies</a> 
<br /><br />Hey Everyone, I wanted to share this article I just recently finidhed with everyone, there is tons of good content and info in here! Enjoy! ~ Mark
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1f0225936d01ef3acb8932a8411a2e5" url=""><![CDATA[Step by Step Guide to Building a Website<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Fmark-choo-step-by-step-guide-to-building-a-website"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/mark-choo-step-by-step-guide-to-building-a-website</a> 
<br /><br />Over 70-Guest took this Class! I will pretty much take you by the hand and show you exactly how to build a website, blogs how to start one and much much more…. I will show you everything you need to know so you can start building websites immediately. We will even cover how to start a popular blog site.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="fe5dbffd70beae34dc91ef2c7694489" url=""><![CDATA[Viridian Fundraising Program vs. Linx2Funds FREE Fundraising<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fworkwithmarkchoo.com%2Fviridian-fundraising-program-linx2funds-free-fundraising-program"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://workwithmarkchoo.com/viridian-fundraising-program-linx2funds-free-fundraising-program</a> 
<br /><br />You may have been searching the internet looking at ether the Viridian Fundraising Program or the Linx2Funds FREE Fundraising Program, and you’re probably wondering which is better? Or more importantly, which one will raise more money? Luckily, you found my website, and in this article I am going to give you all the info you need so you can make an informed decision.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="1c9588847086a123ccd5354fefce3724" url=""><![CDATA[Show Me the Money<br/><br/><a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeweeklytraining.info"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.freeweeklytraining.info</a> 
<br /><br />Don't be left in the dark. Register to find out what 90% of members don't know about creating cash flow &amp; residuals.....<br /><br />This Wednesday, January 25th @ 9pm EST Diane will unveil a method of making money which she assures you've never seen before. Take the time NOW to capitalize on multiple revenue streams.<br /><br />== &gt; Click HERE to Register: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeweeklytraining.info"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://www.freeweeklytraining.info</a>
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>