<author type="socialmedia" lang="en" gender="xx" age_group="xx" url="">
	<documents count="18">
		<document id="3267ff6b23488995dc88dd8b783927e7" url=""><![CDATA[Diet Reform<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/ohmy.gif" alt=":)" /> I have made the following adjustments to my diet. As a human being, and more so as a Christian, and ultimately as an Adventist, I have purposed in my heart to avoid:
<br /><br />1) unclean meats as described in Lev. 11 and Deut. 14
<br />2) animals that have been strangled (Acts 15:20, 29; 21:25)
<br />3) all and any manner of blood (Acts 15:20, 29; 21:25; Lev 7:26)
<br />4) the fat of ox/cow-cattle, sheep and goats (Lev. 7:23)
<br /><br />(The fat of clean fowl is not expressly forbidden. The fat or oil of clean fish is not mentioned.)
<br /><br />If there are any more prohibitions I should make with regard to food and drink, I invite the Holy Spirit and servants of God to instruct me accordingly. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="6386261084e0a62b2b472cfb16c2ddfe" url=""><![CDATA[Advent blog<br/><br/>Calling all Seventh-day Adventists and Sabbathkeeping Christians!
<br /><br />Visit practicalsabbath.blogspot.com for tips and advice about practical Sabbathkeeping!
<br /><br />-- I love the Lord; He knows what's best for me. --
<br /><br />[By Elder D.C. Edmond, from InsightMagazine.org] <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" /> Kissing...is foreplay –- an activity designed to prepare the body for sexual intercourse...First, a lot of young people who did become involved in premarital sex also had no intention of becoming involved in it -–they simply lost control. And second, that loss of control almost always started with kissing...
<br /><br />As I write this column, I’m sitting in the Atlanta airport, waiting for a plane to take me to Jackson, Mississippi. If I want to go to Jackson, I need to hurry and finish this article. (They just made the announcement to board the plane!) If you want to fly somewhere, you go to the airport and get on a plane. That’s what planes are for, to take you places. But if I didn’t want to fly to Jackson, I certainly wouldn’t get on this flight. In fact, I wouldn’t even be here at the airport.
<br /><br />What I’m saying is that if you really don’t want to take a trip to &quot;Premarital Sex City,&quot; then why are you using the vehicles designed to get you there?
<br /><br />And now I’m going to catch my plane!
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> ...holding someone’s hand may be a simple act of affection to you doesn’t mean it has the same effect on your boyfriend. Anytime you engage in an activity that involves physical contact with someone for whom you have strong feelings, you have to take into consideration what effect your action has on the other person.
<br /><br />Are you sure that holding your boyfriend’s hand is nothing more than a simple act of affection for him? Does it stimulate him in any way? (And would he admit it if it was stimulating<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" />...
<br /><br />I do know this: The longer you can go without touching each other at all, the better off the two of you will be. 
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/blink.gif" alt=":)" /> In essence, masturbation is a form of sex—with one's self. &quot;Self-sex,&quot; if you will. 
<br /><br />In masturbation there is sexual stimulation, gratification, and at the end, climax. As far as I'm concerned, that's sex. And biblically speaking, sex with anyone other than one's own spouse is wrong.
<br /><br />...That &quot;urge&quot; or &quot;drive&quot; you get to have sex with someone to whom you’re not married ought to be called what it is -– &quot;temptation.&quot; And there aren’t a whole lot of things Christians can do with temptation besides resisting and/or avoiding it.
<br /><br />So here are a couple points to keep in mind regarding this subject:
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/laugh.gif" alt=":)" /> 1. If masturbation is a sex act committed with one's self (and I think it is), then it's wrong.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/laugh.gif" alt=":)" /> 2. Sex is an act of giving to one's spouse. Masturbation is not about giving at all -- it's about gratifying one's own sexual desire. It has nothing to do with anybody but the person involved in the act.
<br /><br />A person (even a married person) who approaches sex as nothing more than an act to gratify his or her own desires is a dangerous partner. Is anyone attracted to people who think sex is only about what they want, what they need, or what feels good to them?
<br /><br />That is not the kind of person you want to be or be with. 
<br /><br />...<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /> I don’t want to come across as flip or smart-aleck in any way, but I would like to suggest another alternative besides masturbation -– self-control. When you’re tempted to be sexually active, you don’t have to do anything to anyone -– including to yourself.
<br /><br />You can overcome sexual temptation, as well as any other temptation, but there are some things you have to do.
<br /><br />First, you have to call what you’re going through what it is: &quot;temptation.&quot; It’s not just an &quot;urge,&quot; or a &quot;need,&quot; or a &quot;drive,&quot; or all the other things we call it. It’s first and foremost a temptation.
<br /><br />And second, remember that any temptation can be overcome through prayer and by avoiding those things that are tempting. That means you can’t read just anything or look at just anything (or everyone) or listen to just anything.
<br /><br />By following these principles and relying on God’s strength, you can overcome.
<br /><br />[By Pastor Steve, from InsightMagazine.org] <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> ...Unlike animals in heat driven to mate, God created human beings for a highly sensual experience through sexual intercourse. He wired our brains so that this expression would be far more than merely sex. For humans, this act is supposed to be based on the intimacy between two people who are married to each other.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> When a person masturbates, they could be having a fantasy about having sex with someone that they don’t personally know -— a movie star, a music star, a friend, anyone. This approach to sexuality is certainly self-centered rather than selfless — the way God designed sexual expression to be. Also, the immediate gratification element assocated with masturbation can create problems later when a person is traveling the winding pathway of relationship with a real person. For most people, their sex drive begins during their early adolescent years. In Bible times this is the age when people got married. But in the Western world today, marriage doesn’t come for more than a decade after adolescence for many people.
<br /><br />...sex is often misused by the world, and that God desires for us to be pure. Above all, He always desires the best for us — no substitutes.
<br /><br />(For more sexuality advice, visit Insightmagazine.org -- the Adventist life resource for youth)
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /> (Blogger's opinion) By forcing them to put career and financial success as priority over God and His commandments, I think the youth of today have been cheated, by secular society, out of the joys of courtship and marriage. People marry too late and leave themselves a time gap (usually a decade or more) perfect for Satan and his minions to work their temptations until those who cannot take it stumble, crumble and fall.
<br /><br />If what Pastor Steve Case says is true (&quot;For most people, their sex drive begins during their early adolescent years. In Bible times this is the age when people got married. But in the Western world today, marriage doesn’t come for more than a decade after adolescence for many people&quot<img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" />, then I dare say that WE as young Christian people have a tough time in a society that wants us to get married beyond the age of 25 (sometimes 30...or never!).
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" /> “Therefore, since WE HAVE A GREAT HIGH PRIEST who has gone through the heavens, JESUS THE SON OF GOD, let us hold firmly to the faith we profess. For we do not have a high priest who is unable to sympathize with our weaknesses, but we have one who has been tempted in every way, just as we are—yet was without sin. Let us then approach the throne of grace with confidence, so that we may receive mercy and find grace to help us in our time of need.” 
<br />                    —Hebrews 4:14-16.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2b2282d252697063fd0739b45eb92c38" url=""><![CDATA[What is IMVU?<br/><br/>A gripe
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/book.gif" alt=":)" /> Have you heard of IMVU? If you have, consider this: IMVU is a service, right? But it's also a company. A company called 'IMVU' ( or 'IMVU, Inc.'? ) that operates an online community platform called 'IMVU'. 'IMVU' is also a brand: the brand of a system of homepages, each presumably managed by a person who assumes a 3D avatar that may very well have no resemblance to his true form and stature, and even more so if it's a non-humanoid avatar (e.g. a desk, a logo, a burning bush or a Sukhoi fighter jet).
<br /><br />So, when I say &quot;I met someone on IMVU&quot;, I refer to the ONLINE COMMUNITY PLATFORM. If I say &quot;IMVU deleted my account&quot;, I refer what the COMPANY or SITE MODERATOR/ADMINISTRATOR has done. And if I were to write that some panels on my homepage are &quot;automatically updated by IMVU&quot;, it would mean that the SERVICE -- not the site moderator nor the company per se -- updates the panels, because it seems highly unlikely that an IMVU staff has been assigned to my homepage for the purpose of adding or subtracting data and cross-referencing entries, when these tasks are best computerised.
<br /><br />Ah, what the....!
<br /><br />My IMVU homepage is [avatars.imvu.com/guest_victorong].
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="26af28a99fb342f565dc0a7f4221e3e5" url=""><![CDATA[I make mistakes<br/><br/>I make mistakes; please forgive me. I am still learning. I do apologise. Ask me to think things through; perhaps there is something I don't know. Have I hurt you? You can tell me what I must do to set things right. We can work together! I dread militant responses to my failures and omissions, because I know I can fly, and I want elbow room to make the best of life and do good unto many people. It's great that many folks have let me go. They let me try again. It's awesome.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="d75bfe1b6d37bb3758c9e39ea72dfa8" url=""><![CDATA[I'll try to shun...<br/><br/>I don't like 'critical points' -- i.e. eleventh-hour emergencies -- when situations like these could have been avoided with ample preparation in advance. Don't give me critical points: go moderate on me!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="e0760dc1a795f7af2312a36cc9646c64" url=""><![CDATA[The aches of a designer<br/><br/>I'm more of a words-person; still, I make designs for different purposes, and I especially enjoy designing flags, banners, logos and page templates. Most of my designs I try to keep as simplistic as possible, so that people can remember them easily, or use them without having to scale a steep learning curve, or appreciate them without getting a headache.
<br /><br />However, the nightmare of my being an amateur designer is this: the process of putting together a definitive design seems as arduous as waiting for the cathedral at Chartres to reach completion. (The cathedral was completed in 1260.) 
<br /><br />The more you proceed into a design, the more difficult it is to bring it to satisfactory completion. Recently, an unusual perfectionist mentality has invaded me, prompting me to keep at a near-finished design for hours on-end: arranging, tweaking, pondering, deleting, adding, and fuming at how imperfect it still is.
<br /><br />Thus, it takes ages before I finalise a piece of work, though intermediate designs look acceptable -- even wonderful -- to my viewers.
<br /><br />A design can never be too great, right? When it finally is, I think it'll strike me down like a lightning bolt, for I'll be so overcome by its perfection.
<br /><br />Save me, somebody. Save me! <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/blink.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a3b45aa1bd04034c015eafe195e76061" url=""><![CDATA[Russia for Russians?<br/><br/>What about &quot;America for Americans&quot;?
<br />Who is an &quot;American&quot;? A 'white' man of Irish descent? A 'black'? A 'yellow'? Who is an American?
<br /><br />An American is one who has an American passport, who contributes to the development of physical, social and spiritual infrastructure in America, and who is concerned about world peace and harmony.
<br /><br />Since the Soviet Union (Sovetskiy Soyuz, more appropriately translated as 'Union of Councils' or 'United Councils') is a union of different countries comprising various nationalities, e.g. Ukrainian, Russian, Estonian, Turkmen, Georgian, Armenian, etc., it is acceptable if the national leader isn't a 'white Russian'. Not one race should be disallowed from serving in legislative, executive and judicial capacities; even a member of the smallest migrant race can be considered for political office based on his/her work performance, attitude, ethics and other merits.
<br /><br />Hence, I don't see why Stalin being Georgian invalidates his leadership of the USSR. What invalidates his leadership is not his ethnicity, but his high-handedness and cruelty.
<br /><br />If there is a significant Jewish community in the Russian Federation, Vladimir Putin being President is no problem, if he is indeed part-Jew.
<br /><br />Also, the emphasis on &quot;white russians&quot; may be unhealthy as this denotes the kind of racial supremacist line that can serve to undermine national development and the work to make life more comfortable for 150 million people. Even if a Tatar rules all of Russia, so what? If he does his job well, puts food on people's tables, gives them warm clothes to wear and maintains essential services like water, electricity, heat and post, shall we demand his resignation just because he isn't a pure Russian?
<br /><br />Think: what if Barack Obama becomes the next president of the United States? He ain't as &quot;white&quot; as Bush or Clinton, you know. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />According to a report in The Economist, a documentary film entitled &quot;Kursk: A Submarine in Troubled Waters&quot;, and impressions I have gathered, Mr Putin has had a hand in disrupting Russia's democratic processes (e.g. the parliamentary elections last year), but I am in no way opposed to his position at the helm of the state; my primary concern is that he takes care of the welfare of the Russian people by creating opportunities for them. It is also my hope that crimes against the poor man be met with swift and sensible justice.
<br /><br />It is also my hope that he works amicably with the Communist Party. Perhaps it'll be good for Putin to develop and implement a brand of socialism that will propel Russia forward economically, socially and technologically, without causing too much damage to the environment.
<br /><br />1. Was armed conflict in Chechnya necessary?
<br />2. Do you hate the Chechen people, i.e. people of Chechen ethnicity?
<br />3. Is Chechnya an asset to Russia, or is she more of a liability?
<br /><br />4. How should the Russian government treat minorities? By minorities I mean the Tatars, Chuvashs, Chechens, Vietnamese, Jews, Chukotko-Kamchatkan, Armenians, etc.
<br /><br />&quot;The Russian Federation is a diverse, multiethnic society, home to as many as 160 different ethnic groups and indigenous peoples.&quot; (Quote: Demographics, in: Russia | From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia)
<br /><br />&quot;The term multiculturalism generally refers to a state of both cultural and ethnic diversity within the demographics of a particular social space.&quot; (Quote: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FMulticulturalism"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Multiculturalism</a>)
<br /><br />5. If Russia had a neo-Nazi president and a predominantly neo-Nazi parliament, would it guarantee reasonable press freedom -- the kind of press freedom Russians do not have under Vladimir Putin?
<br /><br />6. Which is more preferable:
<br /><br />a. white supremacy, or
<br />b. service to the people, regardless of race, language or religion?
<br /><br />=======
<br /><br />&quot;We, the citizens of Singapore 
<br />pledge ourselves as one united people, 
<br />regardless of race, language or religion, 
<br />to build a democratic society, 
<br />based on justice and equality, 
<br />so as to achieve happiness, prosperity and 
<br />progress for our nation.&quot;
<br /><br />&quot;The National Pledge was written by Sinnathamby Rajaratnam in 1966 shortly after Singapore's independence. Mr Rajaratnam revealed that the dream was to build &quot;a Singapore we are proud of&quot;. He believed that language, race and religion were divisive factors, but the Pledge emphasises that these differences can be overcome if Singaporeans cared enough about their country. The draft text was handed to the then Prime Minister Mr Lee Kuan Yew, who polished the text before submitting it to the Cabinet.&quot;
<br /><br />(Source: <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FSingapore_Pledge"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Singapore_Pledge</a>)
<br /><br />The Singapore National Pledge was written by an Indian and handed to a Chinese. See also <a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FCivilian_War_Memorial"target="_blank" rel="nofollow">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Civilian_War_Memorial</a> ; &quot;(t)he four elements (of the Civilian War Memorial) are joined at the base, representing unity amongst the four major ethnic groups in Singapore: Chinese, Indians, Malays and other groups.&quot;
<br /><br />Imagine this:
<br /><br />We, the citizens of Russia 
<br />pledge ourselves as one united people, 
<br />regardless of race, language or religion, 
<br />to build a democratic society, 
<br />based on justice and equality, 
<br />so as to achieve happiness, prosperity and 
<br />progress for our country.
<br /><br />[P.S. I'm not Singaporean.]
<br /><br />Thank you for your attention, and forgive me for my mistakes (if any).
<br /><br />&quot;The Soviet Union (Sovetskiy Soyuz, more appropriately translated as 'Union of Councils' or 'United Councils') was a union of different countries comprising various nationalities, e.g. Ukrainian, Russian, Estonian, Turkmen, Georgian, Armenian, etc. Not one race should be disallowed from serving in legislative, executive and judicial capacities; even a member of the smallest migrant race can be considered for political office based on his/her work performance, attitude, ethics and other merits.&quot;
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="973ade83566c210e1be031cf06951b32" url=""><![CDATA[Why I identify myself with KeADILan<br/><br/>Because it is not named after a particular race of people, nor after a particular religion, nor after a particular socio-economic ideology, KeADILan (i.e. Parti Keadilan Rakyat <strong>[PKR]</strong> <em>English</em> People's Justice Party) has the potential to become an inclusive, loving and progressive party.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="cecf90db4aabc43a90e381a7fc45540b" url=""><![CDATA['No' to Falun Gong petition<br/><br/>If I have contributed signatures to one or more petitions calling for an end to the persecution of Falun Gong practitioners, or signatures to any petition, list or form prepared by the CIPFG (Coalition to Investigate the Persecution of Falun Gong in China), or to &quot;a worldwide million-signature campaign calling for the Chinese Communist Party (CCP) to stop the persecuting of Falun Gong in China&quot;, I deeply <strong>regret</strong> my decision(s).
<br /><br />I <strong>do not</strong> want the Chinese Communist Party to collapse. I am a revolutionary, and refuse to destroy a Party that can be reformed and reshaped into better and more glorious form. 
<br /><br />Workers of the world, unite! 
<br /><br />===== 
<br /><br />If I have contributed signatures to any petition, list or form prepared by the CIPFG (Coalition to Investigate the Persecution of Falun Gong), I deeply <strong>regret </strong>my decision(s).
<br /><br />=====
<br /><br />If I have contributed signatures to one or more petitions calling for an end to the persecution of Falun Gong practitioners, I deeply <strong>regret</strong> my decision(s). 
<br /><br />===== 
<br /><br />If I have contributed signatures to &quot;a worldwide million-signature campaign calling for the Chinese Communist Party (CCP) to stop the persecuting of Falun Gong in China&quot;, I deeply <strong>regret</strong> my decision(s).
<br /><br />I <strong>do not </strong>want the Chinese Communist Party to collapse. I am a revolutionary, and refuse to destroy a Party that can be reformed and reshaped into better and more glorious form.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="ffe2f6bdf0787c9b26b0dafde1284121" url=""><![CDATA[<br/><br/><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />a return to love - marianne williamson
<br /><br />Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate.
<br />Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure.
<br />It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us.
<br />We ask ourselves, Who am I to be brilliant,
<br />gorgeous, talented, fabulous?
<br />Actually, who are you not to be?
<br />You are a child of God.
<br />Your playing small does not serve the world.
<br />There is nothing enlightened about shrinking
<br />so that other people won't feel insecure around you.
<br />We are all meant to shine, as children do.
<br />We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us.
<br />It is not just in some of us; it is in everyone.
<br />And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously
<br />give other people permission to do the same.
<br />As we are liberated from our own fear,
<br />our presence automatically liberates others.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />The innate failure of human self-sustenance – victor ong
<br /><br />Our deepest fear is that we feel inadequate,
<br />even if we are powerful beyond measure.
<br />It is our darkness that most frightens us.
<br />And we refuse to have anyone delve into those depths.
<br />We ask ourselves, “Who am I to be brilliant,
<br />gorgeous, talented, fabulous?”
<br />Actually, who are you not to be?
<br />You are a child of God.
<br />Your playing small does not serve the world.
<br />There is nothing enlightened about shrinking
<br />so that other people won't feel insecure around you.
<br />We are all meant to shine, as children do.
<br />Yet, when we shine, 
<br />so we do it so irreverently that
<br />we do not make manifest the glory of God that is within us,
<br />but impose our inflated egos on our fellows.
<br />It is not just in some of us; it is in everyone.
<br />And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously
<br />give other people license to do the same.
<br />Thus we liberate some, 
<br />but make monsters out of others.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="c05e5bd49e5498fb3e314b499ea60149" url=""><![CDATA[THE SON OF GOD<br/><br/>Jesus Christ, You came to save our lives;
<br />Jesus Christ, The Son of God!
<br /><br />Long ago in Bethlehem, t'was born a God-and-man,
<br />His name was Jesus Christ, He came and ask for hearts to repent.
<br /><br />But the little people said, &quot;You come to preach your dreams,
<br />but we just want a king.&quot; And they crucified their King!
<br /><br />Jesus Christ, You came to save our lives;
<br />Jesus Christ, You came to rid our crime;
<br />Jesus Christ, You bore our sin and shame;
<br />Jesus Christ, Lamb of God!
<br /><br />Now on this seventh day, let all our voices ring,
<br />we know that come what may, we have an Advocate to the King.
<br /><br />In eighteen forty-four, He trod the Holiest Place;
<br />Our scrolls read case-by-case, but His children have no fear!
<br /><br />Jesus Christ, The Way the Truth and Life;
<br />Jesus Christ, We sing Your song of triumph;
<br />Jesus Christ, Your blood on Calvary;
<br />Jesus Christ, Lamb of God!
<br /><br />Jesus Christ, You came to save our lives;
<br />Jesus Christ, You came to rid our crime;
<br />Jesus Christ, You bore our sin and shame;
<br />Jesus Christ, The Son of God!
<br /><br />Jesus Christ, The Son of God.....!
<br /><br />JESUS CHRIST!
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3a03927a2b41e0839f6a84b21c25ddc1" url=""><![CDATA[Power Rangers Gospel Force<br/><br/>Thank you, Lord, for my &quot;artistic flair&quot;, as my friend Nicodemus so praised earlier today; I'm glad the promo banner for PracticalSabbath.blogspot.com looks good.
<br /><br />I pray that the 153,000 people affected by the floods in Johor would get all the help they need, including the assurance of a Gospel that saves the living from greater uncertainty. I ask that You bring some good out of this great evil, comforting the people with Your presence and the provisions that Your servants can bring them. If there's anything we can do, inspire us and we'll do them. Give us courage, Lord.
<br /><br />I pray the Aenon Farm camp would come to pass, even if numbers are not-too-substantial. If it's something that can in some small way hurry Your return, then please make it happen.
<br /><br />Tracts, banners and a DVD library are being done to furthur the Gospel, but the work is small and slow. Give us more heat and kindle the fires of passion within us; make us have hearts for the people of Johor, to send out the simple salvation message. I pray for more Johoreans to unite under the sign of Your Sabbath -- the mark that identifies the saved with the Saviour, the creature with the Creator.
<br /><br />I pray for Samuel's victory in his interpersonal relationships and the obstacles he encounters in the workplace. I ask that the gates of hell prevail not against him. Remind him to live by Your law, and give him the strength to do so.
<br /><br />There's a girl in Germany who does not yet know You; You must intervene in her life and compel her by Your love! O perfect Lord, show her that You are the Answer for her world!
<br /><br />Sheron &quot;took a fall this week&quot;. (What is THAT supposed to mean?!) I ask that You preserve her, sustain her and send a good number of angels to keep her safe. If I were Satan -- the Evilest of Evil -- I would want her down and out, totally wasted and cheated by man and demon. Please protect her, Lord. Preserve Sheron from the savages and ravages of this sin-ridden world. If she is physically ill, see to it that she is not spiritually so. Thank you, Lord. And rid her presence of those &quot;stalkers&quot;.
<br /><br />Thank you, Father in Heaven. In Jesus' name I pray, Amen.
<br /><br />Yours sincerely,
<br />Victor Ong
<br />Power Rangers Gospel Force
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="3172fb90ae64cf345a62f57dff487bb" url=""><![CDATA[How to be glad it's NOT over<br/><br/>How to be glad the Sabbath is NOT YET over
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />ONE
<br /><br />Join a committee at church, sit on the board or SERVE in some ministry on the Sabbath: you'll be surprised HOW LITTLE TIME there is for the work of God during the week. Soon there'll be lots to do on Sabbath and no reason to be bored!
<br /><br />TWO
<br /><br />RESERVE all your daily Sabbath School Study Guide lessons till Friday night, and do them ALL AT ONCE -- meticulously. You may end up going to bed at 1 in the morning when you're done.
<br /><br />THREE
<br /><br />WRITE a tract. Do it slowly and prayerfully, with many drafts. Then THINK about how you're gonna get it printed during the week, and how to distribute them among the masses.
<br /><br />FOUR
<br /><br />Are you a homemaker? Or do you have a talent in cooking?
<br />Before the sun goes down Friday night, WHIP UP a sophisticated dish for the 50 people at church, ready for REHEATING the following day. Alternatively, put together something SIMPLE early Saturday morning, e.g. a big cake from the fridge, stir-fried veggies or cut fruit.
<br /><br />...to be continued...
<br /><br />(This message written from personal experience. Tried and tested. For the practical Sabbathkeeper who does not define 'WORK' or 'no WORK' in the physics sense of the word!)
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/w00t.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="2ce44e85216a032bf2a860eb849852c" url=""><![CDATA[Not Here, But Above<br/><br/>I realise that it is for my own eternal good that I am unable to find great satisfaction in my work. The labour which I desire to do I cannot and am forbidden to do, but the labour which I dread to undertake I am coerced to do. It is not work that is against the law; in fact, the job is perfectly legitimate. It is just that I am not allowed, by authority and circumstance, to pick and choose my tasks. I work for my keep, yes, but I am not happy, not fulled-up, not satisfied.
<br /><br />And then I realise: Victor, set your affections on things above. One cannot hope to find lasting peace and joy in secular labour. You job will not bring you that indwelling satisfaction that won't burn out. Pursue after your fancy, and get what you want, but the initial passion may die out.
<br /><br />It is not on this earth that I find true happiness. It is with the Lord that I find balance to the curse that is my labour. There are times of joy in my work, yes, but also seasons of drudgery. What I can hope for now is Jesus' soon return.
<br /><br />Imagine the danger if I were to really find a job or make out a career that I'm really in LOVE with. I fall head-over-heels with my pet joy. I spent hours doing this job, poring over the paperwork, visiting the worksites and skipping Sabbaths to close sales and total accounts. Then whom do I worship? Such work, such love would be legitimate, granted, but it may just mess up my priorities.
<br /><br />In fact, examining my character, it WOULD affect my priorities, substituting worship of the true God (my Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ) with my multimillion-dollar business. Which, if one really thinks about it, will fade away when the Earth is destroyed.
<br /><br />As such, I will continue to be passionate for the Lord, hungering for more Word and zealous for the Adventist Church.
<br /><br />I pray, though, that I'll never get tired with the things of the Kingdom, as I am already tired with the things of the world. Sustain me, Lord God.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /> God Seals Our Spiritual Marriage
<br /><br />To seal our spiritual marriage for eternity, He has promised never to forsake me (Psalms 55:22; Matthew 28:20; Hebrews 13:5), to take care of me in sickness or in health (Psalms 41:3; Isaiah 41:10), and to provide for every need that could possibly develop in my life (Matthew 6:25-34). Just as I received Him by faith and found His promises all-sufficient, I keep on trusting Him for every future need, and He never lets me down. (source: Amazing Facts Study Guide #3)
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="5f80f5690c65689e83a875638708e879" url=""><![CDATA[The Time of Jacob's Trouble<br/><br/>Alas! for that day is great, so that none is like it: it is even the time of Jacob's trouble; but he shall be saved out of it. (Jer. 30:7)
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> 
<br /><br />I saw that the four angels would hold the four winds until Jesus' work was done in the sanctuary, and then will come the seven last plagues. These plagues enraged the wicked against the
<br />righteous; they thought that we had brought the judgments of God upon them, and that if they could rid the earth of us, the plagues would then be stayed. A decree went forth to slay the saints, which caused them to cry day and night for deliverance. This was the time of Jacob's trouble. 
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angel.gif" alt=":)" />
<br /><br />As Satan influenced Esau to march against Jacob, so he will stir up the wicked to destroy God's people in the time of trouble. And as he accused Jacob, he will urge his accusations against the people of God. He numbers the world as his subjects; but the little
<br />company who keep the commandments of God are resisting his supremacy. If he could blot them from the earth, his triumph would be complete. He sees that holy angels are guarding them, and he infers that their sins have been pardoned; but he does not know
<br />that their cases have been decided in the sanctuary above. He has an accurate knowledge of the sins which he has tempted them to commit, and he presents these before God in the most exaggerated light, representing this people to be just as deserving as himself of exclusion from the favor of God. He declares that the Lord cannot in justice forgive their sins and yet destroy him and his angels. He claims them as his prey and demands that they be given into his hands to destroy.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/ninja.gif" alt=":)" />  
<br /><br />As Satan accuses the people of God on account of their sins, the Lord permits him to try them to the uttermost. Their confidence in God, their faith and firmness, will be severely tested. As they review the past, their hopes sink; for in their whole lives they can see little good. They are fully conscious of their weakness and unworthiness. Satan endeavors to terrify them with the thought that their cases are hopeless, that the stain of their defilement will never be washed away. He hopes so to destroy their faith that they will yield to his temptations and turn from their allegiance to God.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/book.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="7164946d5d63c40470630cf5c7920406" url=""><![CDATA[Angelic Protection in the Time<br/><br/>Angelic Protection in the Time of Trouble
<br /><br />Come, my people, enter thou into thy chambers, and shut thy doors about thee: hide thyself as it were for a little moment, until the indignation be overpast. (Isa. 26:20)
<br /><br />In the day of fierce trial He [Christ] will say, &quot;Come, my people, enter thou into thy chambers, and shut thy doors about thee: hide thyself as it were for a little moment, until the indignation be overpast.&quot;
<br />What are the chambers in which they are to hide? They are the protection of Christ and holy angels. The people of God are not at this time all in one place. They are in different companies, and in all parts of the earth. 
<br /><br />I saw the saints leaving the cities and villages, and associating together in companies, and living in the most solitary places. Angels provided them food and water, while the wicked were suffering from hunger and thirst. 
<br /><br />During the night a very impressive scene passed before me. There seemed to be great confusion and the conflict of armies. A messenger from the Lord stood before me, and said, &quot;Call your household. I will lead you; follow me.&quot; He led me down a dark passage, through a forest, then through the clefts of mountains, and said, &quot;Here you are safe.&quot; There were others who had been led to this retreat. The heavenly messenger said. &quot;The time of trouble has come as a thief in the night, as the Lord warned you it would come.&quot; 
<br /><br />In the time of trouble just before the coming of Christ, the righteous will be preserved through the ministration of heavenly angels; but there will be no security for the transgressor of God's law. Angels cannot then protect those who are disregarding one of the divine precepts. 
<br /><br />In the closing period of earth's history the Lord will work mightily in behalf of those who stand steadfastly for the right. In the midst of the time of trouble--trouble such as has not been since there was a nation--His chosen ones will stand unmoved. Satan with all the hosts of evil cannot destroy the weakest of God's saints. Angels that excel in strength will protect them, and in their behalf Jehovah will reveal Himself as a &quot;God of gods,&quot; able to save to the uttermost those who have put their trust in Him.
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="a9a034d2e1e7a3d513936de6bb908815" url=""><![CDATA[What Music Means to Me<br/><br/>[A LETTER TO MY FRIEND]
<br /><br />Dear Sam,
<br /><br />In view of what has been said yesterday regarding music, allow me to share with you what music really means to me:
<br /><br />Music for the occasion ~ to suit the intellect, to appease the mood, to challenge the apathy, to celebrate the joy, to calm the senses, to understand difficult things, to end all wars, to express love, to personify virtues, to instill orderliness, to enforce discipline, to promote honesty, to tangibilise the heart, to tame the environment, and most of all, to represent Jesus Christ.
<br /><br />The apostle Paul said, &quot; 'Everything is permissible' but not everything is beneficial. 'Everything is permissible' but not everything is constructive. Nobody should seek his own good, but the good of others.&quot; (1 Cor 10:22-24) He mentioned this in the same spirit in an earlier chapter, &quot; 'Everything is permissible for me&quot; but I will not be mastered by anything. 'Food for the stomach and the stomach for food' but God will destroy them both. The body is not meant for sexual immorality, but for the Lord, and the Lord for the body.&quot; (1 Cor 6:11-13) 
<br /><br />Music is our tool, so we are not to be mastered by it. Pastor Samuel is right; not all forms of music are constructive. Nobody should seek his own good, but the good of others; if it is music that does not edify my fellow brother- or sister-in-Christ, it must not be performed.
<br /><br />True, music is for the ear and the ear for music but God will destroy them both. The ear, and thus the mind, is not meant as the Devil's workshop, but as the abode of the carpenter of Nazareth our Lord Jesus Christ. 
<br /><br />However, to deny ourselves the joy of using music to express our deep-seated emotions and surest convictions is bondage. People who advocate total abstinance from particular genres of music may inadvertently &quot;bind heavy burdens, hard to bear, and lay them on men's shoulders; but they themselves will not move them with one of their fingers.&quot; (Matt. 23:4) 
<br /><br />Music serves to imbue gusto, liven the lifeless and inspire the weak. It is a tool that, if properly and prayerfully wielded, can be used to express the reservoirs of our faith. 
<br /><br />We mustn't be enslaved by music, but neither are we to be enslaved by the lack of it.
<br /><br />And this, Sam, is perhaps why 107FM does not refrain from broadcasting contemporary music with fast tempos and multilayer instruments.
<br /><br />Yet, I must agree that one can have too much of a good thing; a good thing at a totally wrong time; and a too much of a good thing too long a time.
<br /><br />Yours respectfully,
<br />Victor
<br />Johor Bahu
]]>
		</document>
		<document id="740d5ad3ea6d58e82659fc37dd6bbfce" url=""><![CDATA[Marriage: the low-down<br/><br/> THE 'LOW-DOWN' IN MARRIAGE!
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /> Let's look at why people marry. If you're a Bible person, look no place first but Genesis chapter 2, verse 24:
<br /><br />&quot;Therefore shall a man leave his father and his mother, and shall cleave unto his wife: and they shall be one flesh.&quot;
<br /><br />Or in the New International Reader's Version (NIrV): &quot;...a man will leave his father and mother and be joined to his wife. The two of them will become one.&quot;
<br /><br />So we know that marriage began in the Garden of Eden, and that in context, it was natural for a man to &quot;cleave&quot; to a woman for she was &quot;taken out of man&quot; and was a suitable &quot;helpmeet&quot; for him. Far from being inferior to a man, a woman is actually very important, even indispensable, because there are some things women can do that men cannot. Men need women; women must enlighten me as to whether they need us! Single-parent, motherless families are testament against chauvinistic contentions that women are expendable toys. Meticulous paperwork brings sanity to an office, meets legislative requirements and moves the economy -- the work of women. And who can forget their role in the last world war? Munitions factories, codebreaking stations and telephone exchanges were staffed with women, many of whom had husbands fighting on the frontlines.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /> Now for some fun facts:
<br /><br />MARRIAGEABLE AGES IN 26 PLACES
<br /><br />M - Male
<br />F - Female
<br />'p - parental consent
<br />'j - legal /judicial consent
<br /><br />Madagascar: M-17; F-14
<br />Sudan: onset of puberty
<br />Brazil: 18/16; adolescent 12-17 with 'p
<br />Brunei: no minimum age specified
<br />Iran: M-15; F-13
<br />New Hampshire, USA: M-14; F-13 ('p, 'j)
<br />Yemen: 9
<br />Scotland, UK: 16
<br /><br />Kenya: 16
<br />Morocco, Ethiopia: 18
<br />Somalia, Argentina: M-18; F-16
<br />Tanzania: M-18; F-15
<br />Missisippi, USA: unlimited with 'p
<br /><br />Canada: 18/16/14
<br />Mexico: M-16; F-14 ('p, 'j)
<br />Venezuela: M-16; F-14 with 'p
<br />Paraguay: M-16; F-14
<br /><br />California, USA: 18 with 'p
<br />Arizonia, USA: 16 with 'p
<br />Ohio, USA: below M-18/F-16 needs 'p
<br />Pennsylvania, USA: 16 with 'p; below 16 with 'j
<br /><br />Singapore: 21; 18 with 'p; below 18 with special marriage license
<br />Thailand: 15 with 'p
<br />Ireland: below 16 ('p, 'j)
<br /><br />==========
<br /><br />Here you see knots being tied early, i.e. before 18 or 21 years of age.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /> Are those in so-called &quot;less-civilised&quot; societies wiser than we are? Some of them legalise marriage at adolescence! And many of them understand -- more than we who call ourselves refined -- that marriage is a commitment and should last forever. 
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> In my humble and most excited opinion, by forcing us to put career and financial success as priority over God and His commandments, I think we as the youth of today have been cheated, by secular society, out of the joys of courtship and marriage. People marry too late and leave themselves a time gap (usually a decade or more) perfect for Satan and his minions to work their temptations until those who cannot take it stumble, crumble and fall.
<br /><br />If what Pastor Steve Case of InsightMagazine.org says is true 
<br /><br />&quot;For most people, their sex drive begins during their early adolescent years. In Bible times this is the age when people got married. But in the Western world today, marriage doesn’t come for more than a decade after adolescence for many people&quot;,
<br /><br />then I dare say that WE as young Christian people have a tough time in a society that wants us to get married beyond the age of 25 (sometimes 30...or never!).
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /> Many contend that under-18s and under-16s are too young to understand &quot;commitment&quot;, &quot;responsibility&quot; and &quot;faithfulness&quot;. Yet in Western Europe and the USA, it does not seem that the 'grown-ups' have any better understanding of these terms, considering the high divorce rates and deplorable sexual promiscuity. Conversely, we see in traditional societies (esp. Asian and African) children who understand and make their practice filial piety, respect for elders, loyalty to friends and diligence in labor. They are deft with their hands and quick in their minds, and are acquainted with Nature and the customs of the commune in which they live.
<br /><br />On the contrary, city kids have for themselves excessive pampering and princely treatment that serve to deaden their senses to the realities of a fallen world. Adults struggle to make them comfortable -- as though this were good parenthood -- and later lament when their children evolve into rebellious, frightened, idle or suicidal teenagers.
<br /><br />Do we want teenagers who shuffle in the streets past midnight, get hooked on drugs, booze and MTV, and drool over their pillows at 10a.m. on a Saturday morning, to start a family? No. Then why do we bring them up that way?
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/ohmy.gif" alt=":)" /> Before we move on, we must not exclude the facts in societies with low marriageable ages: many of the women involved are subjected to varying degrees of sexual and physical abuse; many adulterous men are also not promptly and exactly punished for their transgressions.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> 1 Corinthians 3:18-20 reveals that it is not academic competence that makes a man (or woman), but the soundness of his morals and the integrity of his heart: &quot;Let no man deceive himself. If any man among you seemeth to be wise in this world, let him become a fool, that he may be wise.&quot;
<br /><br />Continuing in verses 19 and 20, &quot;For the wisdom of this world is foolishness with God. For it is written, 'He taketh the wise in their own craftiness.' And again, 'The Lord knoweth the thoughts of the wise, that they are vain'.&quot;
<br /><br />And my sister Elyssa has this to say about young people, esp. children: they have childlike faith and are more heaven-worthy than we 'grown-ups' are. This &quot;childlike faith&quot; is a product of the faithfulness we increasingly do not see in adults...in the adults that make up this doubting generation. Chidren can be more resolute about things than we grown-ups can; while we're often double-minded (another god, another job, another woman...), children are simple-minded. And this is the faithfulness many Americans refuse to manifest.
<br /><br />The wisdom of the world is foolishness with God -- we arm ourselves with PhDs, MBAs and BScs and call ourselves competent and smart, but have we been outfitted for Heaven? Nah! Not even for friendship. Much less marriage! The truly clever person is the one who delights himself in God's moral code (see the Ten Commandments) and who endeavours to live in favour with God and Man.
<br /><br />But are our schools building youth like that?
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/whistling.gif" alt=":)" /> It can be said that the apparent immaturity of city adolescents is due to lousy education. Youth receive inadequate upbringing in a society that feeds them with trash and ungodly messages via TV, video, dirty magazines and tabloids, and the Internet. Schools are stupidly secular, propagating ethics and values that many are forced to unlearn in their later years for the sake of business and enterprise. The Creator and His Law is forsaken for things unnominative and unabsolute; everything moral is relative, and you are deemed narrow-minded and old-fashioned if you espouse absolute rules regarding, say, sex, marriage, dress, dance, etc.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cry.gif" alt=":)" /> Youth soaked and dyed in such an environment is justly unfit for marriage and the commitment it entails. The joy quickly passes as trials loom large on the honeymoon horizon: bills, food, education, house, car, etc. And yes, the under-18s and under-16s of today's cosmospolitan cities are largely not well-equipped to handle these challenges. A great many do not stand on firm psychological, spiritual and emotional plateaus. They know no trade with which to sustain themselves, and are given a lot of time to indulge in excesses, making what is for fun a continuous enterprise. With their intemperance they gratify the lust of the eyes, the lust of the flesh and the pride of life. Since they have not received much true and rigorous Christian education in their childhood (5-13 years), many teenagers are still confused, unmotivated, paranoid and some downright idiotic.
<br /><br />Right then, are parents when they deny their children marriage until, as Elder D.C. Edmond of InsightMagazine.org suggests for his daughter Courtney, age 25. With all the filth the Church of Hollywood throws at everyone, adults need more time and more effort to groom their children, especially if they live in big cities. In the meantime, teenagers are unable to placate perfectly normal desires, i.e. to foster boy-girl relationships and eventually marry and comsummate; they suffer the onslaught of, and many fall casualty to, popular media depicting men as sex-masters and women as sex-toys, detaching affection from physical intimacy, and blurring the line between Love and Lust; they endure &quot;urges&quot;, &quot;drives&quot; and &quot;desires&quot; for a decade after their first blossom because they are not yet ready for a huge responsibility as marriage. For many in their 20s and even 30s, marriage has become an insurmountable task. And why? Because society does not prep the youth in the way of the LORD.
<br /><br />But what about the needs and desires of our young people? Why do we pretend their whinings, midnight phone calls, sneak dates, love letters and 2-hour-long instant messaging sessions are no indication of their desire to leave and cleave, to have and to hold? Why should we allow them to entertain sexual fantasies that repeatedly break the 7th Commandment? Why do we continue bringing up our kids in the big cities, when Adventist pioneer Ellen G. White encourages living away from the cities, where decadence and godlessness prevail?
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /> But what about parenthood? Will teenagers make good parents? Well, “train up a child in the way he should go: and when he is old, he will not depart from it” (Proverbs 22:6). While this is easier said than done, it is not undoable. That being said, we must let the Bible define what is “good”, and this makes for good long Bible study. However, if God does not succor parents in childbearing and childrearing, or if the instruction of the Scriptures is unfathomable and there is no such thing as a ‘Holy Spirit’, then we surely cannot raise good teenagers, and they cannot make good parents, and they cannot raise good teenagers themselves, etc.
<br /><br />A lot of children do not cherish the money; they do not invest according to their needs and squander their parents’ finances on unimportant things. Money can solve a lot of problems and meet a lot of needs, but it is often expended selfishly and in utterly irrelevant areas. We also observe many teenagers wasting dollars on the gratification of carnal pleasures. These young people have not been readied for family management. They are not prepared to take care of spouse, kids and pets! Should we stop being so lenient and detached about how our youth are spending their allowances? Don’t we imagine how poor spending habits can mess up our children’s paychecks in the future? We could be more caring.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /> We despise our youth (see 1 Timothy 4:12). Not fast and soon enough are they equipped for the challenges of living in a world where Satan is the “prince of the power of the air” (Ephesians 2:2). This Satan prowls to and fro across the earth, seeking to deceive and destroy Man, but many of us take our own sweet time when it comes to sanctifying ourselves and our children. When our youth rise up to challenges in church and community, many adults are hesitant to let them take the reins. Small wonder, when these adults know how inadequately they have been brought up. They are of the not-too-inaccurate opinion that our young men and women aren’t ready for their own family, business and enterprise. In spite of clear biological signals and emotional turbulences, they must thus deny youth the pleasures of courtship and marriage.
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/ohmy.gif" alt=":)" /> Of course, marriage is not for everyone. In 1 Corinthians 7:8-10, the apostle Paul wrote, “I say therefore to the unmarried and widows, it is good for them if they abide even as I (an unmarried person). But if they cannot contain, let them marry: for it is better to marry than to burn. And unto the married I command, yet not I, but the Lord, ‘Let not the wife depart from her husband…’”. In verses 37 to 39 of the same chapter, we see:
<br /><br />“Nevertheless he that standeth stedfast in his heart, having no necessity, but hath power over his own will, and hath so decreed in his heart that he will keep his virgin, doeth well. 
<br /><br />So then he that giveth her in marriage doeth well; but he that giveth her not in marriage doeth better. 
<br /><br />The wife is bound by the law as long as her husband liveth; but if her husband be dead, she is at liberty to be married to whom she will; only in the Lord.” 
<br /><br />The NIrV says the First Corinthians verses this way: “I (the apostle Paul) speak to those who are not married. I also speak to widows. It is good for you to stay single like me. But if you can't control yourselves, you should get married. It is better to get married than to burn with sexual longing. I give a command to those who are married. It is a direct command from the Lord, not from me. A wife must not leave her husband… 
<br /><br />But suppose the man has decided not to marry the virgin. And suppose he has no compelling need to get married and can control himself. If he has made up his mind not to get married, he also does the right thing. So then, the man who marries the virgin does the right thing. But the man who doesn't marry her does an even better thing. A woman has to stay married to her husband as long as he lives. If he dies, she is free to marry anyone she wants to. But the one she marries must belong to the Lord.”
<br /><br /><img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/blink.gif" alt=":)" /> So should we advocate young people to marry young? At 18? At 15? At 13, even? Yes, if we can provide the kind of education that will ready them, groom them, strengthen them for marriage. But it seems the majority of our 'adults' and so-called 'grown-ups' are too incompetent to construct that kind of Christ-centered education system. These adults conform to the world -- hook, line and sinker; pace, style and all -- and do not feel the sense of urgency to nurture our children FAST.
<br /><br />We have the ideals, but no one's pushing. <img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/ninja.gif" alt=":)" />
]]>
		</document>
	</documents>
</author>